Fm Movie
DEDICATED TO OUR BELOVED PARENTS,
WHOSE PRAYERS ALWAYS INCLUDE OUR NAMES
We're never really fine
after losing the ones we love.
After losing my mother
and my husband Arfan,
I feel like I'm living
in a black-and-white world.
A dull, colorless life.
Baskara.
My flesh and blood.
He's being raised
by another family in Solo.
Separated hundreds of kilometers
away from me,
his biological mother.
Is this what it feels like
walking along an endless road
with rain that keeps pouring?
And all of the flowers in my eyes
begin to wilt.
Happy ninth birthday, Baskara!
You've grown so much.
You're in third grade now, aren't you?
I hope you become a great kid
and love your parents always.
Let's blow out the candles!
Let's do it.
Here…
Sometimes,
the best thing we can do…
…Bas.
…is pretend to be happy.
Happy birthday, sweetheart!
Happy birthday, my favorite grandson.
Stinky!
Stinky face.
You must eat well, okay?
- Blow out the candle.
- Blow out the candle!
Happy birthday, Baskara.
I'll always pray for the best for you.
Morning.
Aqilla, sit with us.
Okay.
I need you to work overtime
for the next two weeks.
We must prepare for our presentation.
- Can you do it?
- Of course, Mel.
There are 24 hours in a day,
but I can work for 25 hours.
Amazing! You're our key player.
I live to work, not the other way around.
Watch your health.
Well, whatever you want.
- Here.
- Oh!
What is it?
It's my son's birthday.
You still celebrate
his birthday every year?
Pardon me, Aqilla.
As your best friend
who sees you every day,
I know you're pretending to be happy.
Aren't you tired?
I'm tired just from watching you.
It's enough for me to see Baskara
through Yumna and Arif's social media.
However,
their accounts have been inactive
these past few months.
It worries me a bit.
Why don't you go to Solo?
Mel, we must prepare for our presentation.
Why are you sending her on a vacation?
Not a vacation.
It's about her biological son!
Aqilla only has Baskara in her life.
Aqilla.
Maybe it's time to stop acting happy.
But I gave up custody to Yumna and Arif.
What would they think
if I visited suddenly?
Baskara is your son!
As long as he has your blood,
you have the right to know about him.
You have the right to know
about his adoptive family.
You have the right to know how he's doing.
Good afternoon, Ma'am.
Could you keep this? I'll be back.
Have a nice trip.
Please.
Peace be upon you.
Anybody home?
The number you're calling is unavailable.
So how was school?
- Hello, Mbok Tun.
- Hello!
I've made fried chicken
with the recipe of Mama Yumna.
Hey, say something.
Huh?
Come on.
Miss Aqilla!
Miss!
Bas!
Baskara!
Bas.
Oh my God.
You've grown so much, dear.
You look handsome!
You were this tall.
Now you're this tall!
Mbok Tun.
Bas.
Happy birthday, dear.
- I hope you become a great kid,
- Amen.
- devout,
- and always love your parents.
- Amen. Thanks, Miss.
I have a surprise for you.
Close your eyes.
Ta-da!
Wow, Lego! Thank you, Miss!
I love you, Miss.
Thank you, sweetheart.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too, Miss Aqilla.
Baskara, may I come to your house?
- Sure.
- Okay!
Let's go. Take your present.
Mbok, may I come in?
Let's go.
Yay!
- So, how was school?
- It was fine.
Let's do homework together later.
Okay!
There are 6,413 pieces in this set.
- Can you help me build this?
- Of course!
- It's gonna be so much fun!
- Of course.
We can play with it later.
Baskara, lunch.
Okay.
Mbok.
May I feed him?
No.
His parents taught him to eat by himself.
He must do his homework later.
I know he's a grown kid.
But it's been a while since I fed him.
I'll feed him while
he's doing his homework.
No, you can't.
Yes, I can.
No.
Yes.
I don't mind.
- 20 times 20 is 400.
- Very good.
Baskara.
Did you go somewhere nice
for your birthday?
I was at home with Mbok Tun.
Why?
Dad's in the hospital.
Grandma is busy taking care of him.
Mom's also busy.
She sells batik at the market by day
and takes care of
her online shop at night.
Nobody helps me with my homework.
How long has he been in the hospital?
It's been around four months now.
Four months?
Why is he there?
Bas.
I was told it was a headache.
He also couldn't move his body.
Mom took Dad to the hospital
But he still hasn't returned.
Bas…
I'm not allowed to visit
because children are
not allowed in hospitals.
How's his condition?
I don't know.
BUNG KARNO GENERAL HOSPITAL
CENTRAL SURGICAL UNIT
Mom.
Dear God.
Fathan!
You've just arrived?
I'm sorry.
It took a day
from my office to the airport.
There's no direct flight
from Kalimantan to Solo either.
How's Arif, Mom?
He's been unconscious for two weeks.
He's in a coma.
The blood vessels in his brain burst.
Bas.
- Yes?
- Is that Dad's shirt?
Yes, this is Dad's shirt.
Whenever I miss him,
I'll just sniff his shirt.
It smells like cajuput oil.
What's that?
This?
This is Dad's letter to me.
Whenever he missed me,
he would write me letters.
Mom brought them to me every day.
But these days
he never writes to me anymore.
I miss Dad so much.
Bas, let's continue your homework.
Come on.
BUNG KARNO GENERAL HOSPITAL
NOTICE OF ARREARS
Hi, Big Brother.
I'm home.
Why does Dad have to go?
I want to stay with you and Mom.
I don't want to leave you.
Neither do I.
But you have to promise me
that you'll always be fine.
Listen to Dad and don't make him angry.
Okay?
No!
If you're here,
who am I going to sleep with?
Who am I going to play with?
When will I see you again?
I don't want to be alone.
Listen.
Call us when you get there, okay?
Look at me. I'm strong!
So should you be.
You're my best little brother.
- Please don't take Fathan.
- Enough!
Burhan, please!
- Fathan, let's go.
- Don't take him away!
Fathan!
- Mom!
- Fathan!
- Let's go.
- Mom!
- Fathan!
- Arif!
- Arif…
Arif!
Arif! Fathan!
Fathan!
- Fathan!
- Arif!
Arif!
- Fathan!
Fathan!
After all this time,
this is how we meet again?
You told me
I had to be strong.
Now how can I?
I'm sure
he can hear you.
Pray for him, Son.
KLEWER MARKET
Get these sleeping gowns!
It's not here.
Yumna, why are you closing so early?
I'm going to the hospital.
Arif's brother just arrived.
- Oh my God!
- Oh my.
How's Arif now?
He's not awake yet. Please pray for him.
I hope he gets better.
Amen.
- Of course he will.
- I'm leaving.
- I'll be going.
- Take care.
- Take care, Yumna.
- Yeah.
Yumna!
Fathan.
- Hi.
- Mother.
- Where's Baskara?
- At home.
I went straight from the shop.
So, Arif…
Pray for him.
Of course.
I hope he gets better.
Yumna.
Ma'am.
I'm so sorry to hear about Arif.
How do you know Arif is sick?
Your social media has been inactive.
I came here to find out.
Can I see him?
He can't have visitors.
I think you should return to Jakarta.
Thank you for your concern.
Excuse me.
Yumna.
Why is he hospitalized?
Why is he here for four months
and why can't I visit?
It's our family's business.
I thought
you gave Baskara up entirely to us.
Let us live in peace.
It's all for Baskara.
Yumna.
Yumna?
Excuse me.
I don't know about
your problems with Yumna.
But please stop bothering us.
You're not part of this family.
Why do you care?
Arif is Baskara's father.
My biological son.
Aqilla.
Once again, I'm asking you politely.
Please pray for Arif
and leave us all alone.
I'm sorry for bothering you, Ma'am.
If there's anything I can do to help,
just tell me.
Thank you.
Yumna.
Dear God.
She's here with such bad timing.
Why is she so curious about our family?
She let Baskara go to us
because she knows
we have everything she doesn't.
Here Baskara has a mom, dad,
and grandmother.
If she knows Arif is in a coma,
she'll take Baskara from us right away.
Are you sure?
There's no other reason.
Fathan.
Help us protect Baskara.
I'll stay at the hospital.
She's right.
You're our only hope.
I'm sure
sooner or later she'll go to Baskara.
I'm home.
Bas?
Welcome home.
Come here.
- So you're Baskara?
- Yes.
You're Uncle Fathan from Kalimantan?
Yes.
Were you at the hospital?
Yeah, I was there.
How's Dad?
He's still in treatment.
Keep praying for him, okay?
I will.
Any letter for me?
Doesn't he miss me anymore?
Honey.
Of course Dad misses you.
Right now he's focusing on getting better.
Pray for him, okay?
Is it Fathan?
You've grown so much, and so handsome!
Mbok Tun?
Yes, it's Mbok Tun!
Sorry, I'm bad at faces
but I remember your name.
- Great.
- Mbok Tun.
Take Fathan to Grandma's room.
He needs to shower
before returning to the hospital.
Yes, Ma'am.
It's okay, I got it.
No, it's fine.
I can even carry you just fine.
Come on.
Come on!
- Have you eaten?
- I have!
- What did you eat?
- Fried chicken.
Mom.
Mbok Tun's fried chicken
isn't as good as yours.
The recipe is not the same.
Have you done your homework?
Of course.
I'm so happy today.
Miss Aqilla helped me with my homework.
And?
She also brought me a present.
A huge Lego set!
Mbok Tun?
Yes, Ma'am?
Mbok Tun.
Was Aqilla here?
She was outside as we arrived.
Baskara.
Uncle Fathan will pick you up
at school tomorrow.
Thanks, Mbok.
Yes, Ma'am.
Why are you here?
Am I wrong wanting to see my own son?
Yes, you are.
You abandoned your own child
and now you want him back?
You're selfish!
Selfish?
If I was selfish,
three years ago
I wouldn't have given him up
to Yumna and Arif!
If it's still not enough for you,
I didn't know my son was still alive
seven years before that
when I had nobody else in my life.
I never abandoned my son.
I'm sorry, I misunderstood.
I'm Fathan, Arif's younger brother.
Aqilla.
I just arrived from Kalimantan yesterday.
Why are you in Solo?
I wanted to make sure Baskara
and his new family are okay.
The truth is,
Arif has been in a coma for two weeks.
Yumna's having a tough time.
I apologize on her behalf.
Since Arif was sick and unable to work,
she's been working all day.
She has to divide her time
between selling clothes,
going to the hospital,
and raising Baskara.
What can I do to help her?
I want to lighten her burden.
I believe you mean well.
But pardon me,
your presence here upsets them so much.
I hope you understand.
Miss Aqilla!
Hey!
Are you coming to my house?
I need your help with homework.
I can't go today.
Let Mom help you study.
But Mom is busy.
She manages her online shop at night.
Bas.
I'll help you do your homework.
How about I help you study here?
But not too long. Mom's waiting for you.
Come on!
Let's pack up so Mom won't wait too long.
Hello?
Okay.
Thank God.
Let's go.
- We must go to the hospital.
- Huh?
- Can I go with you?
- Yes. It's urgent!
We'll use my car.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Come on!
Come on.
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
Excuse me,
children are not allowed to enter.
We're all here, dear.
We all love you.
If this can help you go in peace…
then I'll let you go.
I can't stand seeing you like this.
I just can't.
I promise…
I'll take care of Baskara.
There is no god
but Allah.
O Allah…
Arif…
Dad!
Dad…
Arif…
Dad!
Please, Arif…
Dad…
Dad, don't leave me.
Ma'am.
Please accept my condolences.
Dad, don't leave me…
- Dad…
- Arif…
Arif…
Bas, you have to be strong.
You'll get through this.
Why did he leave? I want him to stay…
I know, but you have to be strong.
I need my dad….
I must leave now.
Peace be upon you.
Fathan.
- Here's condolence money for Yumna.
- Don't leave me…
- Please take it.
- …Dad.
Thank you.
BORN 18 APRIL 1984, DIED 29 JULY 2024
From Aqilla.
Bas.
Let's go home.
No! I want to stay with Dad.
Come on.
No.
I want to stay here with Dad.
Bas.
Let's eat. I'll feed you.
I'm not hungry, Mom.
Bas.
I know you're sad.
I'm sad too.
We all miss Dad here.
But we must get through this together.
You have to eat, okay?
Mom.
When will Miss Aqilla visit?
I don't know, honey.
Come on, have a bite.
Come on.
Ma'am.
Grandma refuses to eat.
She hasn't eaten all day.
- Okay. Please feed Baskara.
- Yes.
Bas?
Bas? Baskara?
Mother, you haven't eaten all day.
Let me feed you.
You'll get sick if you don't eat.
Have some bites, okay?
I'm not hungry.
I'm still thinking about Arif.
It should have been me instead.
Oh, dear God!
Mother!
Do you want to leave us?
Don't you love me and Baskara anymore?
The son I carried for nine months,
the one I raised,
the one I nurtured,
the one I prayed for…
He left too soon.
It should have been me.
It should be children
who bury their mother
and not the other way around.
Mother.
Yumna, let me take care of Mom.
Excuse me.
Mom.
Did you forget?
You still have another son.
If you want to eat,
I promise you
I'll figure a way to stay here with you.
Let me help.
Stay with me.
Fathan.
Don't leave me.
Okay, Mom.
Mbok Tun!
Mbok!
What happened, Baskara?
Why did you wash Dad's shirt?
It's been four months.
Of course, it needed washing.
You should have asked me first!
Baskara, it's just Dad's dirty shirt.
But this shirt isn't dirty!
It had Dad's scent here.
I sniff this shirt whenever I miss him.
But what should I do now
when I come to miss him?
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Bas.
I'll put some cajuput oil
on the shirt, okay?
Allah the Almighty has spoken the truth.
Let's pray for the late Arif Nasuha,
the son of Burhan. Al-Fatihah.
I seek refuge in Allah
from the accursed Satan.
In the Name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
All praise is for Allah,
Lord of all worlds.
The Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Master of the Day of Judgment.
It is You we worship,
and You we ask for help.
Guide us along the straight path.
The Path of those You have blessed,
not those You are displeased with,
or those who are misguided.
Thanks. Now excuse me.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Excuse me.
Yumna. Ma'am.
Sorry I was late. My flight got delayed.
I'm really grateful for your invitation.
Anyway…
Here's some condolence money.
Please take it.
I'm sorry. I can't take this.
You've helped us so much.
Yumna, please accept this.
This is for Baskara.
Just take it as an emergency fund.
I can afford to meet his needs
without relying on other people.
But I'm not other people.
Just take it.
This is a gift from God.
This is her way to
pay tribute to our family.
- But, Mother…
- Yumna.
Thank you.
Bas.
I must go back to Jakarta.
When will you return?
This house feels empty since Dad died.
You always come here with a smile.
It cheers me up.
Bas.
I'll return soon
but now I must leave.
Let me walk you to the front.
I'll come with them.
Yumna, Ma'am, excuse me.
- Peace be upon you.
You came here straight from the airport?
We've got work to do.
Amazing!
- So proud of you.
- Aqilla, you're the best.
So amazing.
Amazing.
Bas?
Why do you look pale?
Are you sick?
The teacher told me
he couldn't focus during class.
He still misses his dad.
Bas.
Wanna go out with me?
Yeah.
May I take him out?
Please, Uncle.
Okay.
- What do you want to get?
- Airplane!
They all look so good!
This one's nice.
Bas!
- You like it?
- Yes!
You want it?
I want this!
Thank you.
It's a cool toy.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Mom.
Hey, honey.
Bas.
Why didn't you stop by my shop?
Didn't you miss kupat tahu at the market?
I went out with Miss Aqilla
and Uncle Fathan after school.
- Out?
- Yes.
Out where?
We rode the steam train
and went to other places
and visited an antique shop. It was fun.
Miss Aqilla bought me this plane.
Cool, isn't it?
Baskara, listen to me.
You must go straight home
after school tomorrow.
Keep Grandma company.
Or you can visit me at the shop.
You shouldn't see Miss Aqilla anymore.
Why? She's a good person.
But this is for your own good.
If I can't see Miss Aqilla,
who will help me with my homework?
Grandma can't.
Mbok Tun definitely can't.
There's Uncle Fathan.
But he'll return to Kalimantan soon.
You can come to my shop
then I'll help you do your work.
I want Miss Aqilla to help me.
But I said no!
I still want to see Miss Aqilla!
Bas! Don't you talk back to me!
Go straight home after school
and do your homework alone!
Understood?
Yes, Mom.
Fathan.
Is this how you protect our family?
You let Aqilla
pick up Baskara from school.
Is my request too much for you?
You asked me too protect this family,
but perhaps this is
how Aqilla protects Baskara.
She doesn't just want to protect him.
She wants to take him away!
Which side are you on?
We should be on the same vessel
and work together to keep it from sinking.
Do you want to lose Baskara?
We've lost Arif…
I'm on our family's side!
I don't want us to turn a blind eye
and take away someone's rights.
You're talking about rights?
Can't you see me?
Don't you think I deserve to be a mom?
I work all day long.
Who do you think I work so hard for?
It's for this family and Baskara!
Yumna.
One day,
we must accept the fact
that Baskara will grow up
and he gets to choose
between this family or Aqilla,
his birth mother.
Arif named him Baskara.
It means "ray of light".
If he leaves,
this house will no longer have light.
Hop on.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Mom.
Where are you going this early?
You look handsome.
And smell so good.
Hush!
I'm going to the bank
to take care of mortgage arrears.
Thank God.
Thank you for helping out our family.
Anytime.
Can I ask you
to pick up Baskara at school?
- What time?
- One o'clock, as usual.
Mbok Tun, we must leave at 12
to pick up Baskara.
Aye aye, Ma'am.
Okay.
- I'm off.
- Take care, Son.
Bye.
Hello?
It's 2 PM.
Why didn't anyone pick up Baskara?
I called Fathan but he didn't answer.
Oh no, I overslept!
Fathan asked me to pick up Baskara.
- I'll go get ready.
- No, it's okay.
I'll go pick him up.
Okay?
Can you watch my shop?
I'm picking up my son.
- Of course. Be careful!
- Thank you.
Which one do you want?
Yes, I'm on my way.
Please tell him to wait.
Thank you, Miss.
- He's been waiting for you.
- Yes.
- Thank you so much.
- Of course.
- What took you so long?
- I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Okay, hop on.
- Thank you, Miss.
- You're welcome. Bye, Baskara!
- Ready?
- Yeah!
I'm here with Amel.
We'll go through some pointers
from Miss Dita.
Shall we start now?
- Hold up.
- I'm sorry, Aqilla.
I think you're not serious
with this project.
Let me take this call.
I'm afraid it's urgent.
Fathan, what's up?
Oh, no.
Which hospital?
What's happening?
Okay, okay.
What's up, Aqilla?
Yumna and Baskara
got into motorbike accident.
I must go to the hospital.
I'm getting chills. Are you serious?
Okay, Aqilla.
Why didn't he pick up?
- Nurse.
- Can I help you?
A boy and his mom on a bike accident,
where are they?
We took them to the morgue
five minutes ago.
Excuse me.
Bas…
Baskara…
I'm so sorry…
Miss Aqilla!
Baskara, are you okay?
Did you get hurt?
Just a little scrape.
Our bike was hit by a car.
Bas…
Yumna.
If I may,
- I want to take Baskara out this weekend.
- Okay, Bas.
I want to go! Can I go with Miss Aqilla?
Can I?
Uncle Fathan will come along.
Thanks, pretty Mama!
Baskara?
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Grandma.
It's just a little scrape here and there.
Mbok Tun, go change his clothes.
Yes. Come on.
- Yumna, are you okay?
- Yes, Mother.
Are you coming in?
No, I'm going home.
Excuse me, Yumna.
Aqilla.
Please…
Keep the secret about Baskara between us.
Of course.
- Peace be upon you.
- And upon you.
Oh, wow!
Uncle Fathan!
Uncle Fathan! Miss Aqilla!
LAKE SARANGAN
- Bas.
- Yes?
- Look at the stars!
- Oh, right!
- Beautiful, aren't they?
- Yeah!
- Miss.
- Yes?
Remember when I wanted
to come with you to Jakarta?
Yes.
Who do you live with in Jakarta?
I live alone.
You're alone?
You don't have parents?
I did.
But my parents have died.
My mom had my dad.
What about you?
Me…
I had Arfan.
He was so handsome.
I love him so much.
But he's long gone too.
Do you and Arfan have kids?
I'm sorry.
I've made you sad.
It's okay.
Miss.
Yes?
I have one more question.
What is it?
But please don't get mad.
I'm curious.
You and my parents,
are you related or something?
I don't understand.
And why do you care for me so much?
Bas…
I love you so much.
When I look at your face,
it reminds me of Arfan.
He was so handsome
and so kind.
Just like you.
I just wish
I could divide myself in two.
Half to stay with my mom here
and the other half
to come with you to Jakarta
so you wouldn't be alone anymore.
Thank you.
I'm so happy to hear that.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I love you, Miss Aqilla!
So what's your plan?
No idea.
What about you?
I'm returning to Kalimantan next week.
In Banjarese language, "Hauli gawianku."
I'm sorry, what?
It means "back to work."
Next year, I'll return to Solo for good.
I want to spend more time with my family.
Especially my mother.
I don't want to die with regrets someday.
Regrets for what?
For not spending time with family,
and how I can be happier than today.
I don't want that either.
All this time, I've been working nonstop
as if I'm chasing something
while my one and only dream
is to be close to Baskara.
So we're both the same.
We're afraid of dying with regrets.
The way I see it,
Baskara is lucky to have you as his mom.
I see your sacrifices for him.
Fathan.
Be honest.
Why do I feel like you're on my side?
Because I see myself in Baskara.
Baskara has two mothers
and lost his father.
Just like me.
I have a mother and a stepmother.
My dad got remarried.
After a while,
fate brought me back to my birth mom.
So,
however complicated it is, I believe
that Baskara will return to you.
Baskara, wanna ride on a plane together?
Of course!
The three of us can go together.
Yeah.
- Peace be upon you.
- Grandma!
- Thank you for taking Baskara out.
- Mbok.
Anytime.
Well, I'm leaving now.
- Peace be upon you.
- And you too.
- You're not staying?
- No, but thank you!
Okay, take care.
Fathan.
- What is it?
- I should be asking you.
How is this house certificate back here?
Where did you get the money?
Yumna.
- Aqilla paid it off.
- Then give it to her.
Tell her I'll pay her back.
But she helped us willingly.
I don't need her help!
Yumna.
Please accept my help.
This is for Baskara and no one else.
This is so you can focus more
on raising Baskara.
I can do it myself.
What do you want to prove to us?
- What do you mean?
- You know.
You want to show that you're his real mom
and you want to bribe us
to give him up, right?
Oh my God, Yumna!
Yumna, Aqilla, let's talk nicely.
Yumna. How can I be calm about this?
If you failed to pay the mortgage,
then where would you live?
Yumna.
Remember when you both
got in a bike accident?
Baskara's father died
in a motorbike crash.
So what do you want me to do?
You know very well
as a single mother and breadwinner,
I work so hard for this family!
- Yumna…
- Just accept my help.
I don't want to owe you.
Calm down.
Mom! Miss Aqilla!
- So all this time, I'm not your son?
- Bas…
You've been lying to me?
Bas, that's not…
You're a liar!
Bas…
Baskara!
Bas!
Bas, open the door!
Please, let me explain.
Bas?
Yumna is your only mother.
- Lie!
- Please open the door.
Bas…
You've thrown me away!
No, I've never thrown you away.
Liar!
Bas…
Honey, please open the door.
- Please open it.
- I hate both of you!
- Aqilla, I think you should go.
- Go away!
Go away!
Bas…
I'm not opening the door!
Please don't leave me.
Arif, please forgive me.
I've failed to keep my promise.
What do I do without you?
Please give me a sign
to show that I'm not alone.
I can't do this without you.
I need you so much.
I need you…
Bas?
Bas.
It's Grandma. Please open up.
- Yes, Grandma.
- Bas?
Grandma.
Who are my real parents?
Bas…
You are Yumna's
and Miss Aqilla's son.
You should be grateful
for having two mothers.
Don't be mad at them.
When you grow up,
you'll understand everything.
Miss, would you like buy this?
BATIK MURNI - WE HAVE BATIKS FROM SOLO
Yumna.
What do you want?
Can you please talk to Baskara?
Isn't this what you've been waiting for?
He finally knows.
But it hurts seeing him
finding out this way
and now he's rejecting me.
You're hurt because he's rejecting you?
Do you ever think
about my feelings at all?
That's not what I mean.
None of this would have happened
if you listened to me
back at the hospital.
You should've returned to Jakarta.
Let me deal with my family alone.
Yumna.
I've been sharing with you willingly.
I'm fine with letting you
take Baskara away from me
even though he's the only light I've got.
But why don't you want to
share your troubles with me?
Why are you refusing my help?
No matter how much you help,
it means nothing if it hurts Baskara.
Listen.
When you came to us three years ago,
Arif and I planned to tell him
about his real mother
but later, when he's an adult.
Not now.
I know, but it's out of our control.
We're both at fault here.
You're the one who brought up
about the house certificate.
Arif as the head of the family has gone.
In this situation,
why are you still refusing my help?
I'm just a lowly merchant.
It's nothing compared to your fortune.
But don't you dare insult me.
I can raise Baskara just fine!
You should go back to Jakarta
and let us live in peace here.
Yumna, I never mean to insult you.
All works are noble.
I appreciate everything.
But everything we do is for Baskara.
I'm here to share with you all my troubles
and my struggles.
Why can't you do the same with me?
I want you to.
Yumna.
If I wanted to take him away,
I'd call my lawyer and take DNA tests.
But I didn't.
I'm returning to Jakarta tomorrow.
If you may, please tell Baskara everything
and tell me how it goes.
Please forgive me.
- Peace be upon you.
- And upon you.
Bas.
Do you remember
when I told you
that you were also Aqilla's son?
Yeah, I remember.
Actually…
I didn't want to tell you yet
since you were just a kid.
The plan was
your Dad and I
would tell you when you turned 18.
Bas.
Here…
You have Aqilla's flesh and blood.
She carried you for nine months.
She put her life at risk
to give birth to you.
So please don't hate her, okay?
If I'm Miss Aqilla's son,
why am I here with you?
We were asked to take care of you.
But Aqilla never knew.
She always looked for you.
Until finally,
she found you here in Solo
with Mom and Dad.
Bas…
You are her biological son.
Sweetheart.
She's been waiting for you for ten years.
She's all alone in Jakarta.
Will you go there with her?
I only ask for one thing.
When you're there,
please don't forget about me.
Don't forget about Grandma,
and Mbok Tun.
And don't forget to pray for Dad.
Although you're not my real mom,
I still love and care for you.
I love you so much.
Baskara is leaving for Jakarta?
Yes.
He'll have a better life there.
I need to take care of things here.
Are you okay?
God is willing, Mother.
Please pray for me.
God entrusted us with Baskara.
But he's not meant to be owned.
His name means "light".
Light is to be shared.
What can I give to my Mama
My dearly beloved Mama?
I don't have something precious
For my dearest Mama
All I can do is sing
A song from my heart for Mama
It's just a simple song
My love song for Mama
Miss!
Bas…
Mama Aqilla.
Please forgive me.
You are also my mother.
Bas.
You're Arfan's and my son.
Thank you, Baskara, for accepting me.
This is the happiest day of my life.
Forgive me, Baskara.
I didn't tell you anything.
Bas…
Please take care of yourself.
Take care of Yumna.
I'm leaving now, okay?
But Mom told me
to go with you to Jakarta.
Yes, she told us herself
and she's made the decision.
You're coming with me?
Yes, Mom.
Yumna.
Are you sure?
You've just lost Arif.
Is it the right time for Baskara to leave?
What about you?
I want to give him time
to know you better.
I'm sure
this is the best decision for us.
Yumna.
Take care, Bas.
You must be happy
to have two moms, like me!
One in Solo, one in Kalimantan.
You'll get double pocket money.
Bas.
For these past ten years,
you've given the best time
to Mom,
Dad, and me.
To me as well.
Dad is gone.
Now you're leaving too.
I'll miss you so much.
This house will feel empty.
Call me when you're lonely, Grandma.
Of course I will.
I'll always be your grandson.
Honey…
You and Dad will always be my parents.
Bas.
Take care of yourself in Jakarta, okay?
My love and prayers
will always be with you.
I love you, Mom.
It's time.
Take care.
Yes, Mom.
Bas…
What's not fated for us,
no matter how complicated it is,
will find their way back home.
This house never feels the same.
There is no more light.
There is no more sound.
Like a house without a soul.
But I've got to live.
I can't stay selfish.
I must let you soar high
and create a new story
together with Aqilla,
your biological mother.
Baskara…
I love you very much.
I'll always love you forever.
My prayers will always reach the sky
and be wherever you are.
Dad drew this?
Yes! Good, isn't it?
Arfan and I went to the same college.
He was a great painter.
He's handsome, isn't he?
He is.
Just like you, Baskara.
Are you happy here?
I'm happy.
ANDRE WASN'T EVEN FIVE MONTHS OLD
WHEN HE WAS ADOPTED.
I'm happy and I don't mind being adopted.
I'm just curious about my background.
ANDRE FLEW FROM THE NETHERLANDS…
‪NOT INSPIRED BY ANY FILM, SIMPLY DEPICTS
‪A REAL-LIFE EXPERIENCE OF AN ADOPTED CHILD
TO PRINGSEWU, LAMPUNG.
How do you feel?
WELCOME TO BANDAR LAMPUNG
A bit nervous.
I've been waiting for so long.
Yeah?
My heart was beating fast.
I couldn't sleep all night!
ANDRE WAS WELCOMED BY THE VILLAGE.
Here…
THIS WAS THE FIRST TIME HE HUGGED HER
AND MUTTERED THE WORD…
Mother…
…TO KARTINI.
FIRST REUNION AFTER 40 YEARS