Fm Movie
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom...
Why is that cat eating her own child?
Dino!
Really...
Ever heard of gracefulness?
My eyesight is bad.
- Like your face.
- So put on your glasses, narcissist.
And stop acting like you can "see" ghosts.
You know I've got...
- "Inner Vision."
Okay?
Now shut up, and retake.
Vira! Dino! Let’s go.
Okay.
Come on.
Someone’s really excited for the move.
Yeah. Can’t wait.
- What’s with you?
What’s with you?!
- What the hell, dude?
- Stop!
Mom! I don’t wanna share a room with her!
As if I want to!
Sure, once you start having wet dreams.
"Dry" boy.
At the old home, I had my own room.
- Good Lord, I missed you! You got so tall!
- Yeah!
And there she is. Vira the Virus.
Shut up, chicken.
- How's school?
- All good.
Hey, I have something for you.
The Picture of Dorian Gray.
What’s it about?
I don’t know.
A friend of mine was going
to throw it away.
- Thanks.
- So?
Dino.
Hold this.
Sis!
You're back with Dino.
We’ve finally reached
this middle-of-nowhere ugly house.
Could you be more negative?
What’s missing? Is the wording too stiff?
Most Indonesian movies sound stiff anyway.
This isn’t a movie.
Guys.
No doubt something sinister
happened here in the past.
And I'm worried
it’s going to happen again.
Hello...
What the hell are you guys up to?
This is Uncle Jamal.
For some reason, women find him repulsive.
Hey!
Don’t ask about his financial situation.
What kind of movie are you guys shooting?
Dino wants to start a horror channel.
That's right.
- You can see ghosts?
- You don’t know I have a sixth sense.
Come on. I’ll show you upstairs.
What you are doing
seems like a lot of fun.
- Of course.
- Can I join your horror thing?
Nah, you don't have what it takes.
What does it take?
Vira!
Are you coming or what?
This is your mom’s room.
It has a bathroom.
This is your room.
The bathroom’s over there.
Why am I staying with Vira?
I’m a big boy now. I deserve my own room.
Well, get your wet dreams started quickly.
Late bloomer, huh?
Vira.
How’s your mom lately?
She’s been weird.
Weird how?
She drinks a lot of milk.
Not to mention cutting up
live chickens for dinner.
- And--
- But she’s not like... that anymore, right?
Well, let me know if something's off.
What do you mean?
What is it, dear?
Your own salon.
It’s finally happening.
You’re still gambling online?
Aren't you tired of losing?
Sometimes.
But Dino-saur,
I only need to get lucky once.
- Give that. I have lucky hands. Yeah.
- What? For real?
- Before we begin,
- You...
I’d like to say a few words.
Since your father left us two years ago,
I...
haven't been quite myself.
I know it wasn’t easy for you all.
I'm sorry
for putting you through that.
But I also want to thank you
for never giving up on me.
That’s why I promised
to turn over a new leaf.
I'll never depend on anyone else again.
We’re all here for you, Mom.
You can still depend on us.
You’re such a kiss-ass.
I’m not who I was anymore, dear.
I’ve changed.
To Mom!
You are on a long school break, right?
Good timing for a move.
I don’t mind missing a bit of school.
I hear you. I skipped school too.
Is that why most girls
think you’re no good?
Want some hot soup on your face, Dino?
So, if you want to have a girlfriend,
you have to...
Old house. New house.
We still have blackouts.
- Dino.
- Yes.
Don’t you think it’s weird
Mom chose to move here?
Seems like nobody wants to live here.
Our neighborhood is so ugly.
So many abandoned houses.
And now Mom's opening a salon.
Who would want to come?
Check out that house.
It’s got a jungle growing inside.
Are you listening to me?
What’s with you?
I was always against moving here.
You were the one trying to win
Mom over and encouraging her.
Now that we’re here, what’s bothering you?
- Well, Mom is different now.
- Yeah.
She’s happier now.
Let’s go there.
What for? Now?
To shoot more content.
Scared?
- Dino!
- Come on!
Fine, let me get my phone.
Slow down.
FORBIDDEN
I feel the presence
of a young boy’s spirit here.
If someone's here,
please, call out to me.
This must’ve been
the residence of some Dutch people
who got evicted in the past.
I’ve also heard
from the locals here that--
Did that look real?
I’m the one who says "cut."
Why did you stop there?
- Fine, fine. Let’s retake.
- Dino.
I’m done over here.
- It's dangerous here. Let''s go.
- One more shot.
Dino, why are you doing somersaults?
This is supposed to be a horror.
Dino, I swear if you fall and die,
I’m walking away.
What did I tell you?
All these houses are dead!
- How am I supposed to get down?
- I’m going home.
Vira... Vira!
Just kidding. You’re actually scared?
Shut up and help me get down.
Guys, here’s our director.
I don't want to.
You’re better off as a camera operator.
Since you have no talents.
Not to mention you don't have...
"Inner Vision."
I knew you were gonna say that.
I sense something
residing within this tree.
Something...
- evil.
- Cut! Moving on.
Not yet. I wasn’t feeling it.
- Nah, it was good.
- No!
We got it.
No, we didn’t! It wasn’t creepy enough.
We’re supposed to give
our audience goosebumps!
Looking at you
already gives me goosebumps.
Stop it! We’re done! Moving on!
When Dad held the camera,
he’d let me have my takes.
Hold on.
I sense something
residing within this tree.
Something...
evil!
What’s so funny?
Too manly to share a room with me,
but too scared of a little...
p-p-p...
pussy!
What’s going on here?
Vira is cleaning my wounds, Mom.
Got scratched by a cat.
Mom! I don’t wanna share a room with Vira!
Why were you out this late?
This is your fault.
You were supposed
to look after your brother.
No, Mom, it’s not her fault.
Sorry, Mom.
You two go up. Take a shower.
Sir, sorry to bother you.
Come check out our new salon.
It's my mom's. It’s right there,
- if you want to visit.
- Excuse me. There's a brand new salon.
- Excuse me. Sir.
- You can get a trim there.
- Please feel free--
- Kid, we’re talking here. Do you mind?
Good morning.
Morning, indeed.
How may we be of service, lady?
I just opened a salon.
A salon?
Maybe you want to check it out?
Here are the treatments.
Wow, full package.
- This is for men too?
- Of course!
- Really?
- Do you want a hair spa?
You can give hair spas?
My head massages are pretty special.
I can give you discount.
You tidied up? I wanted to help.
You can clean up later
when I’m busy with customers.
Sure thing, Mom. I can't cut hair.
It's only the first day,
and we just handed out the flyers.
Welcome.
- I’d like a haircut.
- Of course. Have a seat here.
What kind of style do you have in mind?
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Eight customers on the first day, how?
Why question it? That's good, right?
This must be what they call...
beginner’s luck.
Let me do it.
You must be tired, right?
Fine, I’ll take a bath then.
When school starts,
how will you manage all this on your own?
I’ll manage just fine.
Where have you been?
Exploring the neighborhood.
Made a few friends.
You move quick.
I sure do.
But...
They said this house was empty
because there was a murder here.
The victim...
They were siblings.
Really?
- Then...
- Dino!
Dino!
Mom?
Power’s out again!
What is it, dear?
I found a sanitary pad. Is it yours?
Leave it on the bed.
Are you on your period again?
I thought it had stopped.
Thank you, dear.
Dumbass.
Why so jumpy? Light’s out again.
I know. Why the hell
are you dripping all over?
I told you I was in the shower!
You haven't cut your hair
for a long time, huh?
Yes, it's been a while.
Good morning. Please have a seat.
Vira.
Stop daydreaming.
Make tea for the new customers.
Yes, Mom!
If you’re tired, just go.
Not at all. I am fine!
Sorry for the wait.
Vira.
You’ve been sighing too much.
It’s annoying.
I don’t need you here.
Keep scratching that.
You’ll get an infection.
Where are your friends?
They’ve gone home.
Besides, we never play around here.
Always outside this area.
And she sighs again.
What’s up?
Do I do that often?
Mom said the same thing.
Don’t you think it’s weird?
We live in this godforsaken place,
but Mom’s salon is packed.
What?
You were worried nobody would come.
Now business is good, you're sulking?
- What do you want now?
- You know!
Come on.
One cat attack isn’t enough?
It’s getting dark now.
We can shoot some creepy stuff.
Guaranteed to be viral!
- Let's go.
- Gosh...
Come on! Run!
Vira and I are now in the Amazon jungle!
Chiropractic ghost.
Why do Indonesian ghosts do bridges?
Isn’t it harder to chase their victims?
Careful, it’s slippery.
Now this is content.
So cool.
- Dino...
- It's cool.
Hurry up!
Dino, let’s call it a night.
One more scene!
Let’s just go home. It’s so dark now.
Just one more scene, please.
Don’t you see this place?
Wow!
Do they store dead bodies here?
Start filming!
Dino.
Wait a second.
What’s up?
What?
Run!
What the hell! Not funny.
Haha! Very funny!
Let’s go home. It’s dinner time.
Take a shower right away.
You two are filthy.
Vira?
I peed a little.
Mom, chicken soup again?
Don’t we have anything else?
I’m fine with it.
You eat anything.
You have no taste.
As if you have any.
Mom, I miss your other dishes.
We’ve been having the same--
My son is so handsome.
Dumbass.
...Vira and I are now in the Amazon jungle!
There are leaves.
Dino?
Get up.
Dino, get some water.
Dino, call Uncle Mal!
Mom...
What the hell are you doing?
Call Uncle Mal!
I’m going to the market.
I’m coming with you.
No need.
- But--
- I’ll cook for you tonight.
Something other than chicken soup.
Mom?
Vira?
What’s wrong with you?
Does it feel good?
- Here you go.
- If you like it, feel free to come back.
Can I?
- Of course.
- You're amazing.
- Amazing at what?
- At being pretty.
- So pretty.
- Thank you.
Does this feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Where have you been?
Around.
How’s the book?
- What's the story about?
- Read it yourself.
How lame.
Are you here to see Mom?
I’m here to see you guys.
How's the past week been? You like it?
- We keep getting blackouts.
- What?
We keep getting blackouts.
- What, blacks out?
- Blackouts! Lights out!
- Mom’s salon is always crowded.
- Great then.
Even though we’re
in the middle of nowhere.
Did something bad
ever happen in this house?
Vira, tell me. What’s up?
Ever since we moved here,
Mom changed a lot.
Don’t tell me she...
It’s not that!
So what then?
Mom’s better. That’s all that matters.
When was the last time
you took Mom to the psychiatrist?
It’s been a while.
The doctor said your mom was better.
She doesn't need the meds anymore.
Vira?
Power’s out again.
Yes, Mom, I’m coming.
I’m sleeping downstairs.
Mom?
- What is it, dear?
- Mom?
Mom, did...
I just saw you out there.
Your eyes. They’re problematic.
You’re taking a bath this late at night?
You’re wandering around
this late at night?
Power’s out.
I got hot and was going
to sleep downstairs.
Oh...
I’ll get back to bed then.
Wanna sleep with me instead?
It’s fine, Mom.
- Thank you, sir.
- You're welcome.
Vira!
Come on!
Afternoon, sir.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Hi.
Good afternoon.
What kind of glasses are you looking for?
Thin frames
or thick ones?
It’s for my son. He needs new glasses.
Yes.
This is your son?
If he was your brother, I’d buy it.
Looks like you need glasses too.
What’s with that optics guy?
Didn’t he just creep you out?
I cringed so hard.
What’s with you? He was nice.
We even got a huge discount.
Oh, please, what he wants is so obvious.
At least he’s not your father.
Honey, I’m sorry. I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
What do you want? Tell me!
You’re not leaving us.
Tell me what you want!
No!
I’ll grab a knife!
You wanna see me kill myself?!
Can’t you see we built all this together?!
No!
Do I look pretty?
You do.
Heru says he likes girls in red.
Is that optics guy really your type?
What is it, Mom?
It’s been a while since I last did this.
- Mom? Is that a tattoo?
- Huh?
Nonsense!
Why would I have one?
He’s here.
I’m off then.
Evening, Yanti.
Evening, Heru.
Ah yes.
I brought you...
this.
The lenses are ready.
That was quick.
I also brought you...
this.
They’re lovely.
Are you nervous?
Why is your heart on the right side?
The left side is for ordinary nervousness.
Right now, this is extraordinary.
Shall we?
Where were you all night, Mom?
- Oh, you're the husband? Hello.
- Yes. Hi.
It's beginning to... Do you like my massage?
I'm sorry...
Hello.
Lately the power outages
are so frequent. Why is that?
Where’s Mom?
With a guy who stayed over last night.
- Are they fucking?
- Ew!
That’s disgusting!
Who taught you to talk like that?
Like what?
Where’s the guy from last night, Mom?
We broke up.
Don’t you think you’re overdoing it
with the guys, Mom?
Why?
Can’t you be happy for me?
Dino.
I’ve been seeing things in this house.
And everything has something
to do with Mom.
Then I saw this figure.
Am I losing my mind?
Vira.
Pretending to be asleep?
Did you just come out of your room?
No, Mom.
You love me, right?
What’s wrong with your glasses?
It fell when I was playing soccer.
One of the boys stepped on them.
Let’s eat.
You’re going to wear those broken glasses
forever?
I could wear my old ones.
Forever.
Why did I bother getting you new ones?
- What's the big deal?
- Can you fix it?
Just go to that glasses guy.
What's his name?
One of your fuck buddies.
Do you know how handsome you are?
When you were a baby...
I often wondered
who you would look like.
Mom or Dad?
Thank goodness you look like me.
Even so, your face...
still reminds me of your father.
I often prayed that you
wouldn’t turn out like him.
Entitled.
Ungrateful.
- Mom...
- Stay out of this.
Forgot how to say thank you?
You know how much your glasses cost?
Sorry, Mom...
I’m sick of you.
All you do is demand.
Demand. Demand. Demand!
Where is your gratitude?
You wanna milk your mom to death?
Silence!
Ever since you were born,
my life has been rotten.
Yeah, I’m coming.
BOLD IN JUSTICE, COWARD IN DEBT COLLECTION
Who is it?
- Uncle!
- Vira?
- What happened?
- Mom is... Mom has been...
Mom has been... I’m not crazy. I’m not...
Vira, calm down.
Mom has... What Mom did...
- Dino was...
- Vira.
Vira, please forgive me.
I've been stressed out since we moved.
And I took it out on you and Dino.
I’m so sorry for everything.
I promise...
I’ll go to the psychiatrist again.
For you and Dino’s sake.
Yes, Vira, your mom told me.
I’ll go with her to the doctor.
Okay.
You love me, right?
I’m not sure a shrink can handle this.
Meaning?
I’ve been seeing...
A ghost?
- Looks like you need a shrink too.
- Dino, I’m serious.
How can you say that?
After what she did to you?
What do you expect me to do?
Catch the ghost?
You think this is a joke.
Why am I the only one
who cares about everybody--
You only care about Mom.
Who would, if not me?
You’re always off doing your own thing.
Lost in your books. Making vlogs.
I couldn’t care less
about those dumb vlogs!
They’re just an excuse
so I can be with you!
You’re also always off
playing soccer with your friends.
Have you seen my clothes dirty
from playing soccer?
Do I ever look exhausted?
Or better yet, since when
have I ever liked soccer?
There are no kids
in this godforsaken place.
I have no friends.
I’ve always been alone.
- But I’m always with you.
- Not anymore.
We used to be together.
Now you’re never with me.
The doctor gave me some meds.
Your eyes are red.
Forgive me.
Let’s go in.
I’m making dinner.
Uncle Mal, what else did the doctor say?
All good.
- Dino! Dino! Wake up!
- What?
Look at Mom in the bathroom now!
Are you nuts?
- You have to look!
- No!
You’re coming with me tomorrow.
If I’m wrong,
I’ll never say a word about Mom again.
Ever.
Fine.
That was a long trip.
And now we have a long wait.
You sure this is mom’s shrink?
Do you know
that cats are capable
of killing their own children?
Huh?
If the kittens are distant or sick.
Or if the mother is hungry.
I’ve always hated cats.
That’s not possible, Doc.
I have no reason to lie, dear.
Is this some sort
of patient privacy thing?
This has nothing to do with that.
It’s been over a year
since I last saw your mother.
Who the fuck--
- You lied!
- Vira, what...
- Liar!
- What’s going on?
You lied!
Where have you been
taking Mom all this time?
Witchcraft?
You saw what your mom was like
when your dad left you.
I was just trying to help my sister.
Why take her to a shaman?
Why not a shrink,
like normal people would?
Well, actually...
we tried that.
But it didn’t help.
They were just pushing their meds.
But when I took her to a shaman,
she got better.
Like before.
Like before she got married.
Like before you two were born.
Both of you should be grateful!
You still have your mother!
Look at me. I have no one!
Please...
Please get our mom back.
Look at me.
Please.
Mom...
You told them everything?
Sorry...
I was desperate, Vira.
I couldn’t function at all.
I was scared.
Scared I would put both of you in danger.
The shaman helped me regain myself.
And I was finally able
to restore my spirit.
But it comes at a price.
I had to maintain a certain ritual.
And every time I’m careless,
- I become weak.
- It’s okay.
When I’m weak, I’m not myself.
So, what you’ve been seeing
isn’t me.
It’s the djinn
- that possessed me.
- Djinn?
That’s what you saw?
What are we supposed to do?
Vira, you must help me.
You want to do that, right?
Please...
Please help me get
this djinn out of my body.
Help me.
Please, Vira, help me.
Help your mom.
Please help...
Please, Vira, help me.
Good evening.
I only have tea. But it’s good tea.
Please, help yourself.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Medea.
How may I be of service?
My mom got possessed by a djinn.
Please get it out.
Your understanding of witchcraft
is probably from
horror movies or viral threads.
It doesn’t work like that.
When Yanti first came here,
she had a severe clash within her psyche.
Between Yanti as a woman
and Yanti as a mother.
So, I implanted something into her
to separate those two clashing sides.
But such an implant...
requires a regular sacrifice.
In the form of chicken blood.
I accidentally tasted my son’s blood.
Yanti.
I’ve warned you.
That is the one thing you must not do.
We must pull out that implant.
This is dangerous.
Dangerous how?
That implant has been contaminated.
And it’s craving will never be satisfied
until it has consumed
all of her children’s blood.
Wait outside. All of you.
Yanti, get in.
Whatever you hear, do not come in.
Thank you.
Is it done?
Let’s go home.
Yanti.
You screamed like
you were giving birth again.
I want to thank you both.
You too, Jamal.
I promise to be better.
You don’t need to be better.
You just need to be our mom.
You should move in with us, Uncle Jamal.
For real?
For real. But promise us this.
If you're going to live here,
no more online gambling.
- It's done.
- No more loan sharks.
Sure, sure. I promise.
That’s right.
Stay here.
Live with us.
Alright.
I’m going upstairs.
I need to rest. I’m exhausted.
Don’t stay up too late.
- Uncle Jamal is crying.
- He's crying.
Oh, shut up.
Dammit.
I forgot to say goodbye to Medea.
- Morning.
- Where’s Uncle Jamal?
He went home.
- Without saying anything?
- Said he had some errands to do.
Running away from loan sharks again?
A debt-ridden guy who forgot his wallet.
Even loan sharks would feel bad
if they saw this wallet.
Breakfast is ready.
Take it. Take it.
Your hair grows so fast.
I’ll give you a trim later.
Mom, I’m going out.
Where are you going?
I’m gonna shoot some footage around here.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Did you finish the book?
I did.
Good.
It’s pretty sick.
The main character stabs his own painting.
But he’s the one that died.
How come? Is the painting cursed?
No, it’s the other way around.
The painting bears his sins.
The protagonist is the bad guy.
Not too short, okay, Mom?
So demanding.
What do you say if I color my hair?
What color?
Blue.
How about red?
Your mustache is growing.
How about a shave?
Sure. Like at those barbershops?
Please don’t move.
My son is so handsome.
Too bad his eyes are problematic.
Mom?
Mom!
Uncle Jamal?
Dino!
Dino?
Vira...
I’ve been bad.
I’m an ungrateful boy.
Mom!
Din... Dino!
Dino...
Dino!
Don’t fuss, dear.
Mom...
Do you think you know your mother?
All her life, demanded.
Milked dry.
And discarded.
If it weren’t for me,
your mother would've died long ago!
- Do you think you know your mother?!
- Mom!
Mom...
Your mother was never allowed
to live her life.
Only now,
I'm taking my life back.
Your mother had given her life to you.
Now, are you willing
to give it back to her?
Are you?!
Dino.
Come here, Dino.
Come here, dear.
Mom!
Dino...
Show mommy you love her.
Dino!
Dino, don’t...
I’m sorry.
Don’t...
I’m with you.
I’m with you. Always.
Dino...
I... I’m willing.
I’m willing.
I’m willing, Mom...
Mom?
Why did that cat eat her own child?
Vira...
She's not the mother.