There's something under my bed.
Don't touch the floor.
It can't get you
if you don't touch the floor.
There's nothing under your bed.
- Nothing but dust bunnies.
- I know.
He'll eat you.
Go to sleep, Aurora.
Good night, Aurora.
I wish, I wish, I wish.
I wish, I wish.
I wish, I wish, I wish...
Aurora?
- Yeah?
- Get up here.
Come on.
- Aurora?
- Aurora!
What are you doing out there?
- How'd you get outside?
- Get in here. Are you okay?
Get in here.
I don't like you
going to bed so upset, Aurora.
I want you to think
about all your worries
and put them in my pocket.
Everything you're afraid of.
Everything you're afraid
will happen.
Put it all in my pocket
and I'll hold it for you
so you can sleep.
Hmm?
Are all your worries in there?
Oh. Boop.
Good night, Aurora.
Goodbye, Daddy.
You're too old to suck
your knuckle.
You're gonna get buck teeth.
Good night, Aurora.
Goodbye, Mommy.
Aurora?
What is going on in there?
Mom?
♪ Our Father,
who art in heaven ♪
♪ Hallowed be Thy name ♪
♪ Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done ♪
♪ On earth as it is in heaven ♪
♪ Our Father,
who art in heaven ♪
♪ Hallowed be Thy name ♪
♪ Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done ♪
♪ On earth as it is in heaven ♪
♪ Give us this day
our daily bread ♪
♪ Forgive us our trespasses ♪
♪ As we forgive them
who trespass against us ♪
♪ Forgive us
our trespasses, oh ♪
♪ Our Father,
who art in heaven ♪
♪ Hallowed be Thy name ♪
♪ Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done ♪
♪ On earth
as it is in heaven... ♪
Is that enough money?
For what?
To procure your services.
I haven't counted it.
How do you know
the word "procure"?
Word-a-day calendar.
What's your name?
Or is "A" your name?
Aurora. What's your name?
I've got 327 dollars and...
42 cents here, Aurora.
Where'd you get all this money?
I robbed a church.
Is that enough
to kill a monster?
What makes you think
I kill monsters?
I saw you kill one.
What did you see?
In Chinatown.
Behind a dim sum restaurant.
I saw a dragon.
And you killed it.
You saw me kill a dragon?
How did I kill it, Aurora?
You slid under its belly...
...gut it like a fish.
And then you cut off its head.
You got some imagination.
I got two eyes.
Monsters aren't real.
Yes, they are.
Don't pretend.
Grown-ups don't pretend.
Grown-ups pretend
not to be afraid.
But they are. All the time.
That's mostly true.
- Erora...
- Aurora.
Erora.
- Little girl...
have you told your parents
I kill monsters?
Stop it.
What do your parents think
about monsters?
Do they believe in them?
They do now.
Now they do?
They didn't before,
but now they do.
It's hard not to believe
in something
when it's eating you.
Ate you.
A monster ate your parents?
Yep.
Like the one
you think you saw me
slide under its belly
and gut like a fish?
Yeah.
And this monster lives
under your bed?
Yes.
Show me.
Did you see it eat your parents?
I was under my blanket.
You just heard them
getting eaten?
I just...
heard them getting got.
That's my mom and dad's room.
I think they tried
to hide in there.
There's no blood.
Generally, when something
is eaten, there's blood.
It ate them whole.
Did your mom or dad have a gun?
Somebody had a gun.
You hear a gun go off?
Told you so.
This all looks like
it made some noise.
Your parents
didn't call for help?
You have neighbors.
No one heard this?
It eats everything.
It even eats your screams.
Will it eat your "I told you so"
when it eats me?
I'll tell you
"I told you so" now,
and when you get eaten,
you'll know
I already told you so.
Why didn't you go to the police?
Why aren't you going
to the police now?
I don't know
what I would tell them.
See?
I could tell them, uh,
there's a little girl
who's been abandoned
by her parents.
You can tell them that.
After you kill it.
I'm trying to understand this
the way you understand this,
little girl.
The monster you think
you saw me kill...
I know, I saw you kill it.
Your monster, it's like that?
That's why I hired you.
I haven't agreed to be hired.
I don't know what you saw
behind that dim sum restaurant
but I didn't kill any monsters.
I didn't kill anything.
That's really why you won't go
to the police.
Killing things
is against the law.
Have you killed a lot of things?
You seem like you've killed
a lot of things.
In my experience,
the sort of monster
that can eat a person whole
and not spill a drop
does not do so randomly.
Are you done pretending now?
I'm seeing things
how you see things.
Why would a monster
eat your family?
They touched the floor.
If your monster's like mine,
it doesn't eat people
for walking on the floor.
Why did your monster
want to eat you?
Because I kill monsters.
Hmm.
Yeah. Uh, go home, little girl.
There's something under my bed
that wants to eat me.
Then don't touch the floor.
Didn't think I'd see you again.
I'd hug you, but as you know,
I really don't put effort
into such things.
- You ordered a sandwich?
- I did.
You want half?
I'm trying to unclench my jaw.
It's in a perpetual
state of clench,
so I have to...
uh, release it...
so it doesn't pop out
of my skull
when I take a bite of food.
Mmm.
Mmm, mm.
Mm, mm, mm.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Mm.
Either of these familiar?
Should they be?
They're my neighbors.
Professionally disappeared.
You've actually met
your neighbors?
I'm aware of them.
Daughter was home
when it happened.
She see it?
She heard it.
Thought it was a monster
under her bed.
You're looking for a monster?
The monster's looking for me.
And I think that monster
got the wrong apartment.
Monster's lucky
it got the wrong apartment.
Must have broken in
and realized their mistake.
Had to kill the parents
who'd seen them.
That girl didn't see anything.
They let her live.
I'll take a look at these.
How do you know the little girl
didn't see anything?
She told me
she didn't see anything.
She saw you.
There's a little girl
who knows your face.
She know what you do?
She doesn't know anything.
She saw monsters.
She believes in monsters.
You're a monster.
She believe in you?
I'm not gonna kill
a little girl.
Because you already killed
her parents?
You did not kill
that girl's parents.
Ah, I almost certainly,
if not at least arguably, did.
A cheetah kills a baboon.
Discovers its baby
is still clinging onto dead mom.
What's the cheetah do?
Doesn't eat the baby.
Even a cheetah knows
it's an asshole thing
to orphan a child.
Yeah, I saw that Nat Geo.
Baby died anyway.
Cheetah moved on.
So should you.
Get off the floor!
A monster's coming.
Get under your bed.
There's a monster under my bed.
Get in the closet then.
Was there someone in here?
They get out the fire escape?
She got got.
Your monster?
I'm touching the floor.
Where's your monster now?
Why's it not here?
It's eating.
Come here.
If there was someone
in your room
and they got away,
they will be back.
They didn't get away.
Stay there.
What are you doing?
I'm draining his fluids
so when I cut him into pieces,
it won't be messy.
Why do you have to cut him
into pieces?
I have to get rid
of the body.
Why don't you just
put it in my room?
Let the monster eat him.
Have you ever been to a butcher?
Yes.
What I need to do is like
what they do with pigs and cows
at the butcher,
but with a person.
Only we're trying to get him in
a suitcase, not our stomachs.
- I love pigs.
- Ah, a cow, then.
So anything you're comfortable
with being done to a cow,
you should be fine with me
doing to this guy.
- Can I watch?
- No.
You can't tell
he's people anymore.
You can help me
wrap up the pieces,
if you want.
Who was he?
A killer.
Did he come to kill the monster?
Oh, you have to stop
talking about monsters.
A monster
didn't eat your parents.
Your parents were killed.
Did someone cut them
into pieces?
He came to kill me.
Or you.
He came to kill one of us.
Me, for my reasons.
You, for my mistake.
Why would he wanna kill me?
There was no monster
in Chinatown.
Those were men.
A monster
didn't kill your parents.
Those were men
who wanted to kill me
because of monsters I've killed.
Monsters who were men.
You don't have to feel bad
because a monster
- ate my parents.
- Stop saying that.
Just 'cause you don't want it
to be that way
doesn't mean
it's not gonna be that way.
'Cause that's the way it is.
A monster ate my parents.
A monster will always eat
my parents,
unless you kill it.
I'd love to believe there was
a monster under your bed,
little girl.
Happiest I've ever been
was believing
- in something impossible.
- You're gonna be very happy.
Hi.
I'm Brenda Bautista
with Child and Family Services.
Are you Aurora's...
Yes.
Hello, Aurora.
Hi.
We had an appointment.
We did?
If you'd like,
I can give you a few minutes
to get yourself together.
This isn't coming together
anytime soon.
We'll have to reschedule.
It's challenging being a parent.
Hmm. Particularly
being a foster parent.
Yeah.
Particularly...
being a foster parent.
We're the first...
family to come into her life
since what happened.
And trust isn't easy
in the best of circumstances.
Third family.
You're her third foster family.
They did go over that
with you, right?
- And you do know that?
- Yes. Of course.
Of course, I'm-I'm speaking
in that we're the first family
to come into her life
since the last family did so.
And I've always been--
I'm sorry.
I'm under the weather.
We are all under
the weather here.
You shouldn't come any closer,
or inside.
I was hoping I could use
your restroom.
No.
I should tell you
and I hate to tell you this
because I know how it sounds,
but if you fail to keep
your appointment,
it does go
on your permanent record.
Brenda, you know
how that sounds,
- and you still said it anyway.
- I know. It's not a threat.
I know. Let's reschedule.
Sorry for any inconvenience.
Bye-bye.
You should wash your hand.
Hmm.
That's not your social worker.
That's not her foster father.
So, this is your third family.
How many of your families
has this monster eaten?
All of them.
All of them?
And no one believes you?
Nope.
Maybe we approach this
scientifically.
Children are scientists.
You don't play, you experiment.
Gather data. Analyze.
But your heads are so full
of shit and Santa Claus,
you don't know what's real.
- I know what's real.
- No.
You think you know.
Where did your monster
come from?
I wished for it.
I wished on a shooting star,
like I wished for you
to kill it.
Wishing isn't scientifically
sound, evidence-based thinking,
little girl.
Why did you wish for it?
I wanted it to eat my parents.
Why did you want a monster
to eat your parents?
They weren't very nice to me.
You're mad at Mom and Dad.
You wished they'd go away
so you wished a wish
you wish you hadn't wished.
All your parents
weren't very nice?
Some of them were nice.
Then why did the monster
eat them?
It was trying to eat me.
What have you done, hmm?
Have you seen something
you shouldn't have seen?
What makes you so tasty, Erora?
- Aurora.
- Arora.
- Erora.
- Aurora.
- Yes. Aurora.
I'm wicked.
Who said you were wicked?
It knows I'm wicked.
It keeps eating my family
'cause I don't deserve a family.
I've met wicked.
Trust me, you're not wicked.
Where's your monster now?
It sleeps during the day.
Under your bed?
Under the floor under my bed.
It mostly comes out at night
and tries to eat me.
It won't stop
until it does eat me.
So you should kill it
before it can do that.
Did you try wishing it away?
It didn't work, obviously.
Say I do kill your monster.
Then what? Where do you go?
There are places where children
in your position usually go.
If they catch me.
You don't have any other family?
No.
Do you?
No one who'd miss you
if you were gone?
No.
They were all eaten.
Anybody who'd miss you
if you were gone?
I'd miss you if you were gone.
- What's in the suitcase?
- "Who's in the suitcase?"
- Is it the little one?
- That's the big one.
This is the little one.
He killed her.
You killed him.
Return to sender.
I sent two.
I only saw the one
you sent to kill me.
Lapsang souchong.
You want some?
Yes, please.
I didn't send anybody
to kill you.
Now, I'm asking you
to be honest.
Who was trying to kill whom
and is there an argument
to be made for self-defense?
Because nobody
was supposed to kill you.
I may have thrown
the first... what have you.
Mmm.
Well, I really was just
trying to help.
I saw the gesture
as a professional courtesy. Mm.
I thought I was being
magnanimous.
Sending someone
to kill a little girl?
to kill a witness
who knows your face
and knows what you do.
If you wanna judge me
on the ease
with which I can kill a child,
have at it.
I am eating
a suckling pig tea sandwich.
I was navigating
that little girl.
You seem triggered.
That little girl
clearly triggered you
with the cheetahs
and the baboons.
At least this way,
the deed would be done
and you could suppress
or wallow however you chose,
but it would be one less thing
for you to worry about.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Genuinely, this time.
That first one
was mostly sarcasm.
What happened
to the second package I sent?
Did you kill her too?
What am I gonna tell
these people's families?
I never saw the second package.
Monster under the bed get her?
Yeah, well...
Yeah. Yeah.
No one has heard of the parents.
No one knows anything
about them
beyond the most tedious
of details.
Wasn't even their daughter.
Fostering to adopt.
What happened
to her birth parents?
They abandoned her.
Packed up and left her behind.
Do you see a pattern?
I see a pattern.
I think we know
who the real monster was.
I kill monsters.
No one followed you home.
No one knows where you live.
Although, I would move anyway.
And I found out
who's trying to kill you.
Who?
Everybody.
Everybody's trying to kill you.
It's remarkable.
And in your line of work, inevitable.
So, congratulations.
And condolences.
Is that the baby baboon?
Who's in the little suitcase?
We couldn't get him all in
in one bag.
"We"?
I told you
to wait for me at home.
You weren't coming home.
You were gonna leave me.
That does seem to happen
to her a lot.
Aurora, come over here.
Sit next to me.
I don't know you.
You were gonna leave me.
I never told you I'd stay.
I hired you. You took my money.
Aurora, do you know
that there are cultures
who won't even acknowledge
someone your age is a person?
Delayed personhood,
they call it.
You're just a little body
with a soul
slowly growing inside of it,
eventually becoming a person,
but not a person yet.
So you should let
the real persons talk.
- I am--
- Nope. Shut your mouth.
You want a sandwich?
She doesn't eat pork.
You, you are obviously
going through something here.
I can see that.
Some childhood trauma.
Stop that!
This little girl
is not little you,
and helping her
will not fix you.
I know they say
that you can't truly work
through childhood trauma
without having a child
of your own.
Implying childless people
are broken,
a point of view
I don't subscribe to.
- I'm gonna stop you there.
- There is no stopping
this train. It's going
all the way to the station.
Hired you to do what?
To kill the monster
under her bed.
The monster that ate
her foster parents?
And her birth parents.
And, well, all her parents.
And the lady with a gun
who crawled through
my bedroom window.
- I never saw her.
- I saw her.
I saw her get eaten.
I don't know
what to do with this.
You see?
Who killed the lady with a gun
who crawled through
your bedroom window?
- I never saw her.
- The monster under my bed.
You're not the only one
with a monster
under her bed, Aurora.
Everybody, the everybody
that's trying to kill you,
they're never going to stop
trying to kill you
until they've killed you
or you've been killed.
You can never sleep
in the same bed twice.
He can sleep in my bed.
Let the monster eat them.
Leave now.
Get out of town.
Don't go home.
Don't get dim sum.
Just get out.
Get out of all of it.
Hello. Welcome back.
The usual?
Yes, please.
That lady said you got problems.
At the moment,
I have two problems.
So we're clear,
you're one of them.
You could just be my dad.
You'd be a good dad.
I don't wanna be
one of your dads, Erora.
All your dads died.
Aurora.
I remember thinking my mother
was the most beautiful woman
in the world.
Then one day I took a good look
and realized,
she's not, really.
But my brain
wanted me to think so.
Isn't that silly?
So, whatever you think
you want or need from me
isn't really what you think,
it's what your brain
wants you to think.
And whatever I think I want
or need from you...
It's just what your brain
wants you to think?
Exactly.
We don't really know each other.
- I wished for you.
- Yes, you did that.
But you didn't actually control
any of that happening.
- Yes, I did.
- No. No, you didn't.
- No, you didn't.
- I did.
- Nope.
- Well, you didn't, though.
I--
May I sit down?
I wouldn't if I were you.
Is she your daughter?
- Yes.
- No.
I hate to question
your parenting--
Then don't.
Shrimp shumai.
Mushroom dumpling.
Black sesame dragon cookie.
Purse dumpling. Soup dumpling.
Rabbit-shape dumpling
with shrimp.
I assume you know why I'm here.
- I assume I'm why you're here.
- You are.
She is not.
You can just ignore her.
Maybe we could talk outside.
We just got our food.
Her being here won't stop them.
They will go right through her.
No one knows I've seen you yet.
Shouldn't you tell them?
Tell you what.
While she's having dessert,
I'll join you outside.
We'll discuss
what we need to discuss.
How we need to discuss it.
How about that?
Can we get to-go boxes, please?
You're gonna let
the monster get him?
A monster.
Hi, Aurora. Can I come in?
My dad's in the living room.
Thanks for coming back so soon.
I apologize for this morning.
I hope it all makes sense
once I explain.
- You weren't under the weather.
- No.
Don't touch the floor.
Is it lava?
No, it's not lava.
A monster will eat you
if you touch the floor.
Oh!
I'll consider myself warned.
You'd be the first.
- Erora.
- Aurora.
Exactly what I said.
Probably shouldn't indulge her.
She thinks a monster
ate her entire family.
A monster did eat
my entire family.
Go and tuck yourself in.
Just like I showed you.
I have so many thoughts.
Just grab one thought
out of the air.
Grab it as it passes
over your head
and say it out loud.
- Grab it and say it.
- We're all gonna die.
That's a big thought.
I don't believe
that little girl's family
abandoned her.
Not her first family.
Not her second.
Certainly not those last people.
I-I don't think
they all just left.
I think...
I think they're all dead.
- Two families?
- Three.
I'm not this girl's father.
I live across the hall, 5B.
- Why did you lie?
- Well, I didn't lie.
That little girl lied.
She's very good at lying.
I just met her, and she told me
a monster ate her parents
and then you rang the bell.
I believe she believes
there is a monster.
I don't think
she's lying about that.
She's just delusional.
But there is something
doing something
and you need to do something
about that.
If there is someone
you can call...
...you should tell them that
circumstances are desperate
and immediate.
You should tell them
that presently, like, now.
Because we are in danger
right now.
You, me,
and that sweet little girl.
Why do you think
we're in danger?
Why did you turn off the lights?
Come here.
They followed her home.
They are watching the building.
Her foster parents are missing.
It all stinks like fish.
Hey, it's Bautista.
Anything going on out there?
Yeah.
Something's going on out here.
- You should get up here.
- Copy that.
I think she saw her parents
getting got
and now it has her
seeing monsters.
And those,
those are the monsters.
She could probably explain this
better in her own words
because it happened to her
and it's got nothing to do
with me.
And I'm guessing...
meanwhile, also completely
unrelated to me...
You gonna get that?
I'm debating.
- You want me to get it?
- No.
I'll get it.
Get off the floor!
Get back
under your special blanket.
Why are you here?
There are at least
a half-dozen people downstairs
whose purpose this evening
is to turn you into a carcass.
Yeah, well...
And you led them here,
like the Pied Piper.
Did you have a flute?
Not a literal flute.
This is an ambush.
I know. I'm doing the ambushing.
I'm the bushwhacker.
And, uh, what they're doing
is less ambush-y
and more of a siege.
Yeah, that kid
ain't gonna survive a siege.
She's fine.
I've got the FBI inside
and they're calling in
reinforcements.
I'm just the concerned neighbor,
5B.
It's perfect.
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
I've put a lot of thought
into this.
Really? "A lot of thought"?
How are you quantifying
a lot of thought?
By number or quality?
Because I've heard
very few thoughts
and none of them good.
I'm on the verge
if not over the verge,
of convincing them
that disappeared families
are the work of professionals.
So this could tie up
very nicely for me.
I'm getting Peter to kill Paul.
I don't know
how to be any clearer
than I've already been.
You can't save this little girl.
She's seen your face.
She's seen my face.
She has to die.
All you can do
is save yourself.
I've done my part.
Fellow concerned neighbor.
I'm not with Child
and Family Services.
- Hmm.
- I'm with the FBI.
We've been investigating
the disappearance
of Aurora's family.
Families.
What is happening
in this poor girl's life
that the FBI is investigating?
Normally, I wouldn't divulge
what we know
but being that
we don't know anything,
I might as well share.
We have one clue.
Something strange
at the first house.
How strange?
An open bottle
of thumb-sucking deterrent
on Aurora's nightstand.
Someone was applying it
to her finger
and they vanished
along with the applicator brush,
which was found
under the floorboards
under her bed.
How it got there, no one knows.
Maybe a monster spit it out.
It is a deterrent.
I accidentally touched
the floor.
Don't touch the floor.
It'll eat you.
Get off the floor!
- Okay, okay.
- Get off the floor!
Jesus!
She really believes in it.
Yeah.
I can see that.
Get under your special covers.
Don't come out again
until I tell you so.
Get off the floor!
That's not funny.
It's coming to get you!
Shut up!
Where are you?
We're inside.
Almost there.
Is that you?
Who...
shot me?
Give me that.
How many outside?
I counted two.
And how many inside?
Give me my gun back.
Ow.
Maybe get off the floor.
There's an animal in here.
There's a what?
Something big.
Don't...
...do it.
What is that?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! What is happening?
What's happening?
I think that's the monster
that lives under Aurora's bed.
Uh-huh.
- FBI!
- Get on the ground now!
Drop your weapon!
Get on the floor now!
Down on the floor!
- Uh, no. No.
- No. I-I can't do that.
I'm sorry. No,
it's not gonna happen. No.
Down on the floor!
There is something
in the floor!
Concerned neighbor, 5B.
- You got the girl?
- I got the girl.
I-I would like to sincerely
apologize for my tone earlier.
It wasn't professional.
Please, can we leave?
- Time to go. We gotta go.
- We gotta go. I gotta go.
Let's go. Take me off the floor.
Why aren't we going to the car?
When we get to the car...
Get them up
and get them out of here.
There's something in the floor.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, no.
Oh, my God!
There's something in the floor.
Something in the floor.
There's something...
Erora.
Erora!
Aurora.
Did it eat everybody?
Not everybody.
Just everybody else.
No, stay. Stay where you are.
You believe me now?
Yes.
Are you the happiest
you've ever been?
Happy is not the word I'll use.
We go through the window,
down the fire escape.
Ready?
I told you so.
I didn't taste too good.
Hello, Aurora.
Don't come in here.
I've come to rescue Aurora.
Aurora, you can't stay here.
It's not safe.
Come with me.
I'll take care of you.
Get off the floor.
You don't have to do
what you think you have to do.
But you do have to get off
the floor.
Aurora...
be easier for you
than it is for him.
Mom, get off the floor.
Don't call me that.
It's hurtful.
It's going to eat you.
What's going to eat me, Aurora?
Mom...
It doesn't wanna eat you,
Aurora.
It's your monster.
It's my monster.
You wished for it.
You have to live with it.
I wished for you too.
We're going away now, Aurora.
You can't even say my name.
And I don't even know your name.
You'll think of something
to call me.
And I'll just call you
"little girl."
Stop it.
♪ I am behind you,
I always find you ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ People who fear me
never come near me ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ The city is a nightmare,
a horrible dream ♪
♪ Some of us
will dream it forever ♪
♪ Look around the corner,
and try not to scream ♪
♪ It's me ♪
♪ I am behind you,
I always find you ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ People who fear me
never come near me ♪
♪ I am the tiger... ♪
♪ Yellow eyes are glowing
like the neon lights ♪
♪ Yellow eyes, the spotlights
of the city nights ♪
♪ I am behind you,
I always find you ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ People who fear me
never come near me ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ The city is a prison,
you'll never escape ♪
♪ You're forever trapped
in the alleys ♪
♪ Look into the shadows,
and you'll see the shape ♪
♪ Of me ♪
♪ I am behind you,
I always find you ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ People who fear me
never come near me ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ Yellow eyes are glowing
like the neon lights ♪
♪ Yellow eyes, the spotlights
of the city nights ♪
♪ I am behind you,
I always find you ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ People who fear me
never come near me ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ And if I meet you,
what if I eat you? ♪
♪ I am the tiger ♪
♪ I am behind you,
I always find you ♪
♪ I am the tiger,
tiger, tiger ♪
♪ Tiger ♪