Fm Movie
SATURDAY
Wak Di?
Wak Di.
This is Panji, Wak Di.
Wak Di!
Chaos…
- Chaos…
- Ma'am?
- Chaos!
Chaos!
My promise has been fulfilled.
Wak Di is dead.
Wake up!
MONDAY
DEVLIN, PLEASE TELL ME WHEN YOU'VE
COME DOWN FROM THE MOUNTAIN
I'M SCARED SOMETHING MIGHT HAPPEN TO YOU
Here it is, sir. Excuse me.
Dad.
Devlin is still unreachable.
He went hiking on Mount Merapi on Friday.
He was still communicating
on Saturday afternoon.
But in the evening,
his cell phone was off.
A lot of things might happen
to his cell phone.
It might have fallen down.
It might get drenched in the rain.
Or he could be
in an area without a network.
After all, he's hiking, right?
He's supposed to get back on Sunday.
Now it's Monday and he's not home yet.
Do not anguish
when calamity occurs.
Do not despair…
When bereft.
Whose proverb is that?
Sunan Kalijaga.
Be strong while facing any problem, dear.
Life constantly moves forward
alongside time
which can improve your attitude
to bring about good fortune.
Remember that.
Yes. Thank you, Dad.
Don't keep that long face.
Have you had honey today?
No?
It should be daily.
Okay.
Majapahit was the greatest kingdom
throughout Indonesia's history.
Their sovereignty spanned
from western Indonesia
to eastern Indonesia,
as well as Singapore, Malaysia,
Thailand, Brunei Darussalam,
and the Philippines.
- In the book of Negarakertagama…
- Nes. Awindya.
- In 1293,
- Dya.
- Majapahit hadn't become that vast.
- But thanks to the efforts of…
- Quick.
- Dya.
- …in his quest to continue the dream,
he constructed the Amukti Palapa.
Awindya!
If you can't wait to update
your social media status,
you're free to step out of this class.
This is the place
for those who're willing to study.
Pardon me, sir. But he hasn't replied.
Please do it outside.
Despite being an Indonesian,
you don't want to study our history.
Who knows what he stated in Amukti Palapa?
"Lamun huwus kalah
Nusantara isun Amukti Palapa.
Lamun kalah ring Gurun,
ring Seran, Tanjungpura,
ring Haru, ring Pahang, Dompo,
ring Bali, Sunda,
Palembang Tumasik,
samana isun Amukti Palapa."
Who was the first king of Majapahit?
Kertarajasa Jayawardhana,
from 1293 to 1309.
The succeeding king?
Prabu Jayanegara, 1309 to 1328.
The third ruler?
Tribhuwana Tunggadewi, 1328 to 1350.
And the fourth king was
Prabu Hayam Wuruk, 1350 to 1389.
The fifth, Kusumawardhani
Wikramawardhana, 1389 to 1399.
The sixth was Suhita--
- Hey.
- Hey!
Any word from Devlin?
Dya, you have to see this!
Guys, I just arrived in the village
and they forbade me from climbing up.
They said all the hikers
who went there are still missing.
So, I think I'll just move
to Merbabu instead.
The locals said
this is all because of black magic.
Black magic?
Does magic have a color?
What color is yours, Jo?
Didn't Devlin and the rest
also go to hike there?
Devlin went there?
Dya.
I have to go to Devlin.
Jo, you have to take me there.
Nes.
Dya.
If I may suggest,
we'd better not…
Nothing in this world
can separate me from you.
Except when I run out of data quota.
You are
perfect.
How long until we get there,
according to Google?
My butt is aching, you know?
We've been traveling for five hours.
I counted 1,247 Indomaret stores
we've passed by,
814 Alfamart stores, and 1,476 BCA ATMs.
Three more hours.
In case you haven't decided
what profession you want,
I suggest you become a census taker.
Your dedication to counting
deserves appreciation.
And that's the 112th Pertamina.
ROAD TO MOUNTAIN CLOSED TEMPORARILY,
HEAD OF VILLAGE
Dya!
Right foot steps in first!
Why does it have to be the right foot?
When shaking hands,
do you use your right or left hand?
Right, of course!
I'm talking about my right hand,
not my right foot!
You guys are weird!
Hey, wait!
Dya.
Where the hell are all the locals?
Dya!
No wonder it's empty.
SELO VILLAGE
The village's name means vacant.
Excuse me.
- Nes!
- Dya!
What is that?
Sir!
Wait, sir!
With the passing of our warden, Wak Di,
we need to find someone
to continue his work.
Thus, nature's order will be restored.
Right now, we have not found
such a person.
Regarding the road closure
to the mountain,
it has been planned since Saturday.
It has been reviewed
and reevaluated.
This condition will be ongoing
until we have a new warden.
For the sake of everyone's safety.
Thus, until the new warden is selected,
nobody is allowed to go up the mountain.
Excuse me, sir.
We have four friends
who are still up there.
They were supposed to come down yesterday.
But they're unreachable until now.
I am trying to help them.
But they forbade me from going up
and told me to wait for the SAR team.
I'm sorry, but I'm the one
who forbids the SAR team from going up.
You guys are so mean. You left me!
Bottom line is that
nobody is allowed to go up the mountain
until a new warden is selected.
What is a "kuncen"?
Maybe it's Jackie Chan's brother.
Then what do you propose
to save my friends?
And who's in charge
of appointing the new warden?
This is Mrs. Lakah's fault.
Wak Di could not prepare a replacement
because Mrs. Lakah
is unable to bear a son.
- He's right!
- You're responsible for this.
Don't put the blame on her!
I can't believe nowadays,
we still have people persecuting women
just because they can't have sons.
Despite how science has proven
that it's not women's inability.
You want to blame someone? Blame the men!
Because the deciding chromosome
for the baby's gender is in--
Hi. I'm Awindya.
I'm Yoga.
Diska.
So, your friends are still up there?
The six of us went up there on Friday.
Then, Diska got a high fever
at the third post.
So, I had to come down with her
to see a doctor.
On Saturday, we went back there.
But the locals closed
the road to the first post.
You guys just got here?
I'm Agnes.
Her beloved boyfriend also
went up the mountain on Friday.
And no word from him until now.
She really loves her boyfriend.
That's why we're here.
Can you not embarrass me?
Usually, guys get hooked on you
at the first meeting.
His girlfriend also really loves her.
And he's strikingly handsome.
They're a perfect couple.
I'm Mojo.
I'm single.
No surprise.
Where do you guys plan on staying?
If you haven't thought about it,
you can stay with us.
In the inn for hikers.
Nes.
Can you count how many crickets?
But I count there are
28 hanging things on their houses.
What the hell is that?
That's called offering.
For the last few days, the mountain demon
has hunted for victims here.
The locals believe the offering
will protect them from its assault.
It contains food
and the house owner's body parts.
It could be their nails,
hair, or some skin.
Some even cut their fingers.
For as long as no warden is around,
they seek ways to save themselves.
What does a warden do anyway?
A warden can communicate
with the mountain's mystical beings,
as well as fulfill their needs,
to keep everything in peace.
The word "kuncen" is derived
from "kunci," which means key.
So, he's like a keyholder for the gate
into the mystical realm here.
I think that the gate is open now
and nobody's able to close it.
The gate of the mystical realm is open?
So why's there no replacement yet?
Does nobody want to be a warden?
I mean, with its critical job description,
I bet it pays well. Right?
Not sure if he gets paid or not.
But from what I asked yesterday,
they told me there are many prohibitions
with hard conditions to be met.
Thus, nobody volunteers to be a warden.
Why is that?
Imagine yourself encountering
all kinds of demons every day.
You'd go nuts eventually.
If it has a normal appearance, fine.
What if it has bulging eyes
with sharp teeth?
Still cute, I guess.
What the hell?
Locals call it being possessed.
Is the inn still far?
I think we'd better stay inside the house.
Aren't the demons lurking everywhere now?
How many others are having that seizure?
Hey!
Damn it. Here we go again!
Awindya!
Agnes!
Mojo!
Mojo! Keep calm! Keep calm, okay?
Listen to me! Kneel down now!
Kneel down slowly!
Now, bow down!
- Jo.
Jo.
Jo, are you okay? Steady your breath.
What are you doing anyway,
dancing around in a cemetery?
Look at this.
They said this tree is 1,000 years old.
And there's a sacred tomb here as well.
Come on.
Where were you?
My boyfriend stayed here too.
I saw his car over there.
Okay, I'm turning on the lights.
I'll show you your room. Come on.
Got anything to eat here? I'm starving.
But I can't eat instant noodles.
Hey. What is this?
That's the hiking route.
When you're hiking here,
you need to pass the first post,
the second post, and so on.
Come on.
Wait, I need to ask something.
I noticed you at the cemetery.
You saw something, didn't you?
Why are you asking?
You reacted differently.
You didn't seem to panic.
Honestly, I've never told this to anyone.
But sometimes,
I can see or sense the supernatural.
Diska doesn't know?
There are things keeping me
from talking about this.
Isn't that weird?
I can talk about this openly with you.
Go up.
Dis, you went up there? What's up there?
It's the scenery. Breathtaking.
An irreplaceable joy.
You mean Yoga?
That breathtaking scenery?
Hey, have you ever heard about
the demon's market?
What's that?
You mean where you buy and sell demons?
They said there's a demon market up there.
There's an open field there.
If you set up camp there at night,
you'd hear a crowd
like that in the market.
But when you peek out, you'd see nothing.
For real?
That's spooky.
I hope they don't make me go up there.
Most people say you can buy
mystical items in the demon market.
Such as talismans, keris, crowns
for gaining beauty, wealth, and whatnot.
But maybe you're right.
- You can buy demons.
- Hey.
If you can't see the market,
how do you shop there?
Usually, people would ask for help from
someone well-versed in the mystic arts.
Through an intermediary of psychics.
Sometimes, when you're too smart,
you tend to do weird things.
Can't we shop online?
Someone sent me a message,
asking for an OTP code.
Where can I find this OTP code?
This is a scam. Don't give it to him.
If anyone asks for your personal data,
like OTP code, password, PIN…
But he seems serious.
He says he's a bank officer.
My God, don't you know what a scam is?
This guy's tricking you
into believing he's a bank officer.
Okay, here's an example.
What if I ask for your bank PIN code?
And I say I'm with BCA.
Oh, you work in a bank?
What the hell is that?
Get in.
How long are we staying here, Dya?
So, what are you both up to now?
There's nothing we can do anymore.
So, we're going home tomorrow
and inform my friend's family.
And we'll seek for help in Jakarta.
I have to go up the mountain
tomorrow morning.
Mojo, wake me up early tomorrow.
Didn't they forbid everyone
from going up there?
Forbidden doesn't mean you can't do it.
Devlin and the others are still up there.
If nobody can help them,
I'll do it myself.
You ever hiked a mountain before?
Do you know the route?
All right. I'll go with you tomorrow.
That way, I get to know
my friend's condition too.
Yoga!
I want to go home tomorrow.
I don't want to stay here too long.
Please. Don't involve us
in whatever you want to do.
Besides, you don't need to go up there!
Even the experienced SAR team couldn't--
Diska! Calm down.
I just want to make sure they know…
There's no warden now.
So I can do
whatever I want.
I am certain
that Wak Di
has already prepared a replacement.
But until his final breath,
he kept it a secret.
We have to find the person ourselves.
If there's no warden guarding here
and you summon
the demons from the mountain,
wouldn't that make
this village in turmoil?
Then you understand, yes?
Haunted places tend to attract
all kinds of people.
So, this village should be haunted.
When everyone hears about this village,
they all come here.
They would ask
for power, position, and wealth.
Who could give them that?
Who would they ask for help?
Wak Har.
First,
I need to get rid
of those pesky outsider brats.
Awindya.
Devlin?
Dev?
Win! Awindya! You're sleepwalking!
Awindya!
- Win, wake up!
- Awindya!
Fight it, Awindya!
Win! Wake up!
Awindya! Awindya, wake up!
Awindya!
- Win.
- Dya…
Dya.
Were you sleepwalking?
I wasn't sleepwalking.
Do you realize what you did back there?
You'd better see it yourself.
Jo! Who is that?
Awindya.
What? What's happening to her?
Awindya! Wake up!
Awindya, wake up!
What the hell is going on?
Yoga!
- Awindya, wake up!
- Awindya.
Fight it, Awindya! Wake up!
- Dya.
- Awindya!
Win, wake up!
Jo! Who is that?
Awindya.
- What? What's happening to her?
- Awindya! Wake up!
- What's that noise?
- Awindya!
That was your voice in the video.
What the hell is going on?
Keep quiet. Turn it off.
Someone's being attacked.
We have to help him. Fast.
Wait.
Are you insane?
What can you do to help?
Playing hero,
helping someone from a demon's attack?
If Mojo and Yoga
hadn't helped you back there,
you might've been dead by now!
And now you're still going there!
You'll just create more problems
for the people around you!
Did you ever ask your friends
if they wanted to come here with you?
I bet you didn't.
Because everyone has to do what you say!
You know, Agnes didn't want
to come here in the first place.
And now you're demanding
Mojo and Yoga come with you?
You may say
you've never forced them to come.
But because they care about you,
they're worried to death
if something happens to you
because of your foolishness!
But if you can't see that,
then you're downright egotistical!
I'm sorry.
But I can't just sit and do nothing.
I have to at least try to help.
Yoga.
Yoga!
It's all right.
Let's just go together, okay?
Instead of being alone here,
it's better if you're with us.
You like Diska, don't you?
Sir?
Sir.
Sir, are you…
Awindya!
- Mojo!
- Nes, help me!
Diska! Give me something to tie him with!
Dya.
You haven't had asthma in a while.
Tie him tightly!
TUESDAY
Why didn't you wake me up?
I asked you to wake me up early yesterday.
You were pretty exhausted last night.
You also had an asthma attack.
We are not here for a vacation.
What about those people up there,
whose only hope for help is from us?
Yoga, I'm leaving.
I don't get why
you're still counting on them.
They're newcomers
who have no idea what's going on.
Yoga, even the SAR Team
couldn't help them.
Then I'm sorry if I still have
my hopes of helping our friends.
I'll tell you what.
Let's go up there.
If there's no sign of them up there,
then I promise
we'll go home today, okay?
She left.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Awindya.
The mystical dwellers of this mountain
have barred our way up.
Win!
Dya, listen!
We are forbidden to go up
by the mountain's dwellers!
But we have to go up, Yoga!
Even if this is the only path,
I will keep trying!
Are you insane?
All of us have done exactly what you want!
Why the hell can't you see that?
Stop it!
Stop making us follow your whims!
Don't be selfish!
You said you wanted to go home.
I never stopped you
or Yoga from going home.
You insist on staying here
because you like him, don't you?
Imagine if he were the one
who went missing on the mountain?
Wouldn't you do your best to go up there?
The problem is, you have no idea
what danger awaits you up there!
I just don't want anything to happen
to Yoga and your friends because of you!
- Nes!
- Agnes!
Nes!
Agnes really hates the hospital.
When her sister got sick,
she only got to the parking lot.
Maybe we should try meeting
with the SAR team again
and ask for their help.
Does everyone here
really refuse to be a warden?
Where is Mojo?
He's taking forever in the stall.
Hey, you bought a lot.
- You got any cash to pay?
- What?
- They only take cash?
- Of course!
QR code is acceptable here.
See? That's more like it!
You have it, right?
Yeah. So?
TEMPORARY WARD FOR POSSESSED PATIENTS
Who is that?
Please. Your flashlight…
- I'm sorry. I can't see anything.
- Right. I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Who are these people?
They're the possessed locals.
There are so many of them.
But it's only been three days
since the warden passed away.
The problem is,
some locals refuse to evacuate.
But why do you have to tie them up?
At dusk or when the sun sets, they arise.
They'll attack anyone nearby.
Their strength is unnatural.
One or two people can't hold them.
She appears as though she's waking up.
But she's actually just groaning.
You'll see.
When dusk comes,
the situation will change.
What do you mean?
How is Agnes doing?
No word yet.
Where's Awindya?
She went that way.
Yoga.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey.
What is it?
I have never felt this frustrated.
I have absolutely no solution
to our current problem, Dis.
Our friends up there need help.
But I don't know how.
Maybe it's better
if we go back to Jakarta.
We can seek help there.
And maybe we can get more solutions there.
Hi!
Look here.
The faces of those with a full stomach.
Not sure if we can climb up there.
This was Friday.
Today is Tuesday.
Our friends up there can't wait anymore.
The more time we waste,
the less likely they are to survive.
We need to find a solution here.
This…
All of them possessed?
So, these people… Are they…
Correct. And soon,
they will wake up and go feral.
Two what?
Two more minutes?
What's in two minutes?
They all will wake up?
Will the rope hold them?
Are they going to attack us?
I don't want to get eaten by demons.
Yoga, do you see this?
Scary as hell.
They're all possessed.
See? They're going wild.
But relax. Everything is under control
with my supervision.
Dya, don't act smart!
Something is pulling me in!
It's your bag getting stuck, idiot!
You don't need to run.
I'm taking care of it.
Excuse me. Your friend has woken up.
- Thank you, nurse.
This keris is to obtain a higher position.
Put it inside your working desk.
Yes.
Thank you very much, sir.
Don't hesitate to keep me updated
if you need anything else.
Your friend is very lucky.
Now, we only wait for her injury to heal.
Your friend should have been hospitalized
for one or two days.
But given the hospital's
unfavorable condition,
it's better for your friend
to be discharged.
- Excuse me.
- Yes. Thank you, doctor.
Yes.
Don't be so dramatic, okay?
You didn't see those possessed people.
You'd be grateful you didn't have
to stay here if you saw them.
Possession is not that scary.
I mean, they're still people.
Yeah, they're still people.
But you know there's a demon inside.
Right. Okay, let's just go from here.
Okay. Get changed first.
Where the hell is my bra?
Lame excuse to hug me!
I suspect
our friends up there
can survive only until tomorrow.
And that's only if they are not possessed.
But I'm more pessimistic.
That hospital incident earlier
just convinces me even more
that your friends are
already possessed by now.
So, I think
our best effort now is
to talk to the village elders and hope
someone steps up to be a warden.
Warden is not the solution.
We're dealing with the supernatural here.
Every sacred place must have a warden.
Mountains, lakes, cemeteries.
They need wardens to guard the place.
When there's no warden,
this happens.
Dya! Dya, no!
Dya.
There's a long-haired
black figure over there.
It's watching us.
I think someone is taking advantage
of the warden's absence.
Maybe it's true
that the warden was killed.
Yoga?
Diska!
- Diska!
- Dis.
Diska, calm down.
From now on,
we have to stick together.
Okay.
Let's gather in Agnes's room. Okay?
Nes!
Jo!
Help me! Agnes has changed!
- Look at my shirt!
- Jo!
Hold Agnes down. Don't let her escape.
I'll get a rope!
Hey! I'm the one who wants to escape!
Get here! Diska!
Lift her legs!
WEDNESDAY
Dis, I don't want us to fight anymore.
But please don't try to stop me
from doing everything in my power
to save my boyfriend and friends
whose survival chance is very slim.
- Actually, I--
- May I speak for a minute?
Okay. Well…
I think today is the last day of hope
for our friends' survival.
They've been missing for four days.
If by this evening, we still have
no clear idea how to save them,
then I'm going home.
So, I will stay here
to take care of Agnes, your friend.
And you…
I hope you can do something effectively
to save those people up there.
Not just your boyfriend.
- Actually, I--
- We have to meet the warden's wife.
She understands this matter more.
Let's go, Mojo.
Actually, I plan
to accompany Dis…
Agnes.
Okay, thank you.
Careful.
Jo.
Excuse me, ma'am.
My name is Awindya.
These are my friends, Yoga and Mojo.
We'd like to ask something--
Do you know
what your name means?
I still remember.
You stood up for me
at the village gathering.
Thank you, dear.
Please come in.
What does your name mean anyway?
What do you want to ask? Go ahead.
It's about the warden.
It seems like there is no other way
to save our missing friends up there
except by voting for a new warden here.
We don't vote for a warden.
He is appointed.
All we can do is prepare the candidate
and hope he'll be qualified.
- What's the condition?
- How do we prepare?
The dwellers here
will appoint the chosen one.
In the old times, the designation
was conveyed through the king.
He would prepare the one
by providing him with knowledge
of tradition, culture,
and the supernatural.
What are the preconditions
that must be met?
The mystical dwellers
will inspect the warden candidate
and decide which rituals are required.
As for Wak Di, my late husband,
he was told to enter
an ascetic state and fast
for 40 days and 40 nights
under a huge tree in an old cemetery.
This makes most people
unwilling to be a warden.
Not to mention
having to constantly deal with demons.
Has Wak Di prepared someone
to replace him?
Yes, he has!
The one he prepared all this time
was always kept a secret by Wak Di
because he had
a bad premonition about himself.
After his unnatural death,
the potential warden is always in hiding.
Wardens not only
preserve the harmony
with the mystical realm.
In fact, most of them
prevent people with evil intentions
from exploiting
the mystical mountain dwellers.
Really, Mrs. Lakah has a vast knowledge!
I'm glad we can talk to her.
Yeah.
- Where's the map she made?
- Well…
I think we're still far from it.
It's okay. But we have hope now.
Panji.
Panji?
My gosh!
What do you want?
No, nothing.
You're just creepy.
What do you want?
Panji, are you really Wadi's student?
- Wak Di!
Yes, I said Wak Di!
Please! Panji!
Panji, you know Wak Di has passed away.
Now, with the warden absent,
the consequences are dire,
as people suffer.
It's not just one or two people.
By now, probably more
than 100 people have suffered.
Our missing friends on the mountain…
Nobody can save them.
As someone who has been prepared
by Wak Di,
you must be ready to replace him by now.
Please!
A lot of people's lives
depend on your bravery.
I'm scared I'll end up like Wak Di,
who was killed by a shaman's black magic.
The shaman had been targeting
Wak Di for so long,
waiting for that fateful day
to unleash the mountain's mystic being.
Hence, I covered myself
with black mud to repel all things evil.
Please forgive me, Wak Di.
I failed to protect you.
You don't need to apologize
because you're not at fault.
What matters now is carrying on his legacy
and continuing the progress
to become a warden.
Staying vigilant is a must.
But please keep striving
while remaining vigilant
for the sake of those people.
But this is too early.
I feel I'm not ready to replace Wak Di.
Eight years is not a short period.
Don't let Wak Di's effort and time
in preparing you be in vain.
God Almighty,
please put Wak Di
in the most honorable place beside You.
Before sunset,
please meet me at the old cemetery.
Please look after me as well.
I hope our problem will be over soon.
Yes.
This tomb looks ancient.
Relax, Jo.
Later, during the ritual,
don't beg us to go home, okay?
Do you know the story behind why
asking for money is called ngemis?
This happened during Pakubuwono X.
He was very wealthy and a philanthropist.
He used to give
his wealth away to his people.
And it was always done on Thursday.
Thus his people would say,
"Come, let us ngemis."
So, the term has stuck around to this day.
When people ask for money,
it's called ngemis.
Interesting.
I know it was you who killed Wak Di!
So, you will be Wak Di's successor?
Is that right?
Panji said he would come
before the sun sets.
It's already passed.
I bet
he changed his mind.
Like me.
What if something happened to him?
You're right.
Where the hell are you?
He's our only hope to be the new warden.
Panji!
Quick, cut the rope, Awindya!
- Awindya, hurry!
- Yes!
Panji! Hold on!
Why do I always get…
Mojo! Hurry up. Go get some help!
Mojo!
Mojo, go now!
Awindya, cut it!
Fast!
What else can we do now?
Our only hope is dead now.
I don't know what else we should do
to save our friends up there.
I really counted on Panji
to save their lives,
but now everything has come to this.
I can't think anymore.
I can't think anymore! Help me, Yoga!
Yeah, hello, Dis?
Dis, calm down. I can't hear you.
No, calm down.
What?
Agnes… Something's happening to Agnes.
Insolent!
I ask you to clean this village
of people who intend to fight me.
Yes.
I will find the offering!
Diska.
She is possessed.
She was speaking
an unknown language to me.
And she wrote that
on the wall over and over
and I don't know what it means.
This is Javanese script.
Can anyone read it?
Nes, this is Awindya. You know me, right?
I'm your classmate, Nes.
Do you understand what she said?
"It begins with some life advice
and ends with a clue."
Clue from who?
"Knock on the graveyard's gate
and meditate from midnight until sunrise.
The key to the gateway
shall fall into your lap."
She told us to meditate
in the cemetery at midnight?
I think it's more than that.
It said meditate inside the tomb.
What if it's a trap from the dwellers?
"Know the difference between the beings
who want to help and to hurt you."
- I think it wants to help us.
- Stop it!
I'm not going to indulge
in your opinions anymore!
I want to go home right now!
There's going to be an attack tonight
and I don't want to be a victim!
I don't know what's happening!
We're not going home tonight!
It's too dangerous!
Guys, we've got company!
We don't vote for a warden.
He is appointed.
Until the new warden is selected,
nobody is allowed to go up the mountain.
Do you know what your name means?
I know what we have to do!
Diska.
I promised to go home when we don't have
any more chance to save our friends.
But now I have the solution.
Come on, help me!
Where are we going?
Follow me. Let's go!
For sure. Better than being here!
Hello, Inda.
How are you?
Dad.
Be strong.
What you want to achieve
requires your struggle.
Toughen your heart.
Every problem has a solution.
But this one is tough, Dad.
I'm not sure if I can get through this.
Be wholehearted
in every hardship
and be calm.
I don't know
what you're dealing with there.
But there is one thing about my daughter
that I always believed in.
It's that you're an extraordinary girl.
You have a strong instinct, dear.
And you always fight to get what you want.
Thank you, Dad.
I will be waiting for you at home.
Dad.
What does my name mean?
Yoga.
Okay. Now listen to me, please.
When I'm down under, bury me with dirt.
Dig me up again when the sun rises.
You're out of your mind.
Don't start with that nonsense!
I disagree. You can die from suffocation!
You're calling this an effort
to save those people?
Don't you feel like an idiot
doing what she says?
I understand what Agnes's writings
on the wall meant.
I have a strong reason to believe
the messages are directed to me.
Besides, this still makes sense.
This is not the 40 days
and 40 nights ritual of a warden.
This is only performed
from midnight to sunrise.
You're planning to be the warden?
It wouldn't be a test
if it were that simple.
Please, Yoga. Diska.
Mojo.
Hurry up. Cover me with dirt.
Ten minutes left!
- Mojo, come on.
- Wait.
Come on.
Hurry.
Ten minutes left. Hurry up with the dirt!
Does your phone still have battery?
Let us know if anything!
Yoga, hurry up! Those people are coming!
Quick!
Light the torch over there
and drive them away using it.
- Dis, hurry up!
- Okay.
Yoga! Diska is being attacked!
Mojo! Help Diska now!
I have a few minutes left to bury her!
Hurry up, Jo!
Yoga!
Yoga, he took my shovel!
Yoga! Diska!
Let go of me!
Help!
- Diska!
- Help!
- Help me!
- Diska!
Let me go! Help me!
Let me go!
Diska!
Two minutes!
Mojo! Yoga!
I'll put some
into your jacket's pocket, okay?
Agnes?
Nes?
Diska!
Oh no. Bamboo forest…
Kuntilanak's home.
Mojo! Diska!
Mojo!
Diska!
Dad.
Thank you for all the knowledge
you have given me.
Every piece of knowledge is a treasure
in my life.
Devlin.
I don't know what's become of you now.
But I hope you survive
and you see this video…
Awindya.
Awindya!
Yoga!
You want to be buried alive, huh?
Let me help you.
THURSDAY
Why are you here?
You said you had an event,
so you couldn't come with me.
SUNDAY
Awindya.
Read this book. It's good.
Thank you, Dad.
- Hello?
- Hi, Awindya.
Yoga?
Hey, what are you doing?
Dya.
I want to say something.
I'll make it short.
I like you a lot.
So, I want to tell you
that I'm officially trying
to get to know you now.
But…
Okay. Then?
Miss.
You have a visitor outside.
I told him to wait on the porch.
Yoga, I have a guest right now.
We'll talk later, okay?
Okay. I just wanted to tell you that.
So that you don't misunderstand.
Today's my birthday.
If you don't mind,
I'll pick you up tonight.
Happy birthday.
Share your location.
Yoga…
Good morning.
Wellness and prosperity for you.
I am grateful that we can meet here.
Excuse me.
I am representing
the Society of Heirloom Lovers
Satrio Pinayungan.
We would like to conduct
the Jamas Satu Suro ritual.
As a warden,
if you could please permit us,
we would like to go to Mount Merapi
to perform the offering ritual.