LEFT-HANDED GIRL
Oh, look!
Can you sit up? So crowded…
You make it crowded.
- Jeez, how am I--
- You both shut up, okay?
It feels like a magical place.
Where are we?
Okay, stop yapping.
So much traffic!
So annoying.
- She's not listening.
- I want to help.
- Take this.
- Go inside, there are a lot of cars.
You two go inside.
Hurry up.
- No standing here.
- Okay.
Slow down.
This is a lot smaller than the photo.
This is so delicious.
Can we eat this every day?
Let me tell you.
Some guy in Japan…
He ate instant noodles
every day for a year.
Then he died.
Really?
Are you trying to give her nightmares?
And you know what happened in the end?
What?
There are so many preservatives
in the noodles,
so his body never decayed.
Nobody realized he had died.
Eat up, I-Jing. You have school tomorrow.
Oh, okay.
Do you still want to eat instant noodles
every day?
It's falling out.
Everyone, we have a new classmate today.
Her name is Cheng I-Jing.
She's five years old.
She's in our senior class.
This is her first day,
so she is a little nervous.
So you have to be good friends to her.
Okay.
If she wants to go to the restroom,
what do you do?
Show her the way.
Great. Let's sit down first.
I-Jing, you sit here today.
And you just keep lining them up.
When you are done,
ask me to check them, okay?
This one?
Here it is.
This is the stand.
This stand is at the best location.
This is it!
Look at the length.
This one is spacious.
You have something smaller and cheaper?
The stainless steel sink,
fridge and freezer.
They are all good to use.
You can start making money
as early as this Friday.
If you fail to pay?
Excuse me, you will be shut down.
I'm so bored.
When will we get there?
Are we there yet?
We arrived. This is it.
When you see grandparents,
remember to say hi. You heard me?
Oh, okay.
Do you remember Grandma?
You were this small when I visited.
You don't remember me?
It's okay, no problem.
So cute.
I-Ann.
Your shirt and shorts are way too short.
There are lots of perverts and psychos
out there.
It's dangerous to dress like that.
No worries, I wear these every day.
I told her many times.
She wouldn't listen.
And look at you…
You're looking haggard, you know?
Are you getting enough sleep?
We just paid the deposit.
We can start on Monday.
Why can't we run a fruit stand?
Isn't it easier to wash the fruits
and display them for sale?
Do you know that fruits are easily rotten?
You have to spend twice the money and time
to prepare the food for the noodle stand.
Is it truly a better deal?
If you make money, you can have opinions.
Okay. I will go make money myself.
I'll make more than you do.
Please, please.
No fighting while eating, okay?
She thinks she knows it all.
She didn’t even graduate high school.
Seriously.
Is that my fault?
This is our first family dinner.
Watch your attitude.
Aren't you the problem?
Wait a second.
Why is she eating with her left hand?
Don't worry about it, okay?
Give me a break and eat your dinner.
So annoying.
How come you didn’t buckle up the helmet?
Sister, look. What is that?
Sis, I got a prize at school today.
What are you doing?
Wait until we get home, not now!
I am telling Mom you ran the red light!
If you get there fast,
I won't call you out for farting.
We're almost there.
Whether it's water spilling,
or any other liquid,
let me tell you, its absorption is super.
You really don't want to try?
Uncle, you can use it as a diaper.
Inflation is out of control right now.
Only your salary didn't increase.
Hi, Johnny!
Hi.
Let me introduce my loyal customer.
Come, I-Jing, let me pick you up.
Oh, getting heavy!
Did you eat too much?
Come tell everyone
how useful this Magic Sponge is.
It is very useful!
How useful?
It is the best sponge in the world.
You'll regret not buying it.
Did you hear that?
Thanks to my special guest.
Hurry back to Mommy.
Special price today!
Buy one, get one free.
Mom.
- Did your sister pick you up on time?
- No, but she told me to say that she did.
Three.
But I still think
you need to dress a little sexier.
But I thought
what I wear is very revealing.
Six.
Revealing doesn't mean sexy.
The idea is to create a sexual fantasy
for the customer.
Seven.
Five.
Queen.
Wait, let me introduce.
Hello.
I-Ann, this is Xiao-Ping.
Xiao-Ping, this is I-Ann.
- Who is this?
- I told you. Her name's Xiao-Ping.
Hello. I'm Xiao-Ping.
Why is she here?
I told you I'm hiring a new girl.
That girl Xiao-Mei with her stone face.
Ruined my business.
So I called her and fired her.
Not my business.
This is your business.
I need you to show her the ropes.
Mom, is this the last dish?
Do you need other help?
No, no more.
Okay.
- Go do your homework.
- Okay.
This is betel nut. Betel flower. Red lime.
Get some red lime.
Put it in the center of the betel nut.
Add a betel flower.
This one is done.
- Hi, boss!
- I-Jing is here!
Our champion I-Jing is here!
Ten in a box.
You have to make 300 at once.
Put them in the fridge immediately
to keep fresh. Got it?
You're so skilled.
How long have you been doing this?
Don't be too mean. Be nice.
Don't scare her.
I am very nice.
I explain things very clearly, okay?
$2,000 increase is way too much.
- Mom, look!
- $2,000 increase…
Uncle Ding is out of cigarettes.
Go get two packs of Long Life for him.
Good girl. Thank you.
We also increased the prices.
What else is there to do?
What do you want?
One hundred?
Take a cup for me.
Here is your spit cup.
- What time are you off work?
- Huh, what?
- What's the matter?
- Want to ask you out to sing.
No, I am busy after work.
I have to teach the new girl.
How about when I am done?
Then we'll go singing together.
- Did you wrap this one?
- Yes. Isn't it good?
- Super sweet.
- Thank you.
- I will pick you up after work.
- You are such a smooth talker. Bye.
Bye-bye.
- Greenies, two hundred.
- Greenies are in the boxes.
Get four boxes.
Give them to the customer.
Here. Thank you. Bye-bye.
Count the money,
then put them in this box.
Got it?
How was it?
Nervous? Feeling scared?
Hey, boss lady.
Your employee is sleeping on the job.
You have to dock her pay.
This is for you.
Magic Sponge.
No, thanks.
You save them for your customers.
Don't be so polite with me.
I have a lot in stock.
Take it.
So…
How is the business these days?
Mediocre.
How about this?
This is a free gift for you.
Help me with promotion next time.
Okay?
It's a deal.
Ali, you close up.
- Okay, bye-bye.
- Bye-bye.
You going back?
- Say goodbye to uncle.
- Goodnight.
- Bye-bye.
Mom, can I have a dog?
Huh?
Can I have a dog?
Have a dog?
No way.
Dogs are dirty.
Your mum is dog-tired every day.
You should take care of me.
Stop looking.
Hello?
Yes, this is she.
Did you take my cell phone again?
Don't even ask?
I got a call this morning.
And?
Your father is in the hospital.
So?
So I’m going to the hospital to see him.
You are coming with me.
How is that my business?
I don't want to argue with you.
Okay. I am not arguing.
I am just not going.
I am telling you to go, so you will go!
What about you, after what he did to you?
After all the shit he put you through.
Why are you going to see him?
Not going to answer?
What an idiot.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Who's in the hospital?
Thanks.
Here.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
You can't talk now?
Didn't I tell you not to smoke so much?
Here you go.
- Boss, why are you so late today?
- I am waiting for you to get off work.
Waiting for me to get off work?
You're so sweet.
There is still a long time to go.
Okay, ride safely. Bye.
Do you have two for 200 special?
You're too much. You said you were going
to be late, but an hour and a half hours?
- What the hell?
- Something to take care of at home.
You got things going on at home every day.
Thank God for Xiao-Ping.
- She worked two extra hours.
- They're jumbo.
- Why don’t you give her more hours then?
- All you know how to do is talk back?
What?
2 for 200.
You idiot, you can't do that.
What if he were a cop?
What's wrong now?
She is acting like an idiot.
More money, more problems.
I-Ann. Go pick up I-Jing at school today.
Then help Ali open the stand.
Why me?
How much time are you spending
at the hospital?
He has very little time left. He's dying.
He deserves it.
It has nothing to do with you.
If you were in the hospital today,
he would just abandon you.
Okay. If you must go,
you better find out exactly
how much he made these ten plus years.
Even if he just made one dime,
it belongs to us.
You get it?
Are you done?
Not yet.
Who made a dime?
Shush. None of your business.
Didn't Mom tell you,
never interrupt when adults are talking?
Got it?
Grandpa loves me.
Always loves me.
The class is over. Let's go have snacks.
Okay.
How come you didn't buckle up?
I want an extra-large bubble milk tea.
So I have energy to work.
Let me try. Let me show you. Look!
That's gross.
Come on, one, two.
- Come on.
- Two balls only.
Let's compete. Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
- Wait for me.
Hurry up.
- You don't wait for me.
- You saw that?
- I-Ann.
- No wonder you don't have friends.
You got customers.
- Their noodle is delicious.
- Okay.
I am the champion.
Wonton soup.
One dried noodle, one wonton soup,
and one blanched veggies.
Eat here.
One dried noodle--
Dried noodle, wonton soup,
blanched veggies.
Thanks.
Wait a moment.
The food will be ready right away.
I-Ann. How come
you haven’t come here for so long?
I am working at a betel nut stand now.
Put it here?
Yes, right here.
Oh. You work at the betel nut stand.
Your mom is okay with that?
I don't care about her.
Anyway, I’ll end up earning more than her.
You don't know how to cook, stop it.
- Okay, you do it, whatever.
- You get out.
What a mess.
Come check it out. Multifunction brush.
There are four types of brushes.
You can brush the glass,
the toilet, the tiles, the cracks.
Solve all the problems
with just one bottle.
Hey, hey, hey.
You cheated again.
"You cheated again."
You cheated again. One more time.
Hurry up.
I haven’t finished the hey, hey, hey part.
You cheated.
Okay, play on your own.
Do your drawings. Be good.
- Are you leaving?
- I am leaving.
Bye-bye.
What is this?
Hey, who did this?
I saw some kids
spitting the tapioca balls earlier.
Today's youth… Unbelievable.
This has gone too far!
I have a brush. Let me help you clean.
Pissing me off.
Don't I have enough work to do?
Let me help. Let me help.
Let me tell you, this tool is amazing.
I have four types of brushes.
You can brush glass, brush the toilet…
Go sit over there first.
Wait here. Got it?
Can't speak?
That's great.
No apologies or explanations.
Save the trouble.
I'm not here to converse with you.
I just want to say one thing.
I told you I am not going to read it.
Sis, I want to use the restroom.
Are you surprised?
Do you think Mom
would foolishly wait for you?
She had already met another man
in Taichung.
Next time my mother comes in here,
I want you to tell her
not to come visit you again.
You heard me?
Sis, who's he?
Who's he?
You are so annoying!
Why are you being aggressive?
If you dare tell Mom we came here,
you will be fucked.
I will throw out all your crayons.
You heard me?
What are you crying about? Answer me!
Okay.
This Friday and Saturday,
I have to go to Yilan for some errands.
Go help Ali open the stand earlier.
Then take I-Jing to Grandma's.
Let her stay overnight.
What errands?
He's dying,
what can you be helping him with?
Why are you so opinionated?
You already paid for his debt
more than ten years.
What else do you owe him?
He is dead.
Once I take care of his funeral,
I’ll be done paying. Are you happy now?
The noodle is ready.
Bring it to the customer for me.
All right, I am working, okay?
Here are your noodles.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
There is a customer, take the order.
I want dried noodles, small.
And blanched veggies.
- Dried noodles--
- Help me wash the dirty dishes.
Small meat meatball soup.
Okay.
It will be ready soon.
Okay. Thanks.
Squid ball!
- Okay, I will have roasted corn.
- Okay.
Cheng I-Ann?
It's me, Xie Mu-Xi.
Long time no see.
You look different.
Xie Mu-Xi?
We were in the same class
in Taipei High School.
I changed my name. It was Xie Xin-Yi.
My mom took me to a fortune-teller.
He suggested changing my name
to get a better shot on the college exam.
For real?
More than half of our classmates
changed their names.
For real?
I had no idea.
I didn't know you were in Taipei.
Yeah, I moved back here recently.
Which university do you go to?
I am not in university.
Do you work here?
No, this is my mom's noodle stand.
I come here to help once in a while.
We are throwing a motel party next week.
Pin-Rui is super impressive.
He booked the biggest suite.
Please come. We haven’t seen each other
for so long. It will be fun!
Motel party?
Hurry, get off.
I don't want to go to Grandma's place.
Grandpa never takes showers.
He smells like stinky tofu!
You are the stinky one.
Stop complaining. Go inside.
Listen to Grandpa and Grandma.
Okay.
Eating with her left hand?
Shu-Fen doesn't know how to raise a kid?
Give me a break.
Times have changed.
- Nobody cares about this anymore.
- It makes me angry to see that!
If it were in the old days…
If you insist on using your left hand,
you'll be hung up and beaten.
- You have a U.S. visa?
- Yes.
Let me see.
What are you looking at?
Children should listen and not talk.
Be good, watch them dance.
They are bad.
Be good.
She’s arriving tomorrow night.
Your flight is early Sunday morning.
She’ll have to sleep over at your place.
- Is that okay?
- Okay, no problem.
You need to be careful
when passing the customs.
Don't touch this.
This is worth a lot of money.
Fuck. This is why I don't want kids.
A student in Taichung changed her name
to Guo, Salmon-Don
on the morning of the 17th.
We asked her why changing her name
to Salmon-Don.
And she told my colleague directly.
She is following a promotion
ed by a business.
A known sushi restaurant started
a “looking for the salmon” promotion.
Don't use left hand in my house.
If your name contains “salmon,”
you can invite five of your friends.
Enjoy all-you-can-eat sushi for free.
- Will you change your name?
- No.
Why not?
It just doesn’t make sense to change
my name based on a free meal.
I'll have to keep changing my name
for the rest of my life.
Can you hurry up?
Wait, why the rush?
I have to go open the noodle stand
for my mom.
Why didn't you tell me?
I told you I need to take today off.
Can we not talk about this now?
- Auntie.
- Hi, Qing-Long.
Please come in.
Come in quickly.
Why so nervous?
You don’t understand.
We have a nosy neighbor.
- She's all yours.
- I will take care of her, no worries.
Smoking again?
Go clean up!
Okay, I will leave, okay?
I-Ann.
Your maid Mary doesn't seem to like you.
I have a name. My name is Ali.
Ali you good!
Ali good!
Goodbye, goodbye.
This way, have a seat.
Have a seat.
The magical toothpaste squeezing tool!
This thing is amazing.
With this tool, you use up all toothpaste.
Not a drop left.
- Give it a try.
- Does this really work?
It's great for I-Jing.
Kids are bad at squeezing the tube.
With this tool,
it will be squeezed completely clean.
She doesn't brush her teeth anyway.
No need.
Did you eat?
- I ate already. Thank you.
- I see.
Why do you speak funny?
Be polite!
Kids don't know any better.
Where's your mother? Why isn't she here?
Are you interested in my mom?
I…
Come, let me help.
Wen-Bing, you get in first.
I-Jing.
I was helping!
Oh, right! There are four bags of food
in the refrigerator,
and another four bags in the freezer.
You got it?
I will be back next Tuesday. Goodbye.
Bye.
Hey!
Your grandmother or your mother…
I don’t care what others say.
But not on my watch.
You can’t use your left hand anymore,
got it?
Why?
Why? Left hand is evil.
It belongs to the devil.
If you use left hand you are doing
the devil's work. You got it?
Okay.
Are you serious?
It’s so cute. It's the only thing
your father left behind.
A meerkat?
Not sure where he got one.
Just kept it as a pet.
What's its name?
I don't know.
GooGoo…
Call it GooGoo!
23, 24, 25.
It's right. Thank you.
So easy, right?
Not only easy, but very convenient.
They have cheaper vitamins over there!
Really?
By the way.
Lee wants to know if you want to go again
on the 15th of next month?
That day is my birthday.
Well, this…
My son is coming back to Taiwan,
and throwing me a birthday party.
Okay, we will let you know.
Hey.
Can you tell how old I am?
Sixty-five?
I'm not that old.
I'm not even 60 yet.
Boss, how much is this?
Sixty bucks.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
GooGoo, look!
The Devil Hand got it for me.
Is it pretty?
GooGoo, your ball is over there.
GooGoo.
Get it out of here, take it away!
You look different today.
Do I look pretty?
Pretty!
This can clean the glass, let me show you.
You can spray inside, spray the top,
spray the bottom, spray outside.
After you spray it down.
Johnny, the battery charger
you gave me was lousy.
Bring me a more powerful one
next time, okay?
I will give you something that
would last for a month, okay?
Now you are talking.
Look, once you wipe, right?
It’s spotless, right?
Ali.
- Cook the noodle for me.
- Okay.
Brother Yang, excuse me. Let's go sit
at the back, okay? I'll buy you a drink.
I have some unexpected expenses
this month.
I’ll make sure to pay on time next month!
- I'm sorry.
- Next month?
I didn't receive it last month either.
Do you know?
You should know.
Our night market is the busiest
and most vibrant in all of Taipei.
Yes--
If you keep paying rent late,
then I'll let others take over.
I'm really sorry.
I won't do this next month.
Don't get it wrong. I have to make
so many trips just to collect the rent.
What's up with that?
- I am sorry.
- Yang!
Why so angry? Have a drink.
People are lined up waiting to take over.
You have to pay rent
to keep your business.
Weren’t you looking for the watch that
takes the blood pressure?
I got some in stock. Wanna see it?
- I am really sorry.
- You have it?
Yes. I just had a new shipment today.
Sir, your noodles.
When you are in a bad mood,
you need to have some drinks. Come on.
Perfect.
- Ali!
- You are back.
- Mom.
- I-Jing!
Where did you go? Having that much fun?
I have a rotating savings plan.
And it matures this month.
I don't need that money.
I am thinking…
Do you want to borrow it first?
No need.
You keep the money.
I'll figure it out.
I'm going to close up first.
Hey.
Wait for me when you're done.
We can drink more.
Okay, no problem!
Cheng I-Ann! You are here!
I was looking for you.
You look so pretty today.
I just threw on whatever. You too.
Thank you. Wanna come in and get a drink?
It is so cute. Its name is GooGoo?
Yes.
Does it bite?
No.
GooGoo.
First time visiting, I have to bring you
a gift. I brought some liquor.
Okay, let's drink yours.
I-Jing, time for bed. It's late.
No more playing with GooGoo. Go to bed.
Bye, GooGoo.
Good night.
- That's embarrassing.
- What are they doing?
Do you like college life?
Love it!
How come you're not in university?
My family can't afford it.
I thought you would go
to a national university.
You were a straight A student.
Also, the campus belle.
Everyone was super jealous of you.
Campus belle is an embarrassing title.
I-Jing, did you brush your teeth?
Not yet.
I never thought I'd see you again.
You just disappeared one day.
We moved after my father ran away.
I thought your father left
long before that.
Yeah! Let's open the champagne!
One, two, three, yeah!
Thank you.
Where is the cap?
It's okay.
We are going to finish it anyway.
Smile more. You usually seem a bit gloomy.
You seem distracted at work.
I think when you smile
you look really nice.
What is it?
Drink. What's wrong?
Nothing.
Not drunk.
Okay, just a little.
So how much?
What are you talking about?
Two for 200. 100 for a thigh touch.
Two for 200.
I work hard.
You have no right to criticize others!
Why so nasty?
You college kids think you're hot shit?
Buzzkiller.
Cheng I-Ann!
What's up with her?
What’s the situation?
Are we…
moving too fast?
Why is it so hard to open?
Let me help you.
Ready.
Shu-Fen?
Your mom fell asleep.
Why aren't you leaving?
I am leaving.
Get the fuck out!
Good night.
Do you have ID?
Leave your contact info here.
Hey!
What?
Nothing.
Are you kidding me? You're looking at her?
Quiet down. That’s not true.
- Go ahead if you want to fuck her.
- No. Come back first!
- He is yours.
- What?
Freebies next time!
Okay, thanks. See you. Bye-bye.
- What are you looking at? Go inside!
- Nothing, we were just organizing things.
Had a little quarrel.
Come out.
All right.
Here you go. Go.
Play ball with me?
You like it.
Let me have it.
I-Jing, let's go. We are going to have
a tea afternoon with aunties and Grandma.
But I want to bring GooGoo…
Absolutely not!
Here, I brought gifts for everyone.
- Everyone has one. One bag per person.
- Mom, thanks.
This is yours.
- Here, this is yours.
- This is great!
There is no fish oil?
So we got t-shirts?
These vitamins are the best!
Besides, it has the highest potency!
They are very expensive.
How often do you travel to America?
No. I go about twice a month.
Twice? Twice is a lot.
No big deal. Let me go to the restroom.
Look at her, dodging the topic again.
It's almost Mom’s birthday.
Where to hold the party this year?
Tong-Qing restaurant.
Where else?
- How much is it per table?
- Let me clarify first.
- I have no money to share the bills.
- What's your problem again?
Will our brother share the bill with us?
It is not a lot of money.
Cheng Jiang-Qing's medical bills
and funeral cost me 150K NKD.
He died? When?
What? Does he have no family anymore?
It's not your responsibility
to pay for the funeral.
- Who is he to you?
- I'm his only family.
- Wow.
- How come?
- You need to get your head straight.
- Miss, this is not a small amount.
Are you rich now?
Even if I'm not rich, I still had to pay.
- Can you stop making sarcastic comments?
- Are you running a charity?
He helped you get a job.
He lent money to your husband when needed.
Don’t bring up what happened
a million years ago.
- I paid it back, okay?
- These are two separate matters.
Like I said, if I didn't pay for him,
no one would pay.
It's not about you pay it back or not.
- He helped you.
- These are two separate matters.
- She paid the money back.
- I worked hard.
He passed away. I paid for his funeral.
Not on just… not for luxury spending.
Shouldn't you assess your situation first?
- It's for his funeral.
- You never discuss with us.
- I don't get it.
- You act first and inform us later.
- Look at you now. The choices you've made.
- Weird, this is my life.
- Why are you so involved?
- Excuse me. Please lower your volume.
Because there are other customers.
Thanks.
Who is Cheng Jiang-Qing?
You should think about this.
You're always like this.
Hey, what's going on?
I was only away for two minutes.
- I don't have two.
- No card, drink up!
Over there.
Full house with six.
Too high, I don't have it.
- No card, drink up!
- A-Ming.
None.
I need to talk to you.
Every time she comes to me, it's never for
anything good. Let's hear it. What is it?
I need to take a day off on the 15th.
Grandma's 60th birthday.
- See? Didn't I call it?
- Arrange the work schedule for me.
It’s either being late or leaving early.
You talk to Xiao-Ping yourself.
So she can make her own schedule now?
You do it for me.
Big Two.
Pass.
Girl!
What do you need?
I want leaf wraps.
- What's wrong with her?
- I don't know. I will check on her.
Are you okay?
Come check it out!
Special sale today!
Shu-Fen.
Do you remember drinking at your place
that day? You got drunk in the end?
You fell asleep later.
Do you remember anything
before you fell asleep?
I was drunk that day too.
But it was fun. I am thinking…
if there's a chance,
I could…
go to your place again…
I'll let you work. Carry on.
I-Jing!
What?
What are you doing?
Nothing. Just browsing.
- Let's go have some shaved ice!
- Okay.
GooGoo, I am going to throw the ball.
Look!
GooGoo, don't bother me.
I'm drawing right now.
This will be the last throw.
GooGoo!
Now I am at the scene of the accident.
There was just a motorcycle
self-crash accident here.
When the motorcycle passed here,
it seems like a meerkat fell from the sky.
The motorcyclist was so startled
that they couldn't react in time
and fell to the ground
I don’t know from which floor.
A little animal fell down.
I didn't see it clearly.
And it hit the motorcyclist.
Then he slammed on the brakes.
Then he charged toward that direction.
And then he fell down.
And he started bleeding.
I was scared to death.
A mouse that's bigger
than a cat fell from the sky.
Did it fall right in front of you or what?
It fell in front of my body.
I was startled.
- Are you in pain?
- What nonsense are you talking about?
We can take a look at the scene.
There is a long skid mark on the ground
at the scene, left by the motorcyclist.
There's a pool of unidentified blood
at the scene.
Not sure if it's the motorcyclist's
or meerkat's.
Why on earth the meerkat
would fall from the sky?
Relevant details are yet
to be clarified by the police.
Okay, enough.
Why does it keep replaying?
It's so annoying.
Can I go see it?
No. The landlord knows we have a pet,
we might get kicked out.
Why did it have to jump down
with the ball?
Not your fault.
I know it's not my fault.
That's the Devil's fault.
It's okay.
Don't worry, okay?
Don't be sad.
Hey.
Which one of you is Cheng I-Ann?
You?
Come outside with me.
What the fuck!
- Vixen! Think you can sleep with husbands?
- You fucking psycho, who are you? What?
- A-Ming!
- You don't get it?
This is my husband’s stand!
What? Who are you?
- You slept with my husband, got it?
- Didn't you say you're divorced?
I've never said that.
You told me you're divorced!
Fuck you! Don’t touch my husband!
What the fuck is your problem?
You crazy bitch!
- How dare you hit me?
- Wait!
- Don't run away!
- Calm down!
- Cheng I-Ann, come back here!
- This is embarrassing!
Don't pull me!
I am out! I fucking quit!
Hey, you cannot quit.
Who's going to take care of my shop?
Run as far as you can, please!
Don’t let me see you again!
You should die!
Forgot to tell you, he never wore a condom
and he came inside me.
I am pregnant with his kid, peace out!
This is a fast charger.
It charges in five minutes,
then you can talk for five hours.
200 dollars each.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Come again.
Take a look.
- Johnny.
- Yeah.
Don't I often promote
your products for you?
- Yes.
- You should pay me for the advertising.
Oh. You're charging me
for advertising fees?
Is it enough?
Yes.
- You have to help me with promotion again.
- Okay.
100 for 10 times.
Okay.
I only need one.
50 is your change.
This is called a Magic Sponge.
It is incredibly absorbent.
Come, you can touch it.
Come, you can check it out.
Young girl, wanna check it out?
Don't miss it if you're passing by!
Last time my guy in New York told me
you talked nonstop
for 15 hours on the plane.
That's not true.
Besides, we got along great.
As long as you know the drill.
Make sure she still looks
exactly like her passport photo.
You do the talking at the customs.
No worries.
Call me when you're back.
Okay.
Aren't you going to dance?
Table two.
Boss, sorry.
I-Jing, take a break. I'll clean it up.
Cheng I-Jing!
What are you doing?
You tell me,
how many times have I come here?
Did I receive the rent?
Where is your credibility?
I’m giving you a three-day deadline!
The final deadline.
If you don't have the money, get lost.
If I had the money,
I would definitely give it to you.
Don't be like that. There are
so many people in the night market.
What did I say
when you came the first day?
I told you the payment's due
on the first of every month.
- Don't be like that!
- What do you think this place is?
- A charity?
- All right.
All right. Enough.
Three days!
Shu-Fen.
Let me help you.
I'll figure something out.
I'll get the money.
Why are you smoking in my room?
Go smoke on the balcony!
Why are you home?
Aren't you supposed to be at work?
Mind your own business.
Is it not okay to watch TV?
She hasn’t gone to work at this hour,
she probably got fired.
We're out of money,
you need to go to work.
You're all talk.
Why don’t you go make money yourself?
I am too young!
Whatever.
I have something important
to discuss with Grandma later.
Stay quiet over there, got it?
Okay.
Here you are.
Come in.
I am cooking braised meat.
Hello, I-Jing, here you are.
Why are you here?
Mom called and invited me over.
Aren't you the one
who hates social visits?
Go look at the fish.
Mom, why did you tell her
I was coming over?
- What's the big deal? This isn't a secret.
- But I need to talk to you privately.
Why do you two always end up
arguing as soon as you meet?
When did I argue with her?
What secret are you trying to tell?
Mom, I'm not asking for much.
Only three months.
It should take about three months
to get back to normal.
I already promised your sisters
I would not lend you money anymore.
What does it have to do with them?
I'm not borrowing from them.
Why did you clean up his mess again?
Fish are so dumb.
Fish have no wisdom, so stupid.
At least you can help out
the family a bit, right?
Don't forget, miss.
You still owe me the rent for that house
and haven't paid me back yet.
Hello?
I-Ann.
This is A-Ming.
I need to talk to you.
Fuck you, shut up.
I have something important
to discuss with you.
What about when his factory closed down?
Why didn’t any family members
come forward to help?
You are such a pain.
Cheng Shu-Fen. Get your facts straight!
You're married off already. Shame on you!
How dare you come back to borrow money?
Why are you eavesdropping
on our conversation?
I’m begging you, please wake up!
How long do they need to drag on?
How many times do you need to borrow?
I can’t stand you repeating
the same thing over and over.
All right. Stop arguing already!
My blood pressure is spiking!
Let me tell you.
I… really have no money to lend you.
Heard it?
No money to lend you!
If I were your son, you would have money!
That's right.
A married daughter's like water that's
poured out. I treat my daughters nice.
In the end,
you’re someone else's daughter-in-law.
Mom kindly helped you.
You should be more grateful. When your
husband runs away, don’t yell--
- Watch your bitchy mouth!
- Stop talking nonsense over there!
If it weren’t for the noodle stand
not being able to stay afloat,
do you think I would be here?
Whatever. I don’t know!
Let's go home.
Don't forget, you're a woman.
Do you know this apartment has already
been transferred to our brother’s name?
Idiot!
Mom!
- What is it?
- Is what she said true?
What?
Didn't you say this apartment
would be divided into three parts?
I-Jing!
Go help me arrange the chairs!
PAWN SHOP
Hello, I-Ann? This is A-Ming.
I have something to tell you.
- Whose number is this?
- Don't worry about that for now!
I called you nonstop,
but you didn’t answer.
I have nothing to say to you.
Fuck your mother!
Fuck your rotten stand.
Fuck your crazy ugly wife!
The baby in your belly…
Why are they here so early? Let me check.
Are you Wu Xue-Mei?
Yes. What's the matter?
National Immigration Agency.
We're going to search your house.
Please come in.
I clearly put the passports
and tickets on the table yesterday.
The cops came
and suddenly everything disappeared.
I'm telling you,
everything suddenly disappeared!
Mom, the police are already gone.
You don't have to speak so quietly.
Also, why do they have a search warrant?
The District Prosecutor's Office
has legally indicted 21 people.
Thank goodness. I didn't end up in jail.
What a blessing!
Okay, everyone be quiet.
Line up two in a row.
Come, go out and put on your shoes.
We can go outside and play now!
- Play outside!
- Okay!
Find your own shoes then move forward.
Find your shoes then go to the front.
Let others put theirs on. Be careful.
The cops probably lifted the passports
when you weren’t looking.
Oh, that's possible!
You idiot!
I'm telling you, no matter how much
you make, it's not worth the risk.
How about you with
your porno magazine stash under the bed?
When the police came they turned
everything over. Aren't you embarrassed?
That's called art.
What the fuck do you know?
Art my ass.
They all look the same anyway.
What a heathen.
I have something very valuable for you.
What is it?
Whose is this?
Mine.
Why are you pawning this?
Because my mom has no money,
she needs money.
Does she know you are pawning this?
No.
Try calling again, I dare you!
Believe me, I'll call the police!
Huh?
I thought the Devil Hand could help.
What are you talking about?
I wanted to get money to help Mom.
What money? What Devil Hand?
I don't understand.
This is my Devil Hand.
I am not the one who stole things.
It was my Devil Hand
that stole everything!
Not me.
Who told you all this?
Grandpa.
Slow down.
Cut it out! Hurry up.
Where exactly are we going?
Let's go visit Grandpa first.
I-Ann?
What's wrong?
Grandma! Was it you who told her
this was valuable?
The passports?!
My dear sweetheart, thank you.
If it weren’t for you,
Grandma would be locked up.
Thank you.
The Devil Hand did it!
Not me!
Grandpa!
Can you please tell her
there is no such thing as the Devil Hand?
The left hand has always been
the Devil Hand, okay?
You're not supposed to use
your left hand to do things.
I'm telling you,
none of you are teaching her.
Which era are you from?
Women don't bind their feet anymore.
Lefties are everywhere now!
Please tell her.
The Devil Hand doesn't exist at all.
Okay.
There is no Devil Hand.
It's God's hand.
It's the hand that saves Grandma.
Grandma, can you stop confusing her?
I-Jing, let me tell you.
There's no Devil Hand
or any other supernatural hand.
This is your hand.
Do you hear me?
I threw the ball with my left hand
and caused GooGoo to die.
That was just an accident.
Sometimes accidents happen.
No one can predict them, right?
If that day… if you had thrown the ball
with your right hand,
GooGoo would still have fallen, right?
I've done a lot of bad things
with my left hand.
Huh? What other bad things have you done?
Did you steal all of this?
My Devil Hand did it.
Cheng I-Jing, you stole them.
do you know your child has been missing
for three hours?
Wasn't she playing nearby?
Let's go.
Where are you two going?
To teach her a lesson.
By the way, this is from your mom.
I-Jing, are you here to visit me?
Yes, I am here to return something.
What do you say?
I am sorry.
I stole this.
It's okay.
If you like something, just tell me.
- Don't take it without asking.
- I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
It's all right.
I-Jing, come visit me next time.
- Okay.
- What do you say?
Say thank you.
"Thank you. Sorry."
Thank you. I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Sorry about this.
Sorry, sis.
It's okay. Go. Let's go.
Where did you steal this from? That one?
That store?
Wait.
Go return it yourself.
You have to apologize.
Got it?
Go.
I-Jing, here you are.
I stole this.
Huh?
Okay. No big deal.
No big deal, okay?
- Don't do it again, okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
No big deal. Bye-bye.
Did you apologize?
Yes.
Did the owner forgive you?
You are doing great! Okay?
Remember to say sorry.
You got it?
Go.
I am sorry I stole this from you.
It's okay. Don't do it again.
Bye-bye. Come here.
I'm sorry I stole this from you.
Little girl, you are here again?
Why did you take it?
Okay, it's all right. Don't do it again.
It's all right.
Be good. Bye-bye.
Don't do it again.
Okay.
Did you apologize?
Did you? Okay, that's good. Okay?
It's okay.
Turn around. I'll help you tie the bow.
Okay. The bow is done.
Are the night market sisters ready?
You are so pretty!
You are going to perform on stage, right?
She wouldn't dare.
- Are you two ready?
- Pretty. Ready?
- Let's go. We can't be late. Hurry up.
- You ready?
Let's go. Hurry up, we are late.
Hey.
Your turn.
- Where are we?
- Six.
Seven.
Why are you zoning out?
Forget about her.
Xiao-Ping is hotter.
Stop acting like you know something
and talking nonsense.
It has nothing to do with her. Seven.
Always taking leave for no reason.
Always acting like a green-eyed monster.
Why are you thinking about her?
Taking days off?
By the way, what's the date today?
Friday.
No, I mean the date!
Not what day of the week it is.
The 15th.
Didn't she say the 15th is
her grandmother's birthday?
Yes, her grandma's birthday!
Okay, thank you.
You are very pretty, the best!
You can have some appetizers
and drink first.
If you want to take photos together,
we are ready.
- Is it the time to start?
- Yes.
Okay, get off first.
I'll help you with the helmet.
Let me have it.
Let me help you.
Good.
- This one?
- Yes.
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
Shu-Fen, they are all relatives today?
Should be.
You sit inside.
Okay.
- We're here.
- Big sis.
How are you?
Hi, everyone. My name is Johnny.
- My boyfriend, Johnny.
- Xiao-He.
- Xiao-Hong.
- Xiao-Hong, hi.
- This is my brother.
Her brother.
Zhen-Xing, I am Johnny.
Sit. Why don't you sit down?
Oh, I-Ann. Come say hi.
You've grown up.
Uncle.
Hi, Uncle. Long time no see.
I-Jing, the little one.
Her little one.
- I haven't met her.
- I-Jing.
Say uncle.
You guys go sit over there.
Kids sit over there.
Auntie will take you there.
Okay.
Let the adults talk.
Your daughter?
No. We've only known each other
for six months.
Just met.
Not long.
Anything to drink?
Give me the cup. I will help you.
- Anything.
- Thank you.
Can I use your phone?
May I ask,
is there a Ms. Wu Xue-Mei's
birthday banquet?
Yes.
Is there?
Okay. Thank you. Got it.
Bye-bye.
Sis, you moved back to Taipei?
How long are you staying this time?
Just for the weekend.
Work is busy.
I just moved to Shanghai.
- Johnny.
- Nice to see you.
- Thank you for your hard work!
- Huh?
My sister is difficult.
Not at all. Your sister is very nice.
And what do you do?
Oh, I am in…
trade.
In trade.
Oh. Really?
Have you gone public?
Yes. I'm at the night market.
Public night market trading.
Whatever you need. Let me know.
Anything you can't get, I can.
- Okay.
- Okay, no problem.
Thank you.
Who are you?
She's my younger sister.
And what's your name?
I-Jing.
The birthday star is here!
Uncle, Auntie.
Happy birthday! Happy birthday!
You look beautiful today.
Thanks.
Mom.
Come here.
Dad, you sit over there.
I am sitting with my son.
- Be careful.
- Dad, have some water.
- You rushed over?
- My precious son.
Here. Wanna drink some water?
Dad and Mom, this is my boyfriend, Johnny.
Uncle.
Auntie, happy birthday.
Hello, nice to meet you.
What do you do?
He has a stand in the night market.
He is right next to Fen’s stand.
Selling stuff.
I sell all kinds of things.
I have everything.
If you need anything, let me know.
Hey, I have to go first.
Something came up.
- You are on your own tonight, okay?
- Oh, okay.
- Keep it up. Call me if anything comes up.
- Okay.
What could possibly happen?
I don't get it.
All right then.
Next, let's give Mom a big applause!
Say a few words to us. Mom!
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you everybody, welcome!
Thank you for taking the time to be here.
My precious son.
So thoughtful! So devoted!
To throw this party for me.
Mom, happy birthday!
Thank you.
Before we all start eating,
let's first make a toast,
wish Mom a happy birthday, all right?
Happy birthday!
- Excuse me, excuse me.
- Uncle here.
I'll get it myself.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- Are there no glasses?
- Over there. The drink you just had.
Good girl.
This is my favorite granddaughter.
I mean, you are all my favorites.
All my favorites.
Grandma lied to them.
You are my precious baby.
Grandma. It's your birthday.
We toast to you.
Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday!
While everyone is eating,
I want to take this moment
to wish my mom a very happy birthday.
So I'd like to ask my daughter Meilin
to come up! Meilin.
She also advanced to
the Star Brilliance Grand Finals.
So she is going to sing the same song.
The judge also mentioned
if she pursues opportunities in China,
her future prospects will be incredible!
Mom, happy birthday!
Why are you so slow?
- You are very slow.
- Let's go, let's go.
Let me go get her.
You wait here. Calm down.
Calm down. Wait for me here.
I-Ann.
Can you come downstairs with us?
We need to talk to you.
Cheng I-Ann.
- Fuck! What are you all doing here?
- Step outside to talk.
Cut it out!
We have something important to talk
to you about Please step outside.
I tried calling you
and you wouldn't answer. This is serious.
Birthday banquet, how dare you come here?
I'm giving you a chance to save face--
Shh. Get out!
Come out to talk.
Get out!
I'm giving you a chance to save face--
What's going on?
- Sorry, this has nothing to do with you.
- I am her mother.
You two need something?
You are her mother?
I am her former boss.
I need to talk to her. I am sorry.
- We've been looking for her for two weeks.
- You fucking stinky bitch!
- Why are you doing this?
- Come here.
Don't you know how many guests are here?
I already quit, what the fuck do you want?
Shut up!
Now you can tell me what happened.
How did she offend you?
You feel the need to disturb the banquet.
Well?
No one wants to tell?
Okay, I will tell you!
Your daughter slept with my husband
and got pregnant!
There are a lot of people here.
Don’t be so loud.
Is it true?
It's none of your business.
- I'm asking you if this is true.
- She told us herself.
We have three girls now.
If your daughter is having a boy,
it's ours.
- Impossible! Are you out of your mind?
- Am I out of my mind?
I don’t care
that you slept with my husband.
At this point, I just need a son to help
divvy up the family fortune. Am I wrong?
You slept with my hubby for free!
- Enough.
- I'll go check.
You don't need to worry about the money.
We would pay for everything--
Can you shut up?
We would pay for all expenses.
As long as she is having a boy,
I'll pay for everything!
What's going on?
- I'm asking you if it is true.
- Don’t do this!
I'm asking you if it is true.
Don't do this.
- She told us she's pregnant.
- Enough.
You are talking about this, right?
That's long gone, bitch!
- I am gonna fucking kill you today!
- What are you doing?
Let go!
- Let go!
- Let's go back! Calm down!
- Get out!
- Let's go!
- She seduced my husband--
- I'll call the police if you don't stop!
Enough! Let's go!
- Cheng I-Ann, go to hell!
- Enough!
It's okay.
- Let's go.
- Don't hold me back!
Get out!
Why aren't you leaving?
Sorry. Could you give this to I-Ann?
You still haven't learned your lesson.
When are you going to take
responsibility for your life? You…
Sit.
Is everything okay?
It's okay.
So…
What happened up there?
None of your business.
The reason your mom was so angry is
because she cares about you.
Do you even know my mom?
Just because you slept with my mom
for two weeks, you get to be my dad?
Sis, where did you go?
I talked to her.
There is nothing to talk about.
She is helpless.
Sorry about the commotion earlier.
Disturbed everyone.
First of all, thank you for attending
my dear mommy's 60th birthday banquet.
My mommy did everything for me,
and my dear sisters.
Last year,
the world economy was really bad.
So I started an international company.
The purpose is to support more
families affected by unemployment.
So they can achieve dreams and have hopes.
And my biggest financial sponsor
is my dear mommy.
Please give this great philanthropist
a big round of applause!
Mommy!
Happy birthday!
Wishing you have a long life.
Let's wish our wonderful mom…
Thank you for giving birth to us
and raising us, and teaching us.
Happy birthday!
May you have blessings as deep as the sea
and a life as long as the mountains.
We prepare a special birthday cake
for our mother.
Let's have the waiter bring it out,
shall we?
Wait!
I have something to say.
What's she up to?
Grandma.
Thank you
for never treating me like a child.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Before we cut the cake,
I-Jing and I want to say
happy birthday to you.
Me first.
Grandma, happy birthday!
Next is I-Jing's turn.
Hold this.
Say it.
Great-Grandma, happy birthday.
Sweetie, you said it wrong!
I am Grandma, not Great-Grandma.
Say it again.
Great-Grandma, happy birthday.
I-Jing is right.
Grandma is I-Jing's great-grandmother.
My mom seriously thought
she could cover it all up--
You're drunk.
Can you stop acting like this?
- I am not drunk!
- Sorry, she drank too much!
I gave birth to I-Jing, not you!
What are you doing?
- Can you tell me--
- She should know by now!
What are you talking about?
I only did it to protect you.
Why don't you understand?
You're so young.
With a kid, who would marry you?
Why do I have to marry someone?
For my entire life, you only care
about saving your own face!
Have you ever cared about how I feel?
Mom.
Why am I a great-grandmother?
I am a great-grandmother?
You better explain it right now!
This is so humiliating!
Why does it have to be today?
How could you lie to me
about something so serious?
You’ve completely made me lose face!
Do you have any shame at all?
Do you really not want me
to live in peace?
Or were you going to keep
this secret forever?
That was my original plan.
- Shut up!
- Mom!
- Keep your mouth shut!
- All right.
Just calm her down first.
Bring her back here.
Go sit down.
Go sit down for now.
Just go sit down first.
Calm down.
Today's birthday party sure is
full of surprises.
Look at this
longevity peach birthday cake.
This is a real longevity peach!
Before cutting longevity peach,
first let's sing. Happy birthday song!
Happy birthday to you!
You are in a good mood today.
Not at all.
What are you doing here?
I just wanted to help.
Oh, this is called a Magic Sponge.
Magic Sponges are on sale today!
Hey! Special discount today!
Buy one, get one free.
Buy three for just 50!
Want to take a look?
Here we come.
Be gentler.
Hi, Ali.
I-Jing.
You clean this one.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
Ready for I-Jing's solo concert?
I-Jing's concert!
Mom, look!
Applause and scream!
- Keep it down!
- A concert is supposed to be loud.
- It's embarrassing.
- Time to dance!
That's awesome!
Let me see your hands!
That's amazing!
Subtitles by: Mark Zucker