Hey, come out!
Come out!
Come out, little mice!
In the autumn of 1274,
Kublai Khan attempted an invasion of Japan
when a massive typhoon struck down
his Mongolian fleet.
Seven years later, Khan returned.
On August 15, 1281,
as the fleet readied itself in Hakata Bay,
small bands of samurai took to sea,
a suicide mission
with one goal in mind...
Kill as many as possible.
At the same time,
another typhoon moved in,
crushing Khan's second attempt.
It was a blessing...
another gift from the gods.
The storms were given a name...
"Kamikaze."
Part One: The Calm.
Wait!
BEWARE THE SAMURAI PIRATES
I don't want to be up here.
I want to be on the ground with you.
If you can take the high ground,
then I can make sure you're protected.
Remember what Father says...
- "High ground is the best ground."
- High ground is the best ground.
Plus, it's a great spot for a throne,
my Lord Kitaro.
Very true. From this spot,
I can watch for the wretched scum
who continue to ravage our lands.
Good thinking, General Yoshi.
Of course, my Lord.
General Yoshi?
Yes, my Lord?
What will be their punishment
when we find them?
These villains. These rats.
Their punishment?
The same as always, Lord Kitaro.
Nothing less than their heads!
Yoshi?
Kitaro?
Don't walk in the snow barefoot!
[speaking Japanese]
How playful of you.
Forever, I am with you.
Please... your hand. It is ever so cold.
There's nothing to fear.
For all time to come.
I wish for you to gaze upon me
like that... for all eternity.
I hear you.
I know you.
Please.
I've seen you.
I know your many faces.
I know your smile.
I know why you whisper.
Look upon me with your...
kindest eyes.
Chase him!
[speaking Japanese]
Thunder ripples off of the rocks.
Violent reminders of life.
Within the eye of the storm,
my ravenous soul.
Follow me.
Don't even think about it.
Just let it all go, my love.
It's not that easy.
All you have to do is dance.
You know I can't dance.
Of course you can.
Everyone can dance.
Everyone.
For years...
pain kept me alive.
The relentless current...
of loss and regret.
The infinite weight...
of rage.
Let love nourish me in death.
The immortal breath of surrender.
Part Two: The Kamikaze.
[speaking native language]
We stopped you.
Saved you from yourself.
You are no warrior.
You are not hardened earth.
And you belong to me now.
A fate shared with these other fools!
There is no escape...
but through my stomach.
Hey, kid...
Are you okay?
[speaking native language]
Give me a reason.
Look what has been provided to us.
Excellent!
Here. Eat.
This is for you.
Don't be afraid.
Eat.
If we wished to kill you,
it would already be done.
Do you mind if I clean your wounds?
Your work on yourself is exceptional.
I see that your body recovers quickly.
This is very, very good...
Thank you for this gift.
Enjoying the silence?
I see, I see...
Let us see how quiet
this jungle pig can be!
The worst is over.
Now you will be with us for eternity.
Smell the aromas, and think of your past.
Recall your fondest memories.
Imagine your future...
in a realm of warm light.
To prepare you for your position.
To prepare you for what is coming.
Open up!
Night winds whisper,
"Should this body fall,
time will not descend.
Trees will catch the falling star. Harsh
seas will rinse away the sins of man."
[speaking native language]
General!
This sounds like a mission
for the Samurai Pirates.
High ground is the best ground!
- Nothing less than their heads!
- And how many heads for my boys?
Fifty, Papa! Fifty, fifty! Fifty!
Fine.
I told my boys I would take fifty
of your heads tonight for them. Fifty!
I know what you're thinking,
that sounds impossible.
But I am confident I will be able
to keep my promise.
I cannot decide whether to start
with your head
or yours.
Of course, it doesn't matter.
I'm going to take them both either way.
[speaking Japanese]
The hard part will be
sawing through your neck
with that thing.
Those heads on your shoulders
belong to me.
That's one.
Those are my shoes.
My chosen children,
the time has come to pass down
what is mine to my son.
I am old. I am very close
to what will be...
I am close to what will be
a new journey for me,
and our way of life must be continued.
There is no one better
to continue this path
than my dear son.
[chanting in native language]
As your leader,
I consider myself one with you!
Your hunger is mine--
with only one way to quench it!
By blood!
[chanting in native language]
Get everyone to the boats.
The coward will be
running back to his island.
BEWARE THE SAMURAI PIRATES
I once collected the heads of my enemies.
Little joy was found
in their putrid remains.
Now I collect my thoughts
and nothing more.
How I long for the days of rotting skulls.
Everyone can dance.
Everyone.
Get out of the way.
You find him?
He found us.
What?
A demon.
The Demon! The Demon!
Go!
A demon.
The moon sings to the ebbing tide.
Crimson waves of flesh and bone
roll into the bay.
The sun rises on blood
where once there was sea.
I swim with the dead.
I walk.
[speaking native language]
All of my pain.
All of my rage.
All of my fear.
All of my joy.
All of my laughter
and all of my tears.
Everything that I am
and all that I never will be.
I miss my family.
To live.
To love.
To play.
To dance.
[speaking native language]
I can taste it.
Can you taste it?
Let me. Please.
Let me play with him.
Let you play?
[speaking native language]
Get out there, old man.
Show me the man...
you once were.
The man my father
used to tell stories about.
I knew that you were different!
So you're next.