This can't go on! They've gone too far.
For the honor of this kingdom,
we must seek revenge.
SATYA KENCANA ELEMENTARY
And you...
ART PERFORMANCE
My best knight.
You are to lead my army
on the battlefield.
Thank you, my king.
I will make sure all of them perish.
To war!
Vino!
- Mommy!
- Mom!
I'm so proud of you.
It's nothing, Mom.
It was only a small part.
Everything big
starts from something small.
You're right.
Better than playing a tree.
Weird. Who carries trees around?
INDONESIAN MOVIE AWARDS 2024
Good evening.
Okay, let's get started.
It's time for the category
we've all been waiting for.
Best Actor.
And the nominees are...
The nominees for Best Actor.
Pay up now!
It's only a million. Pay up!
Have mercy!
Arie Kribo in Kokoh Boss.
What are you doing?
On this dam, I want my feelings set free.
Will you dam it...
Kristo Manuel in Tanggul Menanggul.
But you wanna be with me, right?
Look at me! Look!
Vino Agustian in Sejernih Air Mata.
No, look at me.
Why would you listen to him anyway?
Vino Agustian in
Love Elegy Through Four Seasons.
And the winner is...
Vino Agustian in Sejernih Air Mata.
Vino.
Congratulations.
Lukman Sardi. My idol.
Please.
I really didn't expect this.
Right. Please give a round of applause
for my opponents here, Arie...
Then Kristo. Where are you, Kristo?
There he is.
That's enough.
Just relax, guys.
I'm sure next year you can win. Okay?
As long as I'm not there.
So annoying. I'll break his leg.
Why would you do that?
His hands?
The left one, okay?
So he can't wipe his butt.
My manager, Hasto.
Thank you so much, Hasto.
And for my favorite producer,
Mr. Amir, from Bima Sakti Pictures.
And last but not least,
to all my fans, wherever you are.
This award is for you.
I love you!
For the next category, please welcome
Dion Wiyono.
You're number 37.
If you don't mind me asking,
which number is up now?
Nineteen.
- Nineteen?
- You may sit first.
San, they're still on 19.
If you stay here too long,
your boss will be mad.
May I borrow this?
Want me to help you practice the lines?
Sure.
You play Thug 3.
- Thug 3?
- This one.
Sir, please don't.
I just started selling this morning.
Nothing is sold yet.
Shut up!
San...
Don't act pitiful!
No need to be that serious, San.
It's okay. It will make the dialog better.
Give me the money,
or I'll burn your cart!
Well?!
There are no more lines.
This is my brother.
Biological.
Don't do that, man.
- How's Winky?
- Good.
- Okay, good.
- The guest list is good.
Andi's coming.
- Andi... That Andi?
- Yes.
- Gosh, Dim. Why did you invite him?
- It's Andi. How could you not invite him?
- You know him, right?
- Yes. Just relax.
- What if it gets awkward?
- I'll handle it.
Vin, congrats.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Sure.
- Excuse us.
- Wait.
- What now?
- Don't tell me you...
- No, I didn't.
Look at me.
No, I didn't invite your brother. Happy?
Don't you dare.
That's so strange.
- Is this an omen?
- You're too superstitious!
Where are you going?
Home. What if it's ended already?
Fans will ask for photos.
Hasto already called the media.
Do the doorstop first.
Damn it...
Hello.
How are you?
Fine, thanks.
I've been waiting for you.
Wow.
Vino, how does it feel
to get two nominations at once?
It's okay.
Word is you're now the highest-paid actor,
beating Reza.
Come on.
I always have been.
They just found out.
Vino, will there be
a mega project after this?
Every movie with Vino Agustian in it
is a mega project.
Cocky, but right.
Let's take a photo.
Give us your cockiest smile.
LOST IN THE SPOTLIGHT
- Where's Manda?
- I think she's on the way.
What? Call her. Tell her to come quickly.
All good, huh?
- All good. Cheers, Vin.
- Nice.
This can't be.
Next time he can't be late. Okay?
You're crazy.
- Where to, miss?
- Shut it.
- My Libra buddy!
- Hey.
Sorry I'm late. My motorcycle was...
Forget it. Come in, quick.
Vino is waiting. Where have you been?
Vin! Andi!
Andi, my bro!
Damn, I thought you weren't coming.
Thank you.
- Thanks a lot.
- Of course.
- Congrats. Two trophies, huh?
- Three, man.
Right. Two Best Actors
and one Best Supporting Actor?
Winky, this is Andi. This is Winky.
- Hi. Winky.
- Andi.
So, Dimi, Andi, and I
have been buddies since college.
Back when we were
just shabby college kids.
Back then? I still am, Vin.
No, you're not too shabby.
Come on, drink up. Here.
- Sorry. Thank you.
- Drink up.
- What?
- I don't drink.
Shabby people can drink too.
Come on. Cheers.
- It's a party.
- Don't.
- Why?
- He'll get tipsy.
- You ride a bike, right?
- Yes.
Then don't. No.
Vin...
Vino! Come here.
Flo! I'm coming.
Damn.
- It'll be a waste. Wait.
- You're crazy.
How's your documentary, Dim?
Still working on it?
I do have plans to do it.
That's cool.
It's time for people to know that
behind the glamour of the movie industry,
the work of a crew
is anything but glamorous, right?
Yeah, well, but you know how it is.
It's not easy to get funding
for documentaries.
And my movie might upset those producers.
So now I'm just taking my time
working with Vino.
You can watch and learn for free.
What about your movie?
The investor's on board. Wish me luck.
- Amen, all the best.
- Amen.
But...
Are they okay
with your strange movie title?
Mata, Lidah, Telinga.
What's so strange about it?
It's poetic. Poetic!
I mean, it's more like a roll call
for body parts. Just saying.
About that, Dim...
I want Vino to be the lead.
Think he'll agree?
Of course I will. Are you crazy?
Are you serious?
Of course. It'd be crazy
if I weren't in my buddy's first movie.
- Too crazy.
- No kidding, right?
Damn it, now what?
Attention, please.
Guys, please gather here. All of you.
Guys, I want to propose a toast.
For my best friend. Your friend.
Best Actor at the Indonesian Movie Awards.
Vino Agustian!
- Vin.
- What is it?
- Give a speech for us.
- Damn...
Come on. Vino!
Vino! Vino! Vino!
I just want to say thank you so much
for coming here, guys.
I couldn't have made it
without all of your support.
Without all of you,
I could be much greater than this!
You guys are just slowing me down!
Vin. That's enough, come on.
- Hey, not yet, Vin!
- Hold on.
Come on. Wait a second, will you?
There's something very important
that I need to say to you guys.
Nowadays, our movie industry
is trash, you know?
Actors like me don't get paid much.
- That's true.
- Right?
Those damn producers took all the money.
- Indeed.
- Right?
Yet without me,
do you think this movie would be a hit?
Successful? No way.
No, never.
Audiences are coming to movies,
thanks to whom?
Thanks to me!
- Thanks to Vino! Cheer for him!
- Yeah!
They get to enjoy the movie.
They can cry, laugh, thanks to whom?
Thanks to whom, Flo?
Thanks to you, Vin!
Thanks to me!
- Vino, enough.
- Not yet.
Go, Vino!
- I made them successful.
- You did.
And I don't need anyone!
Have some shame.
They are the ones who need me.
Vino Agustian!
- What? What happened?
- What?
Keep the party going!
Enough. Watch your step.
- Vin, that's for Teh Cangkir, okay?
- Okay.
As for Starmie, the contract extension
should be done next week.
Nice.
Okay, we'll leave in five minutes.
What else, Dim?
That's all.
Sorry, Hasto, there's one thing.
We have an overlapping schedule.
How can that be?
You scheduled one launching event
for Indosel's new product, right?
Vino already has a commitment
at that time.
Wait a minute.
I don't think we have a job that day.
Well, yes, it is not a job.
We have Andi's movie screening.
Andy Lau?
No. Not him.
Andi, our friend.
He's making a short film.
That Andi, huh?
Look, Vin.
This kind of thing
is not good for your career.
It'd be an opportunity lost.
Dim. Tell your friend here.
The more jobs he gets,
the more bonuses you get.
Okay. Got it.
Look, Vin. From attending events
and coming to brand events,
we can approach these brands.
Maybe you can be their brand ambassador.
You're right. But I've promised him.
Suit yourself.
By the way, Vin, we're going
to Mr. Amir's office after this.
Mr. Dibyo will be there.
Remember, make a good impression.
This is a big project.
The biggest in both of our careers.
Understood?
I understand, Mr. Dibyo.
Don't worry.
We'll surely make a good one.
I'd rather not make a movie at all
than make a bad movie.
I'll be directing. I usually just produce.
If I'm actually directing myself,
it means this movie's super-duper special.
The thing is, Mr. Amir,
during my time as president,
Indonesia has had many achievements.
So I want this movie to maintain
my good image in the public eye.
Don't worry, Mr. Dibyo.
Vino here just won Best Actor.
Best Actor?
Indeed.
- Do you pray regularly?
- What?
"What"? Do you pray regularly?
Are you a Muslim?
Yes. Yes, sir.
All right. Don't skip your prayers, okay?
Of course, sir.
What about you, miss?
I'm a Christian, sir.
Oh, that's not it.
What I meant was we haven't met.
Who might you be?
That's right. Goodness, sir.
- I'm--
- Mr. Dibyo.
Let me introduce her. This is Sheila.
An actress specializing in melodramas.
After watching her movies,
people take selfies with puffy eyes.
Right, Sheil?
Their caption usually goes,
"I regret not bringing tissues!"
What do you mean?
Oh, that... How do I put it?
They couldn't wipe away their tears,
and the movie was so moving, so sad, sir.
Can't you wipe them on your shirt?
I suppose you can, sir. Yes.
Mr. Dibyo, I assure you.
Sheila will play First Lady
exceptionally well.
All right then, I'd like Vino and Sheila
to do a scene together.
- I want to see it. Can you?
- Sure.
Sure.
You can, right, Vin?
You can, right? Vino, Sheila?
You read the script. One scene, okay?
Ah! I know. I know.
The scene where you first argued.
Yes, it's when Mr. Dibyo
wanted to enter politics!
That's a good idea, Mr. Amir. Yes.
- Which scene?
- Scene 19.
- Right. Okay.
- Have you memorized it?
I have.
I understand...
You have good intentions.
You want to help a lot of people.
But please reconsider.
- Politics is not a game, dear.
- Enough.
Lastri, my dear.
Since when...
have you doubted my resolve?
What happened?
No matter how hard it gets,
I will...
never back down!
Sorry, I think that part was a bit off.
- Okay.
- I'll make it better.
It was a bit off.
No matter how hard it gets,
I will never back down.
Vin.
Vino, why don't you drink first?
I think Vino is a little dehydrated.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Sorry, let's try it again. I was...
- Yes.
- I think you need to step it up.
- Yeah, I was a bit off too.
It's okay. Be confident.
It's okay.
- Keep up with me.
- Okay. I'm sorry, everyone.
Dear...
I understand.
You have good intentions.
You want to help more people,
but please reconsider.
Sulastri, Sulastri, Sulastri.
Sulastri.
Since when have you doubted my resolve?
No matter how hard it gets,
I, Sudibyo Sumarsono,
will never take a step back!
Not even one single step back!
Right?
Right! Long live the freedom!
Sorry, Mr. Dibyo.
Vino wasn't feeling well.
Are you trying to humiliate me, Mr. Amir?
If this movie fails,
I will sue you for defamation!
Sir.
Who is that?
I think I've seen him hung before.
Hanging on the wall. His photo, I mean.
A former president, right?
It's because you partied last night.
I told you this meeting was important.
You should've been ready.
I know. I'm so sorry.
So what do we do now?
Let me take care of it.
You go and see Dr. Yos.
Get yourself checked.
I don't need to see a doctor. I'm fine.
Get checked!
This must be a hex!
Shut up.
When you won Best Actor,
you beat Arie Kribo, right?
Rumor has it he uses black magic.
- Maybe he resents you for winning.
- Here we go again. Enough.
Your magic nonsense won't fool me.
But it makes sense, right?
You got hexed, so you can't act.
That means fewer competitors for him!
You're out of your mind.
Watch what you're saying.
Listen to this.
"Arie Kribo, born April 13th..."
He is a good person, Dim.
You're right.
Aries men are less problematic.
But what's his Chinese zodiac?
Fish dumplings.
Okay, then. Here.
Where is it? Here.
- What is it?
- Read this.
- I'm curious.
- I don't want to.
Vino, I want to see how you act, come on!
I'm exhausted.
Hasto told you to see a doctor, right?
Why don't we go to a psychic?
Vino, listen. I know a good one in Depok!
So my mom lost her gold necklace.
Then the psychic said
that someone close stole it.
Turned out, it was my uncle!
Isn't that cool?
Dimi, it's always someone close
who steals stuff, okay?
If they're far, how would they take it?
By courier?
You have a point.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay, sir.
You handle it. Okay?
I'll make sure everything turns out well.
- I'm off now.
- Okay, sir.
Hi!
It's you.
- How was it?
- Have a cigarette.
No, I don't...
Congrats on getting the role!
Five scenes. Not bad.
Thank you. That's more than enough.
My brother here is still inexperienced,
but he's very talented.
So please guide him.
Sure, I will. Of course.
Right. My fee is 20%, okay?
I usually take 30.
You guys are new, so I'll take 20.
- What do you mean?
- Iksan.
My fee.
Once you get paid, send me 20%.
- Okay, I'll let you--
- Why is that necessary?
That's how things work.
I got him the role.
Share the wealth.
Yes.
But if you don't want to,
that's okay.
- Forget it, then. Thanks anyway.
- Iksan.
Okay, then.
- Excuse us.
- All right.
San, come on.
Why didn't we take his offer?
This is my first role with a lot of lines.
The character even has a name, "Yudhi."
Usually, it's just
"Resident 1," "Robber 2."
Now the name is "Yudhi."
- You are talented!
- That's cool.
We don't need it to be that way.
But this is my chance!
- Tell me, why do you want to be an actor?
- What?
- Why do you want to be an actor?
- Well...
I want to know how it feels
to be anything I want.
Someone other
than this poor and mediocre Vino.
I want to be able to play
any character in a script.
It's fun, and I love it.
It's my childhood dream.
In movies, you can be
any character you want.
But in real life,
you need to maintain one character.
Yeah, but...
We can always find another opportunity.
But if you lose your life values,
you might not get them back.
All right, come on.
I just refilled it.
You don't need to.
So how is it?
Funny.
Are you going to extend the lease?
- The thing is--
- Here we go again. "The thing is..."
I know where this is going.
I want to extend the lease.
What about my repair shop?
What about my rent?
You're two months behind.
Well, the business has been slow.
No wonder. You're too honest as a person.
Learn from my younger brother.
He is smart.
He can invent any problem
even on a perfectly fine motorcycle.
What matters is money!
No, that's dishonest and unfair.
Well, he is a jerk.
I wonder where he learned to be like that?
Give me more time.
This is the last one. One more month.
If I still can't pay,
I will leave.
If you still don't pay by then,
you'll have to leave.
I've given up on you.
Okay?
Sheesh.
Not bad.
Got any rice?
What about Mr. Amir?
He's calmed down. That's why.
Don't mess up again tomorrow.
I understand, sorry for the mess.
You're going to Dr. Yos, right?
Yes, I'm on my way.
All right, then. Bye.
What? Hello?
He hung up.
Sorry, Nad. Please continue.
Just like I said. He put his arm
around me on the first day.
I was very uncomfortable,
but I brushed it off
rather than him thinking
I'm complicated or overreacting.
The next day, he sent me this.
LET'S DO THE READING
IN MY APARTMENT TOMORROW.
OH, IS THAT SO?
SO WE CAN TAKE A BREAK WHEN WE GET TIRED
So what?
"So what?"
Hasto, this is harassment.
It's unacceptable!
Just because he's a top director,
he can do whatever he wants?
Okay, so what do you want to do now?
I've consulted
with the Women's Commission.
I'm going to post the entire story
on my Instagram tomorrow.
Okay, Nad.
Calm down.
Don't let this small thing
turn into a big deal.
It'll trouble us all, Nad.
Small thing?
Here's the thing.
Don't let it ruin your career.
Okay, if you're uncomfortable,
you can back out of this project.
We're only in the reading stage.
I'll let them know.
Now, you can take time to rest.
Calm yourself down.
Hello, Hasto. How's Nadine?
I didn't do anything to her, you know.
It's all good. Don't worry.
She's a bit dramatic sometimes.
What's happening tomorrow?
Mr. Amir.
Another reading session,
but with full makeup and costume,
so I can get in the zone.
Gosh! Vino!
What is it?
Look what Flo posted!
I made them successful.
I don't need anyone!
They are the ones who need me!
So what?
Vino Suvino!
"I don't need anyone.
They are the ones who need me."
You're arrogant!
Come on, I was just caught up
in the euphoria!
What does it have to do
with my current condition?
You're not hexed. You're cursed.
By whom?
By God, of course.
You think God curses people?
A curse, a reprimand, whatever it is,
you are cursed for being too arrogant!
Dim, please use your logic.
It must be some normal sickness.
Your problem is...
Nothing.
What do you mean?
Nothing's wrong with you.
You're perfectly fine.
Are you sure, doc?
You don't want to run a lab check?
Or maybe an EKG?
Do you feel any particular symptoms?
For no reason, he just can't seem to ac--
- Eczema!
- What?
- I can't have eczema.
- Eczema?
My skin is...
incredibly flawless.
So sometimes I wonder,
what does eczema feel like?
It must be agonizing.
But I can't have it.
I'm confused.
Listen. Just go home.
Get enough rest and drink a lot of water.
That's all from me, okay?
Okay, doc.
Uh, Vino.
Smoking.
I mean, cut back on smoking.
I'm a doctor, Vin.
Idiot. You're an idiot.
Got it. Thanks, doc.
Thanks, doc.
He told you to cut back.
Dr. Yos is very understanding.
You can lie, but why can't you act?
What?
You lied about eczema to Dr. Yos,
but you can't act.
Lying is acting too.
You don't get it.
Acting is honesty.
- I know, but what I'm saying is...
- No, listen!
Your curse is very specific!
Usually, in movies, you have to
redeem yourself to go back to normal.
Wait.
Tell me, what did I do wrong?
- I don't know--
- How can I redeem myself then?
Boss! Calm yourself down! Got it?
I am trying to help you,
but I need to think too.
Handle this by yourself. I'm done.
When a woman gets mad
and walks away, hold her back!
You're walking away? But I'm your ride.
Are you serious?
- The director really picked me?
- He did.
It's only three scenes,
but if you give your best,
it'll help you get more roles.
Thank you so much, sir.
I will definitely give my best.
Good!
Who's this?
This is my older brother. Iksan.
He's also my manager.
So I can follow this up with Iksan?
Right.
I will do whatever he says.
I'm Iksan.
I'm Vino's manager.
Vino's manager.
This is all your fault!
Why do you always blame me?
Well, it is your fault!
Why is that?
Okay, calm down.
Sometimes you're also wrong.
Hey. You're defending her now?
But it's true, right?
Fine. You need to pay me back, right now!
You're the wrong one! Stop playing victim!
Cut!
Sorry. Did that hurt?
- Are you okay?
- I am.
- Does it sting?
- Not yet.
Was that... a real slap?
- Vino told me to.
- You did?
Just to make it look more real.
I see, so you can slap him harder then.
Swing your hand to make it dramatic.
- Like this?
- Use your hip.
- You play tennis, right?
- Yes.
Just like a forehand. Right.
Come on. Yeah, like that.
Open your legs a little.
Yes, that way. Right.
Nice! One more time!
- Ready!
- Let's roll!
Slate in!
Slate 106, scene 39, shot one, take two...
THE LOVE MAFIA
Fine. You need to pay me back, right now!
You're the wrong one! Stop playing victim!
Cut!
- Are you okay?
- It hurts.
Does it? Bring some ice here!
Okay, that was a very good shot.
Nice. Very cool!
Okay, next shot,
we focus on this part. Here.
Focus on the impact!
Okay? Next shot!
Ready. Next shot.
Poor thing. Your face got smashed.
I'm fine.
Should I slap the other side
to balance it?
San, stop joking.
Look at you.
But that was cool.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Vino.
- Hi.
Sorry.
The next take
is supposed to be your last scene,
but Morgan wants us to take him first
because he has an early flight tomorrow.
I see.
So what time is mine?
Not long after. Maybe around midnight.
What time is it?
Almost 9:00 p.m.
It'll take too long.
Are you okay with that?
It's fine.
- What's wrong?
- Mr. Hasto. The thing is...
Morgan wants us
to take his scene first, and I...
I see.
Don't worry. I'll talk to Morgan.
- Okay?
- You will?
- Take Vino's first.
- Is it okay?
Sure, it's okay.
- Just follow the call sheet.
- Okay. Thank you.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome. I'm Hasto.
- I'm Vino.
- I'm Morgan's manager.
Can we talk for a moment, Vino?
- Sure.
- Okay?
Wait a bit, okay?
You did a really good job.
- Thanks.
- How long have you done this?
Acting like this?
Maybe around two years?
You've got a lot of potential,
but you need to...
Vino, my bro!
Vino, Vino, Vino.
Brother, brother, brother.
Okay. Let's check.
Makeup... perfect.
Wardrobe... perfect.
The only thing left is you.
But you're ready, right?
You are Vino, after all.
Remember, this is a movie
about our former president.
Indonesians are counting on you!
No pressure! No pressure!
No pressure, okay?
Yeah? Okay?
This movie is going to flop.
No pressure.
You can do it.
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Sure. Please enjoy.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Mr. Vino.
May I take a picture with you?
Sorry, I'm awkward.
I'm the new janitor here.
Sure, no worries.
But post it later,
after the movie is released.
- It's still a secret.
- Got it.
Only for my WhatsApp story.
- Miss, can you help?
- Yes? Sure.
Wait. I'm getting a picture.
Let's do this pose.
Like this.
It's hard.
One, two, three.
You can check it.
Nice! This is what they call couple goals!
- Thanks.
- No worries.
Mr. Vino. Let's take a selfie.
Shall we have a cultural wedding?
I think Mexican.
Are you also an actress, miss?
No, I'm his assistant.
Then I don't need your photo.
- Mr. Vino.
- Yes?
Keep up the good work.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Give me a moment.
- Okay.
Just breathe, Vin. Come on.
Going into labor?
Vino.
- Ready.
- Sheila?
- Ready? Good.
- Ready.
Rian.
Tight shot. Okay? Good.
Okay, ready?
Vino! No, no, no! Sorry.
- Face to face now?
- Yes. Better that way.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
I have sacrificed everything for you.
Everything.
I gave up everything to support
your ambition, and you lied to me?
Lastri...
I'm so sorry.
I know...
I'm wrong.
I'm so sorry.
Dear...
Gomenasai.
Please.
No, no, no, no.
Everything I've done...
is only for you!
I can't, sir.
What's with you?
What?
Gosh...
Idiot.
I can't...
I've tried, but...
This will make it to FYP.
All good.
Everything went well.
Yes. You're welcome.
Our next story comes from
a fun moment with Kristo Manuel.
I hope Hasto doesn't find out.
Celebrating the anniversary
of Kristolicious.
Thank you to my fans from Kristolicious.
KRISTO MANUEL'S FANBASE ANNIVERSARY
Thank you so much. Without you all,
I wouldn't be who I am today.
For me, fans are my number one.
Kristolicious...
Oh my God, Vino!
What now?
Gosh!
Amel!
Amel who?
Your fan!
I have many fans.
But how many of your fans
DM'ed you that they're very sick
and their last wish is to meet you?
Ring a bell?
And what was your response?
- "See you."
- Right. "See you"!
And you haven't seen her.
This is the answer, Vino.
Wait a minute! Don't jump to conclusions.
No, you have to meet her.
You're bad! You lied to a dying person.
No wonder you're cursed.
But how can you--
You keep making excuses!
Stop!
Two things.
One. I agree that you need to meet Amel.
Don't be a bad person!
Two.
Mr. Amir is waiting for you. Let's go.
- What about Amel?
- Give me time!
What if you don't have time
to see her, Vino?
Bro!
Iksan!
It's your fault, Nung.
He can't hear anything
when he's wearing those headphones.
Why are you blaming me?
It's normal for things to work perfectly
after being repaired.
You should've made the sound
leak a little.
I'll make your head leak!
Iksan! Bro!
Maybe I just shove this in your mouth.
He's right there.
You're stressing me out.
Iksan. What did you say?
Look.
VINO'S ACTING IS BAD!
Everything I've done...
is only for you!
What's with him?
I don't know.
Has he gone mad?
I don't get it.
Vino, my brother. This is bad.
Luckily, the reading was private.
If it were open
and someone filmed it and spread it,
we'd be doomed.
Sir!
Everything I've done...
See? We're done.
I have requested them to take it down.
But it has been reposted
by many gossip accounts.
...is only for you!
I'm so dead.
HASTO JUANDI
MR. SUDIBYO
Mr. Amir.
I have an idea.
- Don't worry, Hasto.
- What do you mean?
This has gone viral, Vin.
That means we pulled it off.
Pulled what off?
It's a gimmick.
The more viral it goes, the better.
What?
Are you serious?
Mr. Dibyo, it was all staged.
We designed this to go viral.
So people keep talking about it.
That's success, right?
So that's what happened. That's brilliant!
Right?
It was Mr. Amir's idea to create hype.
He always comes up with something.
Tell him to be careful.
His tricks are getting obvious.
Netizens are smart these days.
Sure. It's all good, sir.
All good for now.
Vino, my brother. What about you?
If you don't get better,
then we have a real problem.
We start shooting next month.
Don't worry, Mr. Amir. It's all good.
All good?
Vino.
Have you found a way
to get back to your normal self?
I have.
I have found a way.
- Sir?
- What?
Sorry.
It's a bit cramped here.
LEWD DIRECTOR SCANDAL REVEALED!
I think everyone needs to know
that this still happens a lot.
So to break this cycle of harassment,
I feel the need to speak up.
You told the police.
Aren't you afraid of losing your job?
For now, I'm focusing on this case.
As for my job,
I'll let my manager handle it.
Stupid!
A MOVIE BY ANDI ARYADI
Andi!
- What was that?
- Don't be cruel.
I'm not, I just don't get the ending.
- Okay. Thanks.
- That's his style.
- But I--
- Just shut it, he's here.
- Hi, guys!
- Hi!
- Thanks for coming.
- Cool.
- Insane.
- That was awesome.
- Thanks for coming. Thank you.
- Congrats.
- Crazy.
- That was good.
- Thanks.
- What do you think, Vin?
- About what?
The movie.
I like it.
Really. Especially the ending. That was...
- Magnificent, right?
- So deep.
Awesome cinematography. Memet is the DP?
- Yes. Right?
- He has such good taste.
- Memet's work?
- It is.
I knew that had to be Memet's work.
Vin, about our movie,
when can you start the reading?
Our... movie?
- Which movie--
- My movie.
- Okay, your movie...
- That we discussed at your place.
You said yes.
Oh, that movie.
Okay, what about this?
You just need to talk to Hasto.
Discuss the schedule
and everything else with him.
If he agrees,
I'll be ready to start the project.
Okay? Don't worry.
- Okay.
- Shall we go?
Thank you. Thanks again.
You keep saying "Thank you."
Your movie is great!
- Thank you. Okay.
- Congrats!
- Congrats. See you. Bye.
- Bye.
- Who is Memet?
- Shut it. You're being heartless.
What do you mean?
Hasto will set a high price.
Andi will back out.
It's you who should talk to Hasto.
- Okay, I'll talk to him.
- You will?
- You're such a nag.
- You need to listen!
Ple.
The cleaner!
Oh, I thought you wanted to bond with me.
You wanted the cleaner? Here you go.
I misunderstood.
Damn it!
What's wrong with this bike?
How could it be brought here?
Why are you always cranky?
This old bike makes me crazy!
It's ancient...
It smells like death!
Maybe we should trade it for rice?
As if!
Even the rice vendor wouldn't take it!
We should plant old bikes like this
to grow new ones.
Don't be mean.
Mr. Dono's had it since high school.
It has a lot of memories.
He should've kept this as a memory.
Not a ride, huh?
Shut up! Want me to
fill your mouth with nitrogen?
Excuse me.
Jon.
What brings you here?
Please excuse us.
This is a potential tenant.
I've told you I will extend the lease.
- Why are you doing this?
- Look at you talking.
I know.
But I can't say no to him.
Who knows? You might actually leave.
Who knows?
- Let's check out the house.
- Excuse me.
- Sorry for the mess.
- Well...
- Oh, boy.
Nice hair color. Where do you get it dyed?
Iksan.
Should I pour some oil on the pavement?
Who knows? Maybe he'll slip and fall.
Who knows, right?
You're evil, Nung.
But I have two options here.
Shit! Look at this! Look!
They really did me dirty!
Why would you watch it? Just ignore it!
So what about Amel?
When are we going to visit her?
We need to solve this quickly.
She sent her address, right?
She did. But I don't think
the place is safe.
It's practically the slums.
What are you afraid of?
You're used to being
surrounded by cougars.
That's nothing!
What if I get robbed? Or harassed?
Would you take responsibility?
- Harassed?
- Come on!
You think only women can be harassed?
Men can be harassed too.
Well, you have a point.
I know. What if we ask your brother
to take us there?
Herman!
- Sorry I'm late.
- Hello.
She wouldn't stop talking.
It's okay. Herman is quite free today.
Let's go in. Just follow Herman.
"Herman"? Why is he acting cute?
Can't he just say "I"?
He's a salesman. It's just a trick
so people remember his name.
Get out more.
This is the pool.
You can chill here. It's fun, right?
It is fun.
Right?
Now, Herman will show you
the second floor. Shall we?
Okay.
Vin, if you're afraid
to go to Amel's house,
let me ask your brother to--
No.
I know where this is going.
Vino, Iksan is the best
at handling people.
Remember when you almost
got beaten up in the parking lot?
Yeah, I remember that.
You pissed in your pants!
I said I remember.
Okay, sorry. My point is,
let's just ask for his help.
Why do you keep mentioning him?
Well, only he can help us.
Hello, Vino!
Herman is going to show you the bedroom.
That's where you'll sleep. Come!
Herman thinks this is
what you've been looking for.
You're right.
To be honest, Vino loves it too.
Of course. You said you've been saving
for a long time for a dream house.
So you need to be 100% sure
about what you're going to buy.
That's more like it. Please help me out.
Okay, then.
Herman will negotiate with the owner.
Hopefully, it ends well for us.
See you!
Okay, done! I talked to him.
What do you mean "done"? Dim!
Who did you call?
Jon, the owner is coming to pick that up.
Roger that, sir.
- Iksan.
- Yes, sir.
If you use your salary
to pay the installment,
you will receive less.
Is that okay?
It's okay, sir.
Thanks a lot, sir. I'll be leaving now.
Okay. Take care, Iksan.
Take care of the registration.
I'll get more money.
But if you're not in school,
you're helping me at the shop.
Just take it, Vin.
This way you can be an actor.
But actors don't have
to go to film school.
It's for your networking.
You work so hard to save money
to go to engineering school.
Why am I the one going to college now?
Don't think too highly of me.
I do this for Mom, not for you.
You're not that special.
What are you doing?
- There's an ant.
- An ant?
No need to do that.
- Dim.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Sorry, we have no whiskey here.
Stop it.
I...
- I need your help.
- You reek of cigarettes.
It's from... I was hanging out
with some friends.
Dimi told me everything.
I saw your viral video too.
So that video is real?
Where does this Amel girl live?
In Ka... I think it's Kalibatu.
Nunung, the girl from my shop,
grew up there. I'll ask her later.
But on one condition.
What now?
Quit smoking!
I don't care about your drinking
or getting drunk.
But please respect Mom!
Okay...
We'll go there tomorrow, with my bike.
Okay.
Who is that? Good evening!
- Good evening.
- Are you coming from Iksan's place?
Yes.
Right. I saw your video that went viral.
Don't think about it too much.
Don't stress it.
It's just "haiters."
You know, "haiters."
- Right, thank you.
- Sure.
- Good luck with the patrol.
- Roger that!
- Excuse me.
- Please.
He is a movie star, right?
Yes. Don't embarrass me!
How did I get so lucky to meet
Pasha Ungu this late at night?
- Pasha Ungu?
- Pasha Ungu.
You said "movie star."
Why are you talking about Pasha Ungu?
He's Vi... Vi...
- Vicky Prasetyo!
- Stupid!
- Vicky Burky?
- Whatever!
Reza Arap?
That doesn't even have a "V" in it!
Sorry, I don't get it.
He said to respect your Mom.
What did he mean?
- She died when I was in high school.
- Due to an illness, right?
She suffered from lung cancer.
She was exposed
to my dad's cigarette smoke.
When my dad left us,
she fell sick.
So are you going to quit for real?
We'll see.
What?
- She's been a mistress three times.
- Three times?
- Yes.
- Let's ask them.
She acts innocent.
- Amel.
- There's no way...
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- Yes?
Do you know where Amel lives?
Mrs. Entin's daughter, Amel?
Amel who's sick.
Is it done?
Oh. I'll take you there.
Leave the bike. I'll take you.
Should we take our helmets?
It's safe. Can you watch the bike?
- Sure.
- Let's go.
- Excuse us.
- Yes.
Is it far?
Pretty far, but you have me.
I'll take you there.
- Thanks.
- Is he a celebrity?
I think he is.
Wait a minute.
Can you move aside?
You're a celebrity, right?
- No.
- See? You are.
I recognize your voice.
Vino Agustian, right?
Just take off your mask. I know you.
Whoa! So handsome!
- Can we take a selfie?
- Ma'am, where's her house?
- Wait. I want a selfie.
- You can take it later.
No...
- Sorry.
- Oh my God.
My phone!
What happened, Mom?
- He slapped my phone, and it fell!
- No.
I just wanted a selfie.
- What did you do to my mom?
- Look.
And why a selfie? Are you a celebrity?
He's Vino Agustian, from the soap opera.
I've never seen him in my FYP.
You need to compensate us.
I'll pay for the repairing service.
Just show us the--
What service?
This is not a volleyball game!
- No! You have to compensate!
- Yes.
- Okay.
- No.
- Iksan.
- You already said it.
Okay, then. I'll buy you a new phone.
For real? You better keep your word.
- Let me record this.
- Gosh.
- If you lie, it'll be viral on TikTok.
- Miss...
Where's Amel's house?
Hurry. Move aside! You're not famous!
- He keeps interrupting!
- Come on.
I promise.
"I promise..."
- I...
- Where's Amel's house?
There!
Get well soon, Amel.
I'm sorry.
For not keeping my promise
to see you sooner.
I understand. Thank you.
Do you want a selfie?
I just wanted to see you.
Thank God I still have time.
I have something for you.
I hope you like it.
TO AMEL, GET WELL SOON
Wow!
Thank you for being so kind to me.
Amel.
Promise me.
Keep up your spirit.
I will, Vino.
I'm leaving now.
Thank you, Iksan.
Vino, thank you so much.
I'm the one who should thank you.
But I have to apologize.
Apologize for what?
For that.
Everyone, if you want
to take pictures with Vino,
the fee is five thousand rupiahs.
For a birthday wish video,
it's 150 thousand.
Vino, hurry up!
They're lining up for selfies!
Damn.
Are you kidding? And then?
What else could I do?
I just went along with it.
Crazy. You're like a theme park ride, huh?
It was no joke!
But how's Amel doing?
Poor girl.
They're barely holding up.
Poor thing.
VINO, LIVE AT KONGKOW BARENG TOMORROW.
THE RATING IS GOOD. (CC DIMI)
I don't like these kinds of shows.
Their gimmicks are weird.
I think you should come.
Many actors
want to be promoted on that show.
- Should I?
- Yes.
OKAY, HASTO
But are you ready to go back to work?
Of course I am.
I can't wait to get back on set.
Nice.
All good now!
So here's the thing, Iksan.
I have talked with Vino.
The point is,
we know that Vino has great talent.
But such talent
will be a waste
without a good support system.
Right?
I've been handling actor management
for almost 20 years.
So my experience and my network,
also my connection with top producers,
will definitely help him
maximize his potential.
We're the same, you and me.
We both want the best for Vino.
Right, Iksan?
Okay.
Hear me out. Just to be fair.
Do you like soccer?
In soccer, we know there is this system
called player transfer.
Right?
Let's say Vino is Cristiano Ronaldo,
and I am Manchester United,
who wants to buy him from Sporting Lisbon.
Does that mean that
Portugal League is bad for his career?
No.
But in the Premier League,
he will shine brighter.
TWO HUNDRED MILLION RUPIAHS
Iksan, let's talk about this first.
Listen first.
You knew his plan, and you didn't tell me.
It's not like that.
I wanted you to hear it from him,
so I wouldn't say it wrong.
- What's with you?
- What's with me?
Yeah, what's with you?
Why act like this
when I've got a big chance?
Who the heck is that guy?
What does he know about you?
That's not important!
He knows how the industry works.
Other actors are fighting
to be managed by him.
You're the one who keeps saying
that I have talent. Right?
This is my chance to use my talent
so I can fly as high as possible.
Iksan. Iksan.
If you care about me,
please let him take me under his wing.
His money can help you fulfill your dream.
To have your own repair shop.
This is the time.
Vino, give us some comments.
After the live show.
- Wait.
- No time.
- A question.
- Later. After the--
- Okay. Just a moment, okay?
- Yes.
The viral video about your bad acting,
where Sheila laughed at you.
Are you embarrassed?
I've said it,
it was a gimmick from the producer.
But many netizens don't buy it.
They think it's real.
They can believe whatever they want.
It's their right.
I can't control people's opinions.
You looked weird in that video.
Were you on drugs?
Thanks, everyone.
- Was there a urine drug screen?
- Thanks.
- What's your favorite drug?
- Vino, let's go.
That's insane!
They really said I was on drugs.
- Are there a lot of comments?
- Only one account said that.
I checked the replies.
The others still defend me.
Then why are you so stressed out?
This account pinned that comment.
I know. They're doing that for engagement.
Trust me, the one that left the comment
must be one of their fake accounts.
People are crazy.
You don't need to read that.
VINO, I HAVE REJECTED ANDI'S PROPOSAL.
THE BUDGET IS TOO SMALL.
See? I told you.
Vino.
- Hi, miss.
- Ten more minutes.
- Okay?
- Okay.
In the first segment,
we'll have some casual talk.
We will discuss your new movie.
We'll do a gimmick in the second segment
that I'm going to explain later.
Okay.
- All good?
- All good.
Nice! Thanks, Vino.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks.
I felt relieved, and now I'm pissed again.
It's okay. Just breathe.
Can you breathe later?
What?
I mean, just breathe normally.
Thank you, sweetie.
Welcome back to Kongkow Bareng!
Let's just hang out!
Please give the loudest applause
to our special guest...
Vino Agustian!
- I'm finally invited!
- My twin!
You're overdoing it. Relax.
- It's normal. We are twins.
- What twins?
We're the same.
- How?
- Gosh.
We both have debts.
We're triplets.
PRESIDENT DIBYO'S BIOPIC
- I am.
- You too?
- Let's be straight.
- Okay.
See you in the next episode.
Wait. Ask questions. We just started.
- Just kidding. Relax.
- Okay.
- I'm curious.
- Yes.
So you're going to star
in Mr. Dibyo's biopic?
Yes, right now,
we are still in the preparation stage,
still doing the reading and workshop.
The shooting starts next month.
Vino, do you feel the pressure?
What is the preparation?
And how much is the production budget?
- Ask him one by one?
- Okay.
- We have time.
- All right.
Whoa.
What's the... preparation?
You're being naughty.
One question at a time. Not one word.
All right.
About Mr. Dibyo,
we can say that he's a "forpres."
- "Forpres."
- What?
- Former president.
- I see, you're abbreviating.
That's not wrong, right?
- So maybe LGTTP?
- What?
- Let's get to the point!
- Okay!
It's a movie about a former president.
Yes.
- The budget must be high.
- Indeed.
The producer said it's going to be
the most expensive movie
in Indonesian movie history.
Wow.
Even above The Avengers?
Maybe not that far.
Let's compare it with local movies.
Above Jurassic Park?
Jurassic Park? You said local movies.
Have you seen a dinosaur in Depok?
- I'm dead!
- Again!
That's how you do it!
But why does it cost that much?
Because this is a period movie.
The production design
is massive and very expensive.
We need different sets
for the '60s, '70s, and '80s.
We will also do the shooting
in several cities in Indonesia.
This movie is not only
about his political career,
it's also about his love story.
I see.
And also, his hobbies.
He likes mountain climbing, right?
- Right.
- Yeah.
You know, right?
We'll shoot it in the Himalayas.
- The Himalayas?
- The Himalayas.
In West Java?
That's Majalaya. Next to Bandung.
Hang on. We'll continue after the break.
Stay with us on Kongkow Bareng!
Let's just hang out!
VIN, HASTO SAID YOU ARE NOT AVAILABLE.
I ASKED WHEN, HE HASN'T REPLIED.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
Boo!
Next is segment two.
We'll have the gimmick
to talk about the viral video.
It's simple.
The hosts will slightly roast you.
But you will get angry.
- I will get angry?
- Yes.
It's just an act. You can act, right?
Of course.
- Only an act?
- Right, just an act.
Later, the hosts will panic and apologize.
And that's it. We're done.
It will be good
for our ratings and engagement.
You can act, right?
Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
- We're doing it?
- You can do it.
You're ready.
Recently, there was a viral video
about Vino Agustian.
We'll play the clip
for those who haven't seen it.
...is only for you!
- That's Best Actor?
- What the heck was that?
- Ardit!
- What is it?
I'm so sorry, Ardit.
Who are you?
I'm Ultraman.
Please stop it.
"Please forgive me!"
That's not acting.
That's playing mini soccer.
Maybe I can do this too?
- There's a rumor.
- What?
That was a gimmick for promotion,
do you guys believe that?
No!
I think Vino Agustian's acting skills
are starting to slip.
That's how it is when people are on top.
Some get cocky, some get arrogant.
Some get lost in the spotlight.
Is the best actor like that?
He better quit, and let us do it.
Right!
VINO IS ANGRY NOW
Let us do it!
This's the Best Actor for you.
- I'd lose it if I were him.
- I know.
Why is he shaking, Gel?
Maybe it's his phone?
VINO IS ANGRY NOW
Vino, calm down. Just breathe.
You bastards!
You have crossed the line!
You jerk!
- I'm furious!
- Vino!
Can you see it? I'm so angry right now!
How could you do that to me?
Answer me!
- Vin, it's--
- Shut it!
He's definitely on drugs.
How dare you!
Damn you!
- Commercial break.
- I won't accept this! I'm angry!
- Commercial break!
- You're all making me angry!
- We'll be right back after the break--
- I'm angry! Furious!
Let's just hang out!
- Come at me, all of you!
- Vino! Vino!
Come at me! Bring it on!
Come at me!
Vino!
- Excuse me.
- Wait!
- You can't act anymore?
- Later.
Later, okay?
Just one question.
We need to leave.
So you're really on drugs?
- Where are you going?
- Vino, answer the question first!
- Vino, just one question!
- Answer it.
- Miss, give us a statement!
- Just a short one.
Oh, no...
You haven't eaten, right?
- Later.
- The noodles will get soggy.
I already made it. Don't waste food.
Why don't you just turn it off?
I can't just ignore Hasto. If...
Why are you so scared of him?
- I wonder why.
- What are you doing?
I want you to turn that phone off.
So we can focus on finding solutions.
The netizens are talking about you.
Then fuck them!
I'm sick of it.
Can't I make a mistake?
One slip, then it goes viral.
That's bullshit.
That's the price of your fame, Vin.
You chose that.
What do you mean?
That's what you want.
To fly as high as possible.
That's why you chose Hasto
as your manager.
This is your dream!
Can't you move on?
What do you mean?
This is your dream, Vin.
Accept the consequences.
That's so lame.
So you're still bitter.
Hey! This is not about me, Vin.
It's about your career!
You chose to work with a guy like Hasto!
What did he do wrong?
This is purely just business.
If it weren't for him,
I wouldn't be in this movie.
Do you know how many actors
fought for Mr. Dibyo's role?
- Is this movie that important?
- It is.
It is important to me.
So my name will always be on top.
- Hasto always says--
- Stop mentioning him.
Do you know what's inside his head?
It's just money!
Fuck you! You took his money too, right?
Don't be a hypocrite.
Where's that money now?
Hey.
If you use that money right,
your life won't be like this.
You'd do better than this.
Don't take it out on me
just because you failed in life.
It means you're bitter.
I gave the best years of my life for you.
I never asked for that.
Iksan.
Yes, Mom?
Please take care of Vino.
I will, Mom.
I promise.
Forgive me, Mom. Forgive me.
Thank you, Hasto.
You're welcome.
See you tomorrow.
- Okay. Thank you, Gan.
- See you.
Hi, Vin! I'm off!
- Vin.
- Hasto.
Have a seat. Just have a seat.
Want a drink?
Are you okay?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean...
- Why are you so...
- Don't worry about me.
Just calm yourself. Okay?
What about Mr. Amir?
And Mr. Dibyo?
What about our movie?
Don't you know?
Know what?
What do you think
about the decision, Mr. Dibyo?
Morgan is an amazing actor.
I'm thankful to Mr. Hasto
for getting Morgan to join this project.
Morgan, can you give us some comments?
I feel honored to play Mr. Dibyo.
A former president loved by the people.
And for now, I think I'm more suitable
to portray him compared to Vino.
- Hasto, it's...
- Have you discussed this with Vino?
So I've been replaced by Morgan?
Well, we have to save this project.
We still have time.
Please, give me another chance.
Vin, listen to me.
This is a huge project. You messed it up.
But I managed to sort it out.
You know that Teh Cangkir and Starmie
dropped you as their brand ambassador?
Be patient. This is purely business.
Wait...
How could you do this so easily?
So this is it?
That's all?
- What do you expect from me?
- To fight for me!
After everything I have given you,
you just gave it to Morgan? Wow.
You're a jerk! You are a damn jerk!
Wait.
Wait a sec.
"Everything you have given me"?
From you? To me?
Vino! You should be grateful!
If it weren't for me, you'd still be
bumming with your brother. Got it?
Don't act like I owe you.
I was on set from dawn to dawn. And you?
Just hanging out? Chilling with the VIPs?
You were partying!
What are you going to say?
I don't need this shitty management.
I can take care of myself.
Fuck you.
You're just the same.
You're just as stupid as your brother.
What do you mean?
Don't tell Vino.
I don't want him to cancel
his partnership with you.
No, it's... It's fair for us.
This is just business.
I consider this an investment.
Just accept it. I'm sincere.
I can't.
It feels like... I'm selling my own brother.
You don't need to pay me.
But please don't tell him
I returned this check.
Take care of him.
Please make him a successful actor.
All the best to you.
That's Vino.
Vino!
Hello?
All good?
Got a cigarette?
Sure!
Not all of them.
I can't let that happen.
Now I need to buy a new lighter.
Vin.
Vin!
Hey! Come on.
He didn't finish it.
Ouch!
- Where to?
- Beats me.
You asked me to pick you up. Where to?
Up to you.
Why did I even come here?
You're ready to perform? Okay.
Are you nervous?
Just breathe.
Just breathe slowly. Slowly.
INDONESIA INSTITUTE OF ARTS
In movies, you can be
any character you want.
But in real life, you need
to maintain one character.
We can always find another opportunity.
But if you lose your life values,
you might not get them back.
This is my older brother, Iksan.
He's also my manager.
Don't take it out on me
just because you failed in life.
It means you're bitter.
You've got exams soon, right?
Don't mess around, just focus.
I know, don't worry.
MR. YANTO'S CHICKEN SATAY
MR. YANTO'S CHICKEN SATAY GEN-2
Are you hungry or possessed?
Sheesh.
He's here.
- Andi.
- Hi, Vin.
- About your movie--
- Relax.
I'm not here for that.
Dimi said you need support.
So, I'm here as your friend.
That's okay, right?
Thank you.
- I'll order some satay.
- No.
- Let me. Satay.
- No, thanks. I've eaten.
- It's good.
- I know.
Let's see the theater hall.
Wonder what it looks like now.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
It's awful.
But it has a lot of memories.
Like the memory of the place
where you had a crush on me?
- You're so annoying.
- It's okay, just admit it.
What can I say?
Well, you were cute.
So I'm not cute now? Jerk.
But you have always had
a talent for acting, Vin.
He was a natural even as a kid.
Like Joshua!
You're right.
Dim, do you remember?
He used to daydream there,
pretending there was a podium.
Yeah, I remember that.
He pretended he was receiving
a Best Actor award,
and he gave a speech to thank everyone.
Hilarious.
- Dim, give him the trophy!
- Oh, right!
- Can we use this?
- Yes.
The winner of Best Actor is...
Vino Agustian!
- Give us a speech.
- Thank you.
The trophy is squishy.
- Sorry.
- And it's ripped.
Firstly, thank you, God.
Thank you to my mom in heaven.
Thanks to my theater friends,
you guys are the best!
You know how to flatter us, huh?
And special thanks to my brother, Iksan.
He has done so much for me.
Thanks, bro.
I love you!
- Hope you win again next year!
- Amen!
- What's with him?
- I don't know.
- What...
- I didn't bring my car?
- You didn't. I gave you a ride.
- The key! Hurry!
- Ask nicely!
- Dim, please, the key.
Okay, let's go. Let's go now.
Slow down, you dummy!
Slow down!
- I said, slow down!
- What?
- Slow down!
- You're noisy!
Just drop me off there.
Stop at that corner.
Shut it! Just jump off!
Drop me off here.
Vino, I'm getting off here!
Why am I still here?
Excuse us, please move aside.
Stop! Let us through.
- Vin, gosh, sorry. Be careful.
- Go! Sorry.
- You're so noisy.
- I'm scared. I don't wanna die.
Sorry, please let us through.
- Move, move!
- Vino!
- Stop. Move.
- Let us through. I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- This is taking too long.
Why is it so dark?
Iksan!
Iksan! It's me, Vino!
- Maybe he's not home.
- But his bike is here.
Where is he? Iksan!
Iksan!
Iksan! It's me, Vino!
- It's not locked.
- Yeah.
Iksan?
- Wait here.
- Okay.
Iksan!
Iksan?
Forgive me, Mom.
Forgive me.
Oh my God!
Iksan!
Iksan?
Iksan? Iksan!
It's me, Vino!
Iksan! Iksan?
Iksan!
Fuck!
Iksan, what are you doing?
I should be the one asking you!
I panicked. I thought you went somewhere.
I'm at my own home, in my own bathroom.
What's wrong with that?
But your house is so dark!
My electricity token ran out.
How should I know? I thought you ki--
- Get out.
- What happened?
I'm sorry, Iksan! Sorry.
- Why are you here?
- I heard loud noise!
- I thought something happened!
- He's taking a dump.
Hey! Can you talk outside?
What happened here?
What are you two doing here?
We heard a loud sound on our patrol!
We needed to check to make sure.
Iksan, are you constipated?
Do you want some papaya?
What the heck?
I want to take a dump.
Iksan, what the heck? Stop it!
I'm sorry, Iksan.
Wait.
- Seriously, I'm really sorry.
- Yeah, wait.
Gentlemen.
The two of you can continue patrolling.
Everything is under control.
- Roger that!
- We'll leave now.
I'll put the papaya here.
- You don't need to.
- No worries.
You need that for your bowel movements.
Sorry for disappointing you.
You're too much.
Don't act sad in front of me.
I cannot act anymore!
Don't remind me of that!
That makes me even sadder.
Hey... hey.
You're my brother.
Of course I will forgive you.
What about Hasto?
We had an argument.
- But is he still your manager?
- Nope.
Are you still starring in Dibyo's movie?
Nope.
Damn! That's tragic!
That's not helping.
I'm not helping you, I'm mocking you.
I know. I deserve it.
I really want to hug you.
But I feel disgusted.
Wear some clothes, will you?
You sprayed water on me! Come on.
Sorry about that.
Please be my manager again.
So you can ditch me again
when you find a new one?
No, it's not like that.
I'm serious. I've had enough.
I just want things to be
the way they were.
Whether good or bad...
we do it together.
Yeah, yeah.
I want you to manage me.
This time, I promise that
I will quit smoking.
So the other day...
you lied to me?
- Too hard?
- Damn.
Quite hard.
Does it sting?
- A lot.
- Sorry.
Okay.
So what do you say?
I can't be your manager.
There's someone more capable.
Who?
Me?
Why me?
Why not?
I'm not a people person,
and I'm bad at small talk.
Facing interviews. No, I can't.
Dim, you want to make a change.
I know, but I want to do it
by making documentaries.
Then don't bury your dreams.
By managing Vino, you'll have
way more networking opportunities.
Easier to get investors.
I know, but...
Come on, bro.
If Iksan trusts you, I will trust you!
- Nice.
- I didn't say yes.
You didn't say no.
- Thanks...
- What are you...
I just wanna say I won't let you down.
Disgusting.
But you like it, right?
- I'm Andi.
- Wear some clothes! Let me go!
What happened?
Fuck you!
Let me twist to the left!
I twisted right earlier!
- To balance it out.
- I'll slap you!
- Thanks for the electricity token.
- No worries.
Vin, since you're good with social media,
find me a house to rent
that's smaller than this.
What? I thought you liked this place.
I do, but I can't afford the rent now.
But I'm not asking you to pay my rent.
You're so full of pride.
Nobody's paying your rent anyway.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Replace my bathroom door.
I will!
INDONESIAN MOVIE AWARDS 2025
Give applause to our host.
HOSTED BY TISSA VIANI
Tissa Viani.
And now, I will be announcing
the nominees for Best Actor.
The nominees are...
The nominees for Best Actor.
BEST ACTOR NOMINEES
Morgan Woo in Dibyo.
Kiki Mahendra in Senandung.
Vino Agustian in Mata, Lidah, Telinga.
Copy that, sir. I'll lead the squad.
We leave before sunrise.
Boris Bohir in Ngeri-Ngeri Sergap.
Finally...
Wow, tough competition.
Let's get right to it.
The winner for Best Actor
for Indonesian Movie Awards 2025 is...
Morgan Woo in Dibyo!
Congrats!
I finally got this trophy!
Vino, how does it feel to lose this time?
Embarrassed?
Honestly, I don't mind.
I'm just having fun.
Maybe you want to play
different characters?
In movies, I can be any character I want.
But in real life,
I need to maintain one character.
Right, Iksan?
Iksan, is it true that for Vino,
you refused a check
worth hundreds of millions from Hasto?
Me? Refusing a check
worth hundreds of millions? For him?
That would mean I really love him.
But unfortunately,
I don't love him that much.
Nothing special.
Right, Vino's new manager.
It's Dimi.
- Hello.
- Hello, Dimi.
You can reach out to her
if he has any scandals.
Don't joke like that!
Wait, reach out to me if it's about work,
and call the police
if he has any scandals.
The police, Vin.
Speak of the devil!
What...
I am stoked with this achievement.
All thanks to my manager, Hasto,
who has trusted me
since the start of my career until...
Mr. Hasto?
Yes?
Hasto Juandi, Nadine's manager?
- Yes. Is there a problem?
- Please come with us.
We need your statement as a witness.
- Okay.
- Hasto.
Morgan, it's okay. Don't worry.
- Sir.
- What's this about, sir?
- Sir, wait.
- What case, sir?
Hasto, is it drug-related?
- I know this uphill road.
- Don't say anything.
Just be patient.
- Where are we going?
- Hush. This way.
Is it still far?
On the count of three, take it off.
One, two, three!
Take it off.
Ta-da!
Surprise!
Relax your face.
Gosh. Look at you.
What's the surprise?
You didn't expect
to end up at your own shop, right?
You must be surprised.
- So the surprise is successful!
- True!
Ple?
Nung?
Just wait. Calm down. Look over there.
Jon...
Here's the thing.
You don't need to say anything.
This is my friend, Yosep.
This is the guy you told me about?
Finally, we'll seal the deal.
Of course.
Yosep handles everything
related to notary work around this area.
- Notary work?
- Why are you so surprised?
You think people like me
can't be a notary?
Are you a racist?
I didn't mean it like that.
I didn't think that you were a notary.
I thought you were a bouncer.
Notary is my profession.
Being a bouncer? That's my passion, bro.
Vino, so what now?
- Did you bring the documents?
- Don't worry.
I have everything ready.
The agreement.
- Agreement for?
- Sale and Purchase.
You think I only know how to take things?
I also know about sales.
Are you being racist again?
Iksan.
Now, this shop,
and this house, are yours.
I thought you liked this place.
I do, but I can't afford the rent now.
But I'm not asking you to pay my rent.
You're so full of pride.
Nobody's paying your rent anyway.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Replace my bathroom door.
I will!
Who are you calling?
- Hello, Herman.
- Hi, Vino.
Herman was about to call you.
Herman has negotiated with the owner,
and they agreed to lower the price.
Yeah. Well, about that house...
I think...
I didn't pay your rent, did I?
But you didn't have to buy it.
You didn't have to.
I know I didn't have to.
I just wanted to.
After everything you did for me,
please accept it, okay?
You're too much.
- He's crying.
- Crying.
- Are you crying?
- He's crying.
- Why are you crying?
Look at my big brother, the crybaby!
You're too much.
Iksan! Hey!
Where are you going? Come here.
Iksan, stop crying.
No! Don't smooch me!
Should we join them?
We shouldn't. We're just outsiders.
But this is a very beautiful moment.
Come on.
Okay, come on.
Jon.
What are you doing?
See? I told you. We shouldn't have.
I know. But what about the agreement?
Let's come back later. It's embarrassing.
What are they celebrating?
It must be the New Year!
- Is that so?
- Of course!
Have you got a trumpet?
I haven't. Let's buy some trumpets.
- Get a singer too!
- You're right!
But Independence Day was not long ago.
So now we celebrate New Year in September!
Right! We can celebrate sooner! Come on!
Subtitle translation by:
Radytha P Kamarullah