Fm Movie
INSPIRED BY A TRUE STORY
PODCAST "BELENGGU JIN KAFIR"
- If you'll excuse me.
- Take care.
Maryam.
My name is Maryam.
I'm going to tell a story
I've never shared with anyone.
I've been living alongside
a king of the jinns
who claims to love me.
Based on what I know,
he's from the highest rank of jinn.
I can't say his name,
because I know
he's behind me right now.
- Isn't that Maryam?
- Yeah.
She's always by herself.
I heard she hangs out with demons.
What a weirdo.
Why won't the other kids play with me?
They say I'm weird, that I talk to myself.
They say you're evil,
even though you're kind.
You always give me money for popsicles.
Let's play.
- Weirdo!
- What a freak!
She's friends with demons!
She's gone?
He's not a demon! He's kind!
Prophet Muhammad spread Islam
with his close companions,
and Abu Bakr As-Siddiq was among them.
His full name was Abdullah ibn Abu Quhafa.
I WILL ALWAYS PROTECT YOU
"As-Siddiq" meaning "the truthful"
was a title given to him by the Prophet.
Maryam.
Why don't you explain the history
of Adam and Eve?
Ifrit jinn have been around
since the days of Prophet Sulaiman...
since the days of Prophet Sulaiman.
One that helped move the Queen
of Sheba's throne to Prophet Sulaiman,
which resulted in her embracing Islam.
This jinn is notoriously
powerful and ruthless.
Maryam!
How did you even come up with that?
Are you possessed or something?
Maryam.
You sure are friends with demons!
Silence, everyone!
- You're one of them!
- Demon!
He's my friend, not a demon!
You're the evil ones!
No!
Ifrit jinn have been around
since the days of Prophet Sulaiman.
One that helped move the Queen of Sheba's
throne to Prophet Sulaiman,
Help!
Oh, my God! I seek forgiveness from God!
Stop!
No!
- Forgive me! Forgive me!
- Help!
Help!
Forgive me!
Cruel! You're cruel!
You're cruel!
You went too far!
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan.
In God's name, the Most Gracious,
the Most Merciful.
God, protect me
from the Shaitan's whispers,
and I seek protection
so they don't get near me.
In God's name, the Most Gracious,
the Most Merciful.
Allah, there is no god except Him.
He is always alive and never sleeps.
Everything in the skies and the earth
belongs to Him.
No one can speak to Him on behalf
of anyone else, unless He allows it.
He knows what happened
and what will happen.
No one can know anything about Him
unless He wants them to.
His throne is bigger
than the skies and the earth.
He doesn't get tired of guarding them,
He is the Most High, the Greatest.
In God's name, the Most Gracious,
the Most Merciful.
Say He is Allah, the One.
Allah, the Eternal Refuge.
He does not give birth, nor was He born.
And there is nothing equal to Him.
Pitiful mortals!
The child belongs to me!
Who are you?
What is your name?
I've been by her side
since the day she was born.
Moving as the Earth spins,
like wind through the air,
like water to the waves.
Which tribe do you belong to?
Ifrit.
By invoking the name of Allah,
no harm shall come
from anything in the heavens or the earth.
Truly, He is the All-Hearing, All-Knowing.
By invoking the name of Allah,
no harm shall come
from anything in the heavens or the earth...
By invoking the name of Allah,
no harm shall come
from anything in the heavens or the earth.
Truly, He is the All-Hearing, All-Knowing.
By invoking the name of Allah,
no harm shall come
from anything in the heavens or the earth.
Truly, He is the All-Hearing, All-Knowing.
By invoking the name of Allah,
no harm shall come
from anything in the heavens or the earth...
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan.
In God's name, the Most Gracious,
the Most Merciful.
Thank God.
To put it simply,
jinn can take on any shape
and enter humans
through all kinds of ways.
It could be through haram food
dirty money,
or unclean places.
It could be anything.
Only Allah knows for sure.
What should we do, Kyai?
Is Maryam going to need constant ruqyah?
For how long?
The jinn attached to Maryam
is the king of all jinns.
An Ifrit.
According to Wahb ibn Munabbih
and Abu Salih,
Ifrit is as massive as a mountain.
The Ifrit is an ancient jinn
believed to have existed
even before Prophet Adam.
This jinn is known to be powerful, violent
and dangerous.
They are also commonly involved
in black magic practices.
I see.
Maryam mentioned that.
I thought she was just making it up.
I'm not sure how Maryam
ended up attached to Ifrit,
but I promise that from now on,
I will help protect her.
Our position as humans
is above that of the jinn.
God willing, we can overcome this.
Maryam,
do you like
your friend?
Yeah.
But he hurt my classmates.
I don't like that.
Kyai,
my friend won't bother me anymore, right?
God willing.
If this keeps up, the other kids
won't want to be my friends.
Just make sure you don't give up.
Thank you, Kyai.
We should go.
Okay.
- Peace be upon you.
- And upon you peace.
Farhan.
Rizki.
Is she okay, Kyai?
If God wills.
How's your Al-Qiyamah memorization?
- Thank God, I've memorized it.
- Thank God.
- And you?
- Not yet, Kyai.
Come on, let's hear it.
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan.
Mom, my friend
won't bother me anymore, right?
If God wills, dear.
Maryam,
someone's outside,
the one who gave you the necklace.
The necklace looks great on you.
You look beautiful.
Shall we?
See you, Aunty!
Oh, God!
Wait here.
Come on.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Come on, Bagas. I keep telling you.
You wanna end up like me?
That's just you being reckless, Adi.
Sorry, he doesn't mean it.
No, this is on me.
I'll take you home.
Bagas!
Yes, sir?
Are you and Bagas dating?
He drives you around now, huh?
If you have a boyfriend,
is your demon buddy cool with it?
Don't want Bagas ending up like Adi,
with a hole in his head.
You'll break his heart at this rate.
I think it's too late.
He gave her a necklace.
New necklace, how nice.
Maryam is so lucky.
Getting gifts from demons and guys.
Mar, is it true
your demon friend gives you money?
We'd like some too.
Watch it. He'll haunt you too.
Where is he, then?
You're asking for trouble!
Mr. Taufiq said we're low on fish.
Come with me to the bay after maghrib.
- The bay?
- Yeah.
That's where demons get freaky!
- What demon gets freaky?
- Mar, you're filling in for Kiki.
Yeah, you should go, Mar!
You have Bagas to protect you.
You'll be fine.
This place is actually creepy.
Kiki was right.
This is where the demons get freaky.
I shouldn't have come.
Don't worry.
We've got a devil on our side.
My forehead is still scarred
from last time.
Watch your mouth and shut it!
We've got work to do.
Maryam's friend literally
is a king of the jinn, though.
Demons getting freaky don't even compare.
Ask her yourself.
Maryam, didn't you head out
with Eka and Bagas?
They left already?
Help! Mr. Taufiq!
The ones at the bay got possessed!
No!
Don't bother my friends!
Stop!
I swear, Maryam and I went to the bay!
No, Maryam's here.
She was with me, but then she vanished!
She never left. I saw her here.
What about us? We all saw her too.
- She didn't leave.
- Stop.
Enough.
- Sir, I swear--
- Go home, all of you!
Get out! All of you!
Except Maryam.
Brats.
It's not her fault.
She didn't do anything.
Kiki and Eka both clearly said
Maryam was in two places at once. How?
And the possessions stopped
the moment she arrived.
I didn't do anything.
Yeah, keep telling yourself that.
Seems like the rumors are real.
There's a demon inside you.
Is that true?
Don't come to work for the time being.
Don't do this, I need this job, sir.
Don't bother.
- Please...
- This is my responsibility.
It was my fault.
We shouldn't have gone there at maghrib.
Give me another chance.
If this happens again,
you can fire me.
Whatever.
You love to play the hero, huh?
It's obvious Maryam's the problem.
Maryam.
You're not at fault here.
I'll try to talk to Mr. Taufiq again.
But I have to admit, I saw...
Saw what?
I saw you during the incident.
Was that him?
Are you afraid of me too?
I'm not, and I never will be.
I will always protect you,
no matter what.
Let's get you home.
Where have you been?
Was there another incident?
Yes.
Some workers got possessed, except Maryam.
It's not her fault.
But Mr. Taufiq...
Sorry, Bagas.
But I'm sure you're aware
of what Maryam's been through.
Are you still okay with it?
I don't mind.
I'm serious about her.
What do you mean?
I want to take things further with Maryam.
It won't be easy.
I know that very well.
But you don't have to worry.
I've promised to always protect her.
If you'll excuse me.
- Peace be upon you.
- And upon you peace.
SOME ARE GOOD, SOME ARE NOT.
WE FOLLOW DIFFERENT PATHS.
Do you want to see Ifrit?
If seeing him once is all it takes
to keep him from bothering people...
then, yes.
If you want to see the jinn,
recite Surah Al-Jinn, verse 11,
and repeat it.
But remember, your curiosity excites them.
Be careful.
I ALWAYS PROTECT YOU
Some of us are good,
and some are not.
We follow different paths.
Some of us are good,
and some are not.
We follow different paths.
Maryam?
What's the matter?
Mom.
Maryam.
I'm tired, Mom.
I'm tired of this, Mom.
Be patient, dear.
I want to have a normal life.
Maryam, Bagas told me.
And I've discussed it with Kyai Saleh.
He considers this good news.
Are you sure about marrying me?
I'm scared you'll get hurt.
I'm serious about you, Mar.
Don't be afraid, I'm here.
Let me go get my bike.
Thank you.
See you, Mar.
Bagas!
Bagas?
Bagas! Stop!
Bagas!
All praise be to Allah,
the Most Merciful, the Most Kind.
You alone we worship,
and You alone we ask for help.
Guide us on the straight path.
The path of those You have blessed,
not the path of those who went astray.
Hey! How dare you show up here?
I just want to pray for Bagas.
No! Get out of here! Now!
It's your fault Bagas is dead!
I don't want to see you again!
- Seek forgiveness from Allah.
- Go away!
Let me go! Go away!
You still want to defy me?
I'm capable of killing humans.
A human's life and death
are in God's hands.
- This is my fault.
- Seek forgiveness from Allah.
It's all my fault!
Maryam.
Maryam!
Let's go home.
I should die.
- Don't do this!
- I'm better off dead!
No, Maryam!
- What else am I supposed to do?
- Maryam!
Maryam!
Don't blame yourself.
What can we possibly do?
Someone died!
Bagas died because of me.
Maryam,
don't ever give up.
That's exactly what he wants.
Humans are stronger than jinn.
Rizki.
I'll be praying
until dawn.
Please tell the others
not to disturb me.
Yes, Kyai.
As soon as Farhan gets here,
tell him to see me.
Okay, Kyai.
God is most great.
Peace be upon you, and the mercy of Allah.
All praise and thanks be to Allah.
Almighty God, I have lost, so help me.
Heal my broken heart.
Bring together what has fallen apart.
Truly, You are the Most Merciful
and All-Powerful.
I am defeated by my body and desires,
so I can't keep remembering You
or stay close to You.
Indeed, association with jinn
is a great injustice.
And Allah does not want any injustice
for His servants.
So the wrongdoers were destroyed,
all praise belongs to Allah,
the Lord of all the worlds.
There were men among humans
who seek protection from men among jinns.
I know who you are.
What do you want?
How dare you challenge me?
You think this is enough
to separate me from her?
Maryam,
did you pray?
you want to worship in peace, don't you?
All I want is to worship in peace
and live a normal life.
God has promised
to help His servants
who pray and persevere.
Be strong, Maryam.
Don't give up.
Where are you going, Kyai?
It's time for me to go.
This is all part of God's plan.
What am I supposed to do without you?
I am just a servant of God.
God's the one who's been helping you,
and God will keep helping you after this.
God is most great.
There is no god except Allah.
Be strong, Maryam.
KH. RAHMAT SALEH BIN KH. ABDUL FAQIH
L: 02-01-1965 W: 24-02-2015
What do you want?
You're here for me!
Why are you still bothering others?
What do you want?
Do you want me dead?
- You want me dead?
- Seek forgiveness from Allah, Maryam!
BE WITH ME
Dear...
This is my fault.
- It's my fault.
- Don't do this.
Let me go!
- Let me go!
- Stop!
Take my life instead!
No, Mom.
- Forgive me.
- No, Mom!
No.
This is all my fault, dear.
It's all because of me.
I'm sorry.
I love you, Maryam.
Maryam!
Now who can separate me from this child?
I'm the one who will face you!
You're a coward if you kill her!
You're nothing compared to your teacher,
and even he lost.
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan.
In God's name.
If Shaitan tries to provoke you,
then seek refuge in Allah.
He is the All-Hearing, All-Knowing.
I ask Allah, the Almighty, to heal you.
In the name of God.
Maryam, wake up.
Dear.
I'm Farhan.
Kyai Saleh told me about you.
We've met before,
but you probably don't remember.
We were kids then.
Kyai shouldn't have died.
It's all my fault.
Before he passed,
I didn't get a chance to see him again.
But I know
he wouldn't want you to blame yourself.
As humans,
death isn't our burden to bear.
It's part of God's will.
Hang in there, dear.
Don't give up.
I beg you.
I seek forgiveness from Allah.
Don't bother me.
Let me pray in peace.
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan.
In the name of God.
God is most great.
PEACE BE UPON YOU, FARHAN.
PROTECT MARYAM FROM THE JINN
TRYING TO CLAIM HER.
ONLY LOVE BORN FROM SINCERITY
CAN SHIELD HER. RAHMAT SALEH.
Kyai, I'm sorry.
We couldn't meet one last time.
God willing, I'll carry on your fight.
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan.
I dedicate this prayer to the noble
Prophet Muhammad, peace be upon him,
and to the soul of the late
Kyai Rahmat Saleh,
son of Kyai Abdul Faqih.
There is no god but Allah.
- There is no god but Allah.
Peace be upon you, Jinn.
Whatever you do won't stop me.
She's under my control.
And you will die for nothing.
I seek forgiveness from Allah.
Hey.
I heard she attempted suicide
at the beach the other day.
Then why is she still here?
The new ustaz saved her.
Poor girl.
But she brought it on herself.
Kiki,
aren't you worried
that she's working here again?
What if we end up like Bagas?
- Hell no!
- I don't want that either.
Why'd you say that?
I don't want us to get hurt.
Let's just drop it.
Eka!
Mar, no!
- Maryam!
- Forgive me!
You don't even deserve
- to end up like Bagas.
- Stop!
Mar!
What's coming for you is much worse.
Mar, we were just joking!
You want this too?
No!
Maryam!
Oh, my God!
Seek forgiveness from Allah, Maryam!
Stop! Wake up!
I seek protection with Allah,
the Most Glorious,
and with His perfect words
from the evil that comes down from
the sky and the evil that rises up to it.
Maryam!
Eka!
I got this tasbih
when I was studying in Egypt.
Somehow, it reminds me of a girl
who used to visit the boarding school
and play with Kyai's tasbih.
Take it.
Don't give up.
I'm sure Kyai Saleh
and your friend, Bagas,
would want you to keep going.
You're not alone.
You have Allah.
I'll write a dua for you to recite
after you pray.
MAY GOD'S MERCY BE UPON YOU
I AM THE ETERNAL FLAME
FOR THE SAKE OF GOLD, I LOVE A HUMAN, YOU
O Allah, I ask You to protect me
from the whispers of the devils.
And I ask You to keep them away from me.
O Allah, I ask You to protect me
from the whispers of the devils.
And I ask You to keep them away from me.
EVERY NIGHT, I WRITE FOR YOU
O Allah, I ask You to protect me
from the whispers of the devils.
And I ask You to keep them away from me.
I'D NEVER RUIN YOUR HAPPINESS I LOVE YOU
Why are you ignoring me, Maryam?
Soon, all the light around you
will vanish,
- and only I will remain...
- Stop!
- Stop. Enough!
- ...at the end of your life.
I love you, Maryam.
- Stop!
- Maryam!
- Maryam! I seek forgiveness from Allah!
- Enough!
I seek forgiveness from Allah!
"I will always protect you."
"Be with me."
"May God's mercy be upon you."
"I am the eternal flame."
"For the sake of gold,
I've come to love one human, you."
"Every night in sleep, I write for you."
"I'd never ruin your happiness."
"In all languages, I love you."
I couldn't believe it at first
when Kyai said it's an Ifrit jinn.
Ifrit jinn have been around
since the days of Prophet Adam.
One that helped
move the Queen of Sheba's throne
to Prophet Sulaiman.
Which resulted in her embracing Islam.
This jinn is notoriously powerful
and ruthless.
I'm scared he'll come back.
What should I do then?
Maryam.
- Hello, Ms. Ida.
- Hello.
What should I do, Kyai?
Peace be upon you, Maryam!
Mrs. Yeni!
Peace be upon you. Maryam!
I swear, I saw a guy come in here.
I think it's the ustaz.
And Mrs. Yeni isn't home.
No one is in the back.
Mind your own business!
One of His signs is that He created
spouses for you from your kind
so that you may find peace
and comfort in them.
And He placed love
and mercy between you.
Truly, in this are signs
for people who think.
- Take responsibility!
- Get rid of the demon!
Goodness!
Just get inside.
Everyone calm down!
I seek forgiveness from Allah.
How much longer
do I have to be a burden to others?
I was at Kyai's grave
when I heard his voice
reciting the Qur'an.
Maybe it's just me missing him,
but the verse was so clear.
One of His signs is that He created
spouses for you from your kind.
Spouses from your kind?
Humans are meant for humans,
and jinn for jinn, right?
If you're willing...
In God's name.
Please allow me to marry you.
Didn't I make it clear?
No one can separate me from her!
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan. In God's name.
I will not
let anyone marry her!
I will marry her.
I will make sure your death will be slow
and you will feel every moment of it.
Death is in the hands of Allah, not yours!
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan. In God's name.
We sent the Qur'an as healing
and mercy for those who believe.
But for wrongdoers,
it only makes things worse.
I'm scared, Mom.
I'm worried about Farhan.
Dear,
death is in the hands of God.
You're strong.
You've endured for so long.
You deserve to be loved.
Farhan knows the danger,
but he's still here.
If Kyai Saleh were still alive,
he would've gladly
been your marriage guardian.
If you're marrying me out of pity,
- then--
- It's not out of pity.
It's your choice. I won't force you.
Allah will always make a way,
even if it's not the one we expect.
I believe this.
By God's will,
I will love you for Allah.
Maryam.
His love isn't real,
he's only using you
to test his own strength.
No one loves you like I do,
with a sincere heart, for eternity.
I seek forgiveness from Allah.
Stop this!
Stop messing with my life!
I LOVE YOU MORE THAN ANYONE EVER WILL
I will marry him.
I will marry him!
Allah, I ask You to protect me
from the whispers of the devils.
And I ask You to keep them away from me.
Allah, I ask You to protect me
from the whispers of the devils.
And I ask You to keep them away from me.
Maryam.
I'm going to marry Farhan.
I want peace.
I just want a peaceful life.
Kyai said marriage
is the longest act of worship.
He would be proud of you.
All part of God's plan.
We're just His servants.
We'll do Hajat prayer through the night,
and after Fajr, we'll do the ijab qabul.
Maryam.
- Peace be upon you.
- And upon you peace.
Is everything ready?
- Yes.
- Thank God.
Let's do this.
Ready?
Farhan!
Pardon me.
Maryam is missing.
- Oh, my God.
- She's not in the wudhu room.
Pardon me,
but do you give your blessing
for me to marry Maryam now?
I do.
But she's not here.
By God's will, I can marry her
no matter where she is.
My vow to God reaches the heavens.
It's a vow that can't be broken.
We'll start the aked.
God, with Your permission
I make her my wife,
and by Your words
her honor is lawful to me.
If You allow us to have children,
make them a source of blessing and honor.
Don't let Shaitan take any part of it.
Praise be to God.
Mr. Muhammad Farhan
son of the late Ammarudin,
I give you in marriage,
Siti Maryam,
daughter of the late Farid Zaynun,
with the dowry of a three-gram gold ring
and 200,000 rupiahs in cash.
I accept marrying...
I seek forgiveness from God.
Mr. Muhammad Farhan
son of the late Ammarudin,
I give you in marriage,
Siti Maryam,
daughter of the late Farid Zaynun,
with the dowry of a three-gram gold ring
and 200,000 rupiahs in cash.
I accept marrying Siti Maryam,
daughter of the late Farid Zaynun
with the dowry...
In the name of God.
Mr. Muhammad Farhan,
son of the late Ammarudin,
I give you in marriage,
Siti Maryam,
daughter of the late Farid Zaynun,
with the dowry of a three-gram gold ring
and 200,000 rupiahs in cash.
I accept marrying Siti Maryam,
daughter of the late Farid Zaynun...
I seek forgiveness from God.
Goodness!
Sir!
How could you reject me?
I've always been by your side.
No human has been
as loyal to you as I have, Maryam.
Go away!
Leave me alone!
Don't you remember?
You've been here before.
Don't compare yourself
to the people in my life!
They love and accept me for who I am!
I'll always choose them over you!
I accept marrying Siti Maryam,
daughter of the late Farid Zaynun
with the dowry agreed upon.
Witnesses, is it lawful?
- Yes!
- Praise be to God.
May God bless you
and unite you both in goodness.
You can never get away from me.
Dear Allah,
You have power and I don't.
You know what I don't.
You know the unseen.
So if You see that Farhan
is good for my religion and my afterlife,
then make it happen for me.
Dear Allah,
You have power
and I don't.
You know what I don't.
You know the unseen.
So if You see that Farhan
is good for my religion and my afterlife,
then make it happen for me.
Maryam!
Thank God.
Maryam?
He follows me everywhere I go.
Watches everything I do.
And I know...
he's here.
If God wills.