Have you heard?
Down south,
there's a rumor spreading around
about a powerful dark arts warrior.
They say he wiped out an entire village
by himself.
Slaughtering everyone without mercy.
No one knows where he came from.
Or his real name.
They call him the Devil from the South,
or better known as
Panji Tengkorak.
Oh, Kuwuk, you still believe
in those stupid folk tales?
What folk tales?
I heard it from a local in the south.
A southerner who's full of crap.
Just like you!
Full of crap!
Hey, stay alert!
Let them be, Captain.
Joy is hard to come by these days.
People are too busy fighting each other.
So, what were you discussing?
It's...
Captain!
Kalawereng!
Everyone! Quickly...
Bandits!
Greetings, Lembugiri.
Thank you for bringing me
the item I needed.
Please, no!
You don't understand!
Indeed we do not understand
why you haven't used this thing
to end the war.
THE KINGDOM OF MADYANTARA
Well, Bajra? Any progress?
Greetings, Commander.
We still haven't found him.
But we ran into some bandits.
Good. This will aid our cause.
Yes, General.
People of Madyantara!
Behold, this is proof
that we have not abandoned you.
We can protect you better.
From both the bandits
as well as Aryadwipa.
For Madyantara!
My gold...
General.
We are happy to help
if you ever need us to.
We are honored to receive aid
from the Dewi Tari martial arts school.
Please come in.
Thank you.
What's the problem?
Only those assigned to patrol the forest
are allowed to come in here.
Leave before you get hurt, girl.
Get hurt?
Gantari.
Calm down, let us handle this.
Just wait here and guard the town.
Next.
Hey! Don't cut in!
Get in line!
- Take turns!
- This isn't enough. I want more!
Hey you!
I'm next!
- Move!
- I'm hungry too!
I've finally found you.
Greetings, I'm Bramantya.
I've been searching for you
for a long time.
It seems the incident on Serpent Island
had quite an effect on you.
Who are you?
How do you know about that?
I am an old friend
of your master, Nagamas.
I've been looking for you since
what happened at the fishing village.
Because you wander aimlessly,
I've had a hard time finding you.
Spare me the small talk.
What do you want from me?
I don't want the Serpent Island tragedy
to repeat itself.
Your master and I have a brother-in-arms.
His name is Lembugiri.
He sent me a vision that he was attacked
by the mountain bandit,
Kalawereng.
That's why I'm looking for you.
I know what you're capable of,
and I need your help to find him.
I don't want to lose another brother.
Hey, wait!
Panji!
Listen to me.
There's a reason why you need to--
That's how I defeated those bandits.
You see how great I am?
- Mister, please have a taste.
- Have a drink.
It's okay, I'm good.
What happened next?
Unfortunately, I fell into a ravine
and got separated from the group.
If I hadn't, they would've
arrived here safely.
Had you come sooner, we wouldn't need
the kingdom's protection.
She's right.
I can't say I'll defeat all the bandits.
But at least, I wouldn't extort you.
Just so you know,
the bandit head they displayed
isn't the mountain bandit
who's been terrorizing the town.
Are you saying Commander Wirabaya lied?
I'm not saying he lied, but...
But what, huh?
Crap! I'm done for.
You caused a scene
and still have the nerve to boast?
Hey! What's your problem?
It was just a story,
he didn't mean any harm!
Step aside, little girl!
This is between men!
You insolent brat!
Arrest them!
Come here!
Hey!
Excuse me.
Stop running away!
Let me get a few hits.
Hey, wait.
Aren't you going to help them?
I have no business with them.
If you think I'll help you
in searching for your brother,
forget it.
I'm not interested.
Like it or not,
he's still your master's brother!
I don't know him.
Come back here!
There's more to why
I'm asking you to join me.
Lembugiri has the talisman
that could lift the curse within you.
Indeed.
I know what's inside you.
You know the cure?
Yes.
It's a relic that my brother,
Lembugiri, was carrying.
The truth is, my brother fled his temple
to prevent that relic
from falling into Aryadwipa's hands.
But it's now in the hands
of the mountain bandits.
Help me retrieve it.
Once we do, you can use it
to lift your curse.
I won't force you.
The decision is in your hands.
Stop!
What are you doing, fighting in public?
You! Come with me.
What's going on?
Have you forgotten your manners?
My apologies, Commander.
This all started because of that girl...
I don't want to hear it.
We should set a good example
for the people,
not brawl in public.
Get yourselves ready.
You're joining Bajra
to search the forest for Lembugiri.
Yes, Commander.
Hey, ready to go?
Let's go.
Wait for me, Murni.
We'll be back together soon.
WANAGETIH TEMPLE
Attention, everyone!
For a long time,
we've had to loot and steal
because circumstances left us no choice.
But that time is coming to an end!
All thanks to the relic in this chest.
Now it's our turn to rise,
and those damned kings
will kneel before us!
Is it true that this relic can make me
the king of Madyantara?
Not just Madyantara,
you could become
the king of the entire country.
Only after this chest is opened.
But no matter how hard I try,
the chest won't open.
The chest requires
three special keys to open.
But worry not,
I have a feeling the other two keys
are close.
Panji.
Panji!
Murni.
Where are you, Murni?
Panji!
Panji.
I'm over here.
Panji!
Are you all right?
You went quiet all of a sudden.
Just thinking of a way
to locate Lembugiri.
There's no way we can cover
this entire forest.
What is it?
Fix your cart at once!
We're way behind the group.
Yes.
But the load is too heavy.
Just take this!
Stop. This is our chance.
You're going to ignore them?
This can lead us straight to Lembugiri.
You're letting them run rampant?
Yes.
Don't hurt us!
Someone's playing the hero!
Mom!
Hey!
This is none of your business, sweetheart.
How about you have fun with us instead?
You're asking for it.
Go!
Is that all you've got?
Come at me!
Where are you going?
No!
Who's there?
It's you!
Stop! We're all on the same side.
What do you mean?
From your moves, I can tell
that you're a student of Dewi Tari.
How did you...
My name is Bramantya,
from the Iron Fist school.
Pardon my impudence.
I didn't expect to meet
a legendary warrior such as you.
I'm Gantari, disciple of Dewi Tari.
My master often speaks of you.
Just call me uncle.
Your master must've sent you
to look for Lembugiri.
Is that right?
I was heading to where
Master Lembugiri was attacked
when I heard a call for help.
If you've got your own mission,
you shouldn't be playing the hero.
You're nothing but a heartless
dark arts warrior!
Enough. Please pardon
my companion's rudeness.
If I may ask,
you mentioned knowing the location
of Lembugiri's attack?
Yes.
My friend knows
where the attack took place.
Kuwuk!
You took them all out?
Guess my powers weren't needed.
Stop showing off, Kuwuk. Get over here.
Okay.
Uncle.
He's the only member of Lembugiri's party
who survived Kalawereng's ambush.
He promised to take me to the crime scene.
Right. I know where it is.
I rescued him from the Madyantara troops.
He owes me his life.
Let's keep that part under wraps, okay?
You're welcome to come with us
if you'd like.
After we get them to safety, of course.
If it's not too much trouble,
I'll accept your offer.
Yes, Uncle.
So they're coming with us?
Just so you know,
I threw the fight
at the tavern on purpose.
After all, the soldiers of Madyantara
wouldn't want to lose face
in front of their people, would they?
They're huge and strong,
they'd hate losing to a small fry like me.
You received a vision from Lembugiri?
Yes, I secluded myself
from the outside world for several years.
That was the only way he could reach me.
I didn't know Master Lembugiri
could send visions.
There's a lot you don't know about him.
But I don't get it.
Why did the bandits ambush
Lembugiri's group?
I'm just as confused.
Why would they be so reckless?
...why I got separated.
During the attack, I didn't run away.
I was just hiding.
Then I fell into the ravine. That's why...
Thought it was a tiger.
What are you really after?
You're keeping the relic a secret
from that girl.
What's so special about it?
No one is supposed to know
about that relic.
Because it's no ordinary relic.
Our country's been at war
with Aryadwipa for a long time.
We've fought for years to defend our land.
Yet, the conflict seems never-ending.
We began to realize
that the war would never end.
As the fighting drags on,
more lives will be wasted in vain.
Our goal is to end the war with Aryadwipa.
To do that, we're trying to find
the Adidaya relic,
the relic believed to have helped
the first king unite the entire realm.
With the relic,
we hope to unite both kingdoms.
However...
The power of that relic is too great
for any mortal to wield.
So, we decided to seal the relic
and split its keys into three parts.
After that,
we kept its existence a secret,
ensuring that no one
would ever know about it.
What's the reason for telling me all this?
Not only did you break your oath,
you'd even let me use the relic.
You're Nagamas's disciple, after all.
Despite his temper and madness,
he's always true to his promises.
I believe he wants you to carry on
his oath to protect the relic.
I am not my master.
His oaths are not mine!
But
as long as I can use that relic
to lift my curse...
I will help you.
Good job!
Help!
Stop!
You guys got quite a catch.
So you're the leader of these bastards?
The cowardly general of Madyantara,
who betrayed his country
to save his own skin!
Listen up, Bajra.
You're mistaken.
I didn't escape,
I was... enlightened.
I can explain it if you--
Who'd bother listening
to a coward like you?
Let's settle this one-on-one!
Pick it up!
I accept your challenge.
Let's do this!
What's wrong?
Don't tell me the bandit life
has made you soft.
What about now? You ready to listen?
Never!
You fool!
Don't you realize you're nothing
but a dog to them?
Listen up, my brothers.
I'm giving you two options.
Join me in overthrowing the kingdom
that has tormented you,
or...
end up like your leader here!
Allow me.
You oppose us
because you don't understand us.
Let me help you understand.
Beautiful.
How beautiful.
Please, allow me to join you.
I want to help you
make your dream a reality.
When is that key going to show up?
Be patient.
He'll be here soon.
I'm sick of waiting!
It looks like we'll have to go around...
Hey, wait for me!
Gosh.
Hey! Why are you in such a hurry?
Kuwuk's struggling to keep up.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Do you?
Then go help him.
Gosh.
Easy, Uncle.
That's weird.
I don't see any dead bodies.
I think I know why.
Lembugiri.
Those bastards!
The Earth-Splitting strike!
Uncle, wait!
Kuwuk, help me out!
Don't let him wreck this place!
You should help too! Hurry!
Just let him throw his tantrum.
He'll come to see it's all in vain.
What did you say?
You think you understand how I feel?
No, I don't understand
and I don't want to.
But I know what happens
when rage takes over.
This is bad.
- Uncle!
- Hang in there, Uncle!
Calm down, Uncle.
Hang in there.
Panji is right.
I should have stayed calm.
I'm sorry.
Show some empathy, will you?
He just lost his brother!
Woman.
Grief only clouds our focus.
We must stay alert.
We don't know why they set up this pile...
Kuwuk, hide!
Where?
Under the bodies! Hurry!
Panji! Go help her!
I'll deal with these guys.
What are you doing here?
The old man asked me to helped you.
He'll take care of the rascals over there.
For the record,
I don't need your help.
Yeah. I believe you.
Well, well, well.
Would you look at that, the bait worked.
Take it easy.
I just want to have a chat.
I know what you're capable of.
Especially you, Tengkorak.
I want you two to join me.
I don't care about your plans.
I'm here to take that relic.
This one's mine!
You guys deal with the girl!
- After her!
- Come on!
Why did you stop?
Eldest brother.
Take this!
Come!
Who's there?
Behind you.
I've been waiting for you.
Uncle.
Brother, snap out of it!
They've brainwashed you!
No, Gantari. They've revealed the truth.
We are the ones who were led astray.
Join us. I'll guide you to the right path.
No!
I would never side with the dark arts!
Very well.
You've made your choice.
Murni!
Panji.
You said you were going to train.
But all I see is you lying around.
I rested here after training,
waiting for you.
Are you sure?
Enough with the excuses.
Come on.
Hello, sir, ma'am.
Hello, Murni.
Going out for a walk?
Let's play.
Join us, Panji.
What a great catch!
We were in luck.
Thank you, Panji.
Panji! Help us out too.
I can give you a hand.
This one.
You're so strong.
I need your help too.
Come with me, Panji.
Excuse me.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I have a gift for you.
Really?
Let me guess,
you hid it in that tree again?
How'd you know?
Wait, let me get it for you.
Your headband was worn out,
so I made you a new one.
Murni.
Yes?
I've decided,
I don't want to be a warrior.
But why?
You've been training so hard
with Master Nagamas
to become the greatest warrior.
I'd rather live a simple life with you.
Panji.
I'm so glad to hear that.
Panji, look.
- Murni.
- Yes?
Tell all the villagers to evacuate.
Panji! Where are you going?
I have to inform Master Nagamas.
You go on ahead,
I'll be right behind you.
Panji.
Go now!
Warn the villagers!
Run for your lives!
Evacuate now!
Leave your belongings! Hurry!
Kill them!
Master! The Yellow Pirates
are invading our island!
We have to do something!
Let them come.
I expected their arrival.
Get out of here
and take those items with you.
What do you mean?
Are you facing them alone?
I want to help!
You fool!
This is my fight, boy!
You stay out of it!
But, Master...
If you want to help,
then do as I say!
Yes, Master.
Get off this island with those items!
Help!
Everyone, move!
Where are you going, lady?
Panji!
Where's Master?
He... told us to leave.
It's okay, Panji.
He's a mighty warrior.
If he told you to leave,
then he can handle this by himself.
Come on, people have set up boats
on the other side of the cliff.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Murni.
I can't leave him like this.
Panji?
Keep this book safe.
I promise I will come back to you.
Panji. Panji!
Go now!
What do you want?
Get out of our village!
Panji!
Murni!
What do you want?
Run! Stop it!
Murni!
- Come here!
- No!
- Don't run! Come here!
- Panji!
Murni.
Murni!
Wake up, Murni!
Murni, please! Wake up!
I'm so sorry.
Murni!
Wake up, Murni.
Hang in there, Murni.
I'm here to help.
What's this?
What should I do?
They call him the Devil from the South.
If you're back on your feet,
go back to town.
Leave Kalawereng to me.
You're underestimating me.
Don't worry, I can handle myself.
Are you out of your mind?
You could get yourself killed!
Call me whatever you want.
But I won't turn my back on you.
At least let me help you.
As a knight, I've sworn
to repay those who save me.
Suit yourself.
But that naive vow
will get you killed one day.
I know.
I accept that risk.
What's the meaning of this? Let me go!
Long time no see...
My brother.
It's a pity
that our long-awaited reunion
had to happen like this.
You...
you faked your death to lure me out?
What is this nonsense?
Lembugiri, have you forgotten our oath?
That relic is too dangerous to use.
I knew you wouldn't listen to me.
Here, let me show you.
Kalawereng! Kalawereng!
Hey, Lembu!
You want to make him
the one and only king?
Is that it?
You can't possibly
believe all this, can you?
Once a general betrayed by his own king,
he is destined to be a king
devoted to his people.
He'll be no different than any other king
once he tastes the power of the throne.
Hold it.
We still need the location of the key.
I know.
But he's not going to tell us willingly.
Let me handle this my way.
Gosh. Why is it so quiet?
Please don't kill me, don't skin me alive.
I still have a lot to live for!
Kuwuk?
Gantari! Panji!
Where's Uncle Bramantya?
Well...
Kalawereng captured him.
Kalawereng.
I swear, I didn't mean to leave him.
But you know there were so many of them.
Where did they go?
To the east.
The forbidden forest, Wanagetih.
You're really going there?
We have no choice,
we have to save him.
Go back to town.
You'll only slow us down.
Hey, wait!
Here, you dropped this.
Panji.
You promised we'd never be apart again.
Yes, Murni. I promise.
Then, why did you leave me?
It's true. I'm serious.
He's carrying a skull in his bag.
I think he really is Panji Tengkorak!
You're leaving?
I'm not sure of the difference between
dark arts and white magic anymore.
It thought it was a label for evil
and good warriors.
But in reality, it's not that simple.
My brother joined the bandits.
But you, Panji,
a dark arts warrior, saved my life.
I despise the dark arts
because a warrior used it
to slaughter my family.
He let me live
only to watch me suffer
in this dark world.
But then my master saved me.
She pulled me from that void,
and that's when I decided
to become a warrior
to help others escape that same void.
I understand the void you feel.
Your guilt, your anger.
I've felt it too.
I can help you.
But only if you let me.
I want to know the truth
behind the rumors.
I want to know why you chose
to become Panji Tengkorak.
If I tell you my story,
will you leave me alone?
What Kuwuk said is true.
I'm sorry, Murni.
This is all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
Panji.
Murni?
Where are you?
Panji.
Murni.
I'm here.
I'm over here.
I'm here, Panji.
I was such an idiot!
Why did things turn out this way?
I should've stayed with you, Murni.
If only I had listened to her,
she would still...
No!
This is not my fault.
Murni shouldn't have died.
Murni.
You weren't supposed to end up like this.
It's all their fault!
I swear,
I will avenge you.
I won't stop
until every last one of them is wiped out.
Watch closely, Murni.
You shall be the witness
to my vengeance.
It's over, Murni.
Justice has been served.
Now we can be together again.
Nothing will ever separate us.
What's wrong with me?
In the end, white and dark arts
are the same.
They're both meant to take lives.
And now, I've been cursed by it.
I was cursed to keep living,
for using my beloved to justify
the atrocities I committed.
If you really regret your actions,
why don't you try redeeming yourself?
Redeeming myself?
How?
Taking lives is all I know.
You are Panji Tengkorak.
The undefeated warrior.
You could use that power
to help those in need.
I'm sure that's what Murni
would want you to do.
No. That's enough.
I've told you my story.
Now go.
Leave me alone.
- What is this?
- Excuse us.
Whoever dares to step foot on Wanagetih
will face a terrifying death
at the hands of the gods.
I don't think we're supposed to...
They left me again?
Excuse me. We're just passing through.
What a madman!
Who would've thought
he'd hide the key inside his own body?
See? I told you
he always keeps important things on him.
The question is,
where did he hide the last key?
No matter how much you tear my body apart,
you will never find it!
Nagamas took the key with him to hell.
This must be it.
How do we get in?
You two stay here.
I'm coming with you, Panji.
You won't be on your own this time.
No need. I won't be alone.
Fire!
Fire! Wake up!
- Everyone, get up! There's a fire!
- Open up!
Stop the fire!
Intruder!
Unbelievable!
Who dares to mess with my kingdom?
Show yourself, coward!
You!
That sword...
No!
There's no way he's Nagamas' disciple!
Come and fight me!
Stop running like a coward!
Fine. You asked for it.
There's no doubt,
those are Nagamas's moves.
But why did he destroy our base?
Nagamas's moves shouldn't give
the enemy an opening.
So why did he let Kalawereng strike?
It's as if...
I won't be alone.
I'll need your help.
Quiet, Kuwuk.
Okay.
They're probably keeping Bramantya
in their tent.
Intruder!
I'll create a distraction
to lure them out,
drawing them as far away as possible
so you can sneak in and rescue Bramantya.
Lembugiri!
Impressive!
I never saw your plan coming.
But you don't understand!
You're on the wrong side!
It all started here.
The three of us
who discovered the Adidaya relic
initially swore not to use it.
But over time, our resolve began to waver.
Your master secretly
studied the dark arts.
We suspect he studied that art
to take control of the relic.
This is my business!
Why are you studying that?
We tried speaking with your master,
but it ended in an argument.
We asked him to stop
studying the dark arts,
but he refused and went his own way.
Out of fear that your master
would claim the relic,
one of us acted to prevent it.
By silencing him for life.
Don't you see?
Isn't his technique too similar to
the mysterious figure on Serpent Island?
Yes!
He's the one who sided
with the Yellow Pirates!
He's the one who ruined your life!
That's right.
Don't spare his life.
Kill him!
A life for a life!
I'll deal with him
after the relic is in my hands.
I was surprised to see a young man
fighting with Nagamas' technique.
So it was you who brought him.
However...
Your moves are predictable, Bramantya.
You always carry
something important with you.
Don't tell me, all this time...
You think I'd let a dog like you
claim that relic?
It's for the chosen ones alone!
Uncle.
Thank you.
Kalawereng has been killed!
Kalawereng is dead!
What do I do?
Bullseye!
I'm a natural.
They just keep on coming!
Leave this to me!
- Cover me.
- Got it.
Let's go! We don't have much time!
Let's go, Kuwuk!
Wait for me!
I'll offer you this one last time.
Join me in uniting the world.
Only then, we can achieve true peace.
How ironic.
Killing hundreds to achieve peace?
He's fused with the power of the relic.
It's going to be a tough fight.
You two, get out of here.
Let Bramantya and I handle this.
You want to play games?
Fine, I'll play along.
Is that all you've got?
- You!
- I told you I'd help you!
Playtime's over.
This ends now.
Panji!
My brethren!
All of you have been chosen
to witness this power.
The time has come.
With this power,
we will end all suffering.
We're under attack!
Secure the gate! Quickly!
Run for your lives!
Everyone, calm down!
Soldiers, set up the barricades!
Block them at the entrance!
Yes, sir!
Gather the citizens in one place.
Don't let anyone escape.
The people of Madyantara
stand their ground.
Yes, Commander.
Gantari.
Gantari, wake up. Gantari!
Gantari!
Lembugiri showed you what happened
on Serpent Island, didn't he?
I want you to know.
I deeply regret what happened.
I admit,
I let my emotions get the best of me
when I confronted him.
Do you understand, Bramantya?
I didn't do all this
to control the Adidaya relic!
Nothing can exist on its own.
Everything needs a counterbalance.
Even if I have to study the dark arts...
I'll do it,
if that's what it takes
to stop the relic, Bramantya!
Enough nonsense, Nagamas!
Give me the relic key now
and no one will get hurt.
No one will get hurt?
Can't you see what you've done
to this island?
Even from here,
I can smell the stench
of innocent people's blood, Bramantya!
My face!
Damn you! Kill him!
You're doomed, Bramantya!
Now, I'll take the key with me to hell!
Follow me if you want it!
I regret what I did
after everything turned to ashes.
That's why I chose to exile myself.
I'm sharing this because you are
one of my deepest regrets.
I brought you on purpose
so that after it's all over,
I can tell you everything
and let you end my life.
But right now, I have to stop Lembugiri.
Once this is over, I promise
I'll surrender my life to you.
I will kill you!
But before that,
I'll make sure you don't get killed.
Kuwuk.
- Look after Gantari.
- Okay.
How dare you come down here!
Are you asking for death?
We are not here to ask for death.
We are here to stop the war.
What's happening? Why, Master?
Let us through, Commander.
All we want is to settle the score
with the king of Madyantara.
You are welcome to join us if you wish.
No!
We won't make way for traitors like you!
Soldiers, get ready!
Yes, Commander!
All right, if you insist.
Attack!
They dared to resist us.
Everyone, show no mercy.
Stop this, Lembugiri!
You've gone too far!
What do you plan to do?
Stop me?
I have surpassed even the gods.
You cannot stop me.
Nothing in this world is immortal.
Impressive.
I never imagined mortals like you
would defy a god.
It's a shame, though.
You're nowhere near my level.
Lembugiri, you...
You don't seem to realize.
The power of the relic flows into
the body of its holder.
Whoever wields it,
will possess its power.
Now, then...
Time for you to die.
Panji!
You fool!
Why would you throw your life away
to protect him?
How is this possible?
Could it be...
Nothing can exist on its own.
Everything needs a counterbalance.
...he studied the dark arts
to counter the Adidaya relic?
To keep the relic
from falling into the wrong hands?
And...
that boy has unintentionally mastered it?
Gantari.
If you really regret your actions,
why don't you try redeeming yourself?
You are Panji Tengkorak.
The undefeated warrior.
You could use that power
to help those in need.
I'm sure that's what Murni
would want you to do.
As promised.
You may kill me.
I'm responsible for all your suffering.
If my death can bring you peace,
I'm willing to offer it.
Your death means nothing to me.
Have you heard?
There's a rumor spreading around
about a powerful dark arts warrior.
They say he wiped out
an entire village by himself.
Slaughtering everyone without mercy.
But apparently he stands for the weak.
With his dark arts, he kills the wicked
and fights injustice.
- Who is he?
- Where does he come from?
Nobody knows.
People call him the Devil from the South.
Devil from the South?
But he's better known as...
Panji Tengkorak.