Downloaded from
Fm Movie
The weather in Belitung is so nice today.
Come on. Let's start, honey!
I really love going to the beach.
But every time I go to the beach,
my skin gets damaged.
Does anyone else feel the same way?
But don't worry.
Ever since I started using DV Skincare,
I'm not afraid of going to the beach.
DV Skincare really protects my skin
from sunburn.
That's why my skin keeps glowing, right?
Now onto the next scene.
Apply the product all over your sexy body.
Do I really have to?
Of course you do.
That's what we agreed on.
Don't, Lin.
Just apply the product to your hands.
It's not like you're required to apply it
all over your body, right?
Hey, don't act like
you know everything, Ulfa.
It's all in the contract.
This is entirely Alina's responsibility.
Then where's the contract?
Let me see it!
You know what?
You should be protecting
your girlfriend's dignity.
Instead of exploiting her like this!
Enough, why are you all fighting?
I'm tired. Let's take a break.
All right, let's take a break.
Half an hour.
Lin.
Why do you have to go this far for money?
Do you really have
to expose your body like this?
Aren't you ashamed?
Being watched by all of Indonesia?
Well, it's part of the job
for the client, Fa.
But what's more important, Lin?
Obeying the client,
or obeying Allah?
Come on.
- Hurry, come with me!
- I don't want to!
- Help!
- Come on.
- Please, sir! Please!
- Come on!
Let go!
I'll pay for it.
Forgive me, Lin.
I was wrong.
Why is it you who's apologizing?
It should be Salman who feels guilty.
Your new husband.
All he does is gamble.
He wasted all of Dad's inheritance.
And left debts everywhere.
If you still want to be safe,
you have to divorce him.
Before you lose everything, including me.
Because I don't want to set foot here
if you're still with him.
Oh God, Lin…
Forgive me, Mom.
I didn't mean to hurt your feelings.
I just want you to be happy.
You're here, Alin.
You just got here, dear?
Please take care of your debts
without involving my mom.
Why is she sulking?
Teach your daughter
how to speak to elders!
She knows
which elders deserve respect.
Sorry.
First time at my house,
and things are already like this.
Now you understand, right?
Why do I work hard and accept
all those endorsements?
I thought
your life was fine, Lin.
You looked so happy.
You never looked like you were struggling.
Yeah, but there are a lot of people
like me, Fa.
We just look okay on the outside.
But
in reality,
you know how it is…
But I believe, Lin.
One day,
you'll be happy for sure.
Amen.
Mom, I'm leaving now.
Mom.
I'm leaving now.
Take care, Lin.
Okay?
My beautiful daughter.
All right.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
Sir, please hurry up!
Here, sir. Thank you.
- Hey, that's Alina.
- That's Alina.
Yes, that's Alina.
Isn't she embarrassed?
Yeah, the one who went viral, right?
From Instagram?
Yes, wearing revealing clothes.
Even wearing her university jacket.
How dare she show up on campus?
She exposed herself…
Post more. Something hotter!
Maybe she's open for bookings.
Why is everyone looking at me like that?
Haven't you seen your post
from last night?
My phone's dead. It's not charged yet.
Why are you looking down?
Look at the photos on your account.
Aren't you proud of your own posts?
I didn't post that, ma'am.
How is that possible?
Isn't it on your own Instagram account?
Yes, but my account is managed
by someone else, an admin.
Alina.
What you've done has gone too far.
You should be expelled.
But we'll still give you a chance
to make things right.
Delete your post.
If you do it again,
you will be expelled.
Thank you very much, sir.
But a sanction must still apply.
The sanction is the revocation
of your scholarship.
Sir…
Please, sir.
I really need that scholarship.
You are a famous Instagram celebrity.
Surely it's not a problem
for you to pay tuition.
Sir, please reconsider one more time.
I really need that scholarship, sir.
Mr. Barkah.
Can the decision be reviewed?
The decision is final.
It can't be changed.
And that was a direct order from the dean.
Why are you staring at me?
I want to go in.
You're blocking the way.
Alina, wait.
- Ma'am.
Sorry.
I've been waiting for a long time.
I want to ask about my thesis.
I've read your first chapter.
The revisions made it even messier.
I suggest you find
an Indonesian language tutor.
So I can't move on
to the second chapter yet?
Wait a moment.
I need to speak with Alina first.
Alina.
I'm sorry.
I was harsh and angry at you earlier.
It's because I care about you.
Stay strong, okay?
Thank you so much, ma'am.
- I'll take my leave then.
- All right.
Omar.
Are you upset with me?
No, ma'am.
It's just your assumption.
Let's go in.
Lin?
Damn you, Joe.
What's wrong with you, Lin?
Why are you suddenly so angry?
Have you gone crazy?
You're the crazy one!
What's the meaning of this post?
What's wrong with it?
Because of you,
my scholarship got revoked!
Now I'm getting bullied on campus, Joe!
Okay.
Okay, calm down first, let's…
- Let's…
- We're done.
We're done?
Lin, Alin!
Alin. Lin!
Lin! Wait!
I want to quit college.
Just because the scholarship was revoked,
you're going to quit school, Lin?
You can afford to pay, right?
Don't be silly!
Fa, you just found out yesterday
what my situation is like.
If you say something like that,
then you're just like everyone else.
All my income goes to pay
my stepdad's debts.
That scholarship didn't just ease
my burden,
it was my motivation, Fa.
Now that everyone on campus
is harassing me, what am I supposed to do?
Yeah.
I know you carry a heavy burden.
But what I meant was
dropping out is the wrong decision, Lin.
Or should I
just
pretend to be possessed?
Possessed…
for 24 hours in the middle of the field,
then go viral.
Alina.
There, you're laughing!
Come on, cheer up.
You're my inspiration, Lin.
Hey, Alina.
Alina, wait.
What are you doing here?
I don't want to see you anymore!
I want to apologize!
I want to take responsibility, Alina!
It's so easy for you to apologize, Joe,
after ruining my life!
Ruined?
- But this is important! It's about work!
- Enough.
- This…
- Go away!
Alina!
What are you doing?
Just walk away.
- Where to?
- To the altar!
Be more sensitive.
That guy was stalking me.
Okay, that's it for now. Thank you.
Lin, enough, sit down, Lin!
Whoever posted this…
You're really tacky, you know that?
You're college students.
Why are you acting like elementary kids?
Do you think you're the most righteous?
To the point
you can bully Alina like this?
What's going on here?
Nothing, sir.
All right then.
Let's start today's lecture, shall we?
Fa.
Are you okay?
You look unwell.
Why?
No, I'm fine.
But you're sweating cold and pale.
Really, I'm fine.
I just get like this
when I'm holding back my emotions.
Okay.
All right, see you
in the next session, okay?
Lin.
Look at that, Aisyah.
They say she owns
a Muslim fashion boutique.
She's good,
pretty,
rich,
and devout.
Her life seems so blessed, right?
Who's that?
The one beside her?
Oh, Omar?
I don't know.
But as far as I know,
they often hang out together.
Come on.
Enough, stop talking about others.
Let's go to the mosque.
- What for?
- To the mosque.
Let's go clubbing!
To pray, of course. What a weird question!
Just pray at home.
Lin.
Prayer calms our hearts!
Come on, let's pray!
Let's go!
I'm embarrassed, Fa.
Embarrassed about what?
Well, I don't wear a hijab.
And I've never gone to the mosque
throughout my time here.
Exactly.
We should be ashamed
if we don't go to the mosque!
But wait a second.
I think
I brought a spare hijab in my bag.
Subhanallah, what a coincidence!
How could it be so spot on?
Just when you need it,
and I happened to bring one.
You're sure, right, Lin?
That it's Allah who moved your heart?
And maybe this is a sign.
A sign that you're meant to start hijrah.
Here.
Let me help you wear the hijab, okay?
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
There we go.
See? You look beautiful like this.
Masya Allah!
But isn't it weird
if people see me like this?
People at the mosque are believers, Lin.
They won't bully you!
- Come on, let's go in.
- Let's go.
AL-HURRIYYAH MOSQUE
BATHROOM ETIQUETTE, WOMEN'S ABLUTION AREA
Alin.
I really need to go.
I need to go to the toilet first, okay?
Go and perform your ablutions first.
Okay.
Honestly, I don't accept it.
How come all she got was
a revoked scholarship?
That Alina should've been expelled!
Yeah, totally agree.
She's already ruined
the reputation of our campus.
I'm honestly not surprised.
Pretty people
always get forgiven, of course.
And what do you want done to her?
Stoned?
Whipped?
Paraded around campus?
You're going to pray, remember?
Yet here you are, gossiping.
Hurry, everyone.
Sorry.
Omar, come on!
Yeah.
Alina Saraswati.
Yes?
We're from Rafa Finance.
Sorry, but I've never had
any business with that bank.
Correct.
But your parents owe money to our company.
They disappeared.
So now we're looking for you.
Because they listed you as the guarantor.
Yes, but that's their business, right?
Shouldn't you be collecting from them?
You're their daughter.
If they can't be reached,
then you're the one responsible.
If you keep avoiding us and refuse to pay,
we'll come to your campus.
ALINA, THE CLIENT PLANS TO SUE
THEY WANT COMPENSATION
IF YOU KEEP YOUR ACCOUNT CLOSED
EVEN MILK IS MORE EXPENSIVE,
SHE'S WORTH NOTHING, SO CHEAP
SO CHEAP, SAD,
YOU'RE AN EMBARRASSMENT TO THE CAMPUS
DISGUSTING, PLEASE MIND YOUR WORDS
SHE'S WORTH NOTHING, SO CHEAP, DISGUSTING
Assalamu alaikum.
Alina.
Waalaikumsalam.
Just because of a problem like that,
you disappeared from the mosque, Lin?
I looked everywhere for you.
Fa, please…
Please don't lecture me now.
I'm so overwhelmed.
I'm about to be sued
by the client for damages.
Just now, the debt collectors came here
to collect my stepdad's debts.
Where am I supposed to get the money?
Even my savings are gone.
But problems in life never seem to end.
Then who can help?
Me?
You've helped me so much, Lin.
The one who can really help
is only yourself…
and Allah.
Lin.
Please, listen to me.
When
was the last time
you sincerely prayed to Allah?
The last time…
was when my dad was dying.
After my dad passed away,
I stopped praying altogether.
I was disappointed.
I was angry.
Why did Allah have to take
the person I loved the most?
Astaghfirullah.
Astaghfirullahaladzim, Lin.
You mustn't think like that.
You mustn't have bad thoughts about Allah.
Your dad passed away
because Allah loves him.
Death is certain.
It's only a matter of time.
Don't let it be just because
we're still young,
healthy and beautiful,
that we forget.
Anytime,
we can be called by Allah.
It could be you
or me first.
Until when will you keep
being like this, Mr. Salman?
Our friends and our peers
have all passed away.
We've been given a chance to live.
You should use that chance
as best as you can.
Live, you say?
I'd rather die like them, Han!
Than to live with this kind of reality.
My life has no meaning, Han!
All right, before we begin
today's main lesson,
there's something important
I want to convey.
There's a growing trend among youth
of posting things
about themselves on social media,
photos and images
that expose their bodies.
Allah says in Surah Al-Isra, verse 32,
"Do not approach
unlawful sexual intercourse.
Indeed, it is ever an immorality
and an evil way."
This is considered a vile act
and cursed by Allah and His Messenger!
Even the Prophet said that
a time will come when, among his people,
there will be women who are clothed
yet appear naked!
Curse them because they are indeed cursed!
I also know among you
that some still post those things.
So, know this,
I forbid
any member of this group
from doing such things.
- Because that…
- Lin.
- That's a sinful act.
- Wait, where are you going?
It must not be done.
I'm going back to where I belong.
I don't belong here, Fa.
That's just your feeling.
You're just being sensitive!
I came here because you said
I could learn religion.
That I could find a good environment
that would help me be better,
but now you see it for yourself, right?
Instead, I got mocked.
Lin…
I just want you to be a better person.
I want you,
and me, to be saved
in this life and the next!
Ulfa, okay.
Maybe this is your place.
But it's not mine.
- And don't force me to be in your place.
- Lin…
You don't have to search
for paradise just here, Fa.
Lin…
I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't mean to force you.
I just want us to be in paradise together.
You're not wrong, Fa. Don't apologize.
I'm heading home.
Lin.
What are you doing here?
I've been here the whole time.
You just didn't notice.
Affirmations…
can help relieve stress.
But if your problems keep piling up,
try dealing with them through dhikr.
Don't meddle in other people's business.
You haven't even finished your thesis.
I can help protect you from those guys.
But please don't hold my hand again.
- We're not mahram.
- Why are you always following me around?
You forgot your hijab.
I left it on purpose.
I'm not ready to wear it yet.
Not worthy yet.
You are worthy of wearing hijab.
The proof is
that you look
even more beautiful in hijab.
I'm not lying.
You're prettier than Aisyah.
I'm telling your girlfriend about this!
What a red flag.
Bringing down your own girlfriend
just to flirt with another girl!
What about this hijab?
You wear it.
Wow, you got stung by Lady Gaga!
The long-awaited one finally shows up.
You're cool, Mar.
Just a coincidence.
No, but…
You're pretty clever, Mar.
You approach women
when they're at their lowest
and try to be their shoulder to lean on.
Cool.
Just like, what's it called…
Those Korean dramas, right?
That end happily ever after. Gosh, please!
What are you even saying?
Mar, where are you going?
We're not done, Mar!
Are you following me?
I didn't know you were here too.
Excuses.
I never followed you, Alina.
I really was headed to the library.
The fact that we meet here
is a coincidence.
But did you know?
There's no such thing
as a coincidence in this world.
Everything is already written.
By Allah.
This is your hijab.
Take it.
Because it suits you
more than it suits me.
Alina, wait!
Where are you going?
Home.
There's a path behind campus
if you're still avoiding those guys.
I'm heading home too.
How about I walk you?
I just want to help you.
Nothing more.
Let's go!
This helmet belongs to Aisyah.
It'll definitely suit you.
Okay.
All good?
Are you done?
Done.
Alina.
Actually, I need a favor.
My thesis keeps getting revised.
Because my grammar is a mess.
Would you help me revise it?
Let me take a look.
Hold on.
Here.
Yeah, your grammar really is a mess.
Have you lived abroad for a while?
Will you help me?
There's a fee.
Why didn't you ask your girlfriend?
Aisyah.
She's busy.
I'm busy too.
No time.
No time or
afraid of your boyfriend?
Ex.
It seems like he hasn't moved on.
If I were him, I'd feel the same.
Same how?
It's hard to move on from a girl like you.
Wouldn't Aisyah be angry?
If she knew you're here with me?
Yeah, she'd be mad.
But she doesn't know I'm walking you home.
So, relax.
No need to worry.
Speak of the devil, Aisyah's calling.
Hold on.
Assalamu alaikum, Habibti.
Oh yeah.
Sorry, I can't walk you home.
I have to meet
my thesis advisor at a café.
Yeah, I'm just eating now with Furqon.
Furqon?
It's fine.
I'll stop by your house tonight.
Assalamu alaikum.
You look like a nerd,
but you're actually a player.
You mean me?
Of course, who else?
You're already a pro at this,
lying casually to a girl.
I didn't fully lie.
Actually, I do need a thesis advisor.
Besides,
lying a little for a good cause
isn't so bad, right?
Good cause?
Our good cause.
Hold on.
Assalamu alaikum, Lin.
Waalaikumsalam, Ulfa.
Where are you?
I'm out. I have to take care of something.
What's with your voice, Fa?
You sound so weak.
Are you sick?
No.
No. I'm okay, really.
All right. I'll call you tonight, okay?
Okay.
Take care, Lin.
Don't forget to pray, Alina.
Yeah, Fa.
- That's her!
- Straight ahead, go!
- Alina! Don't run!
- Hop on!
Quick!
- What now?
- Sir, get off and push first!
Your bike's a wreck
and you want me to do it!
- You're still using it.
- Go, chase her!
Who are they, Alina?
Gosh, go faster! They're chasing us!
At least tell me who they are
and why they're chasing you.
Omar, I'll explain later.
Just drive faster for now!
Go! Catch her!
I need to know who's after you.
Omar, please.
You're so nosy.
I'll tell you later. Just go faster!
- Who are they, Alina?
- They're debt collectors!
Face them. I'll stand by you.
No, stay out of it.
Calm down, Alina!
Don't even think about running.
You're supposed to collect it
from Mr. Salman, not me.
We already explained this
yesterday, right?
- Are you senile?
- Relax, sir.
Calm down.
Let's talk this through.
Who are you?
Well…
I'm her fiancé.
I'll take responsibility.
Alina.
Wait over there for a second.
Hey. Where are you going?
- It's fine.
- Relax, sir.
I'll be the guarantor.
My fiancée won't run away.
Then,
what do you have to offer us?
Well, here's the deal, sir.
I have a proposal.
How about…
Why are they taking your bike?
They asked for collateral.
Yeah, I just gave them my bike.
So they won't keep harassing you.
God willing, people entrusted
with something will act responsibly.
People like that can't be trusted, Omar.
Don't be judgmental!
Even a serial killer
can be guided onto the right path.
Come on!
I'll take you home.
Omar.
But what if your bike gets stolen?
If it's meant for me, it'll come back.
Omar, this is my problem.
Why are you the one giving up your bike?
A future husband must take responsibility
for his future wife.
Omar, please don't joke right now.
If I weren't serious,
I wouldn't give away my bike.
WOMEN'S BOARDING HOUSE
Omar.
I'm confused.
We don't even know each other well.
And I'm not anyone special to you.
After this, we'll get to know
each other better, Alina.
Where's your phone?
I want to save my number.
If you need me,
just call me.
You can type in my name yourself.
Maybe you want to put it as
"Future Husband"?
Right, Omar.
If you ever need help
revising your thesis,
let me know, okay?
Sure.
Thanks in advance.
Right, Alina. Sorry.
The helmet.
That's Aisyah's.
Yeah, here it is.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
WOMEN'S BOARDING HOUSE
ULFA… WHERE ARE YOU? I CAN'T REACH YOU.
CALL ME. IT'S IMPORTANT!
Where are you, Ulfa?
Why aren't you picking up?
JOE: WHERE ARE YOU, ALINA?
JOE: ANSWER ME, PLEASE!
GOOD NIGHT, OMAR. THIS IS ALINA.
WAALAIKUMSALAM, ALINA.
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT YOU
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ANYWAY, THANK YOU FOR HELPING ME
WITH YOUR BIKE
I'LL DO MY BEST TO GET IT BACK
DON'T THINK ABOUT IT TOO MUCH
ISN'T THAT MY RESPONSIBILITY
AS A FUTURE HUSBAND TO HIS FUTURE WIFE?
YOU'RE FULL OF SWEET TALK
I'M NOT, I AM SERIOUS
IF MY FUTURE WIFE DOESN'T BELIEVE ME,
IT'S FINE
DON'T THINK ABOUT IT TOO MUCH
ISN'T THAT MY RESPONSIBILITY
AS A FUTURE HUSBAND TO HIS FUTURE WIFE?
In the economic cycle,
there are two main factors.
Namely the household, representing
the consumer side, and companies
representing the producer side.
Is there any question so far?
Sorry, I'm late, ma'am.
You were making content this morning,
weren't you?
All right.
Let's continue.
Alina.
Households are
the unit of analysis reflecting
total goods and services…
- Have you seen Ulfa?
- No.
…demanded by the market
while companies are the unit of analysis…
MANAGEMENT DEPARTMENT
I want to see Ulfa.
Ulfa?
She hasn't come home for two days, miss.
She didn't even say goodbye.
I'm worried about her.
Okay, ma'am. If Ulfa comes back,
please tell her to call me.
Thank you, assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
- Hey, miss. Hold on!
- Yes?
If you see Ulfa,
tell her if she can't pay rent yet,
she doesn't need to run away,
just come home.
I don't mind. Okay?
Yes, thank you, ma'am.
Okay.
JOE: ALINA, WHERE ARE YOU?
WE NEED TO MEET
I HAVE A SOLUTION TO ALL YOUR PROBLEMS
Hey, you.
What is it?
I don't know
why you're getting close to Alina.
What you need to know is
that I'm her boyfriend.
So please,
stay away from Alina.
But what if it's Alina who approached me?
Well,
if you try anything with Alina,
you're finished.
Who are you to Alina?
Her husband?
Why are you stopping me
from getting close to Alina?
You talk too much.
Hey, what's going on?
- What's wrong, Omar?
- Nothing.
It's just some dirt.
Dirt. Never mind.
What is it?
Wait.
I'm confused.
If you love and care for Alina,
you should be protecting her.
Not ruining her life.
Here.
There's an endorsement offer
from a pretty big lingerie brand.
I don't want to take those kinds
of endorsements anymore.
Lin,
your value is in your figure!
You've got tons of fans because of that.
This one doesn't even need
vulgar photos, Lin.
Come on, Lin.
Don't let yourself be influenced
by that Ulfa.
- She's…
- I'm not being influenced by anyone.
It's really just me who doesn't want to.
Then what else can I do to help you?
What about your bike?
What do you mean?
You want to sell my bike?
I'm really strapped for cash.
How much?
Fifty million.
Actually, you could get
more than that, Lin.
Just take this job offer!
That bike you got was also
from my endorsement deal.
Hey, I'm the one who got you that job.
I even made the content for it.
So I deserve my cut.
Yeah, I know.
But that's not what we're talking about.
We're talking about what to do
if you sell your bike.
I'll pay you back when I have the money.
Yeah, but then what am I supposed to use?
Lin, wait.
I'm so sick of you, Joe.
I'll sell my bike for you, okay?
Then what will you ride?
Look, Joe.
We've been together for two years.
But I never felt like you were there
when I needed you.
Someone I just met
gave up his bike just like that
to cover my parents' debts.
I knew it.
So my gut was right all along?
You've been seeing someone else
behind my back.
It's that Omar guy, right?
Why do you always play the victim?
It's not like that, Lin!
Let go or I'll scream.
Assalamu alaikum, Dad!
Okay, Dad.
I will be home soon.
Waalaikumsalam.
Do you still have space?
It's full, miss!
All right.
Omar!
Let's go back together!
It's free. I won't charge you, let's go.
Hey.
It's going to rain. Stop overthinking it.
Hop on, come on!
Mar.
My stomach is killing me with cramps.
Can I go ahead first?
Sorry, okay? Assalamu alaikum!
- Waalaikumsalam.
- Bye, Omar!
I didn't mean to follow you, okay?
I was just looking for shelter.
Then my friend bailed on me.
That's what it's like
when your friend can't be trusted.
You've got to be ready
to get ditched anytime.
Sorry, Omar.
Your bike got taken,
so you're having such a hard time now.
No, Alina.
I didn't mean to bring up the bike.
I already told you.
If that bike is meant for me,
it will come back.
But if it doesn't come back,
then it's not meant for me.
Your bike will come back, really.
I'm trying to pay it off.
Can we not talk about that right now?
BUS STOP
This is great.
Mar.
I need to poop. I'll go to Agil's place.
Here, take my key.
- What do you mean?
- That's it. I'm off!
Bye, Omar.
- Bye, Alina.
- Bye, Alina!
See you!
This isn't a conspiracy.
My friends are just a bit weird!
And now he's given me responsibility.
Responsibility?
I mean I can't just leave his bike here,
or leave you.
Why so quiet?
I was just thinking,
what if your girlfriend sees us
riding this bike together?
Then what?
We're thinking the same thing.
I was also thinking,
what if your boyfriend sees us?
Ex.
We're not together anymore.
Then who are you with now?
With you.
Well, yeah, that's the truth.
You just asked me
who I am with now, didn't you?
Well, I'm clearly riding
this bike with you.
Thank you, Omar.
Alina, wait.
Sorry, Alina.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Omar, can I ask you something?
What?
Why did you offer your bike
as collateral for my debt?
Because I was
in the same place at the same time
when it happened.
And I believe
Allah planned it all.
It's getting late.
I'll head home.
Take care of yourself, Alina.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
WOMEN'S BOARDING HOUSE
Astaghfirullahaladzim.
Hello, Aisyah?
Why are you calling me?
Where is she now?
Okay, I'm coming now.
Aisyah, where's Ulfa?
She keeps calling out your name.
How is she doing?
Come with me.
PROF. DR. SUJUDI PAVILION
Ulfa!
What's wrong, Fa?
Fa.
It's Alina.
I'm here, okay?
Sorry, I never knew
you were going through this, Fa.
Doctor, what's wrong with Ulfa?
She'll recover, right?
Miss,
let's talk in my office.
Come on.
Alina.
Fa?
Yes.
I'm here, okay?
Don't…
leave me, okay, Lin?
Okay.
Pray for me, will you, Lin?
I'll definitely pray for you.
Everyone here is also praying for you.
You have to stay strong.
You have to get better, okay?
You…
don't forget to pray.
Okay, Lin?
Yes, God willing.
Take care
of yourself,
okay?
Okay, Fa.
I bear witness
that there is no god
but Allah…
Fa.
And I bear witness
that there is no god but Allah…
Fa?
…and Muhammad is the Messenger of Allah.
Ulfa, no!
No.
Fa!
No!
Anytime,
we can be called by Allah.
It could be you
or me first.
Ulfa, don't leave…
Ulfa!
Stay strong, Lin.
Ulfa was a very special patient to me.
And it turns out
Ulfa went to the same college
as my daughter,
Aisyah.
I didn't even know
that Ulfa was my dad's patient.
Aisyah is right.
Ulfa only told me
when she was about to meet you.
Her battle was
against terminal brain cancer.
All alone.
Because she didn't want to burden
her family and friends.
This is something from Ulfa.
Stay strong, Lin.
She will surely be placed
in the best place by Allah.
Amen!
Alina.
Let's repent together.
Because if you're not in heaven,
it won't be fun.
I'm so glad
I became best friends with you.
Let's hope we can be best friends
all the way to heaven.
Let me help you wear the hijab, okay?
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
See, now you look beautiful like this,
Masya Allah.
AISYAH: ASSALAMU ALAIKUM, ALINA
LIN, ARE YOU STILL COMING TO MY OFFICE?
Assalamu alaikum, miss. Can I help you?
Waalaikumsalam.
Yes, I was asked by Aisyah to come here.
Oh, Ms. Aisyah. Just a moment, please.
Lin?
Aisyah?
Thank you for coming here.
Come, let's go to my office.
Okay.
Have a seat, Lin.
Yeah.
Aisyah.
Is this boutique yours?
Yes. Alhamdulillah, just a small business.
You call this a small business?
It's really big, Aisyah.
Amen.
Actually, Lin,
I invited you here
because I want to talk to you about work.
My team and I are planning to expand
our marketing overseas
and I want you to join us.
What do you mean?
Yes, let's work together, Lin.
You can be the brand ambassador
of this boutique.
What do you think?
Are you serious?
Am I even a good fit?
Lin, if you weren't a good fit,
I wouldn't offer you this.
Silence
usually means agreement.
So?
Do you want me to go ahead
and draft the contract?
The thing is I still have a problem
with a skincare brand.
They want to sue me.
Because I closed my Instagram account.
But you're still holding
the collaboration contract?
Okay, in that case,
I can ask my legal counsel
to help you resolve the issue.
So, deal or not?
Thank you, Aisyah.
Can I ask you something, Syah?
About what?
Omar?
But I don't mean anything by it.
I'm a bit worried
because Omar hasn't been seen
around campus for the last few days.
Honestly, I also don't know, Lin,
where Omar went.
For now, just focus
on your job and your studies.
Okay, after this,
we'll proceed with the MOU
so you can start working here tomorrow.
In the contract, we never require Alina
to promote our products
by wearing revealing clothes.
So, we agree.
Alina just needs to make a new video
in a way she feels comfortable with
and re-upload it to her social media.
All right then.
It looks like we're all in agreement.
Next, we sincerely apologize again
for the misunderstanding.
So Alina, we can continue
our collaboration
which is skincare for Muslim women.
Later, we can collaborate
with Muslim fashion product line.
What do you think?
I fully support and agree. Thank you.
I also totally agree. Thank you so much.
Yeah.
- Thank you.
One, two, three.
Okay. One more time.
Okay, let's continue, one by one.
Now, here's our newest product.
A tartan-patterned dress that's perfect
for those of you wanting to forget an ex.
Do you happen to know where Omar is?
He hasn't been on campus
for several days either.
And he's not answering calls either.
Exactly, I'm confused too.
Where could that guy have gone?
Hurry and order now!
Dusty pink color,
this one's really premium too!
- Assalamu alaikum.
- Waalaikumsalam!
Salman.
Oh my God, Iwan.
How are you, my friend?
Alhamdulillah, I'm doing very well.
- Let me introduce, this is my wife.
- Yes.
- Assalamu alaikum, Pak Salman.
- Waalaikumsalam.
- This is my friend, Mr. Joni.
- Oh, okay.
Assalamu alaikum, Pak Salman.
Waalaikumsalam.
Thank you so much for coming here, okay?
What is it, Lin?
Mom?
Alina has transferred the money.
Alhamdulillah.
But
it's not that I don't want
to accept your gift, Lin.
But I will transfer it back to you, okay?
Really?
Why, Mom?
Ever since your stepdad
started seeing Ustad Farhan,
he has changed a lot.
He's not like before.
Now,
he runs a coffee shop business.
Alhamdulillah.
It gets a lot of customers.
- Thank you.
- Just a moment, okay?
Lin…
Forgive me, okay?
If I've caused you trouble
all this time.
Please forgive your stepdad too, okay?
Assalamu alaikum, Alin.
Waalaikumsalam.
Forgive me, Alin.
I made a lot of mistakes
and caused you trouble.
I promise, dear.
I'll take good care of your mom.
Okay, Dad.
Alhamdulillah.
Aisyah?
Yes, Lin?
You said you had
something important to say. What is it?
So, here's the thing, Lin.
I got an invitation to go to Uzbekistan,
but I can't go.
There's something
I need to take care of here.
Can you go to Uzbekistan in my place?
But why me?
It has to be you, Lin.
You're our brand ambassador.
And there will be a business presentation
over there.
You are the right person
to represent me there.
Are you ready to take my place?
Waalaikumsalam, Aisyah.
Yes, alhamdulillah, I've arrived.
Okay.
Thanks, Syah.
Waalaikumsalam.
Alina Saraswati.
Assalamu alaikum, Alina.
Waalaikumsalam.
Welcome to Uzbekistan.
Why are you here?
Now,
I'll take you to the hotel
you'll be staying at.
Let me help you.
Please, Alina.
Sorry, Alina.
Come on, Alina.
Assalamu alaikum, Zafira.
Waalaikumsalam, Mr. Omar.
Everything has been arranged.
They will take great care of you here.
Is there anything else I can help with?
There is.
What?
Can you please explain
what all this means?
Why are you suddenly here, Mar?
Please, Mar, don't confuse me anymore.
You've just
arrived here.
You'd better rest first.
Everything will become clear later.
I'll go for now.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll pick you up at 8:30 a.m.
Have a good rest.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
- Salam, Zafira.
- Assalamu alaikum.
ASSALAMU ALAIKUM, ALINA.
I'M ALREADY OUTSIDE THE HOTEL.
NO NEED TO RUSH
Omar.
Omar?
Alina.
Marry me.
Astaghfirullahaladzim.
I mean,
let's go.
You have an important meeting today.
Let's not be late.
Let's go.
Alhamdulillah.
Omar?
- Hey, Aziz!
- My friend.
Hey, my friend. Assalamu alaikum.
How are you?
Where have you been? I've been waiting,
but you never showed up.
Hey, who's this?
Friend or wife?
No, she's just my friend from Indonesia.
Introduce her. I'm willing to marry her.
Don't even think about it.
Okay. Please, take a seat.
Come on, have a seat. Assalamu alaikum.
- Assalamu alaikum.
- How are you?
Please. Make yourselves
comfortable and enjoy.
I'll be back shortly.
Who is it, Mar?
You're not talking about me, right?
His name is Aziz,
the owner of this restaurant.
He said you're lucky to be close to me.
Just joking, Alina.
Actually, I'm the lucky one
to be here with you.
Assalamu alaikum, dear guests.
In the history of our restaurant,
this is a very rare event.
Today at Tandiry,
we will hold a contest between our guests
and our staff.
My friend, Omar, will perform in front.
Everyone, let's cheer!
- Omar!
Oh, Omar!
Who can take this hat?
An empty barrel makes the loudest noise
Turns out, failed.
Who can take this hat?
- Omar!
How was that?
Everyone, our winner is Omar.
Here is the prize
for our champion, friends.
Come on, go ahead. Open the prize!
Coffee?
Thank you.
This place is called Amirsoy.
Beautiful, right?
Do you like it, Alina?
I'd rather you explain all this instead.
What is this game, Omar?
Why did you suddenly disappear,
then show up here?
Who are you really?
Don't even think
about playing with me, okay?
Alina, no one is playing with you.
I'm Omar, the one you know.
Uzbekistan is my homeland.
And Indonesia is my second home.
My dad is from Tashkent
and my mom is from Indonesia.
A while ago, my grandma got seriously ill.
She asked me to return here.
Then what about Aisyah?
Aisyah?
She's my cousin, Alina.
Not my girlfriend.
Besides, I've never been
in a relationship.
There is one woman I love.
But to marry.
Not just to date.
So, you really came here to get married?
No wonder you were so secretive.
My grandma insisted
that I get married immediately.
But she's not the woman I want.
Wait a second.
You just said
you had found the woman
you love and want to marry.
But just now you said
you don't love that woman.
I don't get it.
Because I don't know and don't understand
whether that woman loves me or not, Alina.
- Who?
- You.
I love you, Alina.
Since the first time we met.
But I won't force you.
I only hope
that you'll consider my feelings.
Is Imam Bukhari's tomb far from here?
Quite far.
Do you want to go there?
Yes, since I'm already in Uzbekistan.
Who knows if I'll ever
come back here again.
Looks like
we'll be coming back
to Uzbekistan every year from now on.
Thank you for today.
So, what do you say, Alina?
Will you accept me?
Please answer, Alina.
So I can sleep tonight.
What, is it wrong to have
trouble sleeping for once?
Good night, Omar.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
Excuse me, who are you?
I'm Hasan, Ms. Alina.
I was asked to pick you up
to go to Omar's family's home.
- Please have a seat, Ms. Alina.
- Thank you.
Assalamu alaikum.
- Waalaikumsalam.
- Assalamu alaikum.
You must be Alina.
That's right.
You're very beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm Omar's mother and this is his father.
Oh, I see.
- Hello, sir.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
- Please have a seat.
Okay.
How's Uzbekistan?
Alhamdulillah, I like it, ma'am.
Uzbekistan is really beautiful.
Mom.
Right, Alina.
This is my mother and Omar's grandmother.
I see. Assalamu alaikum.
Tell the guest she may sit.
Okay.
What is your relationship with Omar?
Grandma asked
what your relationship is with Omar.
We're just friends.
We happened to be on the same campus.
- They're friends from campus--
- Lies!
You must be trying
to get close to Omar, right?
I don't like you getting close to Omar.
Grandma says that's a lie.
You actually have
a relationship with Omar, right?
I've already arranged a match for Omar.
He's only allowed to marry her.
Alina.
Grandma says
she's already arranged a match
for Omar with someone else.
So she asks
that Alina stay away from Omar.
Give that girl some money.
Tell her to leave and stay away
from Omar forever.
Here's a small gift.
She asks that you never come
near Omar again, okay?
Sorry, but please tell her this.
I didn't come here
to pursue Omar at all.
And I don't need to be paid.
I will stay away from Omar.
Please excuse me.
I just want to wish
Omar and the woman she chose happiness.
I'm sorry, but I'll take my leave.
Excuse me. Sir, ma'am, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Alina.
Alina.
Omar.
Dad, Mom. Where's Alina?
Alina has already left, Omar.
Alina?
Alina!
Zafira, where's Alina?
Mr. Omar, I don't know.
She hasn't returned yet.
But did you know?
There's no such thing
as a coincidence in this world.
Everything is already written.
By Allah.
I love you, Alina.
Since the first time we met.
I only hope
that you'll consider my feelings.
Aisyah.
Lin, where are you now?
I appreciate what you did
to reunite Omar and me.
But honestly,
this is just too painful for me, Aisyah.
It's not you,
or Omar, but…
Yes, Lin.
I understand how you feel.
But where are you now?
I'm in Bukhara right now.
But please don't tell Omar.
I don't want to trouble him anymore.
Okay.
But please stay safe there, Lin.
Let me know if you need anything.
Okay.
Thank you, Aisyah.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
Alina,
please pick up the phone.
Assalamu alaikum, Aisyah.
You said she's in Bukhara?
I looked for her last night.
I called, but she didn't answer.
You must find her
while she's still there, Omar.
Don't let anything bad happen to Alina.
I promise I'll find her, Aisyah.
I could never forgive myself
if anything happened to her.
Omar, I'm entrusting this to you.
ALINA, PLEASE PICK UP MY CALL
When…
a man has made his choice,
he must be brave to fight for it.
Look at the sheep.
They live out in the wild, in open nature.
But they surely know
when they need to go home.
The signs of the sky stretch wide.
Ma'am?
Isn't the air in this city so refreshing?
Yes.
It's very refreshing, ma'am.
Excuse me, ma'am.
How did you know I was here?
I called Aisyah yesterday.
Alina.
I want to apologize
for what happened yesterday.
I know it must've been really painful
for a woman.
I understand your feelings.
I've been through it too.
But we, as women,
must be strong and resilient.
Ready to accept happiness
and at the same time,
ready to face pain and disappointment too.
Thank you for loving Omar.
I know
Omar really loves you too.
So what is it that's making you
avoid Omar?
I don't want to ruin his relationship
with his family, ma'am.
So, you choose to leave?
Isn't that even more painful for you?
For Omar too?
Yes.
But…
in my opinion, no pain lasts forever.
And wounds will heal with time.
I believe
Omar will find his happiness
with the woman
he's been arranged to marry, ma'am.
Everything comes back to destiny.
If Allah has destined you to be with him,
then no one can ever separate you.
The more modest a woman is,
the more beautiful she becomes.
And special.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll be going now.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam.
O Allah,
the One who opens hearts.
I humbly ask You
to open my grandma's heart.
So she may love the one I love.
Please grant my prayer, O Allah.
"Whoever emigrated
for the sake of Allah and His Messenger,
then his emigration
is for Allah and His Messenger."
"And whoever migrates
for wealth or a woman,
then his migration
is for whatever he intended."
Hadith narrated by Imam Al-Bukhari.
Alina.
I want to migrate with you to Indonesia.
We'll live happily there.
With no one holding us back.
How can you truly love me, Omar?
If you can so easily forget
your grandma's love,
your family,
who has done so much for you.
Just to live with me.
That's not the migration I want.
Goodbye, Omar.
O Allah,
Most Gracious and Most Merciful,
I accept
all Your decrees.
I only want to gain
Your love and blessings, O Allah.
Whoever ends up with him one day,
I pray
You grant her happiness.
I surrender, O Allah.
Amen.
How's my mother's condition?
Her condition has improved significantly.
She's quite stable now.
But if possible, avoid any stress.
Please take good care of her.
Thank you, doctor.
Grandma.
You must be strong. You must recover.
I love you so much, Grandma.
Please forgive my mistakes.
I will follow
all of your wishes.
As long as you get well and healthy again.
Assalamu alaikum.
Waalaikumsalam. Mr. Hasan?
Ms. Alina, we must leave now
for Omar's house.
Grandma wants to meet with Alina.
But I need to go to the airport now, sir.
Because I'm returning to Indonesia.
Just a moment, miss.
I will personally take you
to the airport later.
Wait a moment.
Stay a little longer here.
I want to get to know
my future daughter-in-law better.
Alina, you should stay here
a little longer,
so Grandma Halima can get
to know you better.
Alina, Omar is waiting for you over there.
Omar is waiting for you there, Alina.
Omar bin Ahmed.
Alina?
I want to return this bike key
to its rightful owner.
What do you mean?
The owner once said,
if something is meant for you,
it won't go anywhere.
It will always find its way back.
Then
what happens next?
What do you really want?
To have you completely, Alina.
Finish your thesis first.
Omar.
We're not married yet!
Astaghfirullahaladzim.
I love you so much, Alina.