Peasant.
Please. We've given you
all we have to offer.
This?
This is moldy!
Unsuitable for gnats!
You think thisis a good enough
offering to Balam?
It's all we have.
Balam has taken
everything from us
in search of
I don't know what--
- Aah--
-Omar!
Since this offering
is farfrom satisfactory
and an insult
to the great Balam...
- we must make an example of you.
-No!
Not my children!
Not again.
Please... kill me.
I cannot lose another.
None of you are innocent
in the eyes of Balam!
No, Omar--
Stop--get back!
- Get back!
-On your knees!
- On your knees.
- I'm sorry--
Ready!
- No, no, no--
- Aim!
I love you! No, no, no!
- I love you.
-I love you.
Fire--
Fire!
Lead us!
This new threat is likely weak.
We need to stop it now
before it gains strength!
Either die now or die later!
I offer you precious time.
I suggest you take it.
Okay. Okay, okay.
Go on.
That's right.
Keep moving.
Be careful.
By the gods...
Stop!
What do you want, demon?
Fire!
Aah!
-Go, go, go, go, go!
-Aah!
No sudden movement.
Samira, wait!
Samira! Samira. Stop!
Samira, stay away.
A stranger
has come to us wounded.
We cannot just abandon him
like that.
Demon?
We would be no better than Balam
if we left this...
creature here to die.
How should we do this?
Yeah, Omar, take his legs.
I'll get his arms.
Come on. All right. Gently.
Let's go.
Sire.
Balam, my lord.
We have much to discuss.
The deeper we dig,
the larger the yoshumu
gemstones appear to be.
There's been an incident.
The elders say we dig too deep.
That we may run out.
Do you think we should
cease digging...
or shall we press our luck?
I...
I do not know, my lord.
Where are the rest of
my Warlords?
Where are your guards?
They hunt.
We are lower on food
than I'd like.
Enough, but... just barely.
Are you not worried about
an assassin?
Should I be?
- Of course not.
- Good.
I asked you a question.
Where are the rest
of my Warlords?
Whereis the offering
you were sent to collect?
The offering was a pitiful one,
my lord.
It was rejected.
And vengeance was swift?
It was going to be, but--
But...
but?
Yes, but there was
a vessel, sir.
- A vessel?
- Yes, sire.
Unlike anything I've ever seen.
It flew down from the sky!
You arrive with no Warlords
and no offerings,
and you paint me a picture
of a vessel from the sky?
It's true!
I know it sounds incredible,
but there was a creature!
Oh. Oh.
And now there is a creature.
A great warrior of a thing,
my lord.
It killed the rest
of our Warlords!
OurWarlords?
Yes. YourWarlords, sire.
- That's right.
- This creature...
Spit it out!
It killed them all.
I only just escaped.
I cannot be sure, but...
But it might be working with
the villagers of Al'ahrar
where we were sent
to get the offerings from.
Why would you say this?
Because it did not harm
any of the villagers
we brought with us.
Just... yourmen.
I barely escaped.
I mortally wounded it
while it was distracted.
You shot it in the back...
- like a coward?
- No!
- I--
- You confirmed it was dead!
Yes! Of course!
My lord, I just escaped.
I fired, it collapsed.
I ran here to warn you.
It may come after you next!
Uhh--
Oh, stop.
Daray!
Yes, brother.
What is--
- What has Khalil done now?
- Cowardice.
I will have none of it.
He spoke of a warrior
from the sky
possibly helping
a nearby village.
Obvious lies. He was clearly
stealing from your people,
and he was caught.
Fabricated the story in order
to maintain his innocence.
I trust you, brother,
to investigate.
See if there's anything
to his story.
If there is a creature...
he may be after our gemstones.
Do you think the stories
of the Ancients are true?
That the stones
were placed there
by beings not of this world?
The stories of the elders are
designed to placate the masses.
Bring whomever you wish
to go fight.
To fight whom, the villagers?
Go.
Go!
And send someone
to clean up this coward.
I will not have his stench
befoul my throne room.
Come on.
Let's set him down on the bed.
Hurry.
Go on.
Whatever that thing is,
it's heavy.
Samira. We don't have
a lot of supplies.
Don't use them all on this...
creature.
- We must save him, Papa.
-I agree with you Samira.
But his life
should not come at a cost
of saving ours in the future.
Are you listening to us?
Samira!
I'm being careful, Papa.
I just need to clean it,
stitch him,
and redress the wounds.
That's it. I promise.
- That sounds fine.
-Okay, we save him.
But he can't protect us
in this condition.
And what about Balam?
- Omar--
- No--what? What?
He's coming,
and he won't take kindly
to his Warlords being dead.
Then we will be ready for him.
Do you hear yourself?
He will likely slaughter us all.
Are you ready for that?
And this creature
that Samira is trying to save.
Huh? It's done!
You sound like Hasan.
Oh, I'm...
I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you
outside?
Yeah.
- I love you.
I am sorry about Hasan.
But we are not ready.
And the same fate
that befell my brother
cannot happen to us.
Balam cannot destroy our family.
Now, he has...
he has all the other villages
under his thumb.
If he tells them to attack us,
they will, out of fear.
He can retaliate.
He can starve them.
At the heed of his word.
Omar--
No, he has... he has everything.
He's ruthless.
And this creature
that we're trying to protect
just sealed our fate
by killing the Warlords.
No, we need to gather up
everything
and leave this place
and keep on marching until
we're out of Balam's territory.
Rebuild!
If we keep...
running away...
...that will only make us weak.
Balam is only strong
because of his mines.
He built around them
and created an empire.
If we keep running,
we cannot build.
We have to make a stand.
Here. Now.
Yeah. That's a tall order.
For us, yes.
But if we combine our strengths,
talk to the other villages,
convince them to--
to stand up against Balam...
If we convince our friends
and neighbors, Omar...
The power has always been
with the people.
I had forgotten that
until this...
this creature reminded me.
Do you want to finally
stand up to Balam?
Then let the villagers know
that we have seen
Balam's Warlords defeated.
That it ispossible to rise up
against such evil.
Thank you, Father.
You are a strong warrior.
You are ready for this fight.
But his army...
we need the people.
With them on our side...
we can show Balam
our true power.
And for this... sky creature...
Well, he can be
our secret weapon.
We'll see about this.
Is that blood?
The viscosity's the same,
but the color, it's...
it's all wrong.
No. Not wrong.
Not of this world.
Come on!
Samira, is this...
creature still alive?
His wound is all stitched up
and the bleeding stopped.
But I don't think
that'll be enough.
We can't keep our hopes
in this creature.
We have to focus on
the villages.
We must save him
whether he'll help us or not.
And then we must speak
to the villagers.
They're tending to someone.
Or something.
I will speak to
the other village leaders.
Zaid and Amani are old friends.
They will listen
now that Balam and his men
have threatened our--
Ayman--
Shh...
Whatever it is, it's wounded.
We strike now.
I'm gonna get a clean shot
on its head and end this!
They're here.
Now, we need to give them
the creature.
- No, we can't!
- No, we are dead if we don't.
-Omar!
- No!
This creature's
practically dead.
It's useless to Balam and us.
That's enough!
But--
Down!
Aah!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Stop!
-Omar!
- Get off him!
Back away!
Come on!
Khalil was right.
- Don't touch him!
- You want mercy...
to that?
He must be powerful.
You expect
he will fight yourfight?
He will fight ourfight!
In the name of Balam--
Oh!
Ayman!
Ayman...
Mom!
Oh, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
Ayman!
These are from Minalnahr?
Ah, very promising.
Very promising.
Sire!
Where is Daray?
Where is my brother?
He is dead, my lord.
Aah!
My brother's blood
has been spilled.
My blood!
Swear to me.
The creature dies... today!
My people!
- Balam!
We no longer take fealty
or offerings.
Today we take what is ours!
Tonight...
we march on the people
who threaten our way of life!
Before the sun sets,
we... will... rise!
Balam! Balam!
Rise!
Ayman.
Papa...
saved my life.
I know.
I know he wouldn't have it
any other way.
I need some help.
What was he doing?
I think...
I think it was
a form of respect.
It's okay.
Okay.
Balam is going to strike.
His men being killed is more
than enough justification
for him to clear us out.
Well, he was just toying
with us,
waiting for us to lash out first
so he can justify self-defense.
What is it doing?
I think the yoshumu gemstones
are power to him,
his species.
The same gemstones that Balam
mines at his hidden keep?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, if we can...
if we can use his weapons,
we might have enough firepower
to beat Balam.
With enough gemstones,
he can go back to his home
and we can build ours
without that oppressive Balam
breathing down our neck.
Well, I will go with
the creature.
I'll keep an eye on him.
We'll go to wherever Balam
has his hidden keep.
We'll steal as many gems
as we can.
We'll fix his machine, and then
we'll finally beat Balam.
- Yes.
- Stop calling him a creature.
And...
why do you go with him?
I should go.
We need warriors, right?
Who knows what kind of army
they have?
I can fight.
- Don't make me laugh.
- I'm serious.
Samira, please be sensible.
You're not incapable,
but Omar is highly trained.
He knows how to fight.
- This is serious.
- I'm serious.
And I don't need to fight.
You and him combined cannot
take on Balam's whole army.
Samira.
I can heal him
if he's hurt.
And I'm quiet.
We can slip in and out.
That's what this mission needs.
Not strength, but silence.
What do you want me to do?
Huh?
Do you want me to wait and hope
that you don't end up
in the same place
that our brother and father is?
- What if it turns on you?
- You have no faith.
Samira's right.
We need you
to convince the other villages
to stand and fight.
If Balam shows up,
you must be the one
to help protect them.
You are a formidable fighter.
Samira and I are not.
If we do not build an army,
then it does not matter
what any of us do.
Father did say we need
as many people as we can get.
I'll go with Samira.
Mother, you are a valued elder.
You and Omar
should build the army.
His words will carry more weight
with you behind him,
believing in them.
No, Samira's right.
We have a better chance
with the both of us.
It's settled then.
Once we defeat Balam,
we can rebuild right here.
No more running.
Just like Papa wanted.
And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you have to experience
all these tragedies.
I'm sorry you have to
live in a world
where you have to fight
to exist in one that...
would rather you be erased.
Here.
Take this.
A piece of home.
This is the only home
we've ever known.
If we fight now,
then may we know it as peaceful
for the rest of our lives.
And if we die...
may we die for a cause
worthy of death.
Be careful.
I want to see you again.
- Protect her.
- Of course.
I love you.
I love you both too.
We must track that man
that got away.
Find his footprints...
track his scent,
and lead the way.
Sir.
We've sent messengers to have
every able-bodied soldier
report for duty.
We should be able to march
in a few hours.
Send scouts into the woods.
Sir?
I want the creature
that killed my brother dead
before it lays eyes on our keep.
Of course. Right away.
Looks like blood.
We must be on the right track.
I know you might not be able
to understand me...
but I wanted to say thank you.
For saving us
and for fighting for us.
For helping us bury my father
and laying down that gemstone.
I know it meant a lot to you,
but it means the world to me.
'Cause we've been under this
oppressive regime for so long
that it's hard to believe
that we finally stand a chance
of stopping Balam.
Where'd you go?
Aah!
Thanks.
Wait.
You can't do that.
You cannot leave me alone
like that.
We are a team,
and our survival depends on
us working together, okay?
We are almost to Minalnahr.
Your father was so close
to convince them to rise up
a year or so ago.
Why didn't they?
Ayman said
that they were scared.
But now we have something
for Balam to be scared of.
My son.
You need to be strong,
but empathetic.
We need to show these villages
that we are all fighting
for the same thing--
our freedom.
I will not stop
until they join the fight.
That's my son.
Soul of my soul.
Come on.
- Zaid.
-Stop!
Stand down.
Omar.
Inara. It is good to see you.
I apologize
for the added security.
We've heard rumors of
a mysterious creature
falling from the sky.
Yeah. That's one of the reasons
why we are here.
- You have seen this creature?
- Yes.
We not know what it is,
but we know it's powerful.
And better... he's on our side.
And with its help,
I believe we're strong enough
to do what we should have done
long ago.
Now, the weapons will help.
But Balam's forces
are too massive.
That's why we need you.
It is as I told Ayman
a year ago when he asked.
Balam is simply too powerful.
He has weapons that we could
never dream to possess.
Ayman was just killed
by Balam's men.
I see now why you are
so quick to act.
But it does not change
my answer.
Uh, okay, okay.
The warrior from the sky--
he is on our side.
We have both borne witness
to his power.
Now, his weapons are unlike
anything you've ever seen.
Balam's weapons
can now be our own.
How do you know that you can
trust this creature?
He helped bury Ayman.
And Samira is with the warrior
right now,
finding fuel for his weapons.
These weapons...
how do you know they are
as powerful as you say?
Well, the yoshumu gemstones
Balam stockpiles...
the warrior uses them
to power his weapons.
Now, these weapons are far more
advanced than Balam's.
He even uses it
to heal himself as well.
Samira and the warrior
are infiltrating Balam's keep.
Once they get enough gemstones,
we can defend ourselves
with the creature's weapons
against his army.
We can finally be free!
I am sorry.
Even if what you are saying
is true,
I have seen
what Balam is capable of.
I cannot risk his ire.
It is the reason this village
is a quarter
of what it used to be.
I can no longer remember
the voices of my own children.
But I will never forget
their screams.
He's killing us.
Despite our placating him.
And he demands more and more
and takes and takes
while we--we have less and less.
We can do this.
We just need your army
to help us.
Tonight.
I grieve with you.
I do.
But I cannot stand with you.
Maybe Amani in Tuthisi--
maybe she will have
the forces that you need.
Youhave the forces we need!
It's okay.
We will search for an army.
But I really hope
you reconsider our words.
I will.
Of course.
And my condolences.
I can help you with those.
You use these
to power everything?
The vessel that you fell
to earth in. Yourself.
You know, when I was
trying to heal you,
nothing was helping.
But when Balam's men
came with those masks,
suddenly, you healed.
Your kind
has a very deep connection
with those yoshumu gemstones.
If these gemstones can turn you
into that level of a warrior,
Balam doesn't stand a chance.
No, no, no, no.
How could you let them say no?
We need their help.
His mind is tainted with fear.
There's comfort in knowing
your enemy.
We have planted a seed.
Now we must wait and see
if anything grows.
But what if it takes too long?
What if he waits...
and we're all dead?
Then it's on him.
My son, we have done
everything we can.
Now we go to the next
and keep on trying.
Come on, now.
We have more seeds to plant.
Here.
Another one.
I have one more left.
Hold on. It's stuck.
Aah!
No, please, no! Please!
Oh!
Oh! Thank you.
Thank you!
I will protect these
with my life.
And if you need them,
let me know, okay?
Sir.
You have a visitor.
What news do you have for me?
Do you promise to send me
back to my people
with food and water?
Depends on how much
I like your information.
The people of Al'ahrar,
the ones that you
plan on attacking, they...
they have a plan of their own.
They're trying to amass an army
with the help of the creature
that fell from the sky.
Are you sure of this?
Yes.
Then why don't I believe you?
I think I have all of them.
Did you pick up a scent?
Good. Then I think we're close.
Please do not mistake
my wavering for lies.
I am quite nervous.
Don't be nervous.
You're trying to help
your village.
That is a noble cause.
I feel... compelled to choose
my words carefully. I--
I do not want to say
the wrong thing
and hurt my people further.
You are wise.
But never fear
speaking truth to power
if your words carry the weight
truth has to offer.
Kyro!
Yes, sir!
Escort this man
back to his village.
They will then proceed
to find the people
trying to amass an army
against me!
But please...
Do not harm them.
They're grieving.
That creature killed my brother!
Is my grief not as actionable
as theirs?
Is their family's life
more important than mine?
No!
Their fate is sealed!
You hear me?
Get him outta here!
I am sorry for my outburst.
I just can't understand
how everyone could be okay
with this injustice brought on
by such an evil man.
There can be comfort
in being protected by strength,
now matter how evil
the source may be.
- But that doesn't make it right.
- No, it doesn't.
And hopefully,
we can convince the next people
of what we already know.
It helps to understand
people's fears,
so then youcan give them
solutions to solve them.
You're such a wise mother.
I'm glad it's finally
coming through.
Come on.
We better pick up the pace.
That's Zaid.
He's the leader of a village
near me.
What's he doing
with Balam's men?
He's a traitor.
We have to take him out.
Did you hear that?
Gentlemen.
Omar and Inara will already
be waiting at the next village
if we do not hurry.
I'm sure whatever antelope
we scared
can wait until your return?
Let them go.
Let's follow their trail.
-Who are you?
- I found them here.
I think they're headed
to Tuthisi.
What's going on?
What are we waiting for? Hurry!
Wait. Wait--where are you going?
Where are you going?
Do you have water
in your canteen?
Hey!
Get down!
Oh!
Come on! Come on!
Aah! Omar!
No! No!
Omar! No!
No! Leave me here!
No! No!
We're running out of time.
Balam's army could be marching--
Aah!
Can you help me out?
Can you find something
to pull me up?
A vine or a stick?
Oh, no!
You can't run away like this!
Help me!
Mother. No!
Mother.
Mother!
Inara!
Aah--
Hey, go. Go back.
Omar?
What are you doing here?
Why are you hurt?
You need to see a doctor.
She can--she can help you.
Amani...
Balam's men,
they tried to kill me.
And they took my mother.
And they're coming for all of
us, and we need to stop them.
They're going to keep on
attacking our villages
until there's nothing left.
- That is not possible.
- It is.
But...
but...
we have a new weapon...
a soldier capable
of incredible things.
The time is now
to stop this horrible fate.
Omar.
One of our children threw
a rock at Balam's Warlords
several months ago.
Balam shot him and his family
335 times.
His retribution is swift.
He has guns. I am sorry.
I cannot see another villager
be killed by his hands.
For far too long...
we have woken and rested
to the tyrannical control
of Balam.
Now, we can no longer pay
the heavy price for this burden.
Your crops and villages
belong to you,
not him.
Your lives...
are yours.
- We can offer you medicine.
- I do not need
medicine.
I need...
...your help.
Be safe.
I'm... sorry.
Who was that man?
Oh...
somebody looking for help.
Why didn't you help him?
Let's go back inside, yeah?
I will not help you--never!
Uhh!
You will have to kill me!
You can go.
Return to your ranks.
Tell me where the creature is.
You abandoned me!
You left me trapped in that
hole--I could have been killed.
You cannot abandon me
like that again, okay?
Okay?
You go find
the yoshumu gemstones.
I'll find my mother,
and then we meet back here,
carry the gemstones together.
Every time you lie to me,
I will make you remember it.
So I'll ask you again--
where is the creature?
Technically, that's not a lie.
But I did not like that answer.
Just kill me.
I'm not saying a word.
Kill you? No.
Not when there is
so much empty canvas
waiting for my paint brush.
There is a reason
everyone wants you dead.
You are a monster.
You talk of monsters,
yet you fight alongside
the one that killed my brother!
Killed my only family!
Your Warlords--they're
going to execute my family.
My family that gave you
everything we have
and always have.
When the sky warrior fell...
we had no fear.
No. It felt like our prayers
were answered!
There is no one here
to answer your prayers.
Here, I am God.
I will bestow a plague upon you.
I will ensure generations
of what few survivors there are
suffer for what you have done!
I must address my army.
I'll be back for more fun.
Kill her if she tries anything.
Uhh!
- How many?
- Not including the scouts
already at the village--1,000.
- Will that be enough?
- Against the villagers?
Yes.
Against the sky warrior?
There's only one way to know.
We march at your command.
My people!
I think my head is bleeding.
- Could you check for me?
- Huh?
Take that, you coward!
Ohh...
My daughter.
My precious daughter.
How on earth did you find me?
- Where's the warrior?
- We split up.
He went to find
the yoshumu gemstones,
and I'm here to find you.
We are to join him
and carry as many as we can.
Where... where's Omar?
You should join him.
- No.
- Go. Leave me here!
No, I'm here to find you.
Let me untie you.
No, there's no time.
Balam will be back any minute.
You need to focus
on those gemstones.
- You have to go now.
- Mother.
No. I won't speak on this
any longer.
When we have enough
gemstones to carry,
I will come and find you--
I promise.
Then I will see you soon.
Now, go.
Every stone we can get.
Oh!
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
It's you.
Oh, come on!
Wait! There might be guards.
Whoa.
Wow. It's beautiful.
Take this bag.
Here. Remember...
we have to carry lightly because
we're gonna go all the way back.
But when we defeat Balam,
you can come back
and take as many gemstones
as you need.
Your people.
You've been to Earth before?
Are more of your people
coming to take gemstones?
Balam collects these
because it gives him power.
Is that what you're after?
What have you done?
He tried to kill me
while you were away.
But he wasn't fast enough.
You think I'm a fool?
If you killed him,
how did he get stabbed
in the back?
And more importantly,
where did his mask go?
Where is the person
that killed my guard?
I don't know--
Where...
are...
they?
Balam. We found them.
- Perfect.
- Please...
I will handle it personally.
This should be enough, yeah?
Here. Let's go get my mother.
Oh--ah! Oh!
Oh, my God.
You are real.
- Mother--
- Just get outta here!
You need to have your creature
here lie down before me
and be executed by my hand.
- He can't understand you!
- Make him understand!
Stop all the bloodshed.
Save your mother's life!
All you have to do
is let me kill the...
thing that killed my brother!
You hear that?
There's no escaping now.
Lay down your weapons,
and I'll let the women
go back to their village.
Run!
Come on! They're coming!
Aahhh!
I will watch all of you die!
All of you!
Balam! Balam, are you okay?
We... kill...
every last one of them!
I want those two women
to suffer
for bringing that creature to us
and its threat
to our way of life!
We march on the villages
now!
Leave none alive!
Go!
Yaaahhhh!
We haven't
checked over here. Come on.
Weapons, weapons, weapons!
Come on. I need something.
I hope you're ready
for a fight!
'Cause I'm not leaving here
without one!
Mother, so...
You don't know where Omar is
or if he's even alive?
We were ambushed.
He put up a courageous fight.
But there were too many of them.
They threatened to kill me.
He stopped.
He's alive.
He has to be.
He's strong, and this...
means much more to him
to save the village.
He's a survivor.
You are right.
Now, let's get back
and get him the weapons
he needs.
Come.
Uhh--
Come on!
No, no, no, no!
Uhh--
Grab him!
No, no. No, no, no, no.
Omar!
Samira!
- Get out of here!
- Omar!
Samira--
Oh!
No!
Omar.
Omar! No.
No!
Seize the gemstones!
Keep those two alive!
I want them to watch as I burn
everything they've ever known!
Go!
No! No!
No, no, no!
Come on, get up.
You have to get up.
Warriors!
Slaughter the village!
Charge!
What are we going to do,
Samira?
I don't know, I--
Search for the gems!
- Hey!
- Aah!
If there's anything left
of the creature's head,
I would take it for a trophy.
But I'll make do
with what I have
to ensure it never heals and
will remain entombed forever.
Surrender--now.
I will make you a concubine
and treat you better
than you deserve.
I will let your mother live.
Join me and behave...
and you may even become queen.
No.
Samira, what are you doing?
I knew you would see it my way.
- Uhh!
- Aah!
- Get her!
- No!
If you're going to do it,
just do it, but leave her alone!
Oh, you will both die.
But first, I will use you
both as warnings
to anyone who stands against me!
- Get up!
- Aah! Aah!
Move!
How could I be so foolish?
It's not too late.
Amani. What are you--
Are you joining us or no?
- Balam, he--
- I'm tired!
This is no way to live!
We must help Omar.
Freedom or death.
Now is the time to choose.
Weapons. Weapons.
There has to be something.
There has to--
Your mother has 30 seconds
to live!
You can make a fine queen
one day!
She'll never be a queen
to the likes of you!
You are so fun to torture.
I am sad that I didn't
kill Ayman sooner.
Samira!
Come out now! No weapons!
Or she dies!
Just come out,
or your mother dies!
15 seconds!
Ten, nine, eight...
Seven...
six, five...
Four...
three, two...
One.
Get to cover!
Uhh.
Gimme that.
No more games.
They die like everybody else.
Find them. Find them.
Come on.
What's wrong?
It's not--it's not working!
- What are you doing?
- They don't know that.
Get into position.
I'll distract them. Go!
Go!
Hey, Balam!
- Aah!
Where's the girl?
I don't know.
There!
It coulda been so easy.
All you had to do was...
Oh, shit.
Kyro! Fire the weapon!
Fire the weapon!
For freedom!
Freedom!
You had your chance.
Aah!
You?
No, no, no. Samira!
No...
You have to save her.
After everything
she's been through--
my husband, my sons!
I cannot lose her as well.
You must have some way.
Anara.
Is this--
Samira! My daughter!
Oh, my Samira!
Was I--
You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
You changed your mind.
Amani told me
what Omar told her.
And it all finally made sense.
And we've decided
there is no point
in staying divided any longer.
But once Ayman said
there is strength in numbers.
And, since you and your family
were the ones
that brought us together,
we think you should lead us.
Here.
Omar gave this to me.
It convinced me.
I thought you should have it.
We stand behind you, united.
Just as Ayman,
Hasan, and Omar... dreamed.
I'm too old to lead.
But, Samira, my child,
only if you wish to lead.
My people!
We are to rebuild
not as separate villages
but...
as a city finally united!
Samira! Samira!
Samira!
And you...
you need to rebuild your ship.
You may use whatever we have
at your disposal.
Thank you for saving my people.
Now you need to leave
and go back home.
I...am... home.
Samira! Samira!
Samira!