A TRUE STORY OF ALBI AND SHELLA
WHEN CANCER ARRIVES, LOVE THRIVES
Fifi, get in here.
Rin!
Nia!
Shella, pass!
Shella!
Goal!
Go back!
LUXE CREATION
BUSY LOADING, FORGOT ABOUT HEALING
It's okay.
Come on!
Keep going!
Keep going! Straight!
Straight! Stop.
Okay, this is everything.
Everything?
- Please, okay?
- Yeah.
Got it.
Let's grab some food, Albi. I'm hungry.
There's food over there.
That's for later this afternoon.
No, I'm sleepy. I want to sleep.
Albi, just keep him company.
- You do it. You already slept.
- Albi!
Give me some chili sauce, okay?
- Ma'am.
- Yes.
As usual?
- With what?
- Bakwan.
Must be nice to sleep in the car earlier.
You're always grumpy.
How do you expect to get a girl?
You probably didn't eat
last night's catering, did you?
- Oh my. Albi.
- Oh my.
Shella, you hit someone.
Are you hurt?
Wake up. This is embarrassing.
I'm so sorry, sir. Really sorry.
Get me some wipes. Wet wipes.
- Do you have one?
- I do. I'll grab some.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let me help you up.
Okay.
Are you sure you're okay?
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Come on. Let's continue playing!
- For you.
- No need.
It's fine. It's really dirty anyway.
To wipe it off. Clean your clothes.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I...
Ball?
The ball's a bit dirty.
- It's okay. Don't worry about it.
- Sorry.
- It's fine. It's dirty.
Thanks.
Go for it!
Come on. Keep going!
That ball gave him brain damage.
Looks like you need
to control your strength.
Yeah?
Or you'll end up
hitting someone, like just now.
I know!
Lucky that guy was cute.
Yeah.
- Cute?
- He was.
Alright, try it here.
Try it. Control your power.
Ready?
- Try me!
- One...
Two, three!
Oh my!
Oh my God!
- Sorry.
- Sorry, ma'am.
- Oh no!
- Sorry!
You ruined my sport bike!
- What's wrong with you, girls?
- Sorry!
- Now it's broken.
What were you doing?
Why is it so quiet here?
I mean, what's all the noise?
Oh my!
These girls are really naughty!
Hard to tell them anything.
They never listen!
I already told you not to play ball.
You'll mess up your lady parts!
Better than illegal racing
like Nanang, Bu Nurul.
What's wrong with that?
In the end...
What?
- ...he became deaf.
- What?
They were teasing me
for being deaf, right?
- Hey, tantrum.
- I heard that!
Why do they keep calling me deaf?
- No, no.
- Enough already.
He's just having a centrum.
- I mean, tantrum.
- Yeah.
Why are they teasing me for being deaf?
Let's run.
- Sorry, bro!
- Hey, come here!
- You better watch out!
- Wait a sec.
You're never allowed
on the kiddie ride again!
- Nanang! Stop all this!
- Hey!
Mom, I'm going for a race, okay?
- Hey, Panjul. Hold on!
- Hey!
- What?
- Panjul, Panji.
- Panjul!
- Panjul? My name's Panji!
Yeah, come here!
- No!
- That's my kid!
Hey, Panjul! Where are you going?
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
You stink!
Have you done your homework?
- Not yet.
- Do it first, Dide.
Dide, let's play ball!
- Do your homework first!
- Hurry up!
Dide!
- Dide!
- Shella, we're going out to play ball!
Bye!
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
There's my dear big sis.
You're so diligent.
You must have an agenda.
You're so caring of the little ones.
- Thanks!
- You're welcome.
Hey!
- Dide?
- Ouch!
Dide.
Where were you?
- The river. Frogs.
- What's this? A toad?
Oh man.
- You're so filthy.
- The soup's all gone.
Hold on. Take care of Dide first.
Come on, Dide!
- I don't want to!
- Come play!
- Come here!
- No!
Dry your body first!
Dide!
- Come here! You'll catch a cold!
- Peace be upon you.
I'm giving you to three. One...
- two...
- Dide.
Why are you naked?
- And you're running around.
- He refused to wear clothes.
Put your clothes on.
Come on.
Hurry up. Oh my God.
Why did it fall like this?
- Dide did that!
- It's okay, Mom. Let me handle it.
- Let me do it.
- Is Dad still working?
Probably still out doing gigs.
- Are you making soup?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome, Mom.
Lidya.
- Yeah?
- Can you grab the plates, please?
Veggies again, Mom?
- What?
- I'm tired of it!
Just eat it.
It's healthy, you know.
- Peace be upon you.
- Dad!
- Chicken!
- Peace be upon you too.
We have chickens!
- Yay!
- Where?
Oh, please, honey.
- Dad!
- What is it, hon?
There, I brought some chicken.
Wait.
We're eating chicken!
- Why?
- Stella already cook some soup.
It's okay. Anyone can eat that.
Now we eat the chicken
But tomorrow you get circumcised
Why'd you say that?
- Where are the plates?
- It really hurts, you know.
- Want some?
- You won't be able to walk.
What's this?
- You don't eat chili, right?
- No.
I'll bring it with me, okay?
It's Big Brother.
- Lidya.
- Why are you eating upstairs?
I want to watch.
- Yeah?
- Are you still at work, Mom?
No, I'm at home.
Where are my brother and sisters?
I miss them.
Just a sec.
Here you go.
- It's your brother.
- Hey.
- Brother.
- Hey, Dide.
Hi, Dad.
- Eating, are you?
- Have you eaten, bro?
Yes, I have.
Did you eat your veggies?
Yeah, look. He's eating his veggies.
- That's great!
- Dide.
Eating veggies.
How'd that happen? What's going on?
- Are you still up?
- Ma.
I just got home at six this morning.
You shouldn't do that. You'll get sick.
But I will still pray for you.
May your luck be plenty.
Stay healthy with all that work.
Maybe you'll even meet
a future spouse along the way!
A pretty, kind, funny, and smart one.
Who is that?
Like me, of course! Who else?
Sure, Ma.
I hope I can find a beautiful girl,
who's funny,
who's great at football...
You're already
sweet-talking Mom's kid, huh?
No, Ma. That's...
No, it's just kinda funny,
if someone plays...
- Hey!
- Your table's dirty!
Don't use that wipe!
- Albi!
- My wall's dirtier!
- What's wrong, son?
- Wait a sec, Ma. Hold on.
- What's wrong?
- I want to tidy up!
- My feet are dirty!
- Don't use my wipes!
Are you crazy?
That's just a napkin!
You said you didn't want
any lovey-dovey stuff.
Now you're all lovey-dovey
with a napkin. Make up your mind.
Shut up!
Wanna earn some extra cash?
Help the neighborhood head.
They're looking for people.
Pretty decent pay.
They pay daily.
Perfect for you.
Help with what?
Basically, your job
is just to hold things.
Not yours.
Hold the one that is
getting circumcised, of course.
Haven't you been circumcised yet?
- I have, sir.
- See? Then you can do it.
Just follow along, okay? Let's go.
- Excuse us.
- Sir.
Excuse me.
Hi.
How are you, Albi?
Lift your shirt.
Come on, Dide.
Are you ready?
Why are you so quiet?
Where are your eyes? Come on.
Prepare yourself.
It's going to be cut.
Lidya. Stop it.
They won't cut much. Just a little.
- Cut up into small pieces.
- No!
You know him?
Come, pick up.
One, two, three.
Ouch!
You are so heavy.
Try asking the guy.
It's true, right? You're going
to cut it into small pieces?
Lidya, enough.
- Call Dad.
- Let me fix it.
How come he's not here when he knew
his son was getting circumcised?
That's weird.
- Alright.
- Say a prayer first.
Dide, do you know what prayer to say?
The eating prayer.
Lidya! Stop it.
You know your little brother's panicking.
Just keep still.
Sir.
Will it be cut into small pieces?
No, it's not a carrot.
- Relax, okay?
- Okay, let's start.
- Relax.
- Yeah, relax.
Have you been circumcised?
- Yeah.
- Did it hurt?
No.
In the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Relax.
It hurts!
Sorry.
It's like an ant bite.
But it's like being bitten by a tiger.
Hey, Mom. How did Dide's circumcision go?
Thank God, Dide's circumcision
went smoothly.
- You stay healthy over there, okay?
- Dide!
My son is circumcised!
My son is all grown up!
Why are you so late?
Your son's already circumcised.
You asked me to pick up the catering.
It's already noon.
I've asked you since this morning.
- But you said...
- You'll catch a cold, Dide.
Cut into small pieces!
- Sir.
- Yes?
- Sorry...
- It's okay.
Here's my dad's shirt. It seems too big,
but just try it on first.
No need. This is fine.
This can still be folded.
No, you can't. Just wear this.
- I don't want to be a bother.
- It's fine. Just wear this.
- Change first.
- I can't accept this.
Thank you.
Where are the envelopes?
They're in the usual spot.
They're usually here.
Look with your eyes,
not your mouth, honey.
Lidya, did you see the envelopes?
- Look with your eyes.
- They're usually there.
Look with your eyes, not your mouth.
- Someone must've moved them.
- Get used to looking with your eyes.
It's usually there.
Sorry, my family's really loud.
It's okay. It's actually fun.
- It's lively.
- Take this outside, okay?
- To hand out.
- So we count first or hand out first?
Alright, you can do this after that!
Are you continuing after this?
Continuing? No.
I'll probably just take a rest.
That's terrible! This...
This is Dad's shirt
for wiping the kitchen, right, Sis?
- No, it's not.
- Oh my.
- This is from the closet!
- How could you?
- Lidya! Stop it!
- Come on!
- Lidya!
- Please forgive my sister.
She's just kidding.
I really took it from the closet.
It's okay.
It's nice. It has a spicy aroma.
What's your name?
Albi.
- Shella.
- I'm so sorry about the tear and...
- It's fine.
about your head yesterday.
Thanks for this too.
Must be a hassle for you.
- Thanks.
- I'm sorry, sir.
I mean, Albi.
Shella.
Which one?
There you are.
Let's follow her.
Let's go for it.
- Going to sleep?
- Yeah.
Yes!
She followed me back!
HELLO
HI
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BREATHING
Shella!
Hi.
I want to return this.
No need to return it. Just keep it, Albi.
Don't. Your kitchen will be missing a rag.
It's not a rag, Albi!
- Going for a walk?
- Yeah.
- Where are you going?
- To buy bakso over there.
- At...
- Over there.
Just go straight, turn left, turn right,
then straight, and the bakso is there.
Let's take a motorbike, okay?
- Why? It's super close.
- It's far.
- It's really close, Albi.
- Wait. Just take a motorbike!
Are you coming or not?
Yeah, of course.
Let's go.
You're not working right now?
Not right now. I'll start working tonight.
Do people actually call at night?
Yeah, especially if it's at a hotel,
a ballroom, a restaurant.
Hold on. So...
Hotel, ballroom, hall?
- Yeah. That's right.
- You sure?
Is it a mass circumcision or something?
Mass circumcision?
You're a circumcision guy, right?
Okay, so actually,
I'm originally a wedding EO.
Okay? So I help around
if there's a wedding.
You work for an EO?
Well, I'm a migrant,
so I just take any job I can get.
- Where are you from?
- From Medan.
Medan.
So, what are you busy with these days?
You ready?
- Ready.
- It's a long story, though.
- I'm listening.
- Okay.
Before the pandemic,
we used to play soccer a lot.
Then we stopped for a bit,
and now we want to start again.
You're a sogirl?
"Sogirl"?
Soccer girl!
That's so cool!
Sogirl?
So, you like sunflowers, sambal,
and elephants?
That's right.
And you're still single?
Not single, because I'm a soccer player.
I can't play alone, right?
So, I have lots of friends.
Yes, no?
- Stop messing with me.
- Okay.
Have you seen them before?
This one's Kuki.
Kuki.
That one's Kuku.
Kuku?
You named them, didn't you?
Oh, look here!
- Always on video calls, bro!
- Hey!
Well, I can say that...
yeah, I'm still single.
When are you gonna get a boyfriend?
For that, I'll have to ask the person
who likes me first.
Delivery!
Delivery, ma'am!
BAKSO FROM A HANDSOME GUY
FOR A PRETTY GIRL
Shella! Are those bakso?
- Yeah!
- Let's eat.
- Thanks, Shella.
- Yeah.
We've been pretty close for a while now.
But when will he make a move?
I'll ask him later.
Or do you want to help me ask?
- Bye.
- I'm heading home too, Shella.
- Bye!
Yeah, can I help you?
Shella.
Yeah?
There's something I want to talk about.
Yeah, go ahead.
We've been
pretty close now, right?
So, do you think you want
to be my girlfriend?
Why'd you say it over the phone?
It's because if, in case...
I get rejected, I just hang up the phone.
But that's just an example, okay?
So, if you get rejected,
you're just going to hang up.
What if I say yes?
Well, I'll be glad then.
Alright then, I'll just reject you.
She hung up right away.
Why are you such a chicken?
Huh?
- What?
- What? How'd you know I was here?
The sound of the balloon vendor.
- Aw, you found out.
- Why'did it have to be over the phone?
Well... What can I say?
That's all the courage I had.
Try again.
- What?
- Repeat what you said on the phone.
You can just give me the answer, right?
- I'll just go home then.
- Come on!
Fine!
- Try it.
- Fine, I'll say it again.
- One more time?
- One more time.
Alright then.
- Shella.
- Yes.
We've been...
We've become pretty close, right?
Yes?
So...
would you want to be...
my girlfriend?
No, I don't.
- You really don't want to?
- I'm kidding.
Just kidding, Albi. I do.
- Do what?
- I do.
I do want to be your girlfriend!
Praise be to God!
This is for you.
- What's this?
- Ta-da!
An elephant?
So cute!
You like it?
So much!
You...
One, two...
That's enough, Albi.
Eight.
Hug.
Where are we going?
We're going for a ride.
Put in here.
I had bakso earlier.
Bakso, and you didn't invite me?
- Don't be mad, babe.
- No!
I'm not talking to you
until you buy me bakso.
Babe?
- I can't hear you.
- Hello?
Today's practice was really fun.
She's really good at playing.
She's really, really good!
CAPTAIN
It's great to be here again!
I'm so happy!
Wait, do you guys smell that?
What's that smell?
- It smells like...
- What's that smell?
Victory!
Alright, let's go.
One, two, three!
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Don't run!
- No!
Everyone, the new jerseys are ready!
Our new jerseys!
- Which one's mine?
- All in here.
- Let's go!
- Yes!
Wait!
Dila.
Shella, come here! We're done!
Shella?
- Shella?
- Again?
Shella!
- Shella!
Help her!
Hurry!
Slowly.
Hurry.
There's a 9 cm cyst right here.
You've missed your period for three months
and often have stomach cramps?
Yes.
I suggest we perform surgery
so we can find out
if it's malignant or not.
But this isn't dangerous, is it?
Hopefully not.
If you agree to the surgery,
we'll schedule it.
For now, you should limit your activities.
Don't get too tired,
and don't play soccer, okay?
This is still an estimated cost, ma'am.
It could be less or more.
Thank you.
- Is it okay, Mom?
- Don't worry.
- Let's go.
- Auntie.
I have to go. I'm going straight to work.
- Thanks, babe. Bye.
- Yes, babe.
Come on.
‎Okay.
- Be careful, okay?
- Yeah, bye.
Yeah, I'm going. I'm on my way.
We have two big events.
First, a government official's
child's wedding.
Second, a celebrity's child's birthday.
I want all of you to be disciplined.
Don't be late.
Whatever they ask for, give it to them.
Provide it.
- Understand?
- Yes, sir.
Hey.
Charge the walkie-talkie and phone.
Yes, sir.
Alright, you're dismissed.
Yeah, we only won 1-0 earlier.
If you were there,
we definitely would've won 5-0!
SIX MONTHS LATER
Who scored the goal?
- Hold on!
- That one? It was me.
No way. If it wasn't for me,
it wouldn't have been a goal.
- But I passed it to you.
- But I am the one who scored the goal.
- Alright, fine. That's awesome.
- But you admit that.
So you guys are going to Jakarta
for the next match, right?
Shella, it's been six months since we last
saw each other. When will we meet again?
You better actually come! Or else!
Alright, if I can make it, I'll come.
Please, I already miss you.
I'll go first, okay?
- Alright, Shella. I have to go.
- Okay.
- Stay healthy, okay?
- Thanks. Bye.
Hey, Rini, wait for me!
I want to get my clothes.
Mom and Dad's clothes are there too.
Yeah, might as well. It's fine.
Okay.
If you need help, just say so.
I'll tell Mom you're still
lifting heavy things.
Dide, let's go home.
Let's get some snacks first!
Ma'am.
A kilo of eggs.
- What?
- A kilo of eggs.
Just a moment.
Nanang.
Turn off the music.
Turn off the music!
It's noisy. Music.
Music!
- Don't shout at me.
- Dide!
- Come here!
- So noisy!
- What did you want?
- A kilo of eggs.
- Eggs?
- Yeah, eggs.
Yeah, just a moment.
Eggs are expensive right now.
It's 30,000 for a kilo.
Wasn't it 25?
- The feed is expensive.
- Dide!
Thank you.
- Let's play soccer!
- Dide!
- No changes.
- Come on, Dide.
Dide.
Dide, come on!
- I want to play soccer!
- Look at her belly.
- Come on, Panji!
- No wonder she hasn't been around.
Come on. Hurry up!
- She's always at home. Maybe ashamed.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, it's true.
- Her! She's back here!
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Babe.
It turns out that in these six months,
the tumor tissue
has grown faster than expected.
So, I have to have surgery
as soon as possible.
- Babe.
- Yeah.
This is just to draw blood.
We're going to prick you, okay?
Take a deep breath.
- Just look at me.
- It's in.
No need to panic. Calm...
Is it done?
I will wait here, okay?
Bye.
Hello. Good afternoon.
Doc.
So, what are the results?
Looking at its growth,
it's actually too fast for a benign cyst.
But the surgery was successful.
It's been removed, and it's all clean.
We'll do a series of chemotherapy sessions
for prevention.
I think six times will be enough.
One series, six times, is that right, Doc?
Yes, sir.
It's just for prevention, really.
So, when can I get back
to my activities, Doc?
- Babe.
- Easy.
Just do your usual activities.
But don't do anything
too strenuous yet, okay?
Eat a lot, and don't
stress yourself too much.
Thank you.
- I'll be going now. Excuse me.
- Okay.
See? No heavy activities yet.
I'll get better soon.
- Yeah.
- You can do it, babe.
Want a drink?
Lang, where's Albi?
I don't know. Just call him.
Thanks, bro!
You took forever! Deni's been calling you!
Why so sudden?
It's usually in the afternoon!
Let's go. Hurry up.
Where are the car keys?
I have them.
- Why'd you take them?
- Sorry.
- Come on. Hurry up.
- Ouch!
- Speed up!
- I am speeding up.
- We're already late.
- Yeah, just a sec!
Ten minutes.
It's broken!
- Forget it. Just deal with it later!
- Glue. Is there glue or not?
So what about this?
You're already late,
and you broke my mirror.
- I'll just replace it.
- You'll replace it?
From my salary.
You can't just cut your salary!
We panicked. We were afraid of being late.
But you were late, weren't you?
Listen.
If it happens three times...
we're done.
INCOMING CALL
BABE
- Hello.
- Hello, miss.
Do you have sunflowers?
No, sorry.
- None at all?
- Yeah.
To, they don't have sunflowers.
Sir!
Sir, are these sunflowers for sale?
To. Thank you, sir!
Got 'em! Don't worry. Still on time.
Oh my.
Add a few more flowers.
Sir!
- Yeah.
- Sir!
Sir!
- I got the flowers.
- My brother.
- You got the flowers?
- Yeah.
Oh my God, you're amazing.
It's good, right? Are these enough?
Are you wet?
- I was out in the rain.
- Oh my.
- Where do you want them?
- These?
Put them on your head!
What time is it?
What time is it? Where's your phone?
It's here. But...
It fell. It's dead...
- Want me to smash it?
- No, don't.
I called you a million times to tell you
this was canceled.
If this continues,
my company will go bankrupt.
I'm sorry.
ALBI, WHY HAVEN'T I HEARD FROM YOU?
Oh, no.
I'M SORRY, BABE, MY PHONE
DIED YESTERDAY, IT FELL IN THE WATER
I'M SORRY, BABE, MY PHONE DIED YESTERDAY
I THOUGHT SOMETHING HAPPENED TO YOU
I START CHEMO TOMORROW
CHEMOTHERAPY
Will it hurt?
It shouldn't.
But you don't need to think about that.
What you should be thinking
about now is, what do you want to do
once you're well?
I...
Play soccer again.
There you go.
Just think about that, okay?
Don't think about anything else.
Bald-headed!
I'm sorry, I...
It's okay, babe.
I was just... taking pictures.
Let's take one.
Let me do it, Mom.
No need.
I will do it. You just rest.
BABE, I HAVE CHEMO AGAIN TODAY
YOU'RE COMING AGAIN, RIGHT?
Are you okay?
Hello, Albi. Shella!
- Hello, Auntie.
- Hello. Hi, Mom.
I'm here with Shella for her chemo.
Oh, chemo.
Scold her a bit, Mom.
She refuses to eat now.
- You can't do that, Shella.
- Why did you say that?
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- Bye, Mom.
I'm sorry to bother you.
If you have some extra money,
could you help me out a little?
I'll wire it later
when I have the money, okay?
Thank you, Nurse.
Hi, Shella.
How was your chemo today?
It was fine. Yesterday, I felt
nauseous and a bit dizzy.
That's normal, right?
It's okay. It's normal.
Oh, I want to ask, Doc.
What if I don't get better?
What if you do get better?
Don't worry, okay? You can do it.
Stay strong.
Thanks.
Babe, I thought you were asleep.
Sorry, I just got back.
- Babe.
- It's okay.
- Does it hurt?
- No.
No?
Have you eaten yet?
- Come on!
- I still want to play soccer with Panji!
- So I can be a like Shella!
- Go take a bath!
Hurry up! Sheesh!
Go take a bath! Come on!
Shella... Wait first.
Take a bath first, Dide.
Come on.
Shella!
Shella.
Help.
It tickles.
Lidya, this is for Mom too, right?
Hey!
Yes, Shella!
Sir, I'm sorry, but...
Excuse me.
Can I get another advance?
Because
I still need money
for my daughter's treatment.
I know your daughter needs money.
But you haven't paid back
the last advance.
But I'll definitely pay it back later.
I can keep working overtime.
Yeah, but until when?
Until it's paid off, sir.
I'm okay with it.
The amount doesn't have to be
as much as last time. It's fine.
I'm sorry,
I can't help you this time, Erna.
Ms. Erna, someone was looking for you.
Who is it?
- Plate.
- Fine.
Here.
- Flat.
- Oh my God.
Don't tell me...
I already told you.
If someone is sick,
why not just tell everyone?
So they can be visited
and get prayed for. Right?
- True!
- Am I right?
- Right!
Shella must have had an abortion.
Now, what else would she
be hiding if not shame?
Ladies.
Thank you for your prayers
for my daughter.
May her sins be forgiven
and taken by you ladies.
Amen.
Why didn't you say anything?
Hey, her mother was right there,
but you didn't say anything.
Nanang! Why didn't you say
Ms. Erna was here!
I'm so weak now.
- What's wrong?
- I can't feel my legs.
Nanang.
Mom.
Can I say something?
I...
want to...
apologize...
for causing you trouble.
You have never caused trouble.
Don't lie to me.
I heard you talking to your boss earlier.
Dad also works overtime now, right?
Shella.
It's a parent's job
to take care of their child.
So, it's okay.
It's okay.
The important thing is...
you must recover, okay?
You have to.
Alright then.
You should rest.
Shella.
Shella, where's the fruit?
Coming, Dide.
Time for fruit!
Whoa!
Here's more!
Come on. Eat some fruit.
- Lidya.
- In a bit...
Do we have any guava?
Of course there is!
- We have fruits
- We're eating fruits
- What fruit?
- Dide.
What fruit?
Lidya.
Guava, guava
- Now... Dide, what about you?
- I don't want.
I don't know.
Papaya, papaya
Now we have papaya, papaya
Morning!
Babe.
You startled me.
Albi.
My chemotherapy will be over soon.
I can go for walks again. I can
play soccer again.
We can go on dates again.
Date who?
You.
Do you think I want to?
I don't want to.
- You don't want to?
- No.
Albi.
You really don't want to?
I want to get married. Let's get married.
Is this... Is this a proposal?
Where are the flowers?
What?
Why isn't anyone singing?
Yeah, flowers, singers.
Usually there's someone singing.
And... Where's the ring?
Is that what you want?
Hello.
Can you get me the flower vendor
from yesterday
and the wedding singer?
Tell them to get ready. I need...
One thousand sunflowers.
Who's the hottest singer right now?
A thousand? That's too many.
How about ten?
No!
Does it have to be with flowers?
And with a singer and a ring too?
You think if you have flowers,
a singer, and a ring,
you will be accepted?
Babe.
Babe!
No? Babe.
I'm not accepted?
Of course I do.
I only want you.
Smile.
Don't look so forced.
You won't get paid if you do that.
Hey!
Can I get a photo?
Come here.
What are you doing?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Once we're married, I really want
to have a lively home.
Lots of kids, so it's not lonely.
And we will...
The liveliest family.
And the happiest.
- What happened?
- It's okay.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Are you hungry?
- Where's the cake?
Do you know where this is from?
Shella?
Shella, what's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- It hurts.
- What hurts?
- It hurts...
- Come here.
Come here.
Yeah, Lidya? What's up?
ER
Please help my sister.
Come on.
Wait a moment.
Here.
Your hand.
Slowly.
There's a cancerous cell growth
on your ovary.
But wasn't it removed yesterday, Doc?
Yes, it was removed yesterday,
and it was clean,
but on the left side.
Now there's new cell growth
on the right side.
And judging by its characteristics,
this cancer cell is quite aggressive.
There are several spots on the ovary
and also the intestines.
Is that the image? How big is it?
The smallest diameter is three cm,
and the largest is five cm.
My suggestion is to perform surgery
to remove the ovary and uterus.
Excuse me, Doc. This...
Is there no other option besides
removing the uterus?
It seems this is the best option.
But if the uterus is removed,
she can recover, right?
We'll do our best.
Here's the surgery consent form.
If the patient and family agree,
you can sign it.
You do it, Shella.
Excuse me.
Shella, let's play.
You can play with me, okay?
Come on.
Where is everyone?
Drink some water, okay?
You need a lot of water.
I want to break up.
- Babe...
- I can't do this anymore.
Why are you suddenly saying this?
Hey.
Babe.
What's wrong?
We're fine, aren't we?
What do you mean "fine"?
Don't you see my condition?
I have cancer, Albi.
Babe.
How many people survive cancer?
Why are you talking like that?
I've had chemo many times.
I've had surgery.
And now I have to have my uterus removed.
Don't talk like that.
I'll never be the same again, Albi.
This isn't you, babe.
- You...
- There's no hope left.
- There is.
- No.
You can just go home now.
- Let's go home.
- No.
- Go home.
- Babe.
- I...
- Go home.
I just want to be with you.
- I just want to be with you.
- I don't want to be with you.
- But why?
- I don't want to be with you anymore.
- Let's go home.
- Babe, please don't be like this.
- That's enough, Albi.
- Don't be like this.
- Go home.
- No.
I'm sorry if I did anything wrong.
I just want to be with you.
- You didn't do anything wrong.
- I just want to be with you.
Why can't I...
Don't be like that.
Don't send me away like this.
I want to be with you.
You're still young.
You can find another girl.
I just want to be with you!
Marry a woman who can
give you children, Albi.
I don't want to leave!
You want to marry a future corpse?
Shella, no one knows
when we are gonna die.
None of us know
how long we'll live, Shella!
Yes, you are sick now.
But what if I die first?
I somehow died when I leave?
Go home.
Shella.
LUXE CREATION
Sir.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Where have you been?
You used the company car, didn't you?
Whose car is it?
It's yours.
Can't you use your brain?
I told you it was an important event!
You disappeared, and you're all wet too!
Yeah. I was going to...
You're from Medan.
And I helped you.
And you bit me back, you jerk.
- I'm sorry...
- Your mom needs money, right?
Right?
- Why bring my mom into this?
- It's true, isn't it?
Yes, but why bring my mom into this?
Why do you keep bringing her up?
- You bumped into me, you asshole?
- Hey!
- Don't push me!
- You bastard!
- Deri!
- You dare to push me?
- Don't talk to me like that!
- You bastard!
- Get out of here!
- What?
- You don't have to tell me, I'm leaving!
- Enough.
- Get his bag!
- You only care about your job!
- Enough.
- Albi, stop this.
- Calm down.
Albi, calm down.
- That's enough.
- Calm down.
You made me lose money.
Piece of shit!
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
It's okay. It's my fault too.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir. What is it?
Do you have any vacancies here?
Oh, I'm sorry.
All the rooms here are full.
Do you really accept male boarders?
We're full.
- Thank you, sir.
- No worries.
I'm looking for a boarding house.
Do you know any?
There's one next door.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- You're welcome.
Sir, is this a boarding house?
Yes.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
Sir.
- Yes, young man. What is it?
- Do you have any vacancies?
Yes, but the room is small.
How much is it per month?
About 1.5 million.
Peace be upon you, Mom.
Peace be upon you too, son.
Why can't I see you?
Your camera is off.
I know, Mom.
Where are you?
Why is the wall a different color?
I live at a boarding house now, Mom.
Not in the dorm anymore.
Why are you at the boarding house?
What's wrong, dear?
I've told you before,
if you have a problem, you can tell me.
You're all alone there.
And it's far from home.
But that doesn't mean
you can't talk to me.
Well, I just got the place today.
But I
can only pay for a week, Mom.
Are you not working at that EO anymore?
No, Mom.
Be strong, dear.
You'll get a new job soon, okay?
- Amen.
- I'll definitely pray for you.
- Okay?
- Thank you for your prayers, Mom.
Eat up, babe.
Still not feeling better, huh?
Did you know Albi isn't working
at that EO anymore?
I saw him delivering drinks.
When he comes here,
it'll still be on his motorcycle.
Let me take a look.
- Slowly, okay?
- Okay.
If it hurts, just...
Like that.
Not yet.
Only here?
Not this one.
See?
It doesn't hurt.
Out of so many people...
why did it have to be you?
I can't imagine if this...
happened to you...
Mom, Dad, or Dide.
Well...
Maybe you're the weakest
when seeing and feeling this condition.
So, I'm the one who...
But I still can't accept it.
Me neither.
Be strong.
Okay?
I want to be strong.
It's okay.
Come here.
Take those two dirty gallons, okay?
BABE...
ANNUAL CANCER SURVIVORS DAY EVENT
Shella?
Here.
I bought your favorite food.
Do you want me to feed you?
Alright, if you don't want to.
It's nice, isn't it,
to see rain like this?
When you were little...
when you sulked like this...
it was easy to coax you.
I just took you for a walk...
in the rain.
Tired, huh?
Let's go for a walk tomorrow.
With Dide, Mom, and the whole family.
Okay?
Where are we going?
Well, anywhere.
Dide keeps asking to go out.
He says he wants
to go out with his big sister.
ANNUAL CANCER SURVIVORS DAY EVENT
Good afternoon, ladies.
How are you all today? Stay strong, okay?
Good. Stay strong.
Welcome, all the new ladies,
to our foundation.
Let me introduce you to these children.
They are currently undergoing therapy.
These beautiful little ones, stay strong!
Undergo therapy, chemo, radiation.
We can do it!
Don't worry. We can definitely do it.
Just follow the doctor's advice.
You're pretty.
Hello.
Sit here.
Will you touch my head?
- May I?
- Of course.
Really?
Is it okay?
You're beautiful.
Your hair is beautiful too, big sister.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's your name?
Mutiara.
I'm Shella.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too, beautiful.
You're beautiful too.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Don't cry.
No, I'm not crying.
So you don't feel alone.
Besides, this is my duty.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Albi.
No need to say thank you.
Babe, no matter what your condition is...
I will keep fighting for our relationship.
I will not leave.
And you need to know...
you are not alone. I am here.
And we...
accept each other.
Accepting...
is difficult, Albi.
We'll learn to accept it together.
Are you really that fond of me?
Not fondness.
Love.
These are pretty long, isn't it?
Babe, wait a moment.
I'm going bald.
Bald.
One, two, three!
She's going bald.
I'm going bald.
I'm bald.
You're beautiful.
Still beautiful.
Mom.
Hi, babe.
I have a few things I want you to know.
I'm sorry, babe.
Your time has only been spent
through my hardships
and my pain.
I've always asked God
to let me make you happy.
But God's plan is always better.
Please don't get tired, okay?
Your legs are for...
walking with me.
Don't let your hands get tired yet...
for hugging me.
To wipe away my tears.
As for me, now...
I'll just live in the moment, Albi.
Sometimes I have plans, I have hopes...
but they don't come true.
So, why should we think about the future...
if we're not living today well?
I just want to say...
thank you very much, babe.
I love you more, period.
HOSPITAL
Mom, Dad.
In the name of God.
I am ready for the hysterectomy.
Pray for me, okay?
PATIENT SIGNATURE
You have to eat.
You have rice,
fried chicken, and tofu here.
Look, Blisky is sulking.
Someone's refusing to eat.
Let's feed her, guys.
- Here's some...
- I feel nauseous.
- Babe.
- Eat up...
Babe, come on.
- You can eat the sweets later.
- Sis!
- Hey, Dide.
- Dide, wait.
Dide!
- Don't be a nuisance.
- Hey!
Don't jump around.
How are you?
I'm okay.
Hey, why are you sulking?
Look. He's not doing his homework,
doesn't want to bathe.
And now, all he does is fight.
Hey, blame Panji.
Why Panji?
Because he mocked Shella.
He said,
"Shella is bald.
Shella is going to die soon."
Dide!
- Dide...
- Oh my.
- Oh dear.
- No.
- Hey, that...
- Don't jump around in the hospital! Dide!
- That'll hurt her!
- It's okay.
Promise not to jump around, okay?
I just want to sleep with her.
Yes, that's fine, sweetie.
It's okay.
So, have you eaten yet?
- Not yet.
- Why not?
Alright, what do you want to eat?
Chicken.
Alright. I'll go get it for him.
Two, please.
- You have to eat, okay?
- Thank you.
- Kiss Albi goodbye.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Albi.
Why me...
- You don't want to do your homework?
- Hey.
I actually have...
a gift for you.
But you have to close your eyes.
Okay.
- You have to count. One...
- Wait.
- Two...
Three!
Open.
Lidya, this is pretty!
Come here. Join us.
No!
Here, I'll put it on you.
To keep you warm.
Slowly.
- Move over!
- Slowly.
- No way.
- This is good.
- So tonight...
Ow, ow, ow.
Are you kidding?
- Let me hug my siblings.
- Come closer.
- Thank you, Lidya.
- Oh, it's getting cramped.
Ladies. Shella is not pregnant.
The neighborhood head scolded me.
He said it wasn't true.
She's not pregnant.
If she's not pregnant, then what?
She has cancer.
- God forgive me.
- What are you saying?
What do you mean?
You're making things up with him.
No way!
How can someone joke about cancer?
I know where all this news started from.
You, Ms. Nurul.
Hey, why me?
It's your noisy mouth.
All this contraception, you're the cause.
Who said "this"?
- I just saw her like that.
- Both of you.
- You made the assumption.
- But you...
When Shella bought something at your shop?
Who did this?
- You did this.
- I was just kidding.
"Three months, five months."
Who said that?
Mom, there's a letter
from the football club.
- Read this. Football club.
- From where?
How do you know?
There's a picture.
This is a marble. Not a ball.
Cancer. I won't visit her.
Oh, come on.
Dide said it was Shella who registered me.
- What are you saying?
- Yes.
INDONESIAN YOUNG STAR FOOTBALL CLUB
- So it's true.
- Yes.
Oh my God. I feel more guilty now.
Let me take a look.
A job for you.
Oh my God. Still?
No need. I can find a job myself.
Good afternoon.
Hello.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
- What are you doing?
- Hi, Shella.
I brought some fruits.
Healthy snacks for you.
To help you recover quickly.
As for me,
I just cooked some soup.
- Free-range chicken.
- Yes.
Try it later. It's really delicious.
I don't know whether
it's delicious for you or not.
Ms. Nurul made it, so it must be tasty.
Have you already said that
the soup and fruits are delicious?
- I already said it.
- We did!
Sorry for the bother.
- Not at all!
- No.
You scared me.
No problem.
Yeah, it's no trouble.
- Watch out. It's hot!
- Easy.
- What are you doing?
- It is hot.
Yes.
Please sit down, ma'am. Come in.
It's okay. I'll just stay here...
- Nanang.
- Oh my.
- Why are you just barging in?
- Hey.
Shella, I just want to...
I'm sorry...
But I want to...
I also want to thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for what?
Well, you've...
enrolled Panji in your soccer school.
Thank you so much for that.
Thank you. Why are you so kind?
Even though you're often
talked about by her.
I don't want to be friends with you.
- There's still room. Excuse me.
- Yes, sit down.
Move it, Nanang!
- What's wrong with you?
- Try the soup, Shella.
Get well soon.
Her cancer cells keep growing.
They keep enlarging and spreading,
thus pressing on her spine and nerves.
This damage...
is causing weakness in both her legs.
My advice is, we must
perform surgery immediately.
Because if not, the damage will continue.
And at its worst,
it could lead to paralysis.
So, she needs another surgery?
Yes.
I'll excuse myself now.
Ma'am, sir.
Do you feel comfortable?
Why is it affecting her nerves again?
What is it?
- What kind of surgery?
- It spread.
It's so frustrating.
Honey, just let it go.
Doc!
Sorry, Doc.
I just have one question, Doc.
When will my daughter recover, Doc?
Every time we come to the hospital,
we're told she's sick again.
She was sick yesterday, right?
Then after the removal, it was clean.
Right? Now she's sick again.
Even her uterus was removed.
And now it's affecting her spinal nerves.
Relax. I have only one question.
When will my daughter recover?
That's all. I just want to hear it, Doc.
- That's all.
- Sir.
This surgery must be done immediately.
Because it's an emergency.
Just a moment. I'll be back.
Yes.
What's the emergency?
- What?
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm not finished yet.
- Honey!
Shella is sick!
Enough!
Do you want your daughter to recover?
Do you want it or not?
I want her to recover!
Shella is sick.
How can she recover?
By getting treated!
Yeah, but until when?
I don't know!
No one knows!
Until Shella recovers. She must recover!
I understand that.
Let her go through everything.
I can't bear to see her like that.
It's okay. Be patient.
Shella will definitely recover.
Honey.
She will recover.
There, there.
Hello.
I'm not Albi.
How are you?
How is your condition today?
Uncle, I'll take my leave.
Alright.
Bye.
- Thanks, Albi.
- Yes.
It hurts a little.
A little?
A little.
Is it?
You are tired, right?
No.
Not at all.
Liar.
Get well soon
Get well now
Now get well soon
Let me face that way, Dad.
It hurts.
Slowly.
I must recover
Now I must recover
Already recovered
Already recovered now
Wait here, okay?
- Bye.
Stay strong, Shella.
Albi.
Mom.
Hey, son.
I want to...
I want to be at Shella's side, Mom.
I want to marry Shella.
I love her.
You know...
taking care of a sick person...
is not easy, son.
I know.
But I am so proud of you.
If this is truly the best...
and you are capable
of taking responsibility...
then I give you my blessing.
Seriously, Mom?
Thank you, Mom.
Babe.
Shella.
Uncle.
Auntie.
If I may...
and if I have your permission...
I want to marry Shella.
Babe.
This is the first decision
I've made with certainty.
I want to marry you.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
I will.
- Hold it there.
- Okay.
Hold it.
Are you done, Lidya?
Almost.
I hereby marry and wed
Ananda Albi Dwizky
to our beloved daughter,
Shella Selpi Lizah,
with a dowry of two grams of gold
and a set of prayer tools
paid in cash.
I accept the marriage
of Shella Selpi Lizah,
daughter of Didin Jaenudin, with
the aforementioned dowry paid in cash.
While everyone is still gathered,
I'd like to know your thoughts about me.
Before I leave.
Shella, please don't talk like that.
Okay?
Anyone want to start first?
My sister runs really fast.
If she chases me,
she'll definitely catch me.
My sister is chatty.
She usually won't allow me
to play outside.
But...
now she's just quiet.
She used to often invite me...
to make videos.
But now...
we never do that.
Please don't change
when you're there, okay?
I still love you, Shella.
I also love you very much.
Don't forget about me, okay?
Lidya.
What should I say?
What's certain is that I...
love you very much.
Let's stay together until we're old.
It's okay. You have your life...
and I have mine.
We don't have to be together.
But you must remain my sister.
I don't know what I'll do
if I don't have a big sister anymore.
Just a moment, okay?
I have to go to the back.
I am so happy to finally meet you, Shella.
I always prayed...
that Albi...
would be given a beautiful wife...
who is kind and smart
and funny.
Albi said...
it's someone like me, right, Albi?
And God answered my prayers.
Now Albi's wife is truly
beautiful and kind.
Smart.
I love you very much.
I'm so proud of you.
You are a strong daughter.
A wonderful daughter.
Mom's favorite.
Albi.
My dear.
I...
I'm not good with words.
Just a little, my love.
I just want you to know...
I'm so grateful...
to be your husband...
until the end of my life.
Albi...
- Please don't cry.
- You too.
Honey.
But looking back,
it's quite funny, isn't it?
We met because of a soccer ball.
Yes, love.
I felt so refreshed
when I got hit by your ball back then.
Honey, if only on that day
I hadn't met you,
we wouldn't be here now.
Yes.
I wouldn't have known Albi Dwizky.
I also wouldn't have known
Shella Selpi Lizah.
So, thank you, my love.
I got to know a new family.
A warm family.
There's Mom,
Dad, Lidya,
Dide.
Let's gather once again.
Complete
with everyone.
Shella!
Shella, come on!
Oh no, Dide.
Come on. Let's race!
- Yeah, Albi, come on!
- No.
- You can go without us.
- Don't be such a wimp!
- I know.
- You're a wimp!
- Shella wants to come.
- See!
- Who's the wimp, you say?
- Come on, Albi.
Come on!
You're actually scared
of Nanang Racing, aren't you?
- Yeah!
- Why would we be scared?
We'll just let them win, Dide.
- You go first.
- No need. This is Shella Racing.
Alright, one, two, three!
Babe!
Babe?
Babe? Please!
Babe!
Dide!
AMBULANCE
Babe.
Hey, it's me.
It's me.
Slowly. It hurts.
Slowly.
Yeah.
Why did you put it off?
I said to God...
I give up.
I can't do it anymore.
There's just too many difficulties ahead.
My energy is all gone.
My whole body hurts.
Don't say that.
Shella.
Mom and Dad are here.
Why did you put this off?
- Shella.
- Your big brother is here.
- I...
I'm sincere...
Shella!
Shella?
No! Shella!
No, babe...
Shella!
There's actually so much
I wanted to tell you.
But it turns out...
Allah loves you more, Shella.
You should know...
my feet never got tired
of living life with you.
My hands never got tired
of holding onto you.
Holding hands with you...
And...
I'm happy.
I'm happy because you allowed me
to keep accompanying you.
Until we meet in Allah's heaven, my wife.
BORN: 04-04-200
DEAD: 29-08-2024
Thank you, my love.
Thank you so much for everything.
I love you.
Thank you for holding on...
until the very end.
SHELLA SELPI LIZAH PASSED AWAY 16 DAYS
AFTER HER MARRIAGE TO ALBI DWIZKY
THANKS, MY LOVE
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR EVERYTHING
I LOVE YOU! THANK YOU FOR HOLDING ON
UNTIL YOUR VERY LAST MOMENT
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN
IN ALLAH'S HEAVEN, MY WIFE
SHELLA'S ABDOMEN HAD SWOLLEN
BECAUSE THE CYST IN HER OVARY
HAD GROWN LARGER
OVER THE COURSE OF SIX MONTHS
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, BABE
‎BORN: 04-04-2000
‎DEAD: 29-08-2024