Do you know...
why dusk is so easy to love?
Sometimes it's red, blushing happily.
Sometimes it's black, dark and somber.
But the sky...
always accepts dusk as what it is.
See you.
Whether this world deserve us?
Do we pretend not to know,
or not really think about it?
Shy.
Hiding in the shadows,
lying the biggest lie that
we are the highest beings in all of creation.
Oh...
you're practising.
Yes, I have an audition.
Next week.
What if I told you...
Okay, tell me...
No, it's my monologue.
You don't have to answer.
What if I told you...
Why are you looking at me?
I need connection!
Man!
What if I told you...
Karlo, listen to me.
I'm thinking...
my next exhibition must be more explorative.
So, I need more time.
This is the material,
I'll send you the concept soon.
Okay?
No, no, no...
Please,
don't talk about climate change!
What are you?
A 13-year-old Scandinavian girl?
What's next? Pandas or kittens?
Trust me, Karlo.
No, you trust me!
They want something rare and unique.
This is rare.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
It's your birthday?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
So, that's the reason?
That's the reason with all this?
Cheers.
Yes, cheers.
Who knows? Maybe David likes pandas.
It's a polar bear.
No, this is an albino panda.
This is an all white...
See you soon...
See you soon, Karlo.
Hi.
Who are you?
I'm Sore.
Your wife from the future.
Karlo, what are you playing at?
Listen, I'm in the middle of rehearsal right now...
Are you crying?
No. What's up?
I told you,
I hate these so-called jokes.
How many times do I have to...
Hey! What...
What do you mean? What joke?
You think it's funny
to put a girl in my bed?
Or what?
You think I'll like it
because she's Indonesian?
I don't have time for this, Karlo!
Come on!
Jonathan...
What are you talking about?
She has nothing to do with me.
Look, I'm preparing for the casting...
also trying to think of a good reason for David...
to agree with your climate change idea.
I don't have time for this, either.
Are you crying?
No!
Stop this game right now!
It's not funny!
I hate people coming to my house.
What game? Are you drunk?
No, you're the drunk one.
You're so drunk you're crying!
No!
Yes, you are!
Tell her to leave,
and stop crying like a little baby!
I'm not crying.
Crying like a little baby,
that's a good idea.
Thank you.
Let's try again. Okay.
How much did Karlo pay you?
I'll double it.
Get out!
Okay.
Hey.
Don't forget your wallet and phone.
Be careful, don't walk too fast.
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
Sorry.
No problem.
Sorry, I'm late.
Are you okay?
Just great.
Karlo sent a girl to my house.
Like, right into my house.
Why would he do that?
His idea of a joke, I guess.
What did I tell you?
You need a new agent, a professional one.
I have nothing against Karlo personally...
Elsa.
Okay, look, Jo.
Last night I spoke to my dad.
And he agreed to help us out.
He wants to open a restaurant for me.
And you can come along with me.
He'll introduce you to his friends.
So, what do you think?
Oh...
You don't like it, do you?
So what exactly is your plan?
A solo exhibition?
Yeah.
Come on, Jo. You know it.
Don't treat me like your mother,
I'm your girlfriend.
So, act like a grown man.
Do you think I like to keep asking you like this?
Then, stop asking.
Hi, Elsa.
I'm Sore.
Jonathan's wife.
Wife?
She's your wife?
No!
Please, leave now!
Don't trust her.
But I'm hungry.
You can eat somewhere else.
I want to eat here.
Here.
I'm paying you now.
Please leave.
I don't need your money.
I just want to eat.
Then find another table.
I want to eat here with you.
Am I not allowed?
No. I'm having a conversation!
I'm asking you to leave now.
Jo.
Wait.
Why bother talking to Elsa?
You'll break up soon.
You don't want to go
with her to Madrid, right?
Work for his father...
Letting her boss you around...
Am I right?
Just tell her.
It'll be okay.
Yes,
He told me everything.
Sorry, he must've told you he's single.
Right?
We got married in Indonesia, and it's not the first time
he gets involved with a woman like you.
Well, as a wife,
I am expected to have patience.
Right?
Elsa, believe me.
He'll ask you to look him in the eye
so that you'll believe him.
He'll also blame Karlo.
Elsa...
Yes, he always says that when he's lying.
You'll get used to it.
Elsa.
Let her go.
Sorry.
Sorry!
Come on, you'll trip.
Sorry...
Stop!
Enough!
Go, or I'll call the police.
Hi.
What do you want?
Hello, Jo.
For two, please.
Go ahead.
Hi...
Excuse me?
Enjoy.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's your name?
Sore.
Okay, Sore.
After this, we are done.
Tell Karlo this is not funny anymore.
Karlo has no idea.
Ask me.
Anything.
About you.
Karlo, we need to talk.
She knows everything about me.
Who?
Stop!
Sore.
It's fine.
Sore!
No problem.
Her name is Sore.
Oh...
Guys, take five!
Come.
The girl I was upset about yesterday,
she claims she's from the future!
From the future?
She says she's my wife!
And she knows everything about me.
Every little detail of my life.
- What's my mother's name?
- Maya Wiryawan.
Born and raised in Surabaya.
She's one of 12 kids.
She's the second youngest child.
- My elder sibling?
- Sindy?
She's fine.
She should be busy
preparing her wedding now.
Three years from now,
when she gets married,
you'll go home, okay?
That's where you'll meet me.
My younger sibling?
You don't have any.
What else?
Your first girlfriend?
She has nothing to do with you?
No...
Really, I...
would be proud if I'd come up with the joke,
but...
I didn't.
Should we call someone?
Hi.
You're home.
I made you yellow broth chicken soup.
Your favorite.
I used local prawn crackers
for the savory powder, so...
Okay.
Let's say I believe you're from the future.
What do you want?
I want to make your life better.
My life is fine.
Come.
You'll see David tomorrow, right?
Don't show him the Arctic pictures.
He doesn't feel...
Sore, no.
That's the roll from Ladakh, right?
This one. Roll 14, frame 20...
Sorry.
Frame 29.
You said frame 28 is out of focus.
No one knows I took pictures there.
I do.
David will love the pictures of the lady
you met at the temple's door.
I know it sounds crazy.
But if you just have a little more patience,
you'll believe
that I really am from the future.
Wow.
This is fantastic.
I like it very much.
Really?
Very much.
Let's do it!
Thank you.
It has great potential...
Cheers.
Now do you believe
I can make your life better?
From now on,
do whatever I tell you, okay?
Okay.
Promise?
Promise.
Whatever?
Yes.
Okay.
Good morning.
Hi.
What do you want?
Anything.
Seriously?
Thank you.
Let's exercise.
Come on!
Oh God.
Almost there! Look! Come on!
Come on, almost there.
Come on, a little further.
Easy for you to say.
I'm literally carrying you!
Not far, I can see it.
Come on.
Oh God!
Why on Earth did I marry you?
When you grow to like me,
you'll be sorry.
Does this suit me?
Yes.
Okay.
Oh my goodness!
So sorry...
I didn't listen to Elsa's recommendation.
I spoke to an agent in Spain.
I told him I'm trying to make an exhibition in Madrid.
Great!
Do you have any other photos
you think might be interesting?
The Arctic.
I recently just came back from the Arctic.
Is it about climate change?
No. In a way...
Do they always have to talk about that?
No, not that.
It's more complex than you think.
But I'm curious to see from your perspective.
If it's more like this,
show it to me first.
No pressure.
It's always the same topic...
Not this time.
Sorry, I answered right away.
It's okay.
What's this?
Don't open it.
Huh?
Your correspondence with Elsa?
Don't open it.
- What is it?
- Don't open it!
Don't!
Jo! Cut it out!
- Don't open it!
- Jo! Stop it!
Jo! Enough!
- Give it back!
- Jo! Stop it!
Jo! Stop!
- Give it back!
- I'll give it back!
I won't stop
until you give it back!
Jo! Okay, I'll give it back!
You can have it!
Jo...
Our first time...
was after we got married.
You said
you'd protect me
even from yourself.
I said that?
Yes.
Actually, I asked you to.
I once told you.
I only want to have one relationship in my life.
If possible.
And suddenly you promised...
to protect me.
Eh...
But
come to think of it,
I'm already your wife.
But you're not my husband yet.
What are your thoughts
on this?
Nothing.
Nevermind.
What am I sitting on?
My book.
Your book?
- Want me to tickle you again?
- No!
I gave it back.
What are you reading?
"Climate: Change for the Life".
Read it to me.
Hold on.
- Keep your eyes closed.
- Okay.
Can I open them now?
Yes.
In the future...
is Madrid exhibition a success?
I feel like something's missing.
I think...
it'll work.
I know what's missing.
What?
Where are we going?
Why don't you just tell me?
Say something. Jo!
Where are we going?
What if we drink
from an upside down thermos?
What would happen?
I didn't notice.
Jo!
Come eat!
In a minute.
You have to eat.
One more picture.
You haven't eaten anything all day.
Wait. Can you stand right over there?
- Me?
- Yes.
Just one picture.
One, and then we eat.
- Yes, stand over there...
- Promise?
- Just one?
- Just one!
Here?
Now, turn to your left.
Like this?
- Lose the ladle.
- You said one picture.
Yes, but the ladle is distracting.
- Toss it over here.
- I toss, you catch, okay?
Yes, toss it here.
- Okay.
- You said you'd catch.
No, I didn't.
Smile.
Okay, one, two...
Can we eat now?
I'm still thinking about today's sunset.
Will David like it?
Jo...
Go to sleep.
Are you still thinking about it?
Throw it away.
- Just this one.
- I said, throw it away.
- It's been two days. I said...
- Just this one, and that's it.
I can't quit just like that.
- Changing a habit takes time.
- That's not true.
Slowly, you said?
I tried it, and I failed.
Every time I let you have that one time,
you get further away from quitting,
getting more stubborn!
Let's start over.
- It's just this one time.
- No.
It's fine.
We'll start over.
This is not the first time.
It's fine.
Okay?
Eight years from now...
you'll be dead.
A heart attack.
Sore. Your nose...
Sore.
Sore!
Sore! Hey!
Sore, what's happening?
Sore!
If I have to live ten thousand times,
I hope I'll always choose you.
Who are you?
I...
I'm Sore.
Your wife from the future.
You think I'll like it
because she's Indonesian?
I don't have time for this, Karlo.
Come on!
How much did Karlo pay you?
I'll double it.
Get out!
Okay.
Hey.
Don't forget your wallet and phone.
Be careful, you'll...
Sorry.
Hi, Elsa.
I'm Sore, Jonathan's wife.
Let her go.
Come on, you'll trip.
Stop!
Enough! Go, or I'll call the police.
What do you want?
Actually, he can't drink beer.
Can you help me out?
You had your first cigarette in first grade,
in the school's bathroom at recess.
Let's say I believe you're from the future,
what do you want?
I want to make your life better.
My life is fine.
From now on,
do whatever I tell you, okay?
Promise?
Why on Earth did I marry you?
When you grow to like me,
you'll be sorry.
Enough with today's work.
Go to sleep.
I can't sleep before I finish.
Sore!
If you want to die first,
fine, stop listening to me!
Sore! Hey!
Did you forget your promise?
Let's start over.
Just one...
Sore!
Why is it so hard to listen to me?
I told you!
No one orders me around,
not even my wife!
Sore!
My negatives are ruined!
I said, go to sleep!
I'm Sore.
Your wife
from the future.
Are you enjoying it?
Is it worth it?
- Changing a habit takes time...
- Yes.
If you don't want to change,
okay.
It's fine.
I will stay out of your life
I'm just asking one thing from you.
Don't come anywhere near me.
Don't introduce yourself to me
at Sindy's wedding.
Don't ever come into my life,
and make me have feelings for you,
only to watch you die first
and leave me behind!
I was wrong.
I should've accepted that
people don't change.
You speak fluent Croatian,
how long did it take you to learn?
Maybe hundreds of years...
How old are you now?
How old?
A hundred something?
I forgot.
Really?
No wonder you're fluent.
If I have to live ten thousand times,
I hope I'll always choose you.
Meaning?
Good night.
Hello.
Want to try something with truffle?
I sell truffle products.
No...
I'm looking for a job.
Sorry.
We have no vacancy.
Sorry, but we're not hiring.
But I will work hard,
just pay me what you can.
Sorry, I really can't help you.
So sorry.
It's all right.
Listen, I understand.
I like you,
but I can't give you a job.
It's all right.
Thank you.
Wait.
You said you're a fashion designer?
Yes.
My friend owns a bridal shop in Zagreb.
Maybe he needs an intern.
I'm going to Zagreb today.
You can come with me, if you want.
Hello!
Marko!
Wait here.
Come on, that's enough.
I told you
not to listen to your friend's recommendation.
He was a know-it-all.
Look at you now. See?
You look like a lamp. Everything is tilted.
We shouldn't have listened to him.
Hey, you!
Where's Marko?
I...
I want our money back.
This unacceptable
and unprofessional.
Come on, Mom. Calm down.
You want to see?
Come, see for yourself.
Look at your boss' work.
Now I have to find another designer.
Because everything is asymmetrical.
The fabric is hanging on this side.
Go take a look!
Sorry, can you stand straight?
Okay.
Now stand on your toes.
You have to wear high heels
with this dress.
When you sleep,
which side do you sleep on?
Your left side?
How did you know?
There's nothing wrong with the dress.
If you're not comfortable,
we can adjust on this side.
But you are beautiful already.
Is that her?
Yes.
Okay, she's very good.
Listen, I will deduct your rent
from your salary.
Are you okay with it?
Sure. No problem.
Sorry, the place is a mess.
It's fine.
Where's your stuff?
Uhm...
You're such a mess.
Don't laugh.
Your love is stupid.
Thank you.
Hello, Marko.
Hi, Sore.
Coffee?
Thanks, darling.
Marko!
Hi, Elsa!
I opened the door the wrong way.
Hi, darling. You look beautiful.
And you look great, as usual.
By the way,
I loved the dress I wore.
It looked amazing in the pictures.
I'll send them to you.
But I'm here today...
because I'm getting married.
This is Jonathan.
Hi, I'm Jonathan.
Marko...
He'll have his suit tailored here.
I'm looking for a wedding dress.
I have to do measurements.
Yes.
Sore!
Yes?
Do his measurements.
Sorry, please stand here.
Sorry.
Listen.
I've seen it many times.
A young woman like you
wouldn't survive this period.
Period?
The broken heart period.
It's not that, Marko...
Sore, there are three things  you can't change
in this life.
The past, pain, and death.
I just want my employee to focus, okay?
You'd better turn a new leaf.
Move on!
No excuse for this childish behavior.
Grow up!
Do you want this or not?
Listen, I'm tired.
What do you want?
You want to act like this forever?
Listen, I'm tired of acting like your mom.
Telling what you have to do every time.
Send your freakin' mail.
Your dad lives just a couple of kilometers from here.
You don't even have the courage
to meet him!
And...
don't act like a victim.
You're mad at your dad,
but you blame it on me.
I'm tired.
Okay, Jo.
You know what...
it's up to you.
I give up.
Bye.
Bye, Elsa. Let me know.
Marko?
Yes?
You said the past, pain, and death...
can't be changed, right?
Yes, that's what I said.
So, you believe people can change?
Of course people can change.
But,
the change must come from within.
Some people have trouble making peace
with their pain and trauma.
But they can change.
Wait, Sore...
Is it him?
Thank you for everything, Marko.
- I'M IN ZAGREB.
- JO
IF I COULD TURN BACK TIME,
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE MET MOM. - JO
- IT'S MY BIRTHDAY, REMEMBER?
- JO
- ARE YOU HAPPIER NOW, DAD?
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DAD.
- JO
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU STILL CARE,
BUT I SHOULDN'T BE HERE. - JO
Why haven't I opened this?
Jo! Wait, listen to me.
I'm Sore, your wife from the future.
Karlo didn't send me.
In the dark room, second drawer
from the bottom right...
roll number 14, frame number 29.
You took pictures of the lady in Ladakh,
no one knew you took pictures there,
but I do.
Let's go see your dad.
You've been writing these
for a long time, right?
Jo!
- Jo!
- Hey!
Listen to me.
Calm down, listen to me.
I know you've been writing these
for a long time. Right?
Now think it through.
What if you go back home,
without ever seeing your dad...
You'll be sorry, right?
You'll regret it.
So, you'd better come with me.
We'll...
We'll contact you.
Must I start over?
Who are you?
Maybe start from there?
Okay.
One at a time.
From the start.
Hey!
Do you hear me?
Hi.
Sorry...
You're always uncomfortable
talking about your dad.
You always avoid it.
Hi, you're home.
I want to make your life better.
Whatever?
Don't open it!
- I see.
- Give it back!
- Don't open it!
- Jo!
I'm still thinking about today's sunset.
Come eat.
Hey.
We're going to Zagreb tomorrow.
To see your dad.
So you won't regret anything.
No regrets.
Yo've been living here because
your dad lives in Zagreb, right?
You'll never understand.
Then, let's talk about it.
Let's talk.
If we don't talk about it,
how can I understand?
- Nothing to talk about.
- You want to see your dad, not me.
If not, why have you been living in Croatia?
Whether you want to stay angry
or forgive him,
it's your choice.
He chose someone else.
I was four.
My sister Sindy was six.
He married another woman,
abandoning us, can one forgive that?
Now you ask me to choose?
What kind of person left his wife
and kids for his own pleasure?
Huh?
What kind of person?
A person like you.
You're just like your dad.
You die, leaving me behind,
just for things you like to do.
How are you different from him?
How long will you stay angry?
Sore!
If it has to be that way,
let my failure in life...
balances...
my success...
in another version.
There's no such things as parallel lives.
Parallel worlds are just
manifestations of human arrogance.
How arrogant we are,
when we think we can conquer time.
Do we think that by time travelling
and making different choices,
the parallel life will exist?
We know nothing about time.
What is it?
Who are you?
Hi, Karlo.
I'm Sore.
Jonathan's wife.
I come from the future.
Elsa has asked him many times
to see his dad.
But you have to know...
I think Elsa is trying
to control Jonathan.
She meddles in his work.
Even I, as his agent...
respect his choices.
I mean, what do you expect?
He's a man with many scars.
I don't know
if Elsa loves him...
or she's just obsessed to change him.
That's why Jo never changes...
I'm just replacing Elsa,
controlling his life.
Sorry?
Nevermind.
Listen, no one understands him better than you.
You're his wife.
Thank you.
Hey, can I borrow your time machine
for a short time?
I don't have a Time Machine.
I'm sorry.
For forcing you to exercise.
What other plans do you have?
No plans.
Besides, all my plans have failed.
I can't make your life better.
Only you can do it.
But...
I would be so happy
if I could just be there with you.
If you'd let me.
You were once
so angry with me.
Because I forced you to see your dad.
I'm sorry.
Did I tell you about him?
Remember, I'm from the future.
But because you were angry,
I got to understand
your feelings.
You said...
You feel your dad chose
someone else over you.
But you don't choose yourself, either.
You must be so miserable.
For years...
you chose to imprison
your dad in his mistakes,
rather than setting yourself free.
Okay?
Whenever you're ready,
I'm here.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Is our marriage a happy one?
You are so nice to me.
Actually, we fight quite a lot.
Really?
No marriage is perfect.
Each time we stop fighting...
I can question again
why...
I married you.
But I always remember
how every time we stop fighting
and we calm down,
we will care
about each other's feelings.
Who's right or wrong,
we talk about it later.
What's important is...
we try to understand
our feelings.
So, every time I regret
marrying you...
at the end of the day, I always think...
it looks like
even if I get to start over
hundreds of times...
I will always choose you.
You love me that much?
You said it!
- Did I?
- Yes!
I said that?
Do you know
why dusk is so easy to love?
Sometimes it's red, blushing happily...
Sometimes it's black, dark and somber...
But the sky...
always accepts dusk as what it is.
Did I say that, too?
Can I even say such sweet words?
You don't believe me?
Why not?
Really, those are your words.
Oh gosh.
For every sweet word
you used to utter to me
For every gaze you gave me
For every smile you gifted me
thank you!
So little goodness in this life
When the sun shines
Clouds will always follow
But you gave me so much...
We're almost there, right?
sunlight in my life
Sore.
Your nose...
What's happening?
Sore...
Sore!
What's wrong?
Why is it restarting?
I haven't said anything.
Who are you?
Whenever you're ready...
I'm here.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Even if I get to start over hundreds
of times, I'll always choose you.
The night falls early.
The sun is having
an unusually busy week.
These enhanced pictures from...
NASA's Solar Dynamics Observatory
show exactly what's going on.
You can see here on the left,
an explosion of radioactive material
on a scale never seen before.
A gigantic solar flare.
Over the last few days,
there have been more than...
half a dozen similar eruptions.
And look at this image,
super heated energy particles...
Sore.
streaming towards the earth...
at around 800 km per second.
Now you may be able to see for yourself
when this solar wind hits earth.
Beginning 10 May,
Aurora will be visible in North America,
Portugal, Spain, Croatia and some countries in Asia.
He...
He is mad.
Who?
Hey! Sore!
TIME
Is it still far?
Why are you rushing?
Sore!
Whenever you're ready...
I'm here.
Even if I get to start over
hundreds of times,
I'll always choose you.
Sore!
I'm Sore.
Your wife from the future.
I can't, Jo.
Sore!
I can't...
Promise?
Why is it night already?
Jo.
Don't let me fade away with time, okay?
Huh?
Don't forget me.
Promise?
Who are you?
Hi.
I'm Sore.
Your wife...
forever.
Hello.
Jo...
What did you do in the Arctic?
Just the usual.
You've changed.
You're more calm.
And...
I don't know, I just feel that way.
Okay.
So, last night I spoke to Dad.
And he agreed to help us out.
He wants to open a restaurant for me.
And you can come along with me there.
Whether this world deserves us.
Or we pretend...
not to know,
or never really think about it?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I just broke up with Elsa.
Okay.
I don't think it's going to work.
I know that, but why now?
What's happening?
I don't know.
I just feel...
How do I say it?
Longing?
I don't know who or what, but...
When I woke up...
it felt like...
a tremendous feeling of longing.
Longing's good.
Do you know
why dusk is so easy to love?
Sometimes it's red, blushing happily...
Sometimes it's black, dark and somber...
But the sky...
always accepts dusk as what it is.
Yes?
Is this Seno's house?
Yes.
I'm from Indonesia, and...
Oh...
Do you want to come in?
Yes...
Wait here, I will call my husband.
Nothing can justify what you did.
But thank you for the best four years
you've given me.
- I forgive you.
- Jo
Honey?
Yes?
Are you okay?
So, you quit smoking and drinking
at the same time?
That's not healthy, man.
I'm going to miss this.
Come to Indonesia.
Since when do you exercise?
Starting slowly, Mom.
So, why did you come home?
I don't know.
This photo is weird, no?
Is it?
You feel that way, too?
The exhibition is about the Arctic.
Meaning, climate change.
Usually we want...
the atmosphere to stay cold,
like...
we don't want the ice to melt.
But this...
The image of the sunset
in the middle, it feels so...
How do I say it?
Warm?
I don't know, I have mixed feelings.
Or maybe...
this is just an act to look cool?
Excuse me.
I think climate change is not
just about melting ice in the Arctic.
It's not just life that we're going to lose.
But also beauty.
I don't think people will
change out of fear.
But because they feel loved.
This is what I felt...
when I saw the Aurora.
So, I want to share it.
Are you the photographer?
Oh my...
I'm sorry.
- I didn't know.
- It's okay.
You can turn the lights back on.
I'm so sorry, once again...
I didn't mean...
Really, it's fine.
I'm grateful, actually.
I'm so happy
you observe my photos, one by one...
with such seriousness.
Jonathan.
Sore.
THE ARCTIC, 2023
THE ONLY PART OF THE EARTH
WITH NO TIME ZONE
Who are you?
Hey!
I thought you were gone.
I was at your funeral.
I thought you were dead.
Hey!
Who are you?
Sore!
Don't let me fade away with time.
Don't forget me.