Fm Movie
Vegetables!
- That's the boy!
- Vegetables. Sambal.
- Watch it!
- Vegetables.
Fresh vegetables.
Ma'am.
- Would you like some, ma'am?
- Ma'am, chicken.
This bird is 300.
Can't go lower?
It's 300.
- Come on.
- Not yet.
Three hundred isn't enough.
Hey!
Yeah. Nowadays, my husband…
Why has he changed now?
He used to be content with my veggie soup.
Hey, don't you know?
The medicine is very effective.
- Really?
- Of course.
Ma'am, is there one that charms my husband
and makes him loyal?
Make my husband enjoy being at home.
One to make mine smell good and tight.
- Calm down.
- Ma'am, I want to get prettier.
Yeah, so it's tight.
So it smells good.
It's been a long time
since anyone has asked for this far.
Lintrik is an ancient Javanese love charm.
Sacred.
The greater the influence,
the greater the risk.
Many of them end up backing down.
Whatever the cost and risk, I am willing.
This man…
His heart is no longer yours.
I want him home immediately.
But this is expensive.
Kirto.
I'll send
his biggest fear.
Ma'am.
Let me use your power, ma'am.
Where's his underwear?
Here you go, ma'am.
My intention is to draw a card.
Sixty-card deck made
by the Chinese Emperor.
I beg for your help.
Don't you ever dare to fail me.
Let him submit,
full of desire, full of love.
Confuse him, make him go crazy about me.
Bring him to my kingdom.
Succeed and you'll be my master.
Fail and I'll burn you.
Brothers of the four corners,
I beg for your help.
Don't you ever dare to fail me.
So that Ario submits.
My wife is not only beautiful,
but also a home.
Honey, I haven't brushed my teeth yet.
I'm worried, you know.
I'm sorry.
I came home too late.
The bus broke down.
Honey, I'm smelly.
I like your smell.
Okay, let's just take a shower together.
Honey.
Wow, my favorite food.
Yes, I brought it last night
from the eatery.
Here you go.
My favorite.
Thanks, honey.
Of course.
This is too much for breakfast.
I miss the food that made me
fall in love with you.
So cheesy.
Let me try some.
Okay.
The taste hasn't changed.
So good.
Can't you take a day off today?
You also have to open the eatery.
Lilin and Yanto are there.
I can take a day off.
What if the eatery can't pay its debt?
I'll get the penalty.
Your eatery is closed. What would you do?
True, we can have time for ourselves.
But we'll be poor. Would you like that?
Okay.
Honey, when will you
take me to meet your parents?
I've been saving up
to bring gifts for my in-laws.
Relax. I will take you to them later.
Ma'am, your hat fell off.
Wait a minute, honey.
Here you go, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Be careful, honey.
Thank you for making me delicious food.
Your boss hasn't arrived yet?
Not yet, Miss Mara.
Yanto, my name is Amara, not Mara.
People will think I'm always angry.
It's okay. You still look beautiful
even when you're angry.
- Uncle.
- Hey, don't run around.
- Okay.
Here's your coffee, Uncle.
This is what I've been waiting for.
- Good day, Uncle.
- Good day.
Come on, Yan. Be real.
There's no way
Miss Mara will ever like you.
You are half human.
What do you mean? I'm a genuine guy.
Of course.
Half human.
Your name is Yanto Kates.
Half human, half fruit.
You insolent shorty!
Skinny!
Your face looks like a goat.
Do you want to go first?
There they are, Uncle.
Amara, why are you still here?
Shouldn't you be in class?
I am, Andin. I want to say goodbye first.
Besides, I'll never be late.
Study well so you graduate quickly.
- Yes.
- Fine then.
- Andin.
- Uncle.
Uncle.
- I'm off, Andin, Ario.
- Okay.
It's nice to look at Miss Mara.
Don't look at this one.
- I don't want to either.
- Uncle.
Amara.
Okay.
Ready?
Ready.
- Bye.
Sorry, honey.
I'm used to it.
What more do I need to explain?
My parents are old.
They have no money. That's why
they couldn't come to our wedding.
Yes. I understand, honey.
But it takes time
to make my uncle understand.
It's been six months.
Since the beginning of our marriage.
It's okay. I'm off to the office, okay?
Okay, honey.
I'll let you know when I've arrived.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Be careful, honey.
- All right.
Mrs. Andin.
AVAILABLE
Lin, To.
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am.
So comfy, To.
- He doesn't work at all, ma'am.
- No, I'm wiping this, ma'am.
- Nonsense. You're just sleeping around.
- This bottle.
Could you get a plate, please?
- Which one for table 6, ma'am?
- This one.
To, don't mess it up.
Iced degan, not iced dawet.
If he messes up, cut his salary, ma'am.
Table 8 is ready. You can take it out. To.
- This place is new.
- But it's packed, ma'am.
I heard this place is good.
Yeah, it's tasty.
Your goat head dish tastes really good.
Thank you, sir. Please enjoy.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you, ma'am.
You're welcome.
Yes.
Let's try it. Try it first.
What's wrong with this kid?
He's been like this since yesterday.
What's wrong?
Quit playing with your phone.
That's enough.
Let's eat.
Put the phone down. Continue later.
If he doesn't want it,
let's just eat it.
I ordered it anyway.
- It's delicious.
- Yes, delicious.
- It is.
What's wrong, kid?
- There's a goat!
- Of course there is. That's what we sell.
Are you expecting a lizard?
Move over. Let me take a look.
Come and see.
It's goat, right?
See. They're goats.
Honey.
What's wrong? It's me.
What's wrong?
Am I home too late?
You forgot to turn off the stove.
Why are you seldom home?
I want to spend more time with you.
That's the risk
of having a husband with a mobile job.
Honey.
You won't leave me, right?
You're not alone.
And I'm not going anywhere.
I don't know how
my life would be without you.
WHEN WILL YOU COME?
HOW MUCH LONGER DO YOU NEED TO GO?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Anything else you want me to do?
That's all.
All right. I'm taking my leave to go home.
Okay.
Thanks, ma'am.
Hello.
Yes, what's up?
What's wrong? Calling at this hour?
You…
When you're there,
you always seem to forget me.
I work all day.
I'm tired.
There's someone here who needs you, Ario.
I had already dozed off when you called.
All right then.
I'll call you again tomorrow.
Why are you awake?
I want to get a drink.
With a jar?
Who called earlier, honey?
Mr. Nawir.
This late?
That's how he is.
Okay, let's go back to sleep.
Are you thirsty?
Want me to get you something to drink?
I'm no longer thirsty.
You must be sleepy.
You sound confused.
Come on, let's go back to sleep.
Tomorrow, I have to go to Semarang.
Another work trip already? So soon.
That's the job.
Do you want to be poor?
CASH OFFICE, SUGIH WARAS
Mr. Nawir.
Hi, Andin.
You're here early. That's surprising.
Usually, you're late.
What a coincidence.
Snacks for the road.
- For the road?
- Semarang.
Meeting.
Semarang.
- Semarang.
- He's forgetful.
Oh, a meeting with Mr. Artadana.
- Meeting or seminar?
- Meeting to prepare seminars.
Sir, excuse me.
I want to say goodbye to my wife.
Yes, couples need to say goodbye properly.
- Yes.
- A couple is like a soul. Soulmate.
- What is this?
- Snacks, sir.
What for?
- You go in first.
- Chips, sir.
Okay. Thank you, Ndin.
Yes, thank you, sir.
As usual, Mr. Nawir really is forgetful.
He called late at night,
but forgot it in the morning.
That's what happens
when you don't eat enough.
Honey, you only love me, right?
My dear.
I'm yours.
Even though we will only meet
through phone or dreams tonight.
Okay?
Go on, leave. Be careful.
Put on the helmet.
Yes, after this.
- It won't start.
- Wait.
What?
- Be careful, okay?
- Okay.
You write well.
Amara, it's already midday.
Pick up food at your sister's place.
Yes, Uncle.
Okay.
Amara!
Hey! Wake up!
Playing around with Rogo Sukmo…
Amara, wake up!
The nerve of this kid.
How do you know?
I'm the one who taught you.
- Yes, I'm practicing.
- Yes.
But don't play around with it.
Just like you.
Lin.
Here it is, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, ma'am.
Why is it so empty?
I'm not sure why,
but these past few days,
the eatery got quiet.
And Ario is out of town.
Poor Mrs. Andin.
All right, Lin.
Tell Andin I'll be sleeping over tonight.
Okay.
- I'm taking the container.
- Okay.
- I'm leaving now.
- Okay, be careful.
What do you want to order?
What's on the menu here?
We have plenty, but our specialty is
goat head.
It is very special.
Selected and auditioned
from all around the province.
They never work hard.
They are vaccinated regularly and--
I want a special one.
That's all, ma'am?
- Let me prepare it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Have a seat.
- Yes.
Please enjoy.
Ma'am.
Something wrong, ma'am?
How long have you been selling this?
Thank God the eatery has been around
for almost six months.
Is it usually this empty?
No, it's not.
It's usually packed.
You just happened to visit
during the low time.
- I see.
- All right, please enjoy.
Ma'am.
Since it's empty,
please sit with me.
I don't like being alone.
You're not from around here, are you?
No, I was passing by
and I got curious
about the specialty here.
You should use your hands.
It's tastier that way.
Is that so?
Wow, those are some fancy nails.
Thank you.
You should wear it too.
To make it more appealing.
Would you like to wear mine?
I happened to bring it.
Here, just a moment.
Just take it if you want.
No need, ma'am.
I've never accepted gifts from anyone.
I can buy another later.
You're so kind. Thank you.
But it's not necessary.
I have to go.
Just take it, ma'am.
Wow, this is too much.
I'll prepare the change first.
The economy is currently difficult.
Thank you, ma'am.
Would you like the food to go?
I'll pack it up for you.
Just a moment. Please wait.
- Good day.
- I'll just wrap it up.
Ma'am.
Here, Amara.
Is it so hard to get it by yourself?
That's what sisters are for.
What will that lady think about me?
Does it look cheap?
The lady at the eatery earlier?
Yes.
Her nail polish is really good.
Yours is also beautiful.
For real?
Of course.
Nowadays, there are
so many cases of infidelity.
What are you talking about, Amara?
This one.
These ugly people love to cheat.
Look at this.
How dare a face like this cheat?
If Ario dares to mess with you,
I'm your front guard, Andin.
I'll chop his dick.
Hey!
That's spooky.
Is it a cat?
Gosh.
It's dark, Amara.
A moment.
Get the flashlight
in the cupboard over there.
- Okay.
- Go.
Here it is.
There you go.
- It's on, Andin.
- Okay.
- You go up first.
Give it here, Amara.
What do you see?
There isn't anything.
Hold it, Amara.
What do you think that was?
Please.
Don't think about it.
Go to sleep.
All right.
Amara, don't move your legs. It tickles.
Amara.
Andin!
What's wrong?
There's a snake.
Snake?
Snake.
Snake? Where?
- Under the bed.
- Under the bed?
There's nothing, Andin.
Don't be paranoid.
Andin.
Come on.
- Don't make things up, Yan.
- I'm not. It's true, Lin.
What if Mrs. Andin hears it
and can't stop thinking about it,
only to find out it's a hoax?
It's not a hoax.
Remember Surah Al-Baqarah, verse 191, Yan.
Lin.
Didn't you recite it when you were a kid?
You were taught to recite, right?
- I'm non-Muslim, Lin.
- I don't…
I'm non-Muslim. Are you kidding?
You're my friend,
but you don't know that I'm not a Muslim.
- Quit it. I'm…
- Since when, Yan?
I'm serious.
Here, I have proof
if you don't believe it.
- Here.
- What proof?
Surah Al-Baqarah.
I saw Ario in a car with a girl.
Well, here it is.
You shithead!
Take a clear picture, Yan,
not just your face.
I place my face there
so people know I took it.
So they won't call it a hoax.
You're wrong, To.
Ario is on duty out of town.
I believe in you, ma'am.
But…
Stupid!
You're making people worry.
Ask forgiveness from God.
Ario.
- Snakes and ladders!
Why are you here this late, Uncle?
Rather than being alone.
So I'm joining these kids.
- Come on.
- Come on in, ma'am.
- Come on. We'll make ourselves at home.
- Come on, ma'am.
SKIP ONE ROUND
- Four.
Go.
- One, two, three.
- One, two, three. Four.
- I'm going up.
- He's going up.
How many?
- How many steps is it?
- So I go up?
- My turn.
- Yes, ma'am.
Andin, it's your turn.
Ma'am, do you want to know?
Do you want to know
the origin of Yanto Kates?
- Do you want to hear?
- Why?
Well…
My life is actually not that exciting.
- But--
- Spill it out!
So once upon a time,
in ancient times--
Cut it short, Yan.
You're not a storyteller.
Guard my house
from dark magic and woe.
My mother had a stall
at an airport construction project.
She met my father,
who's an engineer from South Korea.
I win.
Four.
Two. Three. Four.
Up again.
- I'm going up.
- Ma'am.
I'll continue the story.
- My God, Uncle!
- Uncle!
- What happened?
- How did you…
- You fell quite high.
- Uncle.
- Ouch, my back!
- Uncle, careful.
- Can you try to get up?
- Can you get up?
- Watch your spine.
- Be careful.
- Come.
Sit slowly.
Why the fuss?
Have a drink, honey.
Honey, where have you been?
It's been days
and there's been no news from you.
Do you even remember that you have a wife?
What are you saying?
I want you to welcome me when I'm home.
I want my wife to be beautiful
and smell nice.
What do I get? A messy house.
Your face is all wrinkled.
Do you think I enjoy this?
Where have you been?
I've been working, you know.
I work in remote areas.
There's no signal.
Do you think I enjoy it?
I couldn't contact you.
I got questioned like this.
For real?
You gave syrup to the others.
This one's mine?
Honey, here's the hot water.
Yes.
We'll meet again tomorrow.
I still have some work out of town.
I'm going to bed now.
I'll call you later.
Honey?
What are you doing?
Eavesdropping?
Why is the door locked all of a sudden?
So what?
Who's calling, honey?
Customer.
You're overly friendly with the customer.
Should I get all angry?
They would run away.
Do you want to be poor?
You'll blame me again.
You'd better take a shower.
You're smelly.
It's tacky.
GALLON MAN
Hello?
Who's this?
That's rude.
You're disturbing my sleep.
Make sure you don't wake me up again.
Honey.
What is this?
I told you not to wake me up.
Whose is this, honey?
Whose is this?
Why is this item in your bag?
If this is lip balm,
I would believe it's yours.
Look at it.
Nail polish.
Whose is it?
Why is it in your bag?
Answer me!
I don't know.
Whose is it?
What are you talking about?
Are you accusing me?
You're acting all weird.
Afraid of goats.
You forgot
to turn off the stove yesterday.
Luckily, the house didn't blow up.
Pulling off your nails.
Hear strange noises in the ceiling.
Do you want to make me crazy too?
I'm not crazy, okay?
I really felt it all.
I saw it all.
Hey.
If you believe your hallucinations,
call your uncle.
Have it cleaned.
He's the best, right?
- Don't bring my uncle into this.
- Why?
Maybe my uncle
was right about you all along.
If you trust your uncle so much,
just go to him.
Who's your husband?
Me or your uncle?
Don't try to change the topic. Answer me!
I don't know.
- Whose is it?
- Mine!
Liar!
Why do you have
this kind of stuff in your bag?
Since when?
Ario.
Are you good?
Why so tense?
Did you see a ghost or something?
Honey.
Sit down.
We have guests.
Please sit down.
So what brings you here?
You came all this way to my house.
Actually,
all this time,
I've been having a relationship
with Ario.
It's been going on for a long time.
A very long time.
If Ario hadn't been there,
my life would be a mess right now.
Business relationships.
Business.
Thanks to Mr. Ario's help,
my business is now running smoothly.
At first,
before I got the loan,
my business was struggling.
Just like your eatery, right?
But now, thank God.
It's growing.
That's why I want to say thank you.
I know.
Ario has
many customers.
Indeed.
The nail polish.
So you bought one too?
I didn't.
So Ario did?
Mr. Ario's such a gentleman, isn't he?
He treats his customers so well.
Let alone his wife.
You're so lucky.
Honey.
Forgive me.
Maybe I'm just not thinking straight.
I heard rumors.
Gossip is the devil's whisper.
I've been working.
I work very hard.
Sometimes, I work until dawn.
For whose sake?
For you.
Have you ever shown me appreciation?
Especially your uncle.
It's as if I have no dignity at all.
I'm sorry, honey.
I should be grateful
to have a husband like you.
It's okay.
Try to change from now on.
GOAT HEAD STEW SPECIAL
Look at you acting all busy.
Look!
Mrs. Andin is sick
because of what you said yesterday.
Don't you know?
- A troubled mind can be very dangerous.
- To.
Yes, ma'am.
You're closing the eatery?
Yes, I closed it. You look very pale.
Don't. We still have a lot of goats.
- But I'm feeling guilty.
- You?
Are you sure?
Do you still have the goat's head?
Yes, we still have it.
- I'll have one.
- We'll prepare it first.
Hey, Ario.
- Why are you here?
- Hi, Uncle.
Yeah.
I'll join you.
Please.
It's unusual.
You're usually on duty during weekends.
Since I'm not working,
I want to have goat head.
Oh, you're here, Uncle.
Hi, Andin.
This is your favorite.
- Ashtray, please.
- Okay.
I'll prepare you some coffee, Uncle.
Very nice.
- Thank you, Andin.
- You're welcome.
Does it taste different?
How are you?
I'm fine, Uncle.
It's just that
my job…
Collecting from clients is tough.
No wonder.
My business…
These coffins are selling well.
Are a lot of people dying?
Well…
My office can only help.
What I mean is…
Gosh.
What's wrong, Uncle?
Uncle, here's your coffee.
Andin, I'm leaving now.
Don't ask me.
Uncle! Wait!
The Lintrik
is not as good as I expected yet.
I want him to stay at home.
There are people
trying to get in the way of our efforts.
They're not just ordinary people.
To make the Lintrik stronger,
you need to perform the ritual yourself.
Do you have the courage?
Let him submit.
Full of desire.
Full of love.
Confuse him.
Make him go crazy about me.
Bring him
to my kingdom.
I've already made
the payment with fragrant rice.
Turn the grinder.
Spin the Earth.
Spinning seven earths, seven guardians.
Heart spirit.
Ario.
Honey?
Ario?
Ario!
Honey?
Honey, stop! What are you doing?
Honey!
Honey?
To collect debts, you need to be fierce,
not cowardly like that.
What is this?
Is this a threat?
This is what I'm selling.
It's dirty.
I came here looking for Ario.
He's not here.
As you can see, it's empty.
Right?
Perhaps he went to see his other wife.
I'm joking.
You really don't know where Ario is?
I really don't know, Din.
- No news from him at all?
- None.
Don't trust him.
He has the face of a fraudster.
How dare you!
Let's just meet him ourselves.
His address is on his ID, right?
- That's right.
- Right? Okay.
Come on, let's go.
Okay, let's go to Semarang.
- Let's go.
- Come.
Your sister's problem
is not a typical one.
I need to find the proof
and find out who sent it.
Why would anyone do
something so evil, Uncle?
Because some people have the guts
to do something good
that people would never do.
Amara.
Close all doors and curtains.
Okay.
Oh ancestors.
My intention is…
Rogo Sukmo.
Uncle!
Amara!
- Amara!
- Uncle.
- Uncle!
- Amara!
Are you okay, Uncle?
I'm okay, Amara. Thank you.
Something's up there.
There?
Yes, Uncle.
There's nothing.
There's something, Uncle.
Okay, calm down. Let's go.
Help!
Amara.
Call your sister.
Don't come back here. It's dangerous.
You go home. I'm going
to the market to get some friends.
- Okay, Uncle.
- Call your sister.
- Be careful, Uncle.
- You too.
- We're almost there.
- We're here.
Could it be that his ID is fake?
- No.
- Impossible.
- We're almost there.
He's been driving all this time lazily.
The car even reeks of oranges.
It's pomelo!
- I don't see any pomelos.
- What's that rotten smell?
You smell like a chicken farm.
- This is the right spot.
- Well…
- It means there's another path underneath.
- This is correct.
Look around. There's nothing here.
Use your eyes.
Where's your family? Wake them up.
- Enough.
- Don't kid around.
So what now? It's obviously wrong.
Are you demeaning my profession?
I've been doing this for 20 years.
I guess downtown fashion is so hip.
There's even a ripped shirt. Look!
- Ripped shirt?
That's Sun…
Sundari?
No.
That's Sun…
- Sun Tae-yong.
- No, that's Shin.
The ghost is really ugly.
Whose car is this?
I'm sorry, but you have already signed.
Please don't take my land.
I'm very sorry, sir.
You have agreed to the terms.
I'm very sorry.
I beg you.
- Please.
- Let's go, sir.
How can I help you, ma'am?
I'm looking for Ario Setiawan.
Mr. Ario isn't assigned here,
but in Yogyakarta.
I am Mr. Ario's customer.
Tomorrow is my last installment due.
That's why I need to see him.
I'm sorry.
You can do the transaction
at the teller or by transfer.
Sorry, we cannot provide a home address.
Welcome.
- We're having a 10% off promotion.
- Yes.
I think this is the place.
- You sure?
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, sir.
- Are you sure, Lin?
- Yes.
- Oh, right.
- Lumpia Samimawon.
SPECIAL PROMO, SPECIAL FUN PACKET
Welcome.
- Is this free?
- Yes, it is.
- Excuse me.
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
- Excuse me.
Do you know this person?
I don't think so.
- He usually buys me this.
- Can I help you?
Yes, sir. Do you know this person?
Please wait a moment,
I'll ask the manager first.
Seems like they know him, ma'am.
Be patient, ma'am.
It's Ario.
Who is he with?
Chop his dick!
Honey!
How dare you!
Honey…
Honey!
Record it, Yan!
Hey! Homewrecker!
Honey, get in the car.
Hurry. Don't make a scene.
- This is my shop.
- Bitch!
Don't leave!
- Don't leave!
- Honey, step out of the car!
- Hey, homewrecker!
- What's going on?
Honey!
- Calm down. We'll find him later.
- It's okay.
We'll find him together.
Look, you're hurt.
Thank you, sir.
To.
Andin.
- You guys be careful.
- Thanks, ma'am.
Please enjoy.
You should eat it with your hands.
It's tastier that way.
Wow, you're right.
I've never had this taste before.
But excuse me. Why is it so empty?
How about this?
What if I help you?
So later, the eatery
will be bigger and busier.
This will be the main item on the menu.
I feel that I want to build more
than just this eatery together.
I want to raise a family
with you.
This is proof
that Ario has been bewitched
by Lintrik.
That woman wants to steal your husband
and she succeeded.
Uncle.
My child needs his father.
Calm yourself, Andin.
Let me handle it, okay?
Fate has brought me
to take care of both of you.
Trust him, Andin.
Imagine it.
If yesterday's video
of us confronting them
got posted on social media…
- What?
- Just imagine.
We'll definitely be rich.
May God's blessing be on it, Yan.
Imagine this.
The story goes viral.
Everyone feels sorry for Mrs. Andin.
Then the eatery is booming.
And then a film producer comes,
listens to our story,
and adapts it into a movie.
Wow. That's the cherry on top.
Gosh.
When this turns into a movie,
I want Jefri Nichol to play me.
He looks a lot like me, right?
You look more like Opie Kumis.
Who will you pick?
- You're asking me?
- Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Dian Sastro.
Okay, Ms. Dian. Pleased to meet you.
I'm throwing away the goat's head.
Gosh! The sun!
I can't be exposed to the sun.
It's scorching hot!
I'm tired.
Gosh. What should I have for lunch?
Jef.
So this is what it feels like
to be called by Dian Sastro.
A knock-off still does it anyway.
Jef, I'm scared.
- What? Scared?
- Jefri.
What great acting.
- She has to be. What a good actress.
- Jef!
Jefri!
- Jefri, look!
- Dian!
What's going on, Dian?
- Jef.
- What's going on?
Jefri, look.
I had thrown away the goat's head earlier.
- And then?
- But it came back out.
Maybe it just rolled away.
Trust me, Jef.
All right then. You stay here.
Let me check.
- Be careful, Jef.
- Got it. No worries.
- I know.
- All clear?
- Clear.
There's nothing here.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
Just calm down.
- Dian!
- Jef!
What is that, Lin?
- How come?
- How…
Run!
NOT AVAILABLE
AVAILABLE
- Hurry, To!
- I know!
Help, To!
- What should I do?
- Get the door!
Hurry!
Forgive me, Jef.
Dian!
Jef!
- Open it, Jef! I'm scared!
- Dian!
Jef, help me!
Dian!
Help me!
Wait a second!
Stop pushing!
NOT AVAILABLE
- Help! It burns!
- Come on.
Help us!
- Help!
- What's going on?
There are goats, sir.
- That's what you sell, idiot!
- Help!
Amara.
Be careful, okay?
Take care of my niece.
Yes, Andin.
Try to calm down.
Uncle has taught me a lot.
Pray for me, Andin.
Amara.
Be careful, dear.
This time around,
the Rogo Sukmo is riskier.
Make sure you follow me.
Yes, Uncle.
- Can you do it?
- Yes.
Oh ancestors.
My intention is…
- Rogo Sukmo.
Why would a woman as young
and beautiful as you need Lintrik?
Those men out there must be blind.
I'm aiming for
someone's husband, ma'am.
Atta girl.
What's his name?
Yanto Kates, ma'am.
How rich is he?
Where's his picture?
I forgot to bring his picture, ma'am.
Fine. Tell me what he looks like.
Yanto Kates is a good person, ma'am.
He's funny.
I feel comfortable around funny people.
I already warned you.
Your skill
is no match for mine.
Show me
where you planted Ario's picture!
And if I don't want to,
what will you do?
Uncle!
Uncle.
Forgive me.
Uncle!
Andin!
My sister!
Amara!
My dear.
The will you gave me…
I'll give it to your niece, okay?
This is from Uncle.
He told me
how to end this.
You guys be careful, okay?
Remember. Wait until it's dark.
I just want to be loved,
but I mess everything up instead.
My mother said
we are raised to believe
that happiness is a man
even though sometimes,
they're the ones who destroy us.
She jumped.
Let's check it.
See, she's the shaman.
People say she's the most
powerful shaman around here.
There's no one else.
See? She jumped and poof!
She's gone.
What do you want?
There's no point coming here.
You killed my uncle and sister.
That's the risk
of meddling in people's affairs.
Why
did my uncle and sister have to die?
Don't ask me.
Ask the woman who paid me.
Her house is enormous.
On top of Ambarawa Hill.
If you manage to survive.
Kirto!
Kill them!
You guys look for Ario's Lintrik
till you get it.
I'm going to that big house.
- Tie him up.
- Okay.
Be careful, ma'am.
You guys be careful too, okay?
Come on, Yan.
Is this the right way?
It is.
What?
It is!
It is.
Pass the market,
there's a garden, turn left.
Shithead!
- It's left!
- Oh yeah, left.
Gosh, I'm confused.
Idiot.
Yan!
- Gosh.
- Come on!
Who's the idiot one?
- Why do we have to wear this?
- Beats me.
There's no one here.
Honey.
Honey, I know what happened to you.
Ario!
Honey!
Stop. Honey, stop!
I know you are bewitched by Lintrik.
Honey, stop!
Hey, homewrecker! Show yourself!
Why are you here?
Looking for your husband?
Oh man.
Why would anyone bewitch this ugly man?
As if he's the last man on earth.
This one's handsome. Worth the Lintrik.
Stop all your evil deeds!
Me? Evil?
Me?
Do you think so?
You are the evil one!
I really hate this man.
I've given it all.
But still,
he chose you.
What did he promise you?
Spring rolls?
You know what?
The spring roll business is mine.
This house, all this wealth is mine!
Hey.
What did he call you?
Did he call you "home"?
Did he?
What home?
- A shabby one?
- You!
You're not just destroying my marriage!
My uncle!
My sister!
They're dead!
You destroyed everything!
I'm the destroyer?
Me?
You're the one who destroyed everything.
And it's better
if we just destroy everything now!
Wicked! You're evil!
Honey, don't do this.
I'm your wife!
Wake up, honey. Honey.
I'm your wife, honey.
Kneel.
Ma'am.
Release Ario.
Kill your husband.
No. I'm your husband.
- Yan.
- Yes.
No. Don't get close yet.
This must be the boss.
No, you'll get possessed, Lin.
- Let's just do it.
- Don't.
Remember, we're helping Mrs. Andin
to finish it quickly.
But what if we get possessed?
Let's ask for permission politely.
Found it.
It's Ario, Lin.
Ario.
Mrs. Andin!
What is this?
Smells like shit.
Smells like goat.
- Do we burn it?
- Go ahead.
What now?
Where's the lighter?
- Oh, that's right.
- Ignite it.
It's burning.
That's it.
Ma'am, what's going on?
No.
Get up!
I am pregnant.
This is Ario's child.
Give me a chance to save my family.
You bastard!
Papa.
What's wrong with Pa, Ma?
Wake up, Pa.
Papa.
I've been married
to this man for seven years.
Papa.
Wake up, Pa.
I do all this
- for my son.
- Wake up, Pa.
Papa.
- I don't want him to grow up fatherless.
- Papa.
Pa…
So you are the homewrecker.
But I know.
- We're both victims of this jerk.
- Papa, wake up.
Papa.
- Ario is cruel.
- Wake up, Pa.
Ario is cruel.
Papa…
My eatery is currently low.
Apologies, sir. This is the bank's policy.
- This is from someone.
- I've tried, Ms. Sundari.
All my efforts have failed, ma'am.
LET'S GO HOME TOGETHER AFTER WORK
I only have this much, ma'am.
Please help me, ma'am.
Come here.
So naughty.
- Do you miss me?
- I miss you a lot. I can't resist.
DEAD STAKE BLACK MAGIC
Baby.
Why so long?
Why are you so eager?
I can't hold it anymore.
Oh no.
- There's no sun.
- No, there isn't.
Your aura…
- What?
- Your aura.
- What aura?
- Such a mess!
- Rafa.
- Jefri.
Rafa.
- Rafa.
- Rafa must be short for Rafatar.
Cute.
So this is what it feels like
to be between two beautiful women.
- What?
- Are you deaf?
Forget it.
What is this? It's a toy!
If he can take it, he'll be able to…
- Oh no. Kick it.
- I don't want to take it.
- What?
- I don't want to either.