Fm Movie
Come, Stephen.
- Come on in.
- Stephen. Get in, my boy.
Why are you hesitating? Come.
Don't be afraid. Get in.
Don't overthink.
Dad is here for you.
Listen to your mom. Come on.
Come and climb up.
Come on, Stephen.
- Good.
- Good. Get in.
Good.
Come, come, come.
What, Stephen? Are you feeling dizzy?
What are you going to do there?
I won't do anything.
Better stay here then?
Please, sweetheart.
Hey! Stop with your "sweetheart" bullshit.
Will I ever lie to you?
Then tell the truth!
That you want to rat me out to the police.
I'll let you go.
I didn't even think about the police.
Hey. I'll let you go if you accept it.
I swear, I won't.
Accept it and I'll let you go.
Please, dear. Please.
You're delaying unnecessarily.
So, if I accept it, will you let me go?
Yes. Accept it, and I'll let you go.
Well, yes. I'm going to the police.
I am going to tell them
everything about you.
Okay. Nice, nice, nice.
So, now for the next step...
What next?
Escaping from him, right?
Why would you say that?
Well, sir,
how can you live with such a person?
Such a person?
A psycho.
Psycho? Isn't that a bit harsh?
What should I call him then?
An innocent boy?
Okay. Calm down.
You are right.
Seems like he's a proper lunatic.
Now he is very angry.
Out of anger, he grabs a knife
and comes to stab you.
For now, as a cue,
imagine I'm the killer.
You role is to scream in fear.
Okay? Can you do that?
Yeah. Okay.
Ready?
I feel the dialogues are out of place.
What makes you say so?
Well,
I know him from my childhood.
And I'm in love with him too.
Then, how could I betray him
and hand him over to the police suddenly?
Okay. You start.
Action.
Hey, I'm running toward you with a knife.
- Is this how you scream?
- Sir. Sorry, sir.
- Imagine this is your life's last second.
- I get it.
Feel the intensity, and scream.
- Want to be a heroine or not?
- I do.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Then you should act like one. Okay?
Yeah. Okay.
Action.
Sorry, sir. Sorry.
- No, no. I'll wait. You cough.
- Sorry, sir.
What is this?
Sorry, sir.
You know what?
I will grab a real knife.
Only then you will feel the intensity.
Okay, sir.
Last take. I can't take it anymore.
Done.
- Ready?
- Yes, ready.
What's your name again?
Simran.
Simran. Nice. Nice name.
Okay, let's go.
Action.
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
The sketch has been sent
to every check post, sir.
We'll catch him before nightfall.
The public should not know
about this. Finish it soon.
Definitely, sir.
Keep me posted.
Sure.
Constable, bring that over.
News flash!
Per the information from the initial probe
of the missing women's case,
the killer's face has been sketched out.
Regarding this, #KillerOnTheLoose
is trending on social media.
The public has been advised
to stay vigilant.
Let's check Puliyakulam Road, too, sir.
Are you sure?
Is it the same car?
Sorry.
Sir, the car has made
a turn near Sowripalayam. Over.
- Have you seen this man?
- Yes, sir.
If you go straight here,
it's the last house.
- I saw him go that way this morning.
- Sir!
Get in quickly.
Madhu, let's go.
Brother!
Sir...
We found him.
What do you want?
Won't talk unless I ask?
I'm a killer, sir.
Oh, that's great.
Who? Where? When?
Seems like you forgot who you killed, boy.
I'm not sure what
these guys are drinking nowadays, sir.
What's up, man? Smoked a joint?
He must have.
Can I get you some tea?
Let's drink and talk clearly.
I killed nine girls, sir.
I'm the one you are searching for.
Okay, sir. Okay.
It's confirmed.
The sketch matches perfectly.
SP and Commissioner are on their way.
We have to watch him, until they come.
I won't run away, sir.
Take your time.
Sir?
Instead of tea,
can I get a cup of coffee?
We've caught the main culprit
responsible for the nine missing girls.
We want justice!
His name is Stephen.
He has been taken into custody
and is under investigation.
We will proceed to court
as fast as we can.
Stop, stop. Wait.
We just caught him.
Give us some time.
We are going step by step.
We'll let you know the details.
A case officer has already been assigned.
Motive and MO will be found soon.
- We will fight...
- Until justice is served.
And we need your cooperation
until this case is closed. Thank you.
How is the government responsible
if a maniac goes on a killing spree?
Court and police are acting fast.
CM is actively looking for a way
to hang Stephen by all means.
What have you done?
You had a clear instruction to shoot him
on sight. Not to let him surrender.
No, sir.
Before we could trace his house,
he surrendered at B2 station, sir.
It feels unsafe to live in a city
where this psycho has been hiding.
If you can't do anything legally,
leave it to the public.
We know how to handle him.
People like him should be shot in public.
What he did is unforgivable.
Hang him! Hang him! Hang him!
The outrage from the public is extreme.
Nine girls, Michael!
No human has the right
to take another human's life.
But I don't know if he is even a human.
The court must hang him for sure.
Do something and finish this off.
Officially, this case is over.
There's nothing more I can do
in this case, as a police.
The killer has surrendered.
It's enough if I submit
the evidences to the court.
He'll be hanged for sure.
But will I get the answer?
Why did he surrender himself?
Six months and nine girls.
He could've surrendered
anytime before, too.
But why now?
Did he get scared?
Or is this a plan, Stephen?
I killed Smitha like this.
Excuse me.
I took Riya's life... this way.
If I couldn't dispose of the bodies
immediately, I'll pile them up here.
Hey, how did you dispose of those bodies?
I'll take them to the forest
and throw them.
And then?
I'll come back.
What do you mean?
Yeah. I'll go and check the next day.
The bodies would've disappeared.
I don't know what happened to them.
Where is that forest?
Velu, search carefully.
Don't leave anything out.
Carefully. On that side too.
Pandi, come and search here.
Ranga, please come over here.
Search on this side.
Don't leave anything out.
Search carefully.
- Velu, look, there's something--
- Sir!
Stephen Jebaraj...
You've declared you don't need a lawyer.
Is that right?
Nodding is not enough. Open your mouth.
Yes, sir.
Why?
Not needed, sir.
For the record, your charges
will be read out now. Listen closely.
Okay, sir.
Between April 2023 to December 2023,
Ramya, Prema, Janu,
Preethi, Vijayalakshmi, Riya,
Smitha, Simran, and Surekha
were the nine victims who were kidnapped
and murdered by the accused.
That's enough.
Do you accept these charges?
I accept.
Who's the investigating officer?
Sir.
What will you do if he says he wasn't
in the right mind while confessing?
Procure proper examination reports
in 15 days' time.
Most importantly,
mental examination should be precise.
Okay, sir.
He looks abnormal as well.
Do you know the profile
of this case outside?
You seem to be very careless.
Is this a petty theft case?
Serial killings.
In my years of service, I have never dealt
with a nine-murder case.
You may leave now.
The accused has to be brought
in the same condition.
No, no, no.
Hey, hold him.
Burn in hell, psycho!
Hold him. Hold him.
I'll not rest until I kill you!
What did my little sister do
to deserve this horrible fate, you coward?
Stephen!
Hey, hey, careful.
Come here, Kuttan.
Super!
Stephen!
Come, let's go.
You said you will give away
the puppy to your friend, right?
What happened?
Mom, he'll grow up in one year.
And then he'll easily save
both of us from Dad.
Hey, Stephen!
Dad.
Despite his ability, he couldn't survive
in athletics due to continuous injuries.
He could only become
my school's sports teacher.
Out of frustration, he started drinking.
He'll drink every day.
He'll also torture me
to become a great player.
Next, plank, 30 seconds.
Hey, bring me the damn omelet!
Bring it right now, you fool!
You useless piece of...
If my situation is worst,
just imagine my mom's.
My teaching form is incorrect it seems.
Says that amateur piece of crap.
Along with him,
that wine shop brat as well.
Apparently, the management has imposed
no-liquor policy during school hours.
I had to go to another liquor store today.
Crappy loafers.
Who are you guys to order me?
I will drink. This is my house.
All right, my father-in-law's house.
Me and my mom
were used to tolerating my dad.
But Kuttan...
Where have you kept Kuttan?
He's in the upstairs room, Mom.
If Dad finds out, we are done.
I told you this is risky.
Why can't you listen?
Stephen!
Where are you?
What's this?
Who gave permission to keep
this good-for-nothing in the house?
Tell me, good-for-nothing no. 1.
Stop crying, good-for-nothing no. 2.
Open your mouth!
Please, Dad.
Please leave Kuttan alone. I beg you.
Answer me, madam.
Shut up, good-for-nothing no. 3.
Use your mouth and talk.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
I said, open your...
Mom...
Kuttan... Kuttan! Kuttan!
Kuttan!
Hey, stop it.
How dare it pee on me!
Hey, clean up the mess quickly.
Or it might infect us!
What are these papers for, madam?
Yesterday went well, right?
I have to conduct a few tests, Stephen.
For assessment purposes.
When I came over just now,
the weather was good outside.
I thought today would be a good day.
But now, it's ruined for sure.
There's no pass or fail in these tests.
What does this image make you think of?
Should I definitely answer?
You can tell me whatever you think of.
It... looks like a demon.
A demon who plans to invade
and destroy the world we live in.
Do you see the sharp horns on his head?
And then, this looks like his chariot.
Interesting.
What do you think of this?
It resembles a girl's private parts.
Okay.
And this?
One minute.
What are you going to do with my answers?
You want to know your result
even before you attend the exam?
But you told me
there's no pass or fail, right?
Everything is for an assessment, Stephen.
Here. Next is IQ and personality tests.
You'll understand
when you see the questions.
Can I give random answers then?
Definitely not.
Answer with honesty.
At the end of the day,
hope all of this is useful to you.
Okay. Let's begin
where we stopped yesterday.
So, your dad is a drunkard,
which is a problem
for you and your mother.
My dad was the starting point
for everything.
But he was not the end point.
Sister, where is room number 305?
Go straight and take a left, ma'am.
Last room.
Hey! Are you that man's wife?
He recorded and posted an explicit video
of the SI's daughter on the web.
Poor girl, she tried taking her own life.
They spared his life with
just a broken hip, because she survived.
Tell him to stay safe indoors.
Or else...
Can't you come sooner?
It's hurting a lot.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I wasn't sober.
Forget this ever happened.
Seems like it'll take six months
for me to walk again.
You better call your dad
and ask for money till then.
Hey. I'm talking to you.
Can't you open your mouth?
- Filthy dog!
- It hurts.
- Filthy dog! How dare you ask for more.
- Don't hit. I'll kill you.
That poor girl's life
has gone to dust now.
You arrogant pervert.
Aren't you ashamed?
How can I even show my face outside?
You filthy dog!
My mom, who was suffering
from my dad's abuse till then,
finally got an opportunity.
She resumed her baking business, which
she had stopped out of fear of my dad.
She took control of the whole house.
Including Dad.
I don't know what mistake I made.
She suppressed and oppressed me too.
Mom had her own reasons.
From the outside,
it seemed like an ordinary house.
But only we knew
that this is her kingdom.
Seems like there's no one at home.
Let's see.
Mm... Guest.
- Hey. Hi, Mithun!
- Hello, Aunty.
Sorry, I was busy with household work.
Come in. Come in, dear.
Please come in.
Hello, Police Officer.
Hello.
I feel like Stephen is hiding something.
Why do you say so?
We gave him a Rorschach test.
Sorry?
Basically, we'll show few images
to our patients.
Wait. I'll give you a demo.
What do you think of this image?
Looks like a chicken hanging upside down.
It's normal when the answer is like yours.
But he described it as a demon,
coming to destroy the world.
- That's abnormal.
- Why,
didn't you know that already
when he killed nine girls?
Me and my team conducted
a few tests for Stephen
to check if he has psychopathic deviations
and personality disorders.
The test says
he's a pathological liar.
It's usual for killers to lie, right?
There is a thing called lie score limit.
It helps with calculating
the extent of the lies.
For example, I'm giving you 100 questions.
In that, I would have asked
something as the 22nd question.
The same question
will be modified as the 69th question.
If there is variation in the two answers
for the same question, it's an indication.
If the lie score exceeds the limit, such
answers will not be taken into account.
Our guy was beyond
the limit of the lie score.
So you mean, the tests are inconclusive.
Not like that.
The Rorschach test says
that Stephen is still a violent person.
But his body language
and his demeanor tells a different story.
What if the girls he claimed
to have killed are still alive?
Now, he's slowly starting
to open up about his parents.
Hey, do you even know
that his parents are not alive?
Yes, I know.
Officially, there is
a police case against his dad.
That he killed his wife
and then took his own life.
But can you collect
additional information?
Only then, I will get more clarity.
What if Seema is right
about Stephen's lies?
What if he has lied to me all this time?
I should meet the characters
of his story in person.
Only then, the truth will come out.
What are you planning, Stephen?
I'll find out soon.
- Brother.
- Sir.
Is Moorthy Sir not here?
No, sir.
He's off duty for two days
for his daughter's marriage.
Okay. Let him know that I asked for him.
Any news about my daughter?
Not yet, madam.
Please be patient for some more time.
He has slowly started to open himself up.
He might stop answering
if I put him under pressure.
Our daughter was our entire world.
How can a human be this cruel?
There are many good people in this world.
They do good deeds
without expecting anything in return.
And there are some people like Stephen,
who commit such cruelty
for no reason at all.
Please be brave.
If we don't get justice
for my daughter and the other victims,
I'll beat that animal to death myself.
What do you think
of Stephen's parents?
Sir, they're really nice people.
They were very helpful and silent too.
His dad wasn't a good man, sir.
He was a problematic drunkard.
Your opinion about Stephen?
Sir, he wouldn't come out much.
Very strict family.
Sir, his dad was always at home.
Only Stephen would come to the store.
His mom wasn't that good, sir.
She'd be roaming at odd hours
for her baking business.
Stephen doesn't even drink or smoke, sir.
A very decent boy.
Bro, one tea.
Mithun?
How are you and Stephen related?
Stephen was my classmate, sir.
We sat in the same bench
from school to college.
He wouldn't mingle with anyone.
But he opened up to me freely, in a way.
I think you would have heard the news.
I did, sir.
I did not expect
him to do such things.
What can I say,
blame it on his upbringing?
Elaborate.
I don't know
what to think about his parents.
One day, in our childhood...
Trust me, dude.
She's beating me a lot nowadays.
Don't lie.
You always say the same thing.
Your mom is a very good woman.
She always gives me cake, you know?
I can give you the cakes myself.
But please trust me.
Stephen!
Oh, no...
- Mom?
- Come here.
Did you serve coffee to Dad?
Of course, Mom.
Did you mix the pill in it?
Pill?
Mithun!
Aunty?
It's quite late.
Can you come back tomorrow?
Okay, Aunty.
Aunty, I love your plum cakes.
Can you bake them again for me?
Why not?
I'll bake them for Christmas.
And if anyone else asks for cakes,
let me know! Okay?
- Sure, Aunty.
- Okay.
Bye, Stephen.
You didn't do the only job given to you.
Too busy playing video games?
No, Mom.
Don't you know the pill has to be put
in Dad's coffee? Don't you know?
- Don't you?
- Sorry, Mom. I totally forgot.
- Nowadays, you don't listen to me at all.
- Sorry, Mom.
Aunty.
I forgot my game CD.
Stephen, go and get it.
Go home safely, okay?
He has told me a lot, sir.
His dad's misbehavior
and how his mom beats him up.
Something was definitely wrong there, sir.
I could sense it.
No one really knows much about them, sir.
Stephen was the one
caught up in this mess.
How is he holding up, sir?
Sir?
Who are you really, Stephen?
Michael!
Moorthy Sir. What a surprise.
My daughter is getting married.
This school's principal
is my family friend.
I came to invite him for the wedding.
I came to your station
in the morning, sir.
You were the one who closed
Stephen's parents' case, right?
I need some details regarding it.
Because Stephen's dad worked here.
He recorded explicit videos
of many female students.
The affected people
seemed to have beaten him.
But no case has been filed.
That's why...
Okay, carry on.
I'll meet you at the station later.
Moorthy Sir?
Even your daughter studied here, right?
Michael.
I was rechecking the evidence.
I noticed a wristband
which was retrieved from Stephen's house.
Regarding Christianity.
I think no one has looked into it.
Can you please...
Hey. What are you thinking?
Sir... regarding Stephen's parents' death,
how did you close the case
without any conclusive evidence?
I did everything for my daughter's sake.
Stephen's dad didn't commit suicide, sir.
Stephen killed him.
It was New Year's Eve.
A call came from the control room.
Everyone was out on duty.
So I attended the call.
Someone had made a call,
informing that he killed his own wife.
After going to the spot,
I got to know it was Stephen's home.
He said his dad killed his mom
in a fit of lust and then turned on him.
He would've definitely done it.
Mad, disgusting pervert he was!
He posted my daughter's video
on the internet.
My daughter went into a shell.
She locked herself at home.
She even tried to take her own life.
Sir, I saw Stephen as my own son.
He is the same age as my daughter.
They were classmates as well.
I closed the case, stating Stephen's dad
killed his mom and committed suicide.
What have you done, sir?
Consider it from a father's perspective.
No, sir!
If he was arrested back then,
nine innocent lives would've been saved.
Dad?
Done with the invitations, dear?
Yes, Dad.
- Wait in the car. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Sir, I understand your concern.
Nothing about the video, or the fact
that I did this for my daughter,
can be leaked out.
I'll take my leave, sir.
Sir?
My daughter is getting married next month.
You should definitely come.
Hey, relax.
Emotional decisions are dangerous.
It's interesting how different minds react
under certain situations, right?
The case files say
his dad took his own life, right?
But Stephen is the one who killed his dad.
Wait... He doesn't know
that we know this information, right?
This is a good opportunity.
We can find out if he is truthful
to you or not through this.
And it'll be easy for us
to assess him and categorize him.
There are only two outcomes.
Option A: Truth.
He must confess
that he killed his own dad.
If he does that, he's truthful to us.
We can move on to next assessment
about his serial killings.
No confusions.
If not,
Option B: Lie.
If he doesn't confess
that he killed his dad,
then he's a liar as the tests say.
He could've hidden more from us.
Both in the past and present.
What if he surrendered
to save someone else?
Or what if he's planning something big?
Option A or Option B?
We'll know tomorrow.
New Year Eve, 2021.
What happened?
Son.
Yes, Dad.
Please help me.
But I'm going out now.
I have kept Mom's saree on the table.
She asked me to iron it.
You better do it. Or else you're doomed.
She beat me up badly last time
because I didn't do a good job.
Then do it properly, Dad.
Why are you asking me?
I slept late last night
after packing the New Year cakes.
I even did your job
without Mom knowing.
Okay, now what?
You want me to iron her saree?
Yes, I'll take care of the rest.
What will you take care of?
Sweep the house, water the plants,
wash the dishes...
Okay, get it done, before Mom comes.
- Okay, son.
- Carry on.
Dad!
What's wrong, son?
I didn't do anything.
I've received a job offer in Chennai.
They have asked me to join in February.
Okay, son.
Dad, at least try to smile?
No, you were better without it.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Love you, Jesus. Love you, Jesus.
Oh, shit!
What happened, son?
Why are you running?
Oh, my dear Lord.
How can you be so careless, son?
It's your mom's New Year saree.
Dad, calm down.
It was my fault, right?
Why are you freaking out?
She'll hit me
for delegating my work to you.
Dad, please calm down.
Let's handle it.
What, son?
Don't you know your mom?
How can we handle her?
Dad, come. Let's leave.
Are you asking me to run away with you?
No.
Let's buy a similar saree
before she comes.
Also, I'll treat you
on account of my new job.
No, please.
I got a job now, right? You don't need
to be scared of her anymore.
No, son.
Dad, when was the last time
you left the house?
I don't remember, son.
Why are you doing all this?
I'm really scared, son.
Dad, I told you
that it's a treat for my new job.
Are you going to take me somewhere
and leave me stranded?
I'm doing everything
that my body can handle.
Even if your mom says so,
please don't give up on me, son.
Dad, it's nothing like that.
Believe me.
Dad, I'll go and have a look.
Got it!
Al right, son, shall we go home now?
Let's go...
but for a long drive.
Son?
Can you buy me a cigarette?
It's been ages.
Congratulations, son, on your job.
Thanks, Dad.
At least be happy
by moving out of the house.
Why, Dad?
All three of us will be happy soon.
Can I get one more cigarette?
I'll finish it off in two minutes.
Can I, son?
Son.
Can I get another smoke?
Tell me, tell me, you filthy dog!
- If you don't tell me--
- I didn't do anything.
The saree seems to be new.
What did you do?
Say it louder.
Don't lie. Stephen took you out, right?
Tell me the truth.
- Let me go.
- Kneel down.
- It hurts.
- I said, kneel down!
Tell me. Tell me!
Please, let me put on my lungi.
I beg you.
Oh, such a decent guy, huh?
Won't you obey my orders?
How dare you disobey me?
Use your mouth, good-for-nothing!
Where did you both go?
Both of you gained the courage
to step out of the house, right?
Tell me!
Mom.
No.
Please, Mom, that's enough.
He can't take any more.
How dare you come in?
Why did you come now?
Sorry, Mom! Sorry!
Looks like you're no longer scared of me.
How dare you defend this filthy dog!
Will you interfere again? Will you?
No, Mom.
Sit.
Sit down!
Hey, switch on the fan.
When I returned home, I noticed
the car's tires were not straight.
I could smell cigarette smoke in the car.
I know that only this man smokes.
After all these years, he can't drive.
Obviously it was you who took him.
I won't beat up the person
who spills the truth first.
I was against the idea from the start.
But he kept insisting.
Your saree got burnt while ironing.
That's why we went to the store
and bought a new one.
Sorry. Really, sorry.
Even you cannot be trusted
in this house anymore. Right, Stephen?
Nothing like that, Mom.
Despite working so hard for this family,
you guys made a fool out of me.
It's nothing, but...
Two good-for-nothings are home, right?
Dad, please take that.
Hereafter, you should come
to the bakery, Stephen.
Hey. What was that?
What's that? Give it to me!
"This is to inform you that you have been
appointed as Project Coordinator."
"And you're supposed
to report on February 2nd
in the above mentioned address."
Why didn't you tell me about this?
I was about to tell you, Mom.
Oh... Is that why you barged in?
I was wondering, how did our boy get
such bravery and courage all of a sudden?
This is the reason, then.
Nothing like that, Mom.
I burnt your saree by mistake.
I'm sorry for coming between you both.
Please leave me and do whatever you want.
What will you do then?
Order me around from Chennai?
No, Mom. I swear I won't.
You're going to earn more than me.
Won't you prance around?
Haven't I seen
this filthy dog prance around before?
I wouldn't do that to you, Mom.
I'll also help you by earning, Mom.
Help? Wow, what a thought.
Mom, I can't take it anymore.
I think I'll go insane.
I can't handle the both of you.
What the hell?
Are you comparing me with this dog?
Mom, please.
Let me go to work.
I will listen to whatever you say.
I'm demanding you not to take this job,
can't you understand?
I'm leaving.
I can't take this anymore.
So, you have made a decision.
Have you?
Fine, son.
Leave now!
Hey!
Will you let me leave for work?
What?
Will you let me leave or not?
Option A or Option B, Stephen?
What will you choose now?
Mom, I'm asking you one last time.
Will you let me leave or not?
You dirty woman.
It's a shame you died.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
My son! Do not cry.
I feel proud to be your dad.
Don't shed tears for this dead bitch.
Call the police.
I will go to jail for you.
Hand me the knife.
It was I who killed her.
Whoever asks, just say that.
Wait, I'll tell them myself.
Hey, move away.
Lying in the middle of the house.
Hello, sir.
I am calling
from Pachapalayam, 5th Street.
Door number 37.
Just five minutes ago,
I stabbed my wife viciously.
Oh, yes, sir. I did a number on her!
Please come soon.
And let the headlines tomorrow be,
"A warrior who slayed his wife."
Then, sir, who'll call the media?
You or me?
Hello?
What's this, son?
They're abruptly cutting the call.
Not a problem.
Be brave.
Don't worry about anything.
Hey, woman, look at my son.
He cut you open pretty well, right?
My son, I'm so happy.
Will you buy your dad a cigarette?
No. Ignore that.
Police and media can come anytime.
I should be in the spot.
Oops. I feel like peeing.
Sorry, no time to use the bathroom.
What is she here for?
Happy new year.
A twist in the nine missing women case!
A man in his mid-twenties has surrendered
at Perur Police Station a few hours ago--
This has caused an uproar.
The case is led by Inspector Michael
with a special team.
Why is he voluntarily
accepting both the murders?
Instead of A or B,
he's surprising us with an Option C.
Can I tell you something even more random?
Stephen was in Chennai for a year
and a half after his parents' death.
I inquired there.
Watch this video.
Sir, I'm here
at Stephen's Chennai apartment.
The security guard is saying something.
Listen to it, sir.
Sir, please repeat
everything you just told me.
Sir?
Sir, this guy was staying here
a few months ago.
Can you say more about him?
Nothing much. He'll just mind
his own business. That's it.
- You mentioned a girl?
- Yes, sir.
There was a girl staying with him.
Her age?
Same as the boy's.
Oh. Can you say more about the girl?
What does she look like? Any details?
She looked very girly, sir.
Stephen went to a church
before he surrendered, Seema.
We'd collected the footage
by tracking his car number.
We thought that he just went
to pray before surrendering.
Now this video makes me wonder.
Stephen is not a believer, Michael.
What if he had gone there
to see someone?
And what if he surrendered
to save that person?
Maybe.
Which church did Stephen go to?
St. Mary's Church, Thondamuthur.
Michael, I told you about a Christianity
band I got from his house, right?
That band had the same church's name.
You see, every year,
we organize a youth retreat.
To restore faith in today's youngsters.
Just two months ago, we organized one.
This looks like a wristband
from that retreat.
Father, is there a list of the attendants?
Sure. Give me an official request letter.
I'll share.
Father, it's impossible for us
to operate this officially.
The entire media is frantic
to get any news about him.
Moreover, there is a CCTV footage
of him coming to the church.
That's why.
Usually,
there will be separate colors
for male and female.
This specific color is for a female.
So, Stephen was not alone
in these murders.
There was a girl with him.
The girl mentioned
by the guard in Chennai
and the owner of the band
could be the same, right?
If we remove the men from this list,
there are 159 names in total.
Sorry, 158.
What next?
That guard mentioned that
the girl is the same age as Stephen.
So, keep anyone in the age bracket
of 22-25 and remove the rest.
Seventy-two in total. What now?
Hopefully, our girl
should be one among this 72.
Interesting.
So, you have also failed at times?
At times. Never mind it.
Okay. Seems like
subtlety is not your thing.
Didn't the police look into this?
They did.
But only after I killed two or three.
I have gone through many
police check posts with bodies in my car.
No one suspected me.
I have an innocent face.
Didn't you share this
with anyone in Chennai?
No.
I don't get along
with anyone that quickly.
So you were alone there?
Yes.
Didn't you kill anyone in Chennai?
Stephen?
I told you, right?
I tried to kill that sex worker.
After that, I ran away from Chennai.
Are you sure?
Madam, I already told you no, right?
- Okay, so when you were in Chennai--
- Madam...
enough.
- Can we continue tomorrow?
- Why?
No...
It's enough.
Sure. No problem.
Excuse me.
Stephen.
Don't get into any negative thoughts.
Any problem, I'm just a call away.
Okay, madam.
- Hello
- Hello.
Stephen is hiding something big.
He's fumbling a lot
when I mention Chennai.
For the first time ever,
he asked to stop the discussion.
For now, we have to find
that girl from church soon.
We'll catch her.
How?
How can I do this, sir?
Please, Father. Try to understand.
He's committed a lot of murders till date.
We have to pursue with even
the smallest of leads regarding him.
If Stephen finds out about it
from the media,
it will be a very big problem, Father.
We cannot deal this as usual.
Sir! You always keep saying
this is a media problem.
That is the truth, Father.
This is a very sensitive case.
Our every movement
is fodder for the media.
What should I do now?
Tell me clearly.
Father,
we should get the 72 girls on this list
to come to the church.
How?
In the Bible, there's someone
named Stephen, right?
Yes. St. Stephen.
- What about him?
- Tell me a little about him.
St. Stephen was the first
to sacrifice his life for Jesus.
He was beaten to death
for preaching Jesus's principles.
Even as he was dying,
he believed that God would forgive
those who killed him.
You can tell this to the girls, Father.
This? How?
Say that St. Stephen came in your dream.
Seems like someone has lied to him.
So, he seems to be very angry on us.
Hence we should ask Jesus for forgiveness.
Tomorrow... Tomorrow is Sunday, right?
Tell them there is a prayer tomorrow
and ask them to come.
Okay.
Michael, they have been waiting
for quite some time.
Shall I start the prayer?
You carry on, Father.
Raju, have our guys taken the list?
It'll be done in ten minutes, sir.
Are you not going
to interrogate any of them?
Even after our lie about St. Stephen,
so many girls have come.
It's doubtful that there is a link
between killer Stephen and them.
There are a few
who have not shown up today.
We need to track them first.
What if there's no clue in that?
No other option, Father,
but to interrogate the entire list.
Let's see, Father.
The Lord shall be with you.
Sister, how many are here?
Fifty eight, sir.
Why have you asked for them to come, sir?
I'll tell you.
Have you ticked the attendees?
Yes, sir. Hand it to him.
Sir.
Our team's list.
Raju, ask Ravi to track the location
of the 14 girls who didn't come.
Okay, sir.
Michael?
What are you doing here?
I was looking for you.
What happened at the church today?
I have checked the girls
who did not attend the prayer.
All of them had valid reasons.
I thought she'll get caught, but it looks
like we have to interrogate all of them.
For that, I've to get permission,
explain the situation.
The important thing
is to keep this information secure.
Why do you have two lists?
One was given by the Father
and checked by the nuns at the front desk.
The other one was taken live by our team.
Have you thoroughly inquired
about the 15 non-attendees?
You don't suspect even one of them?
Not 15. Only 14.
See, look at this.
Your list has 57 names, right?
So, out of 72, if 57 attended,
then it is 15 who didn't attend, right?
Look at this.
The nuns at the church ticked this list.
There are 58 names ticked in this.
Raju? Did you get details
from all the attendees?
Of course, sir. What happened?
You sure we didn't miss anyone?
Sure, sir. There is no chance of missing.
Okay.
Michael.
This name is not in your list.
Mary John.
How the hell did I miss her?
Maybe she would've guessed that
you're police and escaped immediately.
Michael? Where are you going?
I want to know how the nuns ticked
Mary's name which wasn't on our list.
Will anyone be in the church at this time?
That priest's house
is inside the church compound.
I'll come along.
Sir! Madam!
Stephen attempted suicide.
What if Mary has informed Stephen
about our movements?
You go look into Stephen.
I'll ask Raju to come.
I'll take care of Mary.
Seema!
Careful.
Father. Emergency.
Michael?
Mary's name was ticked off by the nuns.
But that name is not on our list.
I don't get it. Calm down.
- Sister.
- Sir?
- You were at the front desk, right?
- Yes, sir.
Did you tick Mary's name?
That name is not on our list.
How can you tick a non-attendee?
No, sir. I wouldn't have done that.
What's the name again?
Mary John.
Mary John? She was there, sir.
Then how is she not on our list?
Maybe your team would've missed
because she didn't sit inside.
Why didn't she sit inside?
Because she was sitting with me.
Didn't you see?
Where? Where? Where?
Is Mary John...
a nun?
No, sir.
She joined here only two months back.
Can I get her address?
You must've passed by her.
She was at the front.
Mary.
Is this your band?
Yes.
How long have you known Stephen?
For the past few months.
Did Stephen come to see you
at the church on July 8th?
Yes.
What did you guys talk about?
Nothing at all.
Do you have anything to do
with Stephen's crimes?
Are you his family?
Who are you then?
I was supposed to be his...
tenth victim.
Sorry?
That's what Stephen said to me.
Then how did you escape?
Stephen dropped me back at my house.
He said it was not safe
to travel alone late night.
What next?
Did he buy you a packet
of milk and bread?
Mary, since you come from a holy place,
I'm treating you politely.
If you continue to lie, we'll expose you
as Stephen's lover or accomplice.
If you tell the truth,
everything will go smoothly.
Stephen was right.
This is why he told me
not to go to the police.
Did he?
He said the good have no business there.
That's exactly what's happening now.
I'm being threatened.
Then tell the truth.
If you're so good and pious,
what have you been doing with Stephen?
I started believing in the Lord
only after he let me live.
In fact, this is my second life.
Then how did you get the wristband?
Didn't you attend the youth retreat?
I did attend.
Because of my parents' compulsion.
I was an actor back then,
doing short films and web series.
That's how I went to Stephen's house
that day for an audition.
I'm not sure what exactly happened.
He suddenly got emotional.
If I don't understand you, then who will?
Okay.
Please wait for two minutes.
Do you have so much faith in love?
I believe love has the ultimate power
to save life at any situation.
Stephen, is that a prop?
No. I've killed nine people with this.
You were supposed to be my tenth victim.
But I don't feel
like killing you anymore.
My heart is telling me
to surrender myself to the police.
Keep this for your safety.
I will drop you back.
Please sit in the back.
Mary.
Thanks for understanding.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
I don't know how my life will turn
after I surrender.
Can I see you for one last time?
We don't even have to talk.
Just want to see you.
Please?
My mom regularly visits
St. Mary's Church, Thondamuthur.
I can go with her tomorrow.
I'll be there as well.
Stay away from the police.
Good people like you
have no place there.
If there's no news
about my surrender tomorrow,
please don't be in this house.
The next day,
I went to church with fear.
Stephen was waiting for me.
We didn't talk.
He watched me from a distance and left.
Why didn't you come to us
after Stephen surrendered?
I saw in the news
that he confessed to all his crimes.
What more can I add?
So, after that, you became a believer?
I barely survived this situation.
I sacrificed my acting, my passion
by devoting myself to the church.
Sir.
News from Chennai.
Mary's photo was shown
to that security guard for identification.
Mary is not the girl
who stayed with Stephen.
Also, Stephen did not attempt suicide.
Someone poisoned his coffee.
We are investigating
if it's the victims' relatives.
What do you think?
Mary doesn't seem to be lying.
We are definitely missing something.
But I'm not sure what it is.
Mary, give your details to Raju.
If summoned for further enquiry,
you should come immediately.
Mary?
What was the audition scene
he asked you to act?
A story about a serial killer.
He said it was a love scene from that.
Love?
You mean,
Stephen was in love with someone?
Apparently, the girl loved him back too.
A girl was in love with Stephen?
That's what he said.
Did he say her name?
Kir... Keerthana?
Krithika.
Krithika?
What did he make you enact that day?
Can you please elaborate?
Have you been in love, Stephen?
Then who's Krithika?
Michael.
Hey girl, it's you
A magnet that pulls me
The eyes that transcend the soul
Your beaming smile
Mesmerizes me
You cast a spell on me
I'm not myself 'cause of you
You blended into my soul
Don't you pass as a dream
You are my love island
My partner for life
You are the walking moon on earth
My beloved moon
I'll wait for you
Will never leave
It's like raining flowers
When you kiss
Let's surpass time
As it never exists
I've lost the path, seeking alone
Your sparkling eyes are a welcoming beacon
In the thought of accompanying you
I lost my soul in you
My words and breath
Raves about your smile, and you
Heaven and Earth
Singing your beauty as a masterpiece
Do you believe in such traditions?
Trust me. This will reunite us
even in our next lives.
Don't be a footprint on the shore
Hey, my dearest rainbow
Won't you slowly settle with me?
In snow or sun, I'll keep you safe
In Pain or pleasure, I'll be your shoulder
You are the walking moon on earth
My beloved moon
I'll wait for you
Will never leave
It's like raining flowers
When you kiss
Let's surpass time
As it never exists
Leaving my past behind,
I wanted to start my life afresh,
with my Krithika in our new home.
But it was too late.
The damage was already done.
Stephen?
Stephen!
You've hung me
a centimeter lower than your mom.
Hang me higher, son.
Don't listen to him!
Let me be at the top.
Petty fool,
you don't deserve to be framed.
- Shut up and hang below me.
- Yeah, right.
You deserve a statue,
but he framed you instead.
First of all, it's a shame
that I'm letting you talk.
Good-for-nothing.
Marrying you was
the worst mistake of my life. Bloody pest!
I'm unable to escape from you,
even after my death.
Mind you, I'll whoop your ass!
Stephen, fix it.
Don't you dare, Stephen.
Do it, son.
Don't do it.
Do it.
- Don't do it.
- Do it.
- Don't.
Krithika.
Yeah?
I lied to you.
I've told you a million times
not to lie to me.
Okay. What is it?
Tell me.
I killed my parents.
Don't blabber.
I'm not.
The police report is fake.
I killed my parents.
What are you saying?
Yes.
Things got ugly that night.
They didn't let me leave for Chennai.
I killed them.
Krithika, you won't leave me, right?
Krithika, it wasn't my fault.
You won't leave me, right?
Tell me.
Tell me, Krithika.
No, Stephen.
- Tell me.
- Go to bed, please.
Stephen, sleep.
Let's talk in the morning. Now sleep.
You know about them, right?
Krithika.
Yeah?
I lied to you again.
What is it?
I didn't kill my parents.
That's what I thought.
Why would you joke about this?
He killed them.
He killed them, Krithika.
Not me.
It was him!
He killed them, Krithika.
- Not me.
- Okay, Stephen. Sleep.
Let's talk tomorrow.
It wasn't me, Krithika.
He killed them.
She's lying, dude. She's a liar.
Why did you tell her?
You should've shut your mouth! As soon as
you fall asleep, she'll go to the police.
We're going to jail. We're doomed forever.
Following that night,
my whole life was a blur.
Krithika.
Can you take a week off?
What's wrong?
I'm not feeling well. That's why.
Okay.
You scared me!
Where are you going?
To the office. There's a lot of pressure
as I didn't go for a week.
They're forcing me to come from today.
Krithika.
Let me drop you.
Let's go.
Hey! Did I scare you?
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
Dude.
Even after all of this,
my Krithika believed in our love.
I know her since childhood, dude.
She's not like that.
She promised
that she'll be there for us, right?
It's better we go to the police station.
Why are you punishing me
for your mistake?
You fool, how can I go inside her office?
It's nighttime. Please let me sleep.
She's sleeping peacefully.
Why do you torture me,
saying she'll rat us out to the police?
I'm trying my best, Stephen.
But nothing is working out.
Can we consult a doctor?
How dare she call us insane? Who's insane?
She's the one who needs therapy.
She's not our Krithika anymore.
She's pretending to deceive us!
Do you still trust her?
God knows what she's up to.
Soon you'll learn your lesson!
Let's not do this.
I'm really scared.
I don't want the pills.
I'm not crazy.
It's not normal to kill one's parents.
I can understand why you did it.
But you don't seem
to have come to terms with it.
So, I'm not normal to you?
Huh?
- Am I not normal?
- Sweetheart, you know I never said that.
Then what is it?
You're not getting punished
on the outside for your crimes.
But your inner self is killing you.
Can't you see that?
Say what you want.
But please don't say
that my parents are normal.
Their whole existence was a crime.
On top of that, they gave birth to me--
Stephen!
We have talked about this a million times.
We have to move forward from this.
Tell me if you are afraid.
I'll turn myself in for you.
Surrender?
What would I do without you?
I'm doing this for us, sweetheart.
No.
I can't. You are free to leave.
- You can go.
- Stephen, Stephen.
Look.
Our love is enough to save us.
- Let me go.
- Stephen.
Come to me if you have faith in me.
I'll be waiting for you.
Everything will be fine, Krithika.
Trust me.
I'm getting better. I promise.
Stephen.
I'm really sick, dear.
Can I go and be with my grandma
for a day or two?
What are you going to do there?
I won't do anything.
I'll just be with Grandma.
You won't do anything, right?
Then stay here and do nothing.
Why are you talking like this?
You must go?
Then accept the truth.
That you want to rat me out to the police
and hang me to death.
I swear it's not like that.
Will I ever lie to you, sweetheart?
Stop with your "sweetheart" bullshit.
Just accept it.
I'll let you go.
Accept it. I'll let you go.
Please, Stephen.
What are you doing?
What is all this drama?
I don't want any of this.
Say, "You are a mad killer."
"I can't be with you."
"I pretended to be in love with you."
"I'm going to rat you out."
Then I'll let you go.
No, nothing like that.
Stephen.
Accept it.
Then I'll let you go.
So, if I accept it, you'll let me go?
Yes, I will.
Okay, then.
Everything you said is true.
I'm going to the police.
Let me go.
I trusted you so much.
How dare you?
Come on, cops. Come get me!
Krithika. Come here.
What?
I feel better now,
after leaving my past behind.
- Come.
- Hey.
Shall we get married?
I mistook the sirens.
I was wrong.
She was the only good thing in my life.
The only one for me.
Killing her
was the biggest mistake of my life.
That's why I hid it for so long.
I can never be with my Krithika anymore.
That is the biggest punishment
anyone can give me.
I lost control after that.
In search of Krithika's love,
I killed nine girls with my own hands.
But when Mary showed me that love,
I realized...
I could never kill Mary.
That's why I dropped Mary at her house
and surrendered.
I could have avoided
the suffering of countless families.
Mom, Dad, my Krithika...
and the nine girls...
I wish I never killed any of them.
I could have lived a peaceful life
like everyone else.
Look here, at your grandma, honey!
In the end,
I was far too gone to turn back.
Seema. Seema.
Seema.
Krithika only has a grandmother.
Her parents passed away
when she was young.
Poor grandmother.
She's not able to grasp the situation.
What do you think, madam?
When we assessed as a team,
he seems stable now, Your Honor.
But he was unstable
during those murders.
I'm not sure whether
I pity Stephen or am angry at him.
Is he fit to stand trial?
Yes.
Does he need regular counseling?
Possibly, Your Honor.
People with a worse past
have led a normal life.
People with a normal past
have led a very violent life.
So the past and present are just reasons.
Does he have remorse?
Yes.
All right. You can go.
Depending on the choices and decisions
an individual makes,
he will be deemed good or bad.
According to the investigation
and reports submitted by Dr. Seema's team,
I'm about to hand my verdict.
Court is a place to unravel the truth.
That's the sole purpose
of law and justice.
Such a place
cannot be used for revenge.
Forgiveness and love
help the world function.
Moreover, Stephen was mentally ill
at the time of the crimes,
and he shows deep remorse
for his wrongdoings.
I hereby sentence the accused Stephen
to a double life sentence.
I advise the prison administration
to pay attention to his mental health
and guide him on the right track.
Court dismissed.
WE WANT JUSTICE...!!
First, stop him!
Clear the way!
Please clear out!
Take cover. Take cover.
Cover up.
- Please move.
- Get him on the bus.
Get in. Get in. Get in.
Start the vehicle. Leave. Go. Go.
Please don't ask anything now.
Don't ask anything now, madam.
We can't comment now.
Nothing can be said. Case is closed.
No comments, please.
The court has given its verdict.
We can't do anything. This is over.
"THE END"
- WITH UTMOST SINCERITY, STEPHEN.
Hey, that's enough, dude.
You also join, dude.
Was it good?
Stephen.
You killed Kuttan, right?
Open your mouth and tell the truth.
Dad didn't kill Kuttan. Say it was you!
I had a sudden urge to kill it.
Hence I did it.
I made two big mistakes in my life.
Became an alcoholic
because I couldn't be a great player.
Then...
loving you unconditionally.
You were the one who set up the cameras
in the students' dressing room, right?
Yes, it was me.
Sad! Dad took the blame for it.
But do you know something?
When I grew up,
I lost my interest in women.
My focus was only on killings.
You were killing cats and dogs
to satisfy your urge.
But soon, you turned towards humans.
Accept that you sliced up your mom,
who objected to it.
Also, accept that you threatened your dad
to confess and then slit his throat.
But why did you kill us?
What was our sin?
Speak up, you filthy dog!
Hey! Who was that?
Huh?
- You say it.
- Filthy dog.
Not you.
- You say it.
- Filthy dog.
- No. You?
Got you!
Huh?
I don't even remember your name.
And how dare you join with them
and call me names?
I'll thrash you.
First of all, whose family poisoned me?
Huh?
That too, in my favorite coffee.
Open your mouth, good-for-nothings.
You all wonder why I killed you?
Only then
will your souls find peace, right?
I missed Krithika at times.
That's why I made you all
audition like her, and killed you.
How polite was I with you all!
Did I misbehave with any of you?
Because I only find the thrill in killing.
I am not interested in anything else.
Understood?
You all are not important in my life.
I'll be doing ten pushups now.
Make sure you all disappear
before I finish my set. Okay?
Please understand.
And don't annoy me.
Dad? How's my form?
Give your feedback, Dad.
Mom, talk to me.
You have all the rights.
Sweetheart?
We used to talk for hours.
How come you're not saying anything?
Say something, dear.
Please move aside. Move.
Look at you!
When we were in the zone, I slipped up
slightly, and confessed to killing them.
But you were like,
"Go, surrender, Stephen,
I'll wait for you."
Really?
I've woven so many lies about Mom and Dad.
But you tried to lie to me?
That you were going to wait for me.
So, I had to kill you too.
But go and ask others.
You, me, our love...
I've sung songs about our love
and portrayed you like an angel.
There's a possibility
that you might've wings right now.
We raised you well.
How did you turn up like this?
Raised me well? Huh?
I was beaten regularly.
But we did that to correct you.
But did that help?
All the time, you both were picking on me.
That was kind of annoying.
So, I got rid of you both.
Actually, I didn't plan to kill Daddy.
But what if he fumbles to the police?
So I slit his throat just to be safe.
But had I known that Moorthy would come
to the spot, I wouldn't have killed him.
Sorry Dad.
Someone will definitely unravel
all the truths about you.
Wait and watch.
Who, Mom?
Seema?
Or Michael?
What is this, Mom?
Everything was a plan, Mom.
Supposedly, if I had been caught
by the police after killing Mary,
they would've killed me on the spot.
This Michael would've put
a gun in my mouth.
They are "good" men.
That's why I made a plan to surrender.
Then I wrote many tests, passed those,
convinced Seema, diverted her to Krithika,
made Michael run around,
brought Mary into the scene,
confused them, cleared them, and so on...
Good Lord!
Had to do too much homework.
Can anyone of you do this?
Tell me. Can you?
All you know is how to die.
Do you know how to survive?
You should know.
You should know how to play with emotions,
manipulate people, cheat, and survive.
You should know all those things!
Only then can you handle this cruel world.
The good people
will eventually end up like you all.
Even after all of my drama,
I was scared about the judge's verdict.
I was holding on to my dear life,
thinking what if he decides to hang me.
Thank God.
He gave me double-life time.
Jail life is not easy, Stephen.
Twenty-eight years!
Oh, you were waiting
all along to say this?
What is this, Dad?
Wait and watch,
I will be out in ten years,
based on my good behavior.
Now, my age is 25.
After 10 years, I'll be 35 or 36.
The point is,
I'll still be alive and kicking.
Will such a life bring you
happiness and peace, Stephen?
Did such a life bring you
happiness and peace, Krithika?
You're still as innocent as ever.
Hey, Daddy. Take a hike, man.
What are you waiting for?
You think this bus will topple?
Nothing like that will happen.
Leave.
Then, don't you all forget.
I must be on my best behavior.
Don't try to trigger me inside the jail.
Krithika?
Would you have really waited for me?
Forget it.
What would I do with your answer now?
It's too late! It's too late!
Leave, leave.
Go, go, go.
If you think I'm crazy, maybe I am.
CRAZY!
If you think I'm evil,
maybe I am.
EVIL!
But for me, I'm just...
No matter how many times I say,
the fact remains true.
I've been wired like this.
What to do?
Committing murder is a...
crime under the law.
Do not share this with anyone. All right?
I still can't figure out
how he disposed of all the dead bodies.
What he said may be true indeed.
He may not know anything
besides throwing them in that forest.
We have been monitoring
that forest till now.
There's no unusual activity, also.
Not even wild animals.
In the second phase of the investigation
of the young women serial murder case,
as per the statement
of the serial killer, Stephen Jebaraj,
it is in the forests of Anaikadu,
near Sathyamangalam in Erode district,
where the bodies were disposed of.
Inspector Michael and team
rushed to the scene yesterday,
only to find no corpse
despite a thorough search.
Only a few ornaments
and evidences were found.
They belonged to the victims,
Surekha and Preethi.
SP George has ordered the public
and media not to go to the spot.
Questions have been raised
as to the veracity of the killer, Stephen.
Where exactly are the missing bodies?