[pensive music]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[suspenseful music]
[upbeat suspenseful music]
[water splashing]
[helicopter whirring]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[water splashing]
[motors revving]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[helicopter whirring]
[motors revving]
[radio chattering]
[rescuers chattering]
[door hisses and clatters]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[radio chattering]
[rescuers chattering]
[straps ripping]
[radio chattering]
[rescuers chattering]
[upbeat suspenseful intensifies]
[intense music]
[heart monitor beeping]
[Sam breathing]
[Sam groans softly]
[pensive music]
[door clatters and buzzes]
[footsteps tapping]
You're awake.
[Sam groans]
[bowl clinking]
[Sam coughs]
Totally normal.
[Sam sighing]
- Where's the, uh, costume
party?
[both chuckle]
- It's just precautionary
measures until you're discharged.
- Oh, I don't know, I think I
might bar this for Halloween.
What do you think?
[Sam chuckles softly]
[Ethan] Congratulations
on your first successful
mission, Sam.
- Thank you.
- Happy to be back?
No. [chuckles softly]
No, I could have stayed up there
forever.
Though, when I feel better,
I would love a cheeseburger.
[both chuckle]
I think we can arrange that.
Hm.
- Sam, can you describe
to me how you're feeling?
Um. [sighs]
Heavy.
Dizzy.
I saw that pen float.
- [chuckles softly]
Anti-gravity, hallucination.
All to be expected.
What's going on here?
- [Michelle] Scan show deep
swelling, but no fracture,
you probably slammed it on
impact.
- We lost communication
with you on reentry, Sam.
What happened up there?
- I got the splashdown
coordinates from mission control.
Everything seemed to be on
track, and,
and then I hit something maybe.
- [Michelle] Do you know
when you lost consciousness?
- I guess in pre-fall.
Is everything okay?
[pensive music]
[Michelle sighs]
- [Michelle] Something
punctured your capsule
and shattered your helmet.
What do you think it was?
- [Michelle] Could have
been meteor debris.
We're testing the particles
we found on your space suit.
You're lucky you survived.
[alarm buzzes]
[Mark] There she is.
Mommy.
[gasps] Busy Izzy, hi.
I miss you so much.
I miss you more.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
They just, they're making me
stay
in this funny chair for a while.
But look, I'm okay.
[Izzy chuckles]
- Daddy, you miss mommy too,
right?
[Mark chuckles softly]
[door blares]
- Look who's here.
- Grandpa.
Hey, pumpkin. [chuckles]
Mark.
[Mark] Good to see you, Will.
You too.
How you doing, kiddo?
I'm okay.
You did not have to come here.
- My daughter just returned
from her first mission in space,
I'm not supposed to come.
No.
[Sam chuckles]
- The team just filled
me in on what happened.
Sounds like a very close call.
- We're all very glad that
you're okay.
Yeah, me too.
- Actually, uh, the Pentagon's
gonna join NASA on this one.
Really?
- We're working on decoding
electrical frequencies
that we picked up during your
reentry,
so there's mutual interest.
- There's been a media
frenzy about your landing.
- The department has secured
a beautiful house nearby
for your recovery, outta the
spotlight.
You and Izzy won't have to
deal with any of that stuff.
- Hey, will you come visit
Mommy, huh?
Yeah, yes, of course.
[knuckles rapping]
Come in.
- Sorry to interrupt. We
need to run a few more tests
before you're cleared
and prepped for transpo,
but then you'll be all
done with quarantine.
Okay, time to go.
We'll see you soon.
Say bye to mommy, sweetheart.
Hey.
When I see you next,
I'm gonna give you the biggest
hug in the whole world, okay?
- [Mark] Remember what
we talked about, okay?
[dramatic music]
Who do I love?
Hmm?
Me.
Can't hear you, who do I love?
- Me.
- Yeah.
See you soon.
I'll see you soon.
[gentle music]
♪ Where
♪ Do we go from here
[vehicle engines revving]
♪ Where
♪ Do we go from here
♪ Baby
♪ I know you love me
♪ Make me strong
♪ Don't make me weak
♪ Get me that candy
♪ Play with my mind
♪ You're begging me down
♪ You're not making me strong
♪ I know that you want
♪ Baby
♪ And I won't be too long
♪ Where
♪ Do we go from here
[car door clicks]
- [Guard] You want this for a
bit?
Captain, I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Yeah, thank you.
[car door thuds]
[Guard] Okay.
[birds chirping]
Welcome.
[Sam sighs]
Body's reacclimating the
gravity,
careful pushing yourself too
hard.
Don't want you passing out on
us.
[Sam chuckles softly]
- [Sam] This really is
something.
Your dad's very proud of you.
[Sam chuckles]
- [Sam] To an embarrassing
degree.
I'm gonna give you the tour.
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hm.
[keys jingling]
[birds chirping]
[pensive music]
- [Michelle] 10 acres
of Virginia wilderness,
only 30 minutes from DC.
[footsteps tapping]
- It's a bit nicer than my
place.
- Apparently, the government
bought this land in the '50s
for weapons testing.
General Harris tells us
it's just mostly housing
for diplomats now.
Next house is miles away.
Oh.
Sounds like a horror movie.
[Michelle chuckles]
The house is two stories.
Up here, we have the bathroom,
library,
fully stocked kitchen,
dining, and living room.
In the nook back there
is where we'll do some
of your medical tests.
This is amazing.
- Downstairs, there's three
bedrooms,
three bathrooms, a den, and a
home gym,
which is about to be your new
best friend
because as you know, atrophy is.
A bitch.
[chuckles] Yes, ma'am.
[door scrapes]
I'm sure you miss space.
[birds chirping]
- I used to have one just like
this.
[Sam groaning]
[high-pitched ringing]
[crowd chattering]
[fire crackling]
[Sam groaning]
[vehicle engines revving]
[crowd chattering]
[Michelle] Are you okay?
[Sam groaning]
[crowd chattering]
What's wrong?
[groans] Just so ringing.
[Sam groaning]
- It's tinnitus, stay super
calm,
and just weighty that, it'll
pass.
Feeling better?
Yeah. [chuckles softly]
[pensive music]
[water sloshing]
Thank you.
- I know you were briefed
pre-flight,
but just as a reminder,
expect everything from nausea
to dizziness, fever,
nosebleeds, hallucinations.
The human body takes time to
remember
how to function on earth.
Right.
- The more you report back to
us,
the better we'll be able to
determine
if we need to consider
delaying future missions.
Delaying future missions?
- If you exhibit any unusual
symptoms
or severe side effects,
we can't just send you back to
training.
All right.
Um.
So, sorry, I'm just, it's,
I'm supposed to go out
to the ISS in, um, two months.
- Honestly, I wouldn't worry
about it.
Obviously, I'd rather have
you monitored at base,
but I don't wanna step on any
toes.
We'll be here every
morning at 7:30 on the dot,
so make sure you're up and
ready.
Get plenty of rest.
Copy that. [chuckles softly]
- These next few days will
be over before you know it.
[footsteps tapping]
If you need anything, just call
us.
[glass thuds]
See you tomorrow.
[footsteps tapping]
[door thuds]
[Sam sighing]
[thermometer beeps]
[pensive music]
[jazz music]
♪ Stay away from your front door
♪
♪ [indistinct] no more
♪ But I love you, oh, so badly
♪ Don't you know that I love you
madly ♪
♪ I can't stay
♪ I can't say
♪ Away
♪ Yeah, I can't say away now
♪ I can't say away
♪ Oh, no, no, no, baby
♪ Stay away
♪ Stay away from your house
[vocalist sings indistinctly]
♪ Stay away
♪ But I love you, oh, so badly
♪ Don't you know that I love you
madly ♪
♪ I can't stay
[tablet beeping]
[footsteps tapping]
Holy shit, you're alive.
[Sam] Val. [chuckles]
- I've never held my breath for
so long.
Don't ever do that to me again,
please.
- I know, they're still
trying to figure out
what happened to me.
- [Val] That's all
everybody's talking about.
I'm sure.
But hey, look.
Look where I'm staying.
Oh.
Hearing like a nice swanky chic
oasis.
[Sam chuckles]
And I didn't get an invite.
Sam.
[suspenseful music]
Hello?
[rain pattering]
Earth to Sam.
Sam, what is it?
Sam.
Sorry, um.
I just thought I,
I thought I just saw something.
[rain pattering]
[suspenseful music]
[creature growls]
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam sighing]
Sorry.
- So, you dying to get back up
there?
The first time in space is such
a tease.
- I've never felt more at home
than I did
when I was up there.
- You're more obsessed with
space than anybody I know,
and that's saying a lot.
- I'm starting to feel symptoms
though.
I had a nosebleed.
Girl.
Remember, in training, they
tell you to report everything,
I'm telling you, don't.
Even if you feel horrible,
keep it to your damn self,
because they will never let you
fly again.
I know.
I'm not gonna tell them any
of this, I already know that.
- I mean, I may as well be
Wonder Woman at this point,
they get a whiff that your
immune system isn't working,
and you're sick or
something, they'll demote you
to clean and puke off
the motion simulator.
- [chuckles] Literally, can't
think of anything worse.
- Listen, you wanna go back to
space,
you have to downplay everything.
Your symptoms will take
a while to go away.
But next time around,
this'll all feel normal.
It's just 'cause it's your first
time.
[dog barking]
All right, you rest up,
I'm gonna come visit you at your
oasis.
[Sam chuckles]
I love you.
- I love you, I love you,
I love you. [lips smack]
Bye.
[rain pattering]
[Sam sighs]
[lights buzzing]
[objects thudding]
[rain pattering]
Hello?
[footsteps tapping]
[pensive music]
What the?
[suspenseful music]
[footsteps tapping]
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[suspenseful music continues]
[jacket rustles]
[switch clicks]
[rain pattering]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
What?
[Sam breathing heavily]
[ominous music continues]
[stone clatters]
[Sam groans]
[crowd chattering]
[ominous music continues]
[vehicle engines revving]
[Sam groans]
[crowd chattering]
[alarm clock blaring]
[Sam gasps]
[Sam sighs]
[Sam exhales]
[pensive music]
[footsteps tapping]
[gentle music]
[fridge door clatters]
[fridge door thuds]
[butter thuds and sizzles]
[switch clicks]
[button beeps]
♪ Sittin' on a red hot stove
♪ It's gonna be fine
♪ Oh, baby
♪ Sittin' on a red hot stove
♪ It's gonna be fine
♪ And baby sing
♪ Sittin' on a red hot stove
♪ It's gonna be fine
♪ Cool me baby
[pensive music]
[Michelle] Hello?
[egg cracks]
Oh.
Just in the kitchen.
[footsteps tapping]
Good morning.
The medical team's here if
you're ready.
I'll be right there.
[footsteps tapping]
[bell clinks]
[Sam gasps]
[Sam sighs]
[gentle music]
[footsteps tapping]
[puzzles clicking]
[Sam panting]
[weights hissing]
[Sam groans]
You all right?
[Sam panting]
Ah, yeah.
I think it's just grip, it's
passing.
[Sam panting]
[gentle music]
[ice plastics rustling]
[footsteps tapping]
[glass clinks]
- The electrolytes will
make you feel good as new.
Mm.
I think I'm past electrolytes.
Day one's intense.
- Well, the rest of the day is
like.
- The more we can monitor your
progress,
the more data we can collect
to better the space program.
- Well, I'm happy to be of
service.
[Michelle] How's the tinnitus?
- It hasn't happened again.
- Awesome.
Any more hallucinations?
- Mm-mm.
- You'll be back in
flying shape in no time.
Just relax the rest of the day,
we'll be back the same
time again tomorrow.
[Sam] Okay.
Make sure to stretch.
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam panting]
[door clicks]
[Sam groans]
[plastic bags rustle]
[Sam sighs]
[phone ringing]
Hey, can you see me?
- Yeah, I can see you, can you
see me?
Yeah.
Hey.
Um.
I was thinking, when I get outta
here,
why don't we go on a family
trip, huh?
Just the three of us
on the beach somewhere.
- I don't know if that's a good
idea, Sam.
Why not?
- I just don't think it's
healthy
for Izzy to see us together
if that's not how it's gonna be.
Come on.
We're still figuring things
out, but we're a family.
Sam, we almost lost you.
We almost lost you.
- [Sam] I want Izzy to
have the family I didn't.
It's just been hard.
- I know it was scary
for you guys, but I'm,
I'm okay.
We're proud of you.
We know that you're one
of a handful of people
that do what you do, we get it,
but you've been MIA for
six months for training.
You're gonna be gone again
for God knows how long
for the next mission
- That, come on, that's not
fair.
You know how important
this mission is to me.
[dramatic music]
And how important you are and,
and Izzy.
- I thought adopting was
gonna bring us closer
when you couldn't.
When we couldn't.
It did.
It has.
Mommy, I made this for you.
[Sam chuckles]
Wow.
Sweetie, is that us?
That's me, daddy and you.
What's that up there?
- Space people.
[phone buzzing]
Ah, shoot.
It's the university, I gotta
take this.
We'll come by and see you
tomorrow, yeah?
Say bye to mommy, baby.
Bye, Mommy.
See you soon.
Bye, baby, I'll see you soon.
[phone beeps]
[birds chirping]
[footsteps tapping]
[high-pitched ringing]
[Sam groans]
[crowd chattering]
[fire crackling]
[Sam groans]
[smoke whooshes]
[crowd chattering]
[birds chirping]
[Sam panting]
[suspenseful music]
[leaves rustling]
[device beeping]
[suspenseful music continues]
[leaves rustling]
[footsteps tapping]
[suspenseful music continues]
[leaves rustling]
[Sam sighs]
[suspenseful music continues]
[footsteps tapping]
[shoe thuds]
[leaves rustle]
[footsteps tapping]
[ominous music]
[Sam groans]
[head thuds]
Aw.
[suspenseful music]
[footsteps tapping]
[knuckles rapping]
[Sam gasps]
Sorry.
Didn't mean to startle you,
Captain.
How are you feeling?
Oh, what is going on?
We found you outside.
Your head was pretty banged up.
[footsteps tapping]
Who's we?
Dad?
Sam.
You gave us quite a scare
finding you out there like that.
[Sam sighs]
Come here.
[hand tapping]
You're supposed to be
getting some rest, kiddo.
- Mm-hmm.
[Sam sighs]
How'd you know where I was?
- We stopped by for a surprise
visit.
You weren't at home, so we did a
sweep.
[footsteps tapping]
Hey.
That'll be all right tomorrow.
- Mm-hm.
[footsteps tapping]
- [William] Let's get some fresh
air.
Okay.
[footsteps tapping]
[gentle music]
[birds chirping]
- You're part of
something really big here.
I'm very proud of you, Sam.
What did I see out there?
Security cameras, or were
they recording something?
- I didn't expect you to wind
it that far from the house.
Didn't think it was necessary
to debrief NASA on the, uh,
on the full rundown of the
property here.
What do you mean?
[suspenseful music]
[footsteps tapping]
[door clicks]
[William sighs]
After you.
[footsteps tapping]
[William sighs]
[secret door clatters and
hisses]
What is this place?
[suspenseful music continues]
Truth is,
it's a safe house.
[Sam scoffs]
It was very James Bond.
[William chuckles]
Follow me.
[footsteps tapping]
[secret door clatter and whirs]
[lights whirring]
- They probably told
you what we told them,
that this house is for
diplomats,
which is not entirely wrong.
[footsteps tapping]
Kinds of people that we normally
host here
are in need of temporary hiding.
[keypad beeping]
Izzy's birthday?
Shh.
[door clatters]
Sometimes a place like this is
more secure than an embassy.
It's amazing.
Sleeping quarters there.
[footsteps tapping]
Mess hall here.
Down here's
the central nervous system in
the house.
Runs on its own separate power
source.
Wow.
- And, uh, just to put your mind
at ease.
[switches clicking]
There are security cameras
outside all around the perimeter.
In an emergency, the house
totally shuts itself down,
locking everything behind
three layers of Kevlar
and copper paneling.
A lot of these switches are tied
to defense systems all around
the house.
And obviously, you won't need
any of this,
but I didn't want you to think
that we were spying on you.
It's good to know.
- [inhales] Anyway, uh,
big secret revealed.
Why don't we go back upstairs
before they come looking for us.
Okay.
[footsteps tapping]
[William sighs]
[monitors warble]
[secret doors clatter and
scrape]
- General Harris?
- Yes.
- It's 18:30, sir.
- Thank you.
I gotta get back to base.
- You all right if I go?
- Yeah, thanks.
[footsteps tapping]
- Probably best that you just
stay put,
try and get some rest.
And please be sure
that Dr. Aiden checks
out that bruise tomorrow.
[footsteps tapping]
[door clatters]
[suspenseful music]
[camera shutter clicks]
[message whooshes]
[phone clatters]
[cabinet clatters]
[pills rattle]
[cabinet clicks]
[water splashing]
[Sam gulps]
[glass clatters]
[message whooshes]
[crickets chirping]
[wind whooshing]
[bubbles popping]
[Sam sighs]
[object clatters]
[creature rattling]
[wind whooshing]
[crickets chirping]
[water sloshes]
- [footsteps tapping]
- [Mark] Hi, there.
You've reached Professor Mark
Walker, you know what to do.
[phone beeps]
Hey, it's me.
I, uh, can you just call
me back when you get this?
I'm not feeling great.
I just wanted to talk,
so hopefully, you're not
sleeping already.
Um, okay, bye.
[thunder rumbles]
[electricity buzzes]
Oh.
[flashlight clatters]
[footsteps tapping]
[thunder rumbles]
[door scrapes]
[crickets chirping]
[thunder rumbles]
[footsteps tapping]
[door scrapes and thuds]
[creature growls]
[footsteps tapping]
[electricity whirs]
[electricity crackling]
[suspenseful music]
[crickets chirping]
[door clicks]
[choir vocalizing intensely]
[door thuds]
[Sam sighs]
[device beeps]
[lock clicks]
[Sam sighs]
Keep it together.
[footsteps tapping]
- [Operator] Breach
detected, lockdown initiated.
[alarm blaring]
[suspenseful music]
[doors whirring]
[doors thud]
[keypad clicking]
[Sam panting]
[high-pitched ringing]
[Sam groaning]
[creature growls]
[Sam gasps]
[ominous music]
[footsteps tapping]
[door clatters]
[Sam panting]
[suspenseful music]
[creature growls]
[lid clatters]
[suspenseful music]
[switches clicking]
[lid clatters]
Oh, come on.
[door clatters]
[Sam sighs]
[door rattles]
[doorknob creaking]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[footsteps tapping]
[ominous music]
[choir vocalizing intensely]
[door clicks and creaks]
[Sam panting]
[footsteps tapping]
[ominous music]
[electricity buzzing]
[flashlight clatters]
[body thuds]
[Sam sighs]
[Sam panting]
[flashlight clicks]
[creature growling]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[intense music]
[Sam screams]
[footsteps tapping]
[door clatters]
[door clatters and whirs]
[door clatters and thuds]
[Sam panting]
[footsteps tapping]
[buttons clicking]
[intense music continues]
[monitors beeping]
[crickets chirping]
[eerie music]
[Sam gasps]
[eerie music intensifies]
[phone vibrating]
[Sam gasps]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[phone vibrating]
Oh, shit.
[footsteps tapping]
You all right, Sam?
Yeah, I think, uh.
There's, I think there's
something wrong with the generator.
Yeah.
Our system's showing
there's been some blackouts.
Might be a problem with the
grid, we'll check it out.
[footsteps tapping]
- Okay to begin testing,
Captain?
- Uh, yeah, I'll just be a
minute, I'm gonna change.
[footsteps tapping]
Can I talk to you for a second?
What's wrong?
Not enjoying architectural
digest Pentagon edition?
[Sam sighs]
Hey, talk to me.
There's something here.
Last night, I, maybe it was
in my mind or something,
but the whole house
went into lockdown mode,
and I almost had a heart attack,
I ended up sleeping in the
bunker.
- Jesus, I wish you had called
me.
I tried, there was no service.
- [William] You wanna
transfer back to base?
- [Sam] I don't want 'em
to know I'm struggling.
- I will scan all of the
security footage
while you're doing your testing.
And then, we'll find out
what the what is, okay?
- I'm sorry, I think I'm
just really stressed out.
Hey.
You don't have to apologize to
me, ever.
How's the bruising?
- I don't know, I haven't
even thought about it.
You got this.
- You all right?
- Mm-hm.
[William] Okay.
[William sighs]
[gentle music]
[tapes ripping]
[footsteps tapping]
[air whooshing]
[pedals whirring]
[Sam panting]
[gentle music continues]
- [Michelle] That doesn't look
like normal bruising, Sam.
That landing was no joke, huh?
- Let's do another extra
tomorrow.
[footsteps tapping]
[birds chirping]
[car engine revving]
[car doors thud and click]
[footsteps tapping]
- [chuckles] Hey.
- Mommy.
[footsteps tapping]
Hi, Busy Bee.
Oh, I missed you.
- How you doing?
- Hey.
Okay.
[door clatters]
[footsteps tapping]
- Makes our place look
like a college dorm.
[Izzy] Grandpa.
Hey, pumpkin.
Oh.
Look at you.
[William growls]
Cool coat.
Oh, you like that?
I like your hat.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey, what happened?
- I lost a teeth.
- When?
Mm, a few days ago.
- Did you give this child some
money?
[shoes thud]
You know, Isabelle,
right after I adopted your
mother,
one of the first gifts I gave
her
was a telescope just like that.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
What do you see, babe?
Let's go talk outside.
[footsteps tapping]
What's wrong?
What else?
- [Izzy] I think, I think I see
Jupiter.
Any stars?
I think I see the Milky Way.
Oh, there you go.
[Mark] Tell me.
[footsteps tapping]
I.
I have this crazy bruising
spreading all over my body,
and, um, I'm basically
seeing things that don't,
that aren't actually there.
Having these nightmares that.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- [sighs] I don't feel good.
Take a breath.
- I don't know to describe
it, I don't feel like myself.
- Have you reported this
to the medical team?
No.
[Sam sighs]
I can't risk not being able
to go on a mission again.
- This is your health,
we're talking about, Sam.
- Listen, I need to tell you
something.
[Sam breathing heavily]
I just, I, I need-
You're scaring me.
I just need you to promise me
that you're gonna believe me.
Yeah.
Yeah, what it is?
Um.
I saw something not
from here.
[pensive music]
What are you saying?
Something
not from
this world.
[Sam breathing heavily]
Okay.
I know it sounds nuts.
That's, I mean.
Why?
- I was broadcasting signals
deep into space, for what?
For, for fun?
I don't know what they were
communicating.
They registered sound waves
on the capsules receiver
right before they lost me.
What if something followed me
back?
[suspenseful music]
Maybe I'm just exhausted.
I think that we, uh.
- Mommy.
- We should.
[Izzy] I saw Pluto.
Oh.
[Izzy] I think I saw Pluto.
- [Sam] That's amazing.
- I guess we're gonna have
to get you a telescope
of your own, pumpkin.
Please, Daddy.
Yeah, yeah, sure, Izzy.
- Do you mind if I borrow
mommy for a minute?
I'll be right back.
[footsteps tapping]
[suspenseful music]
[switches clicking]
There, right there.
[monitor warbling]
Wh-
What?
What happened?
[William sighs]
It was right there.
- I swear.
- Look.
I know this process has been
tough on you, and the family.
[Sam sighs]
Maybe try to get some
sleep on the earlier side.
Lots of water.
- Dad, I'm telling you what I
saw.
It was right there and it,
[sighs]
looked like a.
Sam, listen.
Are you sure you wanna
push through another night?
Yeah, I will.
- All right, I gotta get back to
base. Um.
I think the power here is good.
Don't forget to lock up.
- Mm-hmm.
Sam, if you need anything?
You call me, yeah?
[Sam] Okay.
[footsteps tapping]
Love you.
[William] Love you, bear.
[switch clicking]
[buttons beeping]
[mouse clicks]
[monitors beeping]
[Operator] Analyzing.
There are nine individuals
detected.
[birds chirping]
[footstep tapping]
- [Mark] You wanna tell mom your
joke?
Yeah.
What kind of bee makes milk?
I don't know, what?
A booby.
A booby?
What? [chuckles]
Did your daddy tell you that
joke?
- No, she picked that
one up at school, huh?
Oh. [chuckles]
Jump.
[footsteps tapping]
Don't scurry off too far, okay?
[birds chirping]
[gentle music]
[twig cracks]
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music]
Iz.
Where'd she go?
- She's just here, she couldn't
have gone far. Isabelle!
Izzy, come back here.
Isabelle.
Izzy.
[Sam] Izzy.
Iz.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
- [Izzy] Look, what could I
found.
Honey.
Oh, put that down.
- You had us scared,
you can't do that, Iz.
[objects clattering]
[animals chittering]
- Okay, adventure time
is over, let's go home.
[insect buzzes and crackles]
[insect buzzes]
- Yeah, let's head back, come
on.
[insects chirping]
[ominous music]
[footsteps tapping]
[insects buzzing]
[door clattering]
[footsteps tapping]
What's happening?
I'm scared.
It's okay, it's okay.
Don't be scared.
[glass wall thuds]
[insects rattling]
[insects chirping]
[insects buzzing]
[footsteps tapping]
Oh, my God.
[Sam breathing heavily]
[footsteps tapping]
[ominous music]
Oh, shit.
What is going on?
[insects clattering]
[glass squeaking]
- [Ethan] Would you
please do one last check
around the property?
Thank you.
What do you think?
Probably environmental,
could be a change in weather
patterns.
Weather?
- [Ethan] We have room at
Langley.
[Sam] No, that's okay.
Okay.
Well, I'll call you with
updates as soon as I have 'em.
Okay.
Actually, will you take her?
Yeah.
[footsteps tapping]
Uh, Director Marshall.
Yeah?
- Are there any updates
on the particle sample
from my capsule?
- The lab is still in the
process of running tests,
but I'll let you know as
soon as I receive the report.
Thanks.
The hardest part is over.
[Sam sighs]
[car alarm beeping]
[footsteps tapping]
You okay?
My whole body hurts.
How's she doing?
- She's fine, she's just
exhausted.
- You should take her home to
rest.
You just come home with us.
You know I can't.
It's just a few more days.
- We can come back later
tonight?
Yeah.
I like that.
[pensive music]
[footsteps tapping]
[Mark grunts]
Okay.
So, I'll call you when we're
heading back.
- Mm-hm.
- Take something for the pain,
yeah?
Yeah.
Izzy, I'll see soon.
I'll see you soon.
[lips smack]
I love you.
[car door thuds]
[tires rustling]
[door creaks and thuds]
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[shoe rustles]
[Sam groans]
[suspenseful music]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam groaning]
[Sam breathing heavily]
Oh, my God.
[water splashing]
[Sam groaning]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[Sam screams]
[crickets chirping]
[glass thuds]
[Sam sighs softly]
[lights buzzing]
[door scrapes and thuds]
[table squeaking]
[table thuds]
[suspenseful music]
[Sam panting]
[keyboard clacking]
[mouse clicks]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Sam panting]
[ominous music]
[laptop thuds]
[Sam groans]
[Sam panting]
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam sighs]
What is happening?
[light buzzes]
No.
[suspenseful music]
[lock clicks]
[lights buzzing]
[footsteps tapping]
[objects clattering]
[creature growls]
[door thuds]
[lock clicks]
[light buzzes]
[phone vibrates]
[Sam gasps]
[Sam panting]
[Mark] Sam.
[sighs] Are you coming back?
[Mark] We're on our way.
[Sam sighs]
Sam.
- I'm trying to keep it
together, but I think I'm going.
- [Mark] I'm here, I'm here,
Sam.
[Sam panting]
Mark.
[Mark] Yeah?
[Sam sobs]
Was I a good mother? [sighs]
[Mark] What?
[Sam sobs]
[objects thudding]
Why are you asking me that, Sam?
[Sam shushing]
[objects thudding]
[Operator] Breach detected.
Lockdown initiated.
[alarm blaring]
Oh, God.
Mark.
[Mark] Sam.
[Sam panting]
What's going on?
[doors clattering]
I think.
There's something
in the house.
[creature growling]
[Sam gasps]
[suspenseful music]
[door hisses]
[Mark speaking indistinctly]
- [Mark] I'll be there as soon
as I can.
Please hurry.
[flesh squelches]
[Sam groaning]
[body thudding]
[Sam panting]
[flesh squelching]
[suspenseful music continues]
What the fuck?
[Sam panting]
[creature growling]
[footsteps tapping]
[door clicks and clatters]
[upbeat suspenseful music]
[Sam panting]
[device beeping]
[button clicks]
What the hell?
[door thuds]
[Sam gasps]
[button beeping]
[Operator] Analyzing.
[monitor beeping]
There are two individuals
detected.
[Sam gasps]
[ominous music]
[Sam breathing heavily]
[monitor warbling]
[footsteps tapping]
[monitors snapping]
[button clicking]
Analyzing.
[monitor beeping]
[suspenseful music]
[Sam gasps]
There are three individuals
detected.
[Sam panting]
[alarm blares]
[button clicks]
[machine whirring]
[smokes hissing]
[Sam panting]
[smoke hissing]
[creature rattling]
[Sam panting]
[smoke hissing]
[suspenseful music]
[Sam panting]
[creature growling]
[smoke hissing]
[Sam panting]
[footsteps tapping]
[ominous music]
[creatures growling]
[wheels squeaking]
[smoke hissing]
[footsteps tapping]
[ominous music continues]
[foot taps]
[smokes hissing]
[Sam panting]
[door thuds]
[table thuds]
[creature growling]
[Sam panting]
[suspenseful music]
[smoke hisses]
[Sam gasps]
[Sam groaning]
[Sam panting]
[smoke hisses]
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam gasping]
[ominous music]
[Sam panting]
[door thuds]
[Sam gasps]
[door clattering]
[Sam panting]
[door thuds]
[Sam gasps]
[creature growling]
[Sam panting]
[ominous music continues]
[footsteps tapping]
[kick thudding]
[Sam grunting]
[Sam groaning]
[door clicks]
[upbeat suspenseful music]
[car engine revving]
Where's mommy?
I'm not sure.
Oh, damn it.
Stay in the car.
[car door clicks]
[car door thuds]
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam panting]
[Sam groaning]
[creature growling]
[Sam screaming]
[footsteps tapping]
[crickets chirping]
[suspenseful music]
[car door clicks and thuds]
[footsteps tapping]
[Izzy] What is that?
Izzy.
Izzy, stop.
[Sam panting]
[ominous music]
[footsteps tapping]
Izzy.
Hey, hey.
What do we say about running
off?
Look.
[suspenseful music]
[upbeat suspenseful music]
[Mark] Sam.
Sam.
[Sam panting]
[lid creaks and thuds]
[creature growling]
Mommy, where are you?
Sam!
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[footsteps tapping]
[Sam panting]
[creature growling]
[vehicle engines revving]
- They're not supposed to be
here.
Okay, people let's move in.
[gun clicks]
Try to remember what we're
dealing with
is highly intelligent.
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
Don't do anything stupid.
[footsteps tapping]
[alarm blaring]
[device beeping]
[doors clatter]
Mommy, where are you?
Sam.
Mommy.
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
Sam!
[Sam groans]
[Sam panting]
No sign of her, sir.
Keep searching.
[gun clicks]
[footsteps tapping]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[smokes hissing]
[Sam panting]
[Sam groans]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[Sam groans]
[Sam panting]
[Sam sobbing]
[creature growling]
- Please, please, I have a
family.
[creature growls]
I have a family.
[creature growling]
[footsteps tapping]
[creature rattling]
[ominous music]
[creature growling]
I can.
[footsteps tapping]
[creature growling]
Who are you?
[creatures growling]
[Sam sighs]
How is that possible?
[creature growling]
[vehicle engines revving]
[guards chattering]
[guns firing]
[creature growls]
[guards chattering]
[guns firing]
[footsteps tapping]
[guards chattering]
[guns firing]
[helicopter whirring]
- Marcio, Brown, you take the
perimeter.
Johnson, Sanchez, [indistinct].
Harris, you're with me.
[Harris] Yes, sir.
[footsteps tapping]
[creature growling]
[guards chattering]
[footsteps tapping]
[creature panting]
[fire crackling]
[guards chattering]
[pensive music]
[Guard] Hey, you, stop.
[creature panting]
[gun firing]
[footsteps tapping]
[creature growling]
[device whirring]
[explosion blasts]
[smoke hissing]
[suspenseful music]
[creature growls]
[suspenseful music continues]
Sam.
[footsteps tapping]
[creatures growling]
[pensive music]
What's happening to mommy?
They're not gonna hurt you.
[gun clicks]
[suspenseful music]
- I need all of you to
come with me right now.
[creatures rattling]
[footsteps tapping]
What are you doing?
Put the gun down, Will.
I can't do that, Mark.
[Sam panting]
Look at her.
Sam isn't what you think she is.
[Sam sighs softly]
I put too much time and
effort into getting them
to come back here.
Tell them to leave their ship.
It's government property now.
[Sam sighs]
You knew all this time?
I gave you a life,
real chance of living.
[suspenseful music]
[Sam sighs]
You've been lying to me.
Mendez, this is Harris.
Start your ascent.
Target is secure.
Copy, general.
[footsteps tapping]
[guards chattering]
The mission.
You used me as bait.
I didn't have a choice.
I need you,
and I need them
to follow me back down
to the house right now.
Right now.
- What are you gonna do, shoot
me?
I'm not gonna ask again.
[guards chattering]
[footsteps tapping]
[suspenseful music]
Don't make me do this.
[Mark grunts]
[bodies thud]
[punch thuds]
[Sam groaning]
[gentle music]
[hand squelching]
[punch thuds]
[body squelching]
[gentle music continues]
You've always been.
[Sam growls]
[radio chattering]
[Harris panting]
[footsteps tapping]
You have to go, Sam.
[gentle music continues]
You have to go now.
[creature growling]
Go.
Go, go, we'll be okay.
[footsteps tapping]
I'll see you soon.
[gentle music continues]
[footsteps tapping]
[guards chattering]
[UFO warbling]
[triumphant music]
[UFO warbling continues]
[triumphant music continues]
[Izzy sighs]
[UFO whirring]
[UFO whooshing]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[upbeat suspenseful music]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[choir vocalizing intensely]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[choir vocalizing intensely]
[upbeat suspenseful music
continues]
[choir vocalizing intensely]
[gentle music]
[gentle music continues]
[gentle triumphant music]
[gentle triumphant music
continues]