Fm Movie
We'll release them
once the research is finished, right?
Why?
I feel sorry for their families.
They might go looking for them.
The orchid daisy.
Thank you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bapa.
Be careful.
-Yoseph, the power's out.
-Really?
-Can you fix it?
-Sure.
You can read that?
Oh, yeah, yeah. But I just...
Lunch?
-This one?
-Thank you so much.
This looks so good.
Put it in the middle, the middle.
Okay.
Join us.
Go ahead, eat up.
Come, sit here.
Take a seat.
Come on, join us.
So, how was your day today, guys?
-It's not--
-Go, go. Please.
It's fine.
You can get water
from the kitchen.
Apolo.
Put it on the shelf, please.
Yoseph.
Put it there.
Hey.
You wanna see something?
What other surprise
do you have for me today?
Okay.
Do you remember this photo?
Of course. How could I not?
-X?
-Yeah.
Wait, Mark. What was that?
-What is that?
-I know. I heard it too.
There's people out here with fire.
Split up, right side!
-Hurry. Hurry.
-What are we gonna do?
I don't know. We gotta go.
-Navy.
What's happening?
Pay attention to every
inch of the place.
Close the windows! Now!
What's happening?
No one is allowed to escape!
-Take a weapon!
-Weapons are ready.
Don't let anyone pass.
Don't, hurry, hurry.
What?
Who are they?
Watch the right side!
Yoseph, who the hell are these people?
Yoseph!
What do they want?
Navy.
Put out the fire.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Frans.
What's wrong with you, huh?
Leave the researchers alone.
They've been nice to us.
Move, Bapa.
Frans.
Look at me.
You've gone too far!
Navy, are you okay?
Bapa.
We're just researchers.
We mean no harm.
What do you want?
Money?
Equipment? Food?
-Take it all.
-Stop. Stop. Stop.
Apolo. You know very well who we are.
If anyone has something to say,
speak to the commander.
From now on...
you're under my control.
We're taking you into the jungle.
And you'll only walk free
once our demands are met.
Frans.
Everyone, out!
Take all their stuff!
Faster!
Be patient.
Go! Move!
Breaking news:
A group of researchers...
from the International
Flora and Fauna Global organization,
conducting research in...
Indonesia has given the green light
for a military rescue
led by General Prabowo Subianto.
The government has instructed
General Commander Prabowo Subianto
to conduct a military operation.
Take a seat.
Reporting, sir.
The chosen ones are no ordinary people.
Timur, Sila and their unit
are elite officers
handpicked from the military academy.
The best of the best.
Forged through discipline.
Trained to the highest standards
and tested in unimaginably
extreme situations.
Today, the task they're carrying out
is not an easy one.
But if there's one team that can handle
this challenge, it's them.
Once again!
They are Kopassus, the best of the best.
Move.
-Stand straight.
-Commando.
Commando.
Sit.
-Good luck.
-Thanks, commander.
Commando.
Hi.
Maya.
I'll be leaving soon.
This mission is different
from the previous ones.
This mission is dangerous.
I know.
But I also know...
that you have prepared well.
I don't want you to be worried.
Don't worry about me.
Just do your duty.
Our mission is to rescue six hostages
who were taken by a terrorist group.
Tobias.
The leader of the terrorist group
behind this hostage crisis.
Frans Bunggiangi.
A former soldier who defected.
Yakobus, the village head
who accompanied the researchers,
was found dead.
The hostages we need to rescue.
There are four researchers from Indonesia:
Adinda.
Navy.
Daniel.
And Matheis.
And two foreign nationals,
Mark and Martha.
And two local guides.
Yoseph.
And Apolo.
-Apolo.
-Timur.
Move! Now!
Timur. Timur.
Timur.
Timur!
Yo, prince!
Can't play soccer?
No more excuses.
Not an excuse. I meant it.
It is true that the world goes through
a period of suffering.
The enemy was afraid
running helter-skelter
They are scared...
If you want to be a soldier,
make sure you study hard, okay?
Go ahead, sir.
Be careful.
SANE VILLAGE COMMUNITY HEALTH CENTER
Get in line. Timur, help them line up.
Get in line.
Get in line. There's enough for everyone.
-I want one.
-There's enough for everyone.
Be patient.
Ayah Isman really likes rujak.
Yeah, that's why I tried
to make some earlier.
Ayah Isman said...
Once we catch it,
we should let it go again.
-Why?
-Because it has a family too.
But we were so close
to catching it.
I'm gonna catch up
with the kids first, okay?
I looked here earlier.
Anything else?
I've got nothing. Guys, come help me.
Be patient.
Maybe on the ground?
Timur.
Apolo.
Sila.
-Sila, come here.
-What is it?
What is it, Dad?
Remember.
Even though you don't share
the same blood,
you will always be a family,
no matter what.
You have to promise me
that you will look after each other.
I promise, Dad.
Apolo?
I promise.
Timur.
Don't forget me.
Of course not.
I won't forget you.
I'll make sure to write you a letter.
Take care of Mama Natalia, okay?
What are you doing here?
Why are you so sad?
Timur has a family
and has to go back to Java.
-So, this is goodbye?
-Yes.
Come on, don't be sad anymore.
We're still brothers. We're family.
Come with me, my brother
Come, my brother
I haven't been home in twenty years, Sila.
Hopefully Apolo is doing well.
Soldiers, the fate of the nation
rests on your shoulders.
Better to die
than fail in the line of duty.
God is with us.
Commando!
The forest is four times
the size of Jakarta.
But thanks to intelligence information,
we have identified
possible hostage locations.
We spread out, secure every post and hut
and every village near the forest.
Our mission is to restrict their movement
by securing key locations.
The Kopassus team
will be divided into two groups.
Our hunter team is Eagle Team.
Forty personnel were divided
into eight units.
The strike unit is Jaguar Team.
Team Jaguar is deployed
to complete the mission.
This operation must be carried out
with as few casualties as possible.
The hostages' safety is our top priority.
Timur!
Apolo!
Clear the village!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Reporting, commander.
The village is surrounded by terrorists.
Two guards by the river.
How are things over there?
So far, everything is safe, brother.
Do you see him?
Go check.
Okay.
Beret.
Red.
Checkpoint is near the target, over there.
I'll follow the hostage's trail.
Follow the markers I leave behind.
Proceed.
Dad! Dad!
Where did you go?
-Eli!
-Dad. Dad.
Do not move until I say it's safe.
Where is she?
-Where's Yoseph?
-He's not back yet.
Because of you,
this village has to suffer.
Take this!
Hey.
What are you doing?
Come here. Come with me.
Come here.
Don't be scared.
Come.
Come!
Come here.
Get out!
Come on.
Come on, get out!
Soldiers!
What is your name?
Eli.
She knows the whole area.
Jaguar 3, requesting clearance to advance.
-Proceed to the next checkpoint.
-Copy that.
Commando.
-How is Vy?
-Still has a high fever.
Daniel.
Drink this.
You all right?
You need to eat.
What is that?
Forest rat.
I know it's not ideal,
but you must eat, for the baby.
Okay.
Brother.
Permission, Bapa.
This morning,
the squad sent to Bora village
was attacked by soldiers.
Tomorrow morning, go to Wana.
Tell them to prepare food
and gather the people.
Yes, Bapa.
Frans, tell everyone
we're moving to the next post.
And bring Yoseph here.
Yoseph, Bapa wants to see you.
All right.
Where have you been, Yoseph?
Thank you.
That is the researcher.
The other one is Yoseph, their guide.
Their remaining troops,
they're probably nearby.
They won't let the hostages go alone.
Look at him, he's dying.
If we do nothing, he'll die for sure.
Relax.
Just hold on.
You stay.
Secure the perimeter.
Copy?
Copy that.
Hands on your head.
On your knees.
Get down.
I'm just a civilian.
He's Daniel.
A researcher.
Don't move.
Assemble.
We're going there.
You're dead.
Freeze!
Or I'll slit his throat.
Brother!
-Brother!
-Hey, stop!
Eli, why are you here?
Please, drop the dagger, brother.
Why are you doing what they say?
They killed our Dad!
Please, stop.
Come home.
I don't want to lose you too.
You're all I have now.
I don't wanna be alone.
Brother!
Navy.
What's going on?
Martha has malaria. She's getting worse.
Doc.
We're ordered to evacuate
the hostages Daniel and Eli.
Affirmative.
-Execute.
-Yes, sir.
Jaguar 2, we need rotary-wing support.
Apolo.
Check on the others.
How is the situation there?
Sila.
Hey, how's it going over there?
Apolo.
Bapa.
Now talk.
Yoseph betrayed us, sir.
We've lost many men, sir.
The hostages have escaped.
Give the order immediately.
Hey.
The commander says you need to write
a letter to the government now.
Bapa, brother.
What's wrong?
Wait. Calm down.
The commander...
What?
He wants troops.
Grab all the weapons. We're out.
Faster!
Get ready to evacuate.
Go, go now!
Deploy all units.
Honorable Mr. President.
Permission to report, general.
We sincerely apologize,
but we are in a dire situation.
We are Indonesian and foreign nationals
being held hostage by terrorists.
We have suffered physically and mentally.
Some of us are suffering from malaria,
and one of the researchers is pregnant.
We just want this to end.
We urgently seek your help
to provide food, medicine,
and the ransom they demand,
in the amount they have requested.
And if their demands are not met,
we will not survive.
Give them what they want now.
Jaguar 2, come in.
Jaguar.
Jaguar 2.
Copy, Jaguar 2.
Dismantle the crew.
We will dismantle it.
Take it.
Get the hostages with you.
Apolo.
The aid packages for the hostages
have been delivered.
I repeat. The aid packages for
the hostages have been delivered.
No sign of the other three hostages.
Timur. Timur, that's Apolo!
Waiting on your command, sir.
Too risky.
-Let's observe their movements first.
-Roger that.
Okay.
Apolo.
Timur.
It's me, Timur.
Are you all right?
Timur?
What are you doing here?
I came for you.
Apolo, I already have a wife,
and you have a niece now.
I thought you were missing.
How is Mama Natalia?
She is doing well, right?
You don't know anything about Mama.
She has been gone for a long time.
I'm trying to survive here alone, Timur.
There's no one to turn to. No help at all.
And now you come here
acting like you care.
Apolo.
I didn't come to fight.
I just came here
to make sure you were still alive.
Don't act like I'm one of the researchers.
You've been gone too long.
You should leave now.
Just like you left me before.
Mama.
I've come home.
You go that way, I go this way. Got it?
Go!
Move!
Friends.
Better friends, never.
There was an attack at the mining company.
Civilians were immediately evacuated.
Thirty civilians were killed,
and several victims suffered injuries
ranging from minor to severe.
Please stay strong, Mama.
Apolo's father is now with God in heaven.
We gotta get to Java soon.
Timur.
You know who attacked your family
at the mine, right?
Soldiers.
The government.
You'll never get justice from them.
But now...
Now's your chance for revenge.
You know, Apolo...
This isn't a difficult job.
You're just a guide.
And an informant.
They won't know who you are,
and your family stays safe.
But you have to choose.
You'll be safe with us.
Why didn't you bring Apolo?
He's still my brother, no matter what.
Is he with them?
Apolo is still the same Apolo.
Be alert.
Return to your position.
I've been thinking about Daniel.
Do you think he's okay?
It's so cold.
I know. I know.
Here, let's get you covered.
What do you need?
A sanitary napkin.
Can you handle it?
Stay there! Don't go too far!
Come in.
Commando.
Permission to report, general.
The tracking device
will be connected shortly.
It will report possible
enemy camp locations
so we can plan our movements, general.
Ensure their safety.
Continue with the operation.
Yes, sir!
What took you so long?
What's that?
It's sanitary napkins.
Women's stuff.
-Let me check it.
-You don't need to see it.
Frans.
She's just a woman.
I'm risking my life for this.
Just a woman?
Are you trying to trick me?
Smart-ass.
Get the troops ready.
Drive the soldiers out of this forest.
Yes, Bapa.
They think they can mess with me.
No more leniency, Frans.
I guarantee they'll be taught a lesson.
No more betrayals, Frans.
If that happens...
you know the risk.
Spread out.
Martin.
We received information
from the tracking device.
The hostages
are on the top of the mountain.
This does not match what you reported.
May I report, sir?
I am sure they are close to Team Jaguar 2.
-Are you sure?
-Sir.
I believe that the tracking device
has been tampered with to mislead us.
Forget humans, even monkeys
wouldn't want to live on that peak.
It's extremely cold.
If you don't believe me,
you can come to the peak yourself.
Okay.
I believe you.
Proceed.
Commander.
Stand by for the attack.
Sila.
-Help the others.
-Roger.
Sila?
Timur. Timur.
Are you all right?
Brother.
I told you to leave!
-Apolo.
-Go home!
Apolo. Apolo.
Enough!
Hey, Apolo! Enough!
I remember Ayah Isman always said
we are brothers.
Once we know the positions in
that area...
Commander.
Martin?
Report, commander.
Jaguar 2 is in a firefight.
Many of the troops are wounded.
The other soldiers escaped, Bapa.
Apolo could kill one of them.
But he didn't.
Looks like they know each other.
You're still one of us, right?
Yes, Bapa.
Kill your army friend before my eyes.
Or I will kill him before your eyes.
That's an order.
Move the hostages to Wana.
No more excuses.
Not an excuse. I meant it.
Don't be sad anymore.
We're still brothers.
We're family.
Kill your army friend before my eyes.
You will always be a family,
no matter what.
Look after each other.
Hold on, okay?
You know, Tim...
You're not the only one who's sad.
I am sad too.
Can I really bring myself
to kill my own brother?
Timur, listen up.
We are soldiers.
In war, there is no choice.
It's kill or be killed.
Never forget that.
Have you forgotten?
We made a promise.
To...
To what?
Protect each other?
Yeah, I remember, very well.
But we also promised...
to rescue the hostages.
Not to kill the captors.
Beret.
Red.
Commando, Jaguar 5.
Reporting.
Jaguar 5 has joined Jaguar 2.
Report, general.
The hostages' location has been confirmed.
Let's finish this.
Sila.
Don't move! Drop the weapon!
Drop the gun or he dies! Now!
Timur and I fought for this country.
Why are you tearing it apart?
These are all our islands.
I had no choice, Sila.
Shut up. No more talking.
Sila. You walked into a trap.
Don't be afraid.
Three hostiles approaching.
Get in!
Thank you.
Go help your brother.
Go, now.
Get out, now!
Finish them.
You have to promise me
that you will look after each other.
I promise, Dad.
Apolo?
I promise.
What?
Why don't you promise too?
They are siblings after all.
What about me?
-You're family.
-All right, I'll be the older brother.
-Just be the younger brother, Sila.
-Just be the younger brother.
You're suited to be the younger brother.
Sila.
Promise?
I promise.
Apolo.
Finally, I'm with my family.
Enough, Timur.
It will never be enough, Apolo.
Adinda, take cover.
Stay calm.
-I'm a hostage.
-Stay calm.
We are from ABRI's
330th Infantry Battalion.
Move! Hostages spotted!
Here we go.
Okay.
Reporting, Commander.
Three hostages rescued.
Come home, Apolo.
Come back to your family.
Just like the animals in the forest.
They live side by side, Apolo.
But they hunt each other, Timur.
They protect their own families.
Remember, we promised our father
we'd look out for each other.
We are family. Come home, Apolo.
-Come home, Apolo!
-You're a dad now, right?
Go home. Why are you here?
Your wife is waiting.
Go home, Timur!
I'll keep watch here.
Give my regards to Ayah Isman.
Come with me, my brother
Come, my brother
I just want to let you know that
We are real brothers
Brother and brother, forever
Truly very sweet
What you feel I feel as well
The two of us are real siblings
Apolo!
Move!
No more excuses.
Not an excuse. I meant it.
Come on, let's take a picture.
Come here, Sila.
Please come here.
-No, not like this.
-That's it.
Smile for the photo.
One.
Two.
-Hurry, we've got more to do.
-One. Two.
So, this is goodbye?
Yes.
Come on, don't be sad anymore.
We're still brothers. We're family.
...injured during the mission.
This marks a major success
for Indonesia's military,
answering doubts...
...during the mission.
This marks a major success
for Indonesia's military,
answering doubts
from the international observers
about its ability to handle
high-risk rescue operations.