But a color identifier
only identifies color.
And my toaster
only toasts toast.
Well, my point is I need a
color comparer so when I put
together an outfit and need to
know if my blacks match, I can
go boop boop and it will be
like, you nailed it, honey!
Why don't you just
use Look-See-Loo?
Ugh. I hate it. They're
all volunteers.
It's a total roll
of the dice.
But you can save favorites.
Yeah, I mean, sure, I've got my
girl Janine, but if she's not
available, I always wind up
with this well-meaning dude
whose only fashion experience
is dressing a Grand
Theft Auto avatar.
You're terrible.
All I'm saying is that losing
our vision is way worse for us
goths than it's for you normies.
I'm not a normie, am I?
If you have to ask...
Ash, hold up!
Forgot your, uh...
Your
tape recorder thingy.
-Oh, thank you.
Um, can you put it in my bag?
Oh yeah, sure thing.
Thank you.
So are you actually gonna make
one of those soundscape songs
for the kitchen?
I'm gonna try.
Yeah, look at me, I'm
a rock 'n' roll star.
Okay.
Let's go.
Dude, you gotta wear the hat.
I absolutely do not.
How's anyone gonna know that
you're the Birthday Babe?
Two words: justifiable homicide.
Oh, save that talk for the
office, Detective Fleischer.
Only if you stop provoking an
officer, Detective Zelinskas.
Alright.
So what kind of weird foodie
place are you taking us to?
I am taking us to
the Blind Spot.
Okay.
It's a place where you eat in
complete darkness for total
taste immersion.
Alright, it's quite the
culinary experience.
I think I'd just prefer a meal.
You can go to a
steakhouse at any time.
It wouldn't kill you to try
something new once in a while.
Besides, you can still-
have your steak
and scotch inside.
All right.
-That's the spirit, babe.
Can I have the Zelenskyy
party gather around over here?
Yeah, right here.
-That's us.
Right.
-Let's do it.
Hi everyone.
My name is Ash.
I'll be taking care
of you this evening.
I'm going to start out by
answering absolutely every
question you might have
because I have heard them all.
Sound good?
Great, let's roll.
-Yeah. Come on.
Okay, first off, yes,
I am actually blind.
All of our wait staff is
either blind or low vision.
I have idiopathic optic
neuritis since my early 20s,
and now I can basically see if
the lights are on or off, and
that's about it.
So yes, I am actually blind.
Second, yes, you will be dining
in complete darkness tonight.
No, you will not be
able to see anything.
I'll bring you out your
pre-ordered dishes and drinks.
I can clean up any messes and
take care of anything that you
might need.
The darkness will not be an
issue for me because again, I
am actually blind.
Lastly, you're going to leave
your phones, smartwatches,
basically anything that emits
light in the lockers behind
that door.
I will not look in your lockers.
Both because I'm honest and
because I am
really, truly, 100%,
FDA-approved,
actually blind.
Any other questions?
Yep.
Shoot.
Are you actually blind?
I've heard that
one too, hotshot.
Okay, you guys can go leave
your things in the lockers and
meet me back here in 5 minutes.
Hey,
I'm Cedric.
Oh, I hear you're the
birthday, babe.
It's a hat they want me to wear.
Oh, and you're no fun?
I'm not a flashy dresser.
And you're more of a
gray suit businessman?
More blue suit detective.
A blue suit detective who
doesn't want to be a cowboy?
Yeah, well, I don't think
I remember John Wayne ever
wearing one with pink
lettering on the front.
Eh, I never liked him anyway.
Who'd you prefer?
Joan Crawford, Johnny Guitar.
Oh, such a great one
-Right?
Too few movies have a woman
in the final showdown.
So do you run this place
the way Joan ran her saloon?
More or less, yeah.
I think we're all ready.
Okay, great.
Um, everyone, we're gonna form
a line behind the birthday babe.
He's gonna put his hand on my
shoulder, and then you will all
get behind him and follow suit.
I'm not fragile.
Okay, follow me.
Oh!
Loopety loo!
Here we go, boys!
Okay!
Patrick, Patrick, Patrick,
Patrick, Patrick
Okay, okay, let's go to the bar!
Hey, hey, you were totally
right about this place.
What did I say?
Only Scotch pours
were a little light.
I hope you enjoyed your meal.
You too.
You too?
I-
Come on.
Hey, where's this Uber?
It's coming.
Should have been
on the first one.
I'm the birthday babe.
Patience is a virtue, Detective.
Alright.
I think you made the
right call back there.
What?
With Ash.
Oh, the waitress.
How many drinks did you have?
All I'm saying...
...is I think it's been
too soon since the divorce.
It's been a year.
Sure.
I just don't think
she's that into you.
She so was.
She was.
But it's best to play it safe.
Hey, I see you.
I'm not that drunk.
Get in there.
Well,
okay.
You got this.
Watch and learn.
Excuse me.
What can I getcha?
Uh, no, I was just here.
Did you forget something?
No, I just-
Is Ash available?
Uh, I'd like a word.
Sure you do.
I'll go get her.
Uh, it's Cedric, by the way.
Got it.
Cedric?
Hey.
Hi, how can I help you?
Oh, well, I just wanted to come
and ask if you're seeing anyone
right now.
Oh!
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
I just meant, are you
seeing anyone, like dating?
Uh, not like, you know, seeing.
I know the expression.
Right.
Hey, I mean, you're not stupid.
You're just like
a normal person.
I mean, you are a normal
person, just with a disability.
I mean, differently ability.
But you know what?
I don't care.
In fact, I like it.
But not like that, not
like weird, just like,
I see the value in
diverse perspectives.
Just not in a sighted
perspective way, just like in a
very normal, not weird way.
Because you are, and I am...
...normal.
Right.
God, this is going bad.
Hey, take it easy.
-I feel sick.
Oh.
And then,
he throws up all
over Ashley's shoes.
Okay, not all over.
You're currently barefoot.
Okay, so what did you do?
Well, I helped his friend
roll him into his car.
No, no, no phone
number, no nothing?
No.
A guy literally spills his guts
out trying to ask you out and
you just turn him down?
Okay, you didn't hear his
allyship panic spiral.
Oh, it made me want to go deaf.
I just wanted to
make sure he got home safe.
Ah,
there it is.
-Yep.
What?
Ash turns another potential
date into an opportunity to
take care of somebody.
Big sis never misses a chance.
I'd say she misses
plenty of chances.
Oh, okay.
What's that thing they say
about, uh, stones
and glass houses?
Yeah, boss, you
should be grateful.
Without Ash, you would have the
saddest person
alive in this shop.
Hey!
-Well, yeah, well, we can't
all be U-Haul
lesbians now, can we?
I'm not a U-Haul lesbian.
Okay.
-Okay.
I need some company who's
gotten laid this year.
Where's Gina?
Hey, girl, hey!
Save me!
I'm giving Dani a lift
later on if you want in.
Hell yeah!
I don't want to touch
your stinky feet.
Oh my gosh.
Chop chop, ladies, come on.
Chop chop?
You chop chop, bitch.
His fault.
Yeah, don't put
them on the seats.
Don't put them on the ground.
Home, James.
Yeah, yeah.
Seriously though, you got to
check that thing
with the payroll.
I will.
It's important.
I know.
You know it affects
my benefits, right?
They're very touchy about that.
I get that, yes.
I just-
What is it?
Some guy.
He's just standing in
the middle of the street.
Hey. Hey, buddy!
What was that?
Some LA local color.
Ooh.
Another new boyfriend for Ash.
Shut up.
Hey, Igor, read this.
One moment, master.
Sorry, I can't read that.
Igor, read this.
One moment, master.
Sorry, I can't read that.
Igor, open Look-See-Loo.
Yes, master, opening
Look-See-Loo.
Igor, check favorites.
JP is available.
Igor, call JP.
Ashley, what's up?
What are you doing up?
It must be 3 AM in Tennessee.
Couldn't sleep.
Need help with something?
Yeah, hey, can you read
this expiration date for me?
My phone can't read it.
Uh, move the camera
left a little.
It's smudged, but it looks
like the 7th, which is-
Today
Uh-huh.
Does the expiration date mean
you can't have it
on the day or after?
I wouldn't risk it.
Coward.
I believe the
phrase is thank you.
Thanks.
Screw it.
Black.
White.
You nailed it, honey.
Hey, Jean.
Hey, beautiful.
For our music class at
the Braille Institute-
Uh-huh.
-What do you think about
calling it The Dark
Side of the Tune?
I love it.
Yeah?
-Yes, ma'am.
Better than playing by ear?
Oh yeah, definitely.
You done in here?
Yeah, you?
Perfect. Yeah, Shane, let's go.
Dining room clear?
Dining room clear.
My campers finally went home.
Finally. There's always
that one Party, huh?
So true.
Are you almost ready to go?
Uh, no.
Not tonight.
I gotta stay late.
Inventory?
Um, did- did Dani leave
yet, by any chance?
Yeah, like 20 minutes ago.
How come?
Because I don't want her giving
me the yips before
I go on this date.
Andre, you have a date?
I do, yeah.
With who?
She is a chef
at another restaurant.
Oh, how
soigné?
Yeah, yeah.
How did you meet?
At a bar.
So we're just going to meet
there again after she gets out
of work in an hour.
Yeah. Are you-
are you good to walk
home alone tonight?
Oh, yeah, of course.
You good to finish
cleaning up alone?
Oh, of course. Yeah.
Okay.
Bonne chance
, chef.
Je croise les doigts.
Oh, sorry, excuse me.
Is that you, Ash?
Andre?
I forgot my keys.
I can tell the lights
are still on.
Damn it.
Andre?
Nice job cleaning up alone.
Igor, call 911.
Yes, master.
Calling now.
Igor, go to sleep.
Hey.
-Hey.
If it wasn't so morbid, I'd say
welcome back to the
scene of the crime.
What do we got?
Uh, got a head chef stabbed by
his own knife sometime
after midnight.
No prints, no surveillance
footage, no clear
suspects or motive.
But we do have a witness.
You'll never guess who it is.
Um, Andre has a sister.
I can't remember her name.
So after he stepped on the
glass, he just ran out?
Yeah, I must have left a piece.
Um,
I swear I know her name.
Hey, you keep referring
to this person as a man.
Are you sure about that?
I think so.
Um,
she lives in San Clemente.
Can you tell us anything
else about this person?
He had really heavy steps,
like he was wearing big boots,
probably black-soled.
They found scuff
marks back there.
What else?
He cracked his
knuckles with one hand.
How do you know he did
it with just one hand?
Right, normal people
do it with two.
It was like this.
My granddad used to crack
his knuckles like that.
Anything else?
Um.
Oh, he used this really
antiseptic cleaner.
It smelled like a hospital.
So it was a strong scent?
Yeah, I still smell
it in here.
Lola! Lo Faro.
That's his sister's name.
Okay, great.
You've been very helpful.
Thank you so much, okay?
We'll speak soon.
Okay, so what do you think?
I think boots, knuckle pops,
and hospital smell aren't much
to go off of.
Yeah, fair.
What she said about him going
on a date might lead somewhere.
Maybe.
Got a female chef
meeting out at a bar...
...somewhere.
See if they got
into his phone yet.
Alright.
I know, Dani, okay?
Just come over to
my house later, okay?
Okay.
Okay. I love you.
Hey, it's Detective
Fleischer again.
Yeah?
There's something
I need to tell you.
About Andre?
No, about me, actually.
I'm the person who threw
up on your shoes last week.
I know.
Oh. You recognize my voice?
No, I met you one time.
Your partner told me.
Right. Well, I just wanted to
apologize because that's not
who I normally am.
Great. Is that all?
No?
Can I have some space?
I just- I thought I
should say something, so-
Why? Because it went so
well for you last time?
I'm sorry, my friend just died.
Of course.
-Thank you.
Damn it.
Who is it?
It's Dani.
Ash?
-Mia.
That stupid idiot.
Okay, come inside, okay?
Okay.
I'll make you some tea.
Are you okay?
Um, yeah.
Go- go back to sleep.
Okay.
How long have you been up?
A while.
Do we have work today?
No, check your email.
We are off until
at least Tuesday.
Um, I made coffee, so just
lock up whenever you leave.
Where are you going?
I'm going to try and
feel less helpless.
Detective Fleischer?
Cedric's not here.
I need to speak with him.
And you are?
I'm the witness to
last night's murder.
Yeah, okay.
Is something funny?
No, I get it.
I get it.
You get what?
You're some kind of kiss
on Stripogram, right?
For Ced's birthday?
The hot blind chick.
Miss, "I can't see anything, but
you can see everything," right?
Right.
Ash?
Cedric?
Why did you throw lukewarm
coffee on Detective Chambers?
Because he's a dick.
You're going to need
to be more specific.
Because he's an ableist dick.
Okay, tell me what happened.
Okay, got your mug back, and
I sent Detective Chambers home
for the day.
So his punishment is a day off?
He also has to do a
virtual HR seminar.
How long?
6 hours, no mute.
That's better.
So how are you all doing?
Everyone at the
restaurant is a mess.
But not you?
-No, I'm just so mad.
So you came here to
do something about it?
Yeah, kinda.
I told you we'd be in touch if
we had any other
questions, Ash-
I know, but please
just listen to me.
I know
I'm the blind eyewitness.
I don't need anyone to tell
me how ridiculous that sounds,
but yesterday I just
felt so helpless.
I couldn't help Andre or
myself or anyone, and I,
I hate that,
and I just want to do
something, anything, anything.
So please just tell
me what I can do.
I hear you.
I really do.
A lot of people experience
similar feelings
after a tragedy.
And while I understand how-
This is just a long way
of you telling me no.
This isn't a no.
So what is it then?
It's a not right now.
That's a no.
This isn't helping.
Give me my mug.
You're lucky I'm out of coffee.
Excuse me.
Ash? It's Guy.
Better not stop.
I'm already pissed off at
two cops today.
What did he do this time?
He didn't have any ideas
for how I could help.
Did you have any ideas
on how you could help?
No, not really.
So you both didn't have any
ideas on how you could help?
You know, maybe I
just don't like cops.
I'm just trying to get
the story straight, okay?
Am I free to go?
Let's not go there,
all right?
I'm sure you've been feeling
this mad ever since you woke up.
Technically, it preceded that.
More to my point, I'm sure
you've got some more valuable
information that's stuck
behind a wall of mad, mad, mad.
If you want to be helpful, just
go home, take your mind off-
Are you serious?
Last night, you gave us all the
information you
could by focusing.
You're focused.
So try focusing elsewhere.
See what comes to mind while
you're otherwise occupied.
Kind of like how you have
your best ideas in the shower.
Exactly.
You know, maybe he said
something last week, had a
fight last month.
Maybe it's his favorite ladle.
Who knows?
Okay.
Thanks, Guy.
Do you see someone
over there in boots?
What?
-Like heavy black boots.
Uh, no?
Are you sure?
I don't know.
Detective Fleischer
Get to Palisades Park now.
Who is this?
It's Ash.
The boots guy is
here, I know it.
Hold on.
I'm gonna follow him.
Ash, wait for me
to get there before-
Call for you,
master, from Cedric.
Igor, text Cedric, "Only
call me when you get here."
I don't know what
to tell you, man.
Thanks anyway.
-I'm sorry.
Hope you know how
stupid that was.
Did you find him?
Nope, not a trace.
Any witnesses?
Uh, one kid remembers a blind
lady who seemed nice, and then
she started sprinting
across the park, so.
Is that it?
No one saw a guy in boots.
Okay, are you sure
it was our guy?
Can you give us a second?
Listen.
See?
Heavy boots, strong steps.
Wait for him to
crack his knuckles.
Pop, pop, pop.
Just like I said.
Yeah, I hear it.
And?
And it's not exactly definitive.
I know that.
And it's a bit coincidental,
you finding
him in a random crowd.
Not if he was following me
here.
Until he just left.
There were a lot
of people around,
maybe he needed an opportunity.
This is getting
awfully speculative.
Fine,
don't listen to me.
Just find him.
What's she even doing?
Uh, she was making
field recordings.
It's something that she does
for her music, apparently.
On cassette?
I mean, if we have to play
this, we're gonna have to use
the tape deck in my dad's Buick.
What about you?
Nothing on his phone,
nothing in his apartment.
Mystery date remains a mystery.
You try anyone you might
know in the foodie scene?
No, but it's not a bad idea.
You try Samantha?
I did not call Samantha, okay?
Should probably start with
someone that'll actually answer
my calls anyways.
Though,
a lack of evidence
has got me thinking.
What?
What if we have
this all backwards?
Meaning?
What if the chef
wasn't the main target.
Huh.
Good boy.
How's your head?
It hurts.
I bet.
Um.
Need a hand?
Got it.
So, uh, should I go
screw myself or what?
Do you need something?
Yes.
I need you to stop being such
a baby and such a dumbass.
I'm not a dumbass.
You got yourself hit by a car.
It tapped me.
I was chasing Andre's killer.
Okay, maybe.
But you could have gotten
yourself killed too.
I had to do something.
The cops are useless.
Do you remember that speech
that I give to everyone who
gets referred to the
Braille Institute?
Yes. What does that have
to do with anything-
Trust.
That is the number one thing
I've gotten out
of my vision loss.
Whenever I put my hand on
Shane's harness handle or
somebody's arm to let them
guide me, I have to trust them.
And yeah, sometimes it does
feel like I'm losing some
independence and some control,
but in doing so, I've learned
to put my faith in the people
around me and to trust that
given the chance,
they will help.
You should tell the cop that.
I'm not talking about him.
I know, but I've heard
this a dozen times.
Okay, but did you
actually listen?
Yes,
I hear you.
This is Cedric,
leave a message.
Cedric, it's Ash.
Um,
I just wanted to let you know
that you can trust me because
I've decided to trust you too.
Hey Ashley, what's up?
Oh my God!
Well, can you call 911?
Okay.
I don't see anything.
Still nothing.
I mean are you sure-
Oh my God, okay,
there's someone there.
There's someone there.
I'm calling 911.
What's your address?
I need the police at 14413
Hansmore Place.
Someone's broken into
my friend's house.
She's blind and I'm on
a video call with her.
Okay, good.
I'll stay on with
her to try to help.
Cops are on their way.
5 minutes.
What do you mean?
Ash, what do you mean?
Oh, okay, okay, I got you.
I see him. Do you hear him?
Okay, he's coming.
Get ready.
3.
2.
1.
Yeah, get him!
Swing again!
Ah, it's Cedric!
What?
So no clues to the guy's
age, race, hair color?
I didn't see much other
than he wore black.
Including the boots?
Yeah, big ones.
Call me tomorrow, we'll
take an official statement.
Will do.
Thanks.
Ow.
I hope you know how stupid
that was.
I'm not taking the bait.
You didn't wait for backup.
I was right around the block.
You failed to announce yourself.
Your door was wide
open when I got here.
So you got worried about me?
I was already worried about you.
What do you mean?
Guy's got this theory that the
murderer might be targeting you.
Well, obviously.
I mean, not just because
you're a witness.
You were the last person there
before the murder, and now he's
come after you once,
maybe twice since.
You think this has
something to do with me?
I'm not ruling it out.
Either way, we're going to put
you under round-the-clock
protection,
and either way, that means
that we need to look into your
connection to the case.
Does that mean-
See you tomorrow at 8, slugger.
See you then, birthday babe.
Piping hot cliché for you, sir.
As long as they aren't
hibiscus rose clichés again.
Classic assorted.
Ah, there we go.
But only because the Hibiscus
Rose is sold out.
You snoot.
You philistine.
Anyway, any luck with
that female chef?
No, not really, but
I'll keep working on it.
I mean it's what, 11,000
restaurants in the
LA metro area?
Needle in the haystack
barely begins to cover it.
And?
And Samantha didn't
call me back.
But what about you, huh?
Aside from letting a blind girl
get the once-over on you.
I think we need to look into
your idea about the cook being
collateral damage.
I agree.
Oh, mind if I take two?
Uh, yeah.
Hey, help yourself.
-Thanks.
Hi, Cedric.
Hi!
-Good to see you.
Um, I have donuts.
Do you like donuts?
Oh, thank you.
Yes, I do.
Great.
No, it's too grandma.
It's not enough hospital.
Okay, so too flowery
should be more acidic.
Antiseptic?
They're synonyms.
You want to bet?
Absolutely.
Dinner?
Done.
Hey, Igor, search the
definition of acidic.
Lunch?
I'm more concerned about dinner.
What?
Someone lost a bet.
Where are you taking our
chief witness out to?
We were just joking around.
Does she know that?
Relax.
I know I was the one that told
you to go for it back at the
restaurant, but that was before
she was involved in a crime
you're investigating.
I don't need you to
read me the handbook.
Are you sure?
Because you spent the entire
morning flirting
with her about soap.
I spent the morning
interviewing our witness about
her personal and professional
connections before engaging her
in a casual exercise where she
might reveal something that she
wouldn't have during
the formal interview.
I know the rules, guy.
If you say so.
There's a reason you went
back there that night.
Remember when he had that
girl to the restaurant?
We were all his waitresses.
He loved cheese.
He did love cheese.
I don't think so.
It's like, it's really bad
because his family is just so
unsure of how to move forward.
Excuse me, Ash?
Cedric?
Sorry I'm late.
I thought I'd come
pay my respects.
That's really nice of you.
Is that the cop?
Um, yeah.
Um, Cedric, this is Dani.
We met.
We did.
And Jean.
Hi, nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you as well.
Um, you missed Jean's song.
She's a full-on opera singer.
She sang Ave Maria.
I think actually André
would have liked it.
He wasn't really religious, but
he was really open, even though
he was an atheist.
Agnostic.
They say that's not a religion.
Come on, Schopenhauer.
Let's go get something to drink.
Thank you for coming.
Of course.
I didn't know it was
going to be so casual.
Yeah, it's perfect for Andre.
It was light on the ceremony
and heavy on the fun.
Hmm.
Wish I'd known.
I'm very overdressed.
Are you wearing a suit?
Black with a black tie.
Yeah.
Can I get you a drink?
No, I'm technically on duty.
I took tonight's
shift watching you.
Food then?
I'm starving.
Uh, I can make you
a plate if you like.
No, my restaurant catered this
and I eat there all the time.
Plus, you owe me
dinner.
I know a place.
No that's what I'm saying.
The entire world is based
around sighted culture.
What does that even mean?
For instance, I'm looking at
you while I'm talking to you.
Even though you can't see me.
Right. Otherwise you
might think I'm rude.
Huh.
It's everywhere
once you notice it.
I mean, the restaurant I work
at is literally named after a
common refrain that equates
being blind to ignorance.
I guess I never thought
of it like that.
Most people haven't.
So if you get SSDI benefits,
you can still work?
Yes, but there's a cap
on how much you can earn.
So for blind people, it's
literally $2,700 a month.
If I earn more than that,
I could lose my benefits.
Even Medicare?
Yeah, it's more complicated.
So the SSI, they have a max of
how much you can have in your
bank account, and it's $2,000.
That's it?
Yes. The legislation is decades
old, and they didn't account
for inflation.
If you get married, it's worse.
They have a household
maximum of $3,000 combined.
A lot of people are too afraid
to get married because they
think that they'll
lose their benefits.
That sucks.
I know.
So you can still
see in your dreams?
Colors and everything.
Gotcha.
Yeah, the only difference is my
brain has to make up a face for
someone that I've
met but haven't seen.
So what do I look like?
I'll let you know
when you show up.
Okay.
I'm ready.
For what?
To tell you the story.
What story?
The story.
Oh, you really don't have to.
I hate it, but I'd rather
just get it over with.
That's why I give my spiel at
the restaurant, so that I can
just blaze past it and
not go into the details.
Ash, you really don't
have to tell me.
No,
I do.
It started in the top
corner of my left eye
and it spread
like a shower door misting over.
And my right eye went faster.
And now, like I said, I can
just see when lights are on or
off and nothing else.
What was it?
Idiopathic optic neuritis.
It's a medical equivalent
of, of a shrug.
I did months of treatment and
tests, spinal taps,
MRIs, and steroids.
I even went through chemo.
Still no answers.
I have lesions growing on my
optic nerves for
no apparent reason.
That must have really
pissed you off.
What?
Sorry.
Well, it does.
The not knowing
really pissed me off.
All that uncertainty.
Oh, a complete lack of control.
Yeah, you must have hated that.
I was furious.
I bet.
You know, most people just go
for telling me how brave I am
and they pat me on the hand.
They must not know
you very well.
I guess not.
How does a blind skydiver know
when they're about
to hit the ground?
I don't know, tell me.
The leash goes limp.
Oh God, that's terrible.
Okay, blame Dani for that one.
Hey, do you know any jokes
about drunk blind girls?
I'm not drunk.
Oh, interesting, you
make that connection.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Oh hey, so tomorrow I was
thinking maybe we go down to
the shoe door and
do a boots lineup.
Why? Because the cleaning
lineup was such a
rousing success?
Have you got any better ideas?
No, I'm drunk.
Ah, she admits it
The third watch for your
protective detail
will be here soon.
I'll wait out on the drive.
Oh, okay.
Good night.
I'm coming.
You've been playing with me this
whole time, but that's over.
Now you're gonna get
what you deserve.
Finally.
Igor, search audio
erotica, man for woman.
Igor, cancel.
Igor, search audio
erotica man for woman cop.
Play first result.
Call for you, master,
from Cedric.
Igor, answer.
Yes, master.
Hello?
Hey, I just wanted to let
you know we're gonna have to
postpone that boot lineup.
Really?
Yeah, guys' search for Andre's
date is coming up empty, so I'm
gonna help knock on
some kitchen doors.
That's probably a better
use of your time anyway.
Yeah, boot lineup wasn't
exactly my best idea.
How you feeling?
There may be an ibuprofen in
my future, but not too bad.
Hopefully I didn't
keep you out too late.
Nah, I'm a night owl.
I watched a whole
movie after I got home.
What'd you watch?
Johnny Guitar?
No, Blind Fear.
You ever heard of it?
No, but I can guess
why it caught your eye.
Yeah, it was
actually pretty good.
It was kind of like Die Hard,
but it was about this blind
woman outsmarting an abandoned
hotel full of bank robbers.
And then in the end, you find
out she was working for their
boss the whole time and she
got away with all the money.
Hell yeah!
What a good twist.
It totally got me.
Come on, Detective.
You should know by now not to
underestimate the blind girl.
I should, shouldn't I?
Well, then good hunting.
Thanks.
Finally, I was growing
a beard over here.
How seriously did we look into
the blind members of the staff?
I mean, we gave them
all a once-over.
That's what I thought.
You think they're
worth another look.
Couldn't hurt.
What's up?
I was wondering if you wanted
to finally help me label those
records I got a
couple weeks ago.
Absolutely.
Great.
Final Klaxon by
Silent Ness.
Great record.
So good.
I can't believe you
didn't already have that.
For shame, Ashley.
Okay, I probably have it on a
CD in my parents'
basement somewhere.
Fair enough.
Uh, Chris Bonucci,
total classic.
You better be right
about that one.
Bonucci, can't go
wrong with Bonucci.
It's good to see you.
I've been worried
since our last call.
Yeah, um, I'm sorry
again about that.
Did they catch the guy yet?
Not yet.
Mystic Marine.
Look, after what happened,
it really got me thinking.
Oh?
Like I wanted to know how
you were, but since we only
talk in the app, I
can't contact you.
Right.
But if I had your number,
we could just FaceTime.
I guess, um.
Hey, what's left?
Zempire.
Right.
We're friends, right?
Look, JP.
I care about you.
You don't know me.
Sure I do.
No, you don't.
Well, I want to.
You live in Tennessee.
What if I didn't?
What are you saying?
What if I moved?
For me?
Uh, yeah, not just for you, but
I've been thinking about
moving to LA anyways, so I just
figured I would-
Hey, Igor, read options.
Yes, master.
Call, remove from favorites,
block.
Email for you, Master,
from Look-See-Loo Help Desk.
Igor, read email.
Yes, Master.
Dear user, we have received
your report and are now looking
into the situation-
Igor, cancel.
Yes, master.
Hello?
Ash?
-Yeah, what's going on?
Dani got arrested.
What?
Will you please just listen
to me?
This is absurd.
Her prints were on the knife.
Her and how many other people?
I can't comment on that.
It's a commercial kitchen.
I'm aware.
What about what I heard?
The boots?
When we picked her up, she
was in black steel toes.
That's different
than what I heard.
More like a man, I know.
What about the soap and
the knuckle cracking?
None of which are proof.
She can buy a bottle of soap,
she can crack her knuckles.
That's not the point.
The point is she has a motive.
She loved Andre.
He screwed up her checks.
What?
Some glitch in their accounting
software meant she got paid on
the 31st instead of
the 1st sometimes.
It put her over the SSDI
income limit 4 times last year.
Neither of them caught it
until the government did.
Her benefits are under review.
No, no, she would not
kill him over that.
She threatened him over text.
What did she say?
She said enough.
And you said she left just
before you did that night.
Yeah, but I heard a car.
We think that she may have
used an autonomous rideshare.
You think she ordered
a Waymo to dump a body?
We know she has an account and
she hailed a ride that night.
She was probably
getting a ride home.
We're looking into it.
You're an idiot.
You need to calm down.
No, No, I won't calm down
because I think one of us needs
to give a rat's
ass about justice.
Don't get pissed at
me for what she did.
She didn't do anything!
Prove it!
Give me one bit of evidence
that actually contradicts what
I've said.
Prints, motive, threats,
opportunity, no alibi.
It's circumstantial, but it's
solid, and I'm just
getting started.
Hey, guy, will you
give me a ride home?
Sure.
I'm sorry we couldn't justify
keeping protection on you with
the suspect in custody.
Great.
Ash,
it's probably for the best.
I'm the last guy you should
be going to for dating advice.
Look.
He's a good guy.
He's good police.
He's passionate, he's
focused, he's sure of himself.
He always wants to help.
But he's a control freak and
stubborn son of a bitch.
You got that right.
I mean, from the looks of it,
you might be the same.
Maybe.
It wouldn't work out.
I just watched it
happen with his ex-wife.
She's a sweet woman.
Pediatric nurse, but
she was just like him.
When people rely on
you, you have control.
And if you're not careful,
you get afraid of
losing that control.
Vulnerability is scary,
but without it,
relationship can't last.
I'm sorry, I don't
mean to lecture.
No, um,
it's okay.
Thanks, Guy.
Take care.
They can't certify me as
blind until I get examined by a
doctor, and so I'm just getting
dragged from place to place.
The lawyers will be able to
help with that.
And, um, I know
a guy who does jail
outreach, so he can help too.
How Christian is he?
Um, Christian enough that when
you say stuff like that, he
won't take offense.
Thanks, y'all.
We're gonna get you some help.
Yeah, just hang tight, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
-Bye.
I'm looking for Patterson,
party of one.
Right here.
Awesome, thank you
for your patience.
We are short of staff today.
Um, my name is Ash.
I will be taking care of you.
Ashley,
it's me.
JP?
Listen, I know this is weird.
Do you?
Yes, I do, and I just want you
to know you have absolutely
nothing to worry about.
Like you coming to my
work after I blocked you?
I just came here to apologize.
Great, you apologized,
now leave.
I just want to
talk for a minute.
What happened to you just
wanting to apologize?
You know what I mean.
-You're not my first chaser.
What?
Chaser, devotee, admirer,
all means the same thing.
What are you accusing me of?
Flying across the
country to screw a blind chick.
No, no, I didn't fly.
I live-
I live here now.
That's worse.
You're taking this the wrong-
-How?
I'm not like stalking you.
Then why are you here?
I just want to talk.
-Well I don't.
Why are you being such a bitch?
It was you!
You killed him!
Ash, no!
-Someone call 911!
No, no, no!
Someone grab him!
So when he gave his statement,
he mentioned an
address in Knoxville.
Mm-hmm.
Do you know where he's staying?
I have no idea.
Well, that's not
much to go off of.
Is it enough to get
Dani out of jail?
I hear what you're saying, but
aside from his interest in you,
there's nothing tying
him to Andre's murder.
Great, so we're back to
nobody listening to me.
Let me find him.
And I'll see what
we can do, okay?
In the meantime, can I get
my security detail back?
I wish I could,
but it scared him off
pretty good, right?
I mean, if we're lucky, he ran
all the way back to Rocky Top.
What about me has given you
the impression that I'm lucky?
We'll stay in touch.
Okay.
Uh, hey.
Where is he?
I think after what happened
last time, it's better that I
handle it.
You're probably right.
Yeah.
Igor, search...
...home security stores near me
open 24 hours.
Yes, master.
Igor, call 911!
So you had a stun gun
in your shower caddy?
The box said that it
was water resistant.
Where did you even get
a stun gun?
I got it from a 24-hour
military surplus store off Pico.
No, don't.
-Okay, okay, okay.
Knock knock.
Ash?
-Dani!
I'm right here, I'm right here.
Oh
Are you okay?
Am I okay?
You're the one who
just got attacked.
I'm fine, I'm just so
glad that you're out.
Me too.
Um, Dani, on behalf of all of
us, just want to apologize.
We totally had it wrong, so
hopefully there are
no hard feelings.
Oh, there's gonna be
plenty of hard feelings.
Fair enough.
Please just find that creep.
Of course.
How are you getting home?
We've got a couple
officers with some cars.
Do you want me to come with you?
No, I just want to get in my
own bed and sleep for a week.
Okay, I'll see you
when you wake up.
Okay.
Can I guide you?
I'm good.
Okay, uh, yep, right over there.
I think I owe you
an apology as well.
Shoot.
You had it right,
we had it wrong.
Wherever this JP guy is, we're
gonna find him and put an end
to this.
I don't think I heard
an apology in there.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Come on, I'll get
you a ride home.
Oh, I-
I really don't want to
stay at home tonight.
Oh, of course.
Hotel?
Can I say something stupid?
Sure.
When I thought that guy was
gonna kill me in the shower,
I really regretted
not kissing you.
Oh! Are you okay?
I told you, I'm not fragile.
Hey, wait, wait, wait. Gun.
Oh, gun, gun.
Badge.
Couch.
-Couch? Couch.
Couch. Couch.
Follow me.
That's what I want to do.
I want to make music that makes
people hear the
music around them.
That's kind of beautiful.
Okay, well, I'm going to go
grab a shower before we turn
in, figure out what to do
about all this tomorrow.
Sounds good.
Hey Igor, open games folder.
Yes master,
battery at 3%.
Um, hey, do you have an extra
phone charger I could use?
I want to do Wordle.
Uh, yeah, there's one in the
socket next to the kitchen sink
to the left of you.
You want me to get it for you?
Oh, I can get it.
Thank you.
Can I wear this
shirt on the chair?
Yeah, go for it!
Black.
Hey, did you ever get into
Dave Matthews Band?
Yeah, I saw him once in college.
Ash?
But are you sure?
Guy, I know what I smelled
and what I found, okay?
It's Cedric.
Okay, where are you?
He broke into my house earlier,
so I'm at the restaurant.
Good idea, stay there.
I'll send some guys.
You can all hunker down
there until we've got him.
I'll go myself.
Maybe I can get
him to surrender peacefully.
Okay, I turned a light on in
the back for when they get here.
Keep the door locked.
I'll call when I
know who's coming.
Okay.
And Ash?
Yeah?
Don't feel bad.
I didn't see it coming either.
Thanks.
Call for you, master,
from Cedric.
I know what you did.
What?
I found everything.
Ash, where are you?
Oh, wouldn't you like to know.
I'm sorry, what are you saying?
What I'm saying is the cleaner
that I smelled that night, I
found under your sink.
And the boots that I heard that
night, I found by
your front door.
The black boots.
You mean the cleaner
you spilled on my floor?
Yeah, the cleaner you used
to clean up Andre's body?
And the boots at
the end of the row?
Yes, the, the boots.
They're department issue.
What?
The cleaners used at crime
scenes and the boots are
tactical gear for SWAT raids.
What are you saying?
Any cop could have these.
Cedric-
I'm really sorry about this.
Guy?
I really am.
Screw you.
Stop!
Ash. You know I've got a gun,
but I don't have to use it.
Come quietly,
and I promise I'll
make it painless.
I have a better idea.
No!
Ash?
Damn it!
Where is it?
Come on, come on, come on.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
There you are.
Hey, it's me.
Hey.
Um.
So I just got off the phone
with Guy's ex, Samantha.
My hunch was right.
She's the person
Andre was dating.
Best guess is an
argument over her
got out of hand, and everything
else was just him trying to
cover things up and silence you.
I knew that guy was a jerk.
Is he dead?
Uh, yeah.
What a waste.
We've got people
you can talk to.
Thank you.
Well, I'll go check on that,
and, um, I'll, I'll update you
guys when I can, okay?
I can't believe this.
You're gonna be okay.
Ash, hey, wait up.
Jean said you left.
They said I was free to go.
I just-
I had to get out of there.
Are you okay?
I just killed somebody.
I'm miles from okay.
I'm sorry.
I know he was your friend.
Yeah, he was.
Or I thought he was.
He had us all fooled.
Yeah.
Look, I'm so sorry for
screwing things up between us.
What do you mean?
3 hours ago, I was convinced
you were trying to kill me.
I know.
That doesn't bother you?
There were serious
extenuating circumstances.
Circumstances or
not, it bothers me.
I think it's an issue when the
relationship troubles predate
the relationship.
Well, it seems to me that in
order for you to work through
your relationship problems, you
have to be in a relationship.
I just don't know how we
would get past all this.
Maybe it's what Johnny told
Vienna in Johnny Guitar.
We both just had a bad dream,
but now it's over
and we're awake.
That didn't work in the movie.
So?
Maybe it'll work for us.
Maybe.
Okay.
Can I walk you home?