Chemical evolution.
75% of the universe is hydrogen.
A single electron
creates a unique pattern
as it circles a single proton.
Clouds of hydrogen can
become so thick that
they collapse, ignite, and a star is born.
Inside the star, hydrogen is converted
to helium,
providing heat for billions of years.
Eventually, the hydrogen runs out
and the star begins to glow
red and orange.
Instead of helium, heavy elements,
such as carbon and oxygen, are formed.
Your body is made from these elements.
By looking at their unique patterns,
we can identify your star.
Your chemical mother.
Gunthur,
Satish, what's happening?
Oh, it's great. Yeah,
I got a Cambridge degree
£30,000 in debt, I'm on
a minimum wage and now
I'm taking on an extra
£10,000 in travel expenses.
It would've been better going
to CyberChem in Newcastle
and facing the cold.
That bad?
So, where are you two staying?
We are sharing a flat on Burberry Lane.
Really just around the corner
from me in Linden Avenue.
And how do you guys know each other?
We're friends on World of Warcraft.
Oh, my God.
Advanced Geeks.
How did you two meet?
I found her on Facebook.
So,
erm... What can we do about
travel expenses?
I really can't afford it.
Do you know apparently according
to the New Starters manual,
if you have any complaints,
you talk to a member of staff
or ultimately to the CEO.
Professor Nielson's the CEO.
Yeah, we'll have to talk to him.
And say what exactly?
That we're
happy to work for peanuts,
but we want our expenses paid.
And miss out on a year's worth of
experience when they show us the door.
No.
Well, someone must know what to do.
Forget speaking to the head of our
department. It will have to be the CEO.
Yeah.
And we will be right behind you.
Hang on a minute. I don't remember
standing up as team leader.
Go find another sacrificial lamb.
You'd make a great leader.
I don't want to make it seem
like I'm backing out or anything, but
I don't actually qualify
for travel expenses.
I earn too much already.
Really?
No, but that doesn't mean
I wouldn't stand behind you
and fight for what's right, honestly.
Well, mate, why don't
you just become leader?
My English language would
let you all down, I think.
At some point.
It could give you, like, a bad infection.
Thank you.
Just get the drinks.
Oh.
Yeah, I know.
I knew it's a thing,
but I, I never knew it's called Peggy?
No pegging!
Come in.
Good morning, Professor Nielson.
I'm Alex Summers.
Mr. Summers.
Alex.
It's fine to call me Jon.
Professor Nielson's
a little too grandiose.
Now, I hear you're unhappy
with your expenses.
Well, profes...
Jon, um.
My fellow New Starters and I
feel that being asked to pay
our own travel expenses is, uh,
is unfair.
Really, and what evidence have you
of its fairness?
According to the latest government survey,
75% of all employers
who pay their staff a minimum wage
also pay their travel expenses.
Well, you seem to have done your homework,
but that still leaves 25% who don't.
No, our purpose here
is to provide an environment
with the best equipment
so our New Starters
can create and learn.
But we're paying to be here
and we're not even being taught.
All staff are temporary.
Well, I have to say I had no idea.
You accept the situation isn't good?
Let's just say I accept your description.
I am aware of the managerial situation,
and I am doing my best to rectify it.
But do you really think
that this company needs or wants
groups of New Starters doing nothing?
No, I'm, I'm sure it doesn't.
So what exactly can we do?
Deal with the situation, young man.
Utilize the facilities.
Get something started.
Look, there are still some
good staff on the team.
It is my job
to turn the situation around.
But you are from Oxford.
One of the most prestigious
universities in the world, Alex.
There are no rules here.
This is cutting edge.
Come up with a game plan
and execute it.
Now I
can tell from your expression
that no one has explained
the rules of the game to you.
You work for peanuts,
and we do not charge you
for the use of our equipment.
You then make something that you
think is unique and worth some money.
We then meet and decide
if we can make money from it.
Then if we like it, we exploit it and you.
And in the process of exploitation,
you will earn some money.
You will probably moan about
how little it is, considering that
you invented it, blah, blah, blah,
and then you will go away
and form your new business.
Right.
Right. Then,
if you leave without screaming,
your business will get to a size
where it needs investment.
And then you will speak to me and say?
I need investors.
Use your skills wisely, Alex.
Come up with a new idea.
Network with New Starters and staff.
I will.
Remember, be disruptive.
Make something that disrupts
an existing business or industry,
turn it upside down.
Destroy its sales model.
The more people it affects,
the more money it makes,
and the more people will pay to stop it.
You have got a real opportunity
here at CCL, Alex.
Don't you waste it.
I, I won't. I won't!
Thank you, Jon.
Thank you.
Another sucker exploited,
or a genius in the making.
Hey, Alex, how's it going, mate?
All right, G's.
Just been studying.
Oh, really?
What ya studying?
Chemistry.
I think I have a plan.
But it could be rather disrupting.
Disruption's good.
It's always necessary for a startup.
Yeah, well, this could be like making
a startup with a nuke.
Yeah. Let's do it.
OK, well, um, the guys over at Oxford
and many here have been taking
neuroenhancers.
What the hell are they?
They are similar in effect to
a drug used by kids suffering
from ADHD called Ritalin.
I had to take some myself
to stop me fragging out.
How do they make you feel?
Well, they help you concentrate mostly,
but they also let you sleep
if you stick to the correct dose.
Many have been taking
something called Modafinil.
Wa-wa-wa-wait.
Surely it's going to be
really expensive, no?
£20 to £30 a tab.
Twice a day.
Why don't they just stick to cocaine?
Surely that's cheaper?
Not as cheap as free.
Wait, what do you mean free?
Like for nothing?
Totally free?
Probably not completely free, but
very, very cheap.
OK.
OK, wait.
Ooh.
Seems appropriate.
All right, go on.
OK, I found a method, I think
of producing Modafinil
from basic ingredients
that we could buy from the supermarket.
I can buy caviar from the supermarket
that's not cheap.
Well, my rough estimates
are that we could produce
it at 20p per 200 milligram.
I mean, it wouldn't
be identical to Modafinil,
but it'd be really similar.
Right, OK, here we go.
So this is the big issue.
Gunthur, there is no issue.
If I'm right, it's gonna be just as good
if not frickin' better.
I mean, we'd have to test it on animals
then on primates and
then on a human but...
And then...
And then we make a ton of it
set up an e-commerce website and
sell it.
Yeah but...
what do me and Gunthur get if we help?
I was thinking 50, 25, 25
if you fund and build the production line.
Sounds risky, dangerous and illegal,
but I love it.
OK.
OK, so what do we need?
We have all the equipment in the lab
to make a small sample.
However, there are 10
different processes necessary
to change the raw materials
into the final drug.
Surely if we're doing
this on a large scale,
we can just reduce one of the processes?
Well, that's the problem.
But no, unfortunately.
We're gonna,
we're gonna need a lot of people.
Or use a lab that uses
robotic automation.
Shit, exactly. We could.
We could just repeat
what I'm doing in the lab
but with robots doing
it twenty-four seven.
And who do you know who's been
using industrial robots for the past year?
Do you know what?
I've actually got friends that can help.
Are you kidding?
Sounds like a plan.
Oh my God.
So we're gonna do this?
We're going.
Alex?
Are you in?
What's he been up to?
Jesus, Beth!
Are you insane?
Friggin' just get out of here.
You had a private party?
Satish and Gunthur.
And a friend?
Yeah, we didn't drink much.
So how's the research going?
Really, really good.
I, I got loads done after they left
and I only stopped 'cause I crashed out.
And?
And I...
I think I have an idea I can deliver.
What's this?
Mm.
I just popped by to let you know that
I'm off to my parents' house,
so I'll see you in a couple days.
Hey, Alex.
How's it going?
What is it?
That's the chemical formula
for the project.
And is it still free?
Well, the chemicals are down to
£15,000 and we're only
gonna need 20 milligram per tab.
That's great, that's
50,000 tabs at 30p each.
Hmm.
This is the list of chemical ingredients.
We're gonna need quite
a bit of sodium borohydrate,
methanol and thiocolic acid.
Cool, I'll get started.
But remember, making it,
that's the easy part.
That's just half the battle.
Keeping control of it.
That's the hard part.
Try to keep a hidden secret somewhere
and hide it somewhere safe.
That's a good point.
Hey, thanks man.
48 hours solid work, look at you.
A true benzotrisulphenol derivative.
Technically, you should pack a punch.
Hey, I've been waiting for you.
How did you get in here?
The window.
Come sit.
What do you think?
It's very small.
I hope it's not a character trait.
Could you not have made more?
Em, no, I'm afraid
that's it. 48 hours work.
Well, hopefully
Satish and Gunthur can help you.
How about you tuck yourself in
and I'll join you in a sec?
Phwoar, Kev, the bike looks great.
Good to see you looking healthy again.
You was pissed as a rat the
last time I saw you.
Great party by the way.
Thank you, mate.
Kev, I wanted to ask, we needed
to rent a few robots from you.
What for?
Does it matter?
No, no, no, no, not at all.
Just interested.
Um, just we need to automate
some of the
processes on a project
we've been working on.
OK.
Same price as before, £500 a day?
We actually need 20 robots now
so if we can change the
initial price a little bit?
OK, I've got 20 you can use.
Do you have somewhere we can store
them? Just somewhere to put them for a bit?
Yeah, yeah, sure. You can
use one of the warehouses.
Perfect.
Well, I'll get the guys to wire them up,
but you'll have to program them yourself.
Alright, sweet. Cool. So that's £50 a day.
Um, a thousand times seven
Yeah.
Seven grand.
How about three and a half cash?
That's honestly all I've got right now.
Cash. Just for now as well.
That's all I got now.
Cash.
For now.
Three and a half now
and the rest when you're finished, yeah?
Done deal. Thank you, mate.
What sort of heads do you need?
Um, just some spare parts
from a chemical plant.
OK, if you go to a Bin 3,
there's various pipette arrays,
test tube holders, help yourself.
That'll be more than enough.
Thank you very much.
Top man, thanks mate.
Sweet.
Not enough to do much but
down in one.
Alex! Are you OK?
Liv, hey I got to go.
What's wrong?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Just ah, fell asleep and must have
rolled off the couch.
What you doing to yourself? Maybe
take a break for a couple of days?
No, no, just, uh...
Give me five minutes and we can go.
Are you sure all this stuff's
gonna be safe in the warehouse?
Yeah, cos that's where I'll
be the whole time.
Whoa, Alex,
I'm not camping out.
No, no need, but
you'll come over with supplies, right?
Yeah, sure.
Cool.
Right. Um,
we're gonna need to stop on the way.
Look, since you're staying overnight,
you might as well take your time.
Have a bite to eat, have a shower.
I'm OK.
Cheers, dude. Cheers, thanks.
Be one minute.
All good?
Yeah.
Oh, Beth, you're right.
What, what time is it?
Hey, do you know where Alex is?
Is he not picking up his phone?
No, he's left it
at home. I can hear it ringing.
How we gonna get through to him?
He's working overnight in a
warehouse at Global Robotics.
Where's that?
In the middle of nowhere.
Why didn't you make sure he took his phone?
You know what he's like,
he couldn't wait to start
programming his army of robots.
Well, when am I gonna see him?
I don't know, to be
honest, maybe a few days.
I booked the warehouse for a week.
A week!
No friggin' way.
All right.
Bye.
So ya did actually test it.
How is it?
Well, it hasn't killed me.
Do you think it'd be
OK if I took this tiny bit?
Yeah, sure.
Just sit yourself somewhere down
because it kicks in pretty hard.
Cool, man.
Fucking cool. Um.
I am gonna enjoy today.
Phwoar.
God, this is amazing
God, how did you synchronize all this?
Ow!
Argh! Oh!
Aaaaaah!
Aaah!
Aaah.
Gunthur, you prick, man. That
wasn't funny. What did you do that for?
They must've thought you were an intruder.
What, you've trained the
robots to deal with intruders?
Not me. I just hit the escape button.
Look, there was just a slight hiccup.
Oh, yeah, hiccup.
Let's eat, OK? You'll feel better after and
we'll restart it when we're done.
I've lost my appetite, mate.
I'd like a go at programming
the robots when they're finished.
What sort of programming?
Alex's security code.
Maybe I could turn it into
some sort of product? Sell it!
Yeesss!
And any by-product is a good product,
and it seems to work!
Alex!
I'll just drop these off and be back.
Why? I'll take them.
I'll explain in a second.
I have some news.
Go on.
I think we can accelerate production.
Look, Gunthur called. Is everything good?
Everything's fine.
The sample I made
earlier, it seems to work.
Well, how could you be
sure unless you test it?
You took it!
What about the animal test, the safety?
I took a very small amount, 10 milligrams.
Alex, you're crazy. You
could've killed yourself.
Not really, I'm a chemist.
I know about drugs.
Well, is 10 milligrams enough?
Possibly not, so I took another 5 today.
Alex, you're scaring me.
You sure it's safe?
100%.
All right.
Let's keep this little secret
to ourselves because you
seem to get them robots
running awfully fast.
All right, can we get more drinks?
So what are we doing tomorrow morning?
We are in the lab.
Wahoo!
Well, I'll probably be at the door?
I'll knock on the window.
So you'll knock on the window.
Like an old married couple.
Hey!
Hey, Alex, did you knock your head?
No. Why?
You've got blood.
Oh, shit.
God, it's bleeding. It's just a little bit.
It must have been in the bathroom.
Oh, hang on a minute.
Alex? Sit down.
You alright?
OK.
Uh.
Ohh.
You sure it's not a delayed reaction?
Hm, Satish!
Delayed reaction to what?
To the drink.
Has he taken something?
- Ecstasy?
- Stop no! I haven't taken any E.
Satish, if you know something,
you better say so, because if
- he can't stand I'm calling an ambulance.
- No, no, no ambulance. Look.
Hmm, stop.
Look, he took something that
might have reacted to the drink.
- I'm calling an ambulance.
- No! Stop all the fussing.
What drug did you take?
Jesus, you took the drug you made.
Are you fucking mad!
It was really small, not even five...
You still need to see someone.
If you call an ambulance now,
he'll get sacked straight away.
Hm. Look, just get me
inside. And I'll be fine.
Once, once I have some water.
Come on, yes.
Just take it slow, please.
Come on.
OK.
Just take it easy, OK?
Ooh.
You OK?
Yeah, I'm feeling much better.
Polly, I'm just off.
Can it wait till morning?
It's an emergency,
and I don't know what to do.
OK, what is it?
Two girls in reception
I mean they may be on drugs
or something, but they don't look like it.
Sorry, Polly. You're
gonna have to give me just
a little more than
that, to make a decision.
Are they members of staff?
Yes.
And are they high on drugs?
No, I don't think so.
Well, then why are they here?
One says her boyfriend has
secretly made a drug
here on our premises.
What?
He took the drug and collapsed
last night in the pub.
Is he OK?
Apparently, after a few minutes and
a nosebleed, he seemed to be fine.
What about the other one?
She also saw it happening
and she says it's true.
Uh, let me have a quick chat with them.
Then I'll call security.
There is one other thing.
She showed me a message from her boyfriend.
Says the drug may be passed on by contact.
What does passed on by contact mean?
Two girls think it may be catchy.
Like infectious?
I didn't touch the phone
and I didn't touch her.
And I'm not going back down there.
Shit! Where are they now?
Still in reception.
This is serious, Polly, I bloody mean
it. You need to do exactly as I say.
I'm not going back down there.
I, I need to lock them
in and call security.
You wait here.
Hi, it's me.
Jane Cooper here.
No, I'm not in any danger.
Two members of staff have stated
that they are part of a drug ring and have
made what may be an infectious drug.
We have two of them locked up in reception
but there may be others in the building.
You'll be fine.
OK?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, we're better safe than sorry.
Yeah, yeah, thanks, Gunthur.
Yeah.
Hm.
Yo, this stuff about
history being stored in
elements. How does that work?
Exactly as it says.
The history of each element and the
molecules it forms can be traced back.
So, chemical DNA.
Exactly.
OK.
This is serious stuff. How
you getting all the calculations?
I think I have an idea
where they're coming from.
The drug, maybe?
Yes, Satish, I do think you're right.
Alex, you're sounding kinda weird.
Well, I really? I do feel different.
Am I sounding nasty non-communicative or?
No normally you're a bit distant, aloof.
Now you're not.
Well, it's a good thing, no?
I don't know it's just different.
Well Satish, I discovered something big.
If I'm right, it's gonna
make us very famous.
I'm all ears.
Well, it's a strange and fortuitous
accident, a missing link, if you like,
between a drug that
exists and a hypothesis.
Strange in what way?
In a way that it's an
undiscovered derivative
that's way more powerful than Modafinil.
Somehow, it affects your brain.
Its effects seem to
be very long lasting and
I believe them to be permanent.
So brain damage?
More like a new ability.
To do what?
Think, analyze, predict behavior, Satish
It sounds like your Marvel
Superhero. Is it that good?
It's like another level,
like very few ever get there.
Where everything's clear.
Nirvana?
Probably the closest I'll get.
OK, wait, so, the old Alex,
is he still here?
Yeah, he's right here.
You're speaking to him.
Dude I've not become a different
person. I'm just the same, but smarter.
The same but different.
So what do you think of the diagram?
Yeah, it all makes sense.
I just don't understand the last bit.
This bit? - Yeah.
So, um, you studied
Chemistry as well as Business?
No.
Yeah. When you drove me to Global Robotics,
I must've had some residue on my skin.
Wait, how do you know that?
Don't tell me you're psychic?
Not psychic, just put two and two together.
The drug dissolves in water.
When you touched me, it must
have been absorbed into your body.
Wait.
The drug dissolves in water.
When you touched me, it must
have been absorbed into your body.
So you're telling me I'm infected?
It's infectious! Is that
what you're telling me?
Well yes, I didn't realize
that until this morning.
There was blood on my pillow and I thought
it was mine, but then it dawned on me.
So whose blood was it?
Beth's. I'd been with her all night,
and she received a dose that way.
Alex, I feel weird.
Really? I did the first day, too.
Can you fix it? Can you cure it?
You're not sick, Satish, so
how can you be cured?
All I know is that the change
seems to be permanent.
Right. It doesn't seem to be
based on the size of the dose.
The higher the dose the quicker
the change. But the
change is just that, a change.
I'm reasonably sure
they'll make a discovery that
part of my brain has changed.
I know it all sounds like Science Fiction.
Science Fiction!
Sounds like a fucking Horror
Movie, Alex. I don't want to change.
Reverse it now!
It's, it's not possible or advisable.
Well, it's not every day
we get a visit from the armed forces.
How can we help you?
We're looking for
information on a certain
member of your staff.
Well, what seems to be the problem?
Immigration issues Governmental?
We're looking for any
information on a certain Satish Jarel.
Well, gentlemen, I am sure
I can vouch for Mr. Jarel.
Is that Mr. Jarel?
Yes, yes, it is.
Where was this taken?
Mr. Satish Jarel and Mr. Gunthur Essen
purchased a substantial amount
of chemicals that are on our watch list.
Ooh, you are going to have to
slow down for me, gentlemen.
Your watch list. What is that, exactly?
It's a list of publicly
available industrial chemicals
that are used in certain
terrorist activities.
You suspect Mr. Jarel of
being involved in terrorism?
Mr. Jarel and Mr. Essen transported
the chemicals to a company
called Global Robotics.
Well, I am sure there is a
perfectly reasonable explanation.
That will be what exactly?
Well I, am not sure what it might be.
Let's, let's ask them, shall we?
So the purchase of chemicals
wasn't authorized by CCL?
Definitely not.
Any type of experiment or
manufacturing process must be
carried out on company grounds, and
under a manager's direct supervision.
Oh, forgive me. You must understand that
certain protocols are needed
to be placed in these types of situations.
I am 100% sure they're not terrorists!
How about an employee named Alex?
Alex,
Alex Summers?
Yes.
Yes, well, he's one of our
less well off members of staff.
Perhaps he has a score to settle.
No.
Alex?
I don't think so I...
I'm listening.
I want a full report
emailed to me immediately.
Security says there's a group of
infected people in the Lab
and we should quarantine the area.
Yes, Minister of Internal Affairs please.
It mutates the brain, sir,
and transmitted on contact.
Well, this is one of the largest
BioChem research establishments
in the UK. If you wanted to create an
infectious disease, this
would be the place to do it.
We may be able to contain it, sir.
As long as it doesn't get airborne.
Then we lose control.
I would need the full support
of the Ministry of Defense
and the Department of Health
to maintain an exclusion zone.
Thank you, sir.
Please call for armed back up
and prep them for a chemical attack.
I want a one-mile exclusion zone
around the Lab and Global Robotics.
No one in, no one out.
Straight away, sir.
Let's tell the press there's
been a chemical leak.
The press!
Jesus Christ.
I. I had no idea.
It's not about me.
Three story white sided building
on north side of the road is the target.
Confirm that on
north side of the road.
I'm going to glide.
Thank you guys 10-04.
Brigadier, are you in position?
Yes, sir.
What do you have for me?
The warehouse is some sort of
chemical manufacturing plant.
We have to stop production
before they put it into use.
I want water and electricity cut off now!
Straight away,
sir. I'll get engineers on it.
Brigadier, you understand
that under no circumstances,
the victims are allowed to escape.
We had to
restrain the female students we captured.
It's as if the
drugs affecting their minds,
making them suicidal.
No telling what they might do.
You have my permission to use
whatever force you deem necessary. Over
I'm going to talk to them. No, no.
Just shoot them if they get too close.
Hello, Alex, my name is Clive Leighton
I'd like to speak to
you. May I come inside?
Hello, Mr. Leighton.
Hello, may I speak to Alex?
Speaking
Hello, Alex.
May I come inside?
I'm unarmed.
Sure, come in.
Hello, Alex.
We hear you have a little
experiment going on in there.
And you work for who?
Well, I work for the Ministry of Defense,
Department of Health.
OK, and this is a
quarantine pandemic situation.
Correct.
And you will have to follow
the department procedures.
Very good.
But we are here to help.
We can stabilize the situation.
We can actually help you guys find a cure.
Oh, that's great.
However, I'm not sure I need curing.
Do your friends feel the same way?
You can ask them yourself.
They're all listening.
Satish!
Gunthur!
Don't you think it's about
time we give ourselves up?
We have the area surrounded.
There's no way out.
Checkmate, Mr. Leighton.
Well played.
Well, maybe it's time to give it up.
Just give me 20 minutes
and I'll explain it to the others.
Take your time.
I guess we're beat.
We need to move fast.
Guys, get the Glia.
Once we get it we'll need water
and carbon to complete it, and
they cut off our water supply.
What else are we missing?
Heat.
Hmm, what about this?
Yeah, that'll do.
Then, you know.
We need more time.
We only have 15 minutes Satish.
Even once we gather it together, we
need water and carbon to complete it.
Is someone gonna tell me, what is going on?
Explain when we're done Satish so...
Right. Take this.
Five days solid work and look at you guys.
A true benzotrisulphenol derivative
in the fucking making.
The big day.
You guys set.
Well, hello, Mr. Leighton.
Hello, Alex.
Where are your friends?
They're afraid.
Well, there's no need for that.
We're here to help.
Is that why you have guns?
They're just for protection.
I mean, if we really wanted to
use them, you'd already be dead.
What is your real name?
You can call me Clive.
Hello Clive what would you like to know?
Well, pretty much everything.
When did you come up with the idea?
How did you come up with the idea?
Why didn't you take it to your employer?
Who supplied the money?
What did you feel like
the first time it happened?
And, and how does it feel? And...
That's a lot of questions.
Is there any particular order
you would like them answered?
How about we start
with this place shall we?
Oh, this is a factory to make more.
Yes, I gathered that.
But what were you going to use it for?
If you were me, Clive, what
would be your biggest personal fear?
I would be afraid that I would create
an infectious disease that
could possibly get out of control.
Well, it's interesting you call it a
disease because technically, it's not.
OK, so it's not.
And you don't care about yourself.
Well, how about your friends,
your family, people that you know?
You have an infection, a disease.
Call it what you will.
But it mutates the brain.
It could end human life as we know it.
Now, I have a duty to contain it.
To protect innocent civilians
and evacuate them.
And what would happen to us?
You'll have to stay in a facility
until we can monitor it more.
And what about our families,
our friends, all the people
we bumped into, all those people, are
you going to hold them at your facility?
If the nation, indeed, the
World's safety requires it, then yes.
I have the authority to quarantine
10,000 people if necessary.
As your prisoners.
For their own good.
Alex, we can turn back the clock.
Help you guys get back to normal.
Normal.
What do you mean by that?
Get you back to the way you were.
See, that's the problem right there.
Gunthur are you satisfied
with this situation?
Would you like to see your family again?
Satish you too, your family
wants to see you, but we
can't do that without, working together.
If you gave everyone a pill
to make them stupid, Clive,
how many would take it?
Not many, probably.
We are ten times smarter
than we were yesterday. Wouldn't you like
to know what that feels like?
I might want to, but
it's not worth the risk.
What risk?
That you might be wrong.
That the side effects might make you sick.
I can't risk the human race
on your opinion that it's safe.
You think you're saving the
human race. When really you're
just trying to stop it
from evolving, and I just...
Alex your time is up, and
as much as I'd like
to chat, it's time to go.
We have an isolation truck
outside for you and your friends.
Actually, I don't think
my friends want to go.
I think
you should really be reasonable.
Your machines may be capable,
but they're no match
for the British Army, are they?
I'm
sure they're not. Either way,
I think you and your soldiers should leave.
I really think you should rethink this.
Ahh.
Ah.
Alex is escaping!
Get your men out of there now.
All teams pull back 20 yards Immediately!
Use that and we won't
have anyone to interrogate.
If I don't stop these kids now, this
infection will spread across the country.
Ahhhh.
Roger, bearing 225 degrees.
Going in to attack!
Hunter Brayus,
stay out of the action.
God help us.
Major alert at the
factory. Head back now! Over.
On my way back!
Making it, that's the easy
part. That's just half the battle.
Keeping control of it.
That's the harder part.
Just try to keep
a hidden secret somewhere
and hide it somewhere safe.
That's a good point.
Leighton? Leighton
this is a bloody disaster,
A bloody disaster!
They sacrificed themselves
to help our species thrive.
Bones, flesh and water,
their bodies they did hive.
Hydrogen, Oxygen, Carbon
to make the Glia alive.
The End