Take care.
Don't forget to call me.
I can take care of myself, Mom.
And if someone invites you
somewhere dubious, don't go.
- Keep your prayers and Quran constant.
- I know.
Just focus on your studies, okay?
I will.
God willing, I can take care of myself.
You don't need to worry.
Singapore isn't far from Jakarta
anyway, Mom.
But you can't come home every day.
Keep me updated every day, okay?
Take care of Mom.
Yes, Your Highness.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
I gotta go.
Take care.
Destination, Singapore…
…via gate two, thank you.
Goodness, why does my chest hurt?
No, Sarah.
Mom!
Mom?
Aisyah!
Ness!
Nessa!
- You're finally here!
- I missed you.
I'm glad we're on the same campus again.
Thank God.
Did you wait long?
No, not long.
While we're at the airport,
I'd love to go to Jewel.
So it's like…
Splash! Whoosh!
- It's so fun.
- Yes. Let's go.
This way.
What did you bring?
- You'll adapt really well here.
- Wow!
So you can ride the bus,
LRT, MRT, or even the cable car.
Welcome to your new home!
Aisyah Maksuma.
What do you think?
- Comfy, right?
- Wow.
Just make yourself at home.
Ness, is this for real?
Is this really within my budget?
It's all good.
I chose this so we could live
near each other.
My room is over there.
For prayer, the qibla is that way.
Here's your key.
I got this for you,
since you'll be here a while.
How much? I'll pay you back.
Don't worry about it. We're not strangers.
Now, call your family
so they won't be worried.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
In Singapore yet?
Are you at the hospital?
Is that Mom?
Calm down.
Thank God, Mom is okay now.
At the airport, Mom passed out.
Mom's heart condition has flared up.
Oh, my God.
Here, if you want to talk to Mom…
Aisyah.
Mom.
You don't need to worry about me, okay?
Just focus on your studies there.
God willing,
Sarah and I will be strong here.
I'm sorry I can't be there with you, Mom.
It's okay, you have a bigger priority
right now.
Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too, Ridwan.
- Peace be upon you too.
Aisyah. Ridwan's here.
Give the phone to Ridwan.
Here.
Okay.
One moment, Mom.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too, Ridwan.
Thank you so much for helping Mom.
As long as I'm capable,
I'll do my best for your mom.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Aisyah.
If we happen to meet, can I…
Ridwan, I think my friend called me.
I think she might need something.
Okay, then.
Ridwan is really nice, Aisyah.
He's helping with the hospital paperwork.
And not only that.
He helps me with my store and the taxes.
Yes, Mom.
Ridwan is nice.
He's nice,
but Aisyah has totally friend zoned him.
If you don't feel the same way,
don't lead him on.
You know I don't have
any feelings for him.
I think he's a really good guy.
He has no flaws.
A guy
is always nice during the courtship phase.
The issue is once they've won
the girl over.
You still don't want to get married?
I haven't even begun
my postgraduate studies.
Why are we talking marriage again?
You'll marry after graduation, then?
So, when will they discharge you
from the hospital?
The doctor said when I feel better,
I can go home.
I'm feeling better already.
But don't change the topic, Aisyah.
I will keep you updated, Mom.
Aisyah,
don't let the way
your dad's and my marriage ended
make you doubt or avoid marriage.
Not every marriage ends up like ours.
Yes, my pretty mom.
Oh, my God!
Aisyah.
Aisyah?
It's your first day,
and you already met a guy?
Yes.
What if he's a human trafficker?
That would be terrible.
Day one in Singapore.
Classes haven't even started,
and someone kidnaps you.
But, Ness, he looks like a good guy.
Well, if all bad guys
looked like bad guys,
the police wouldn't have to work hard
to do their job.
You have a point there.
Right, instead of grumbling,
here it is, Chef Aisyah's fried rice.
You're great at changing the subject.
Not really.
- Let's eat!
- Enjoy your meal.
Aisyah.
Surau?
Yeah.
We'll go to the canteen together.
Oh, God.
Oh, it's not praying time yet.
one smashed chicken set, and you?
Done?
Done.
You can speak Indonesian?
I can.
My mom's Indonesian.
So, I can speak Indonesian a little.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
We're just greeting each other.
It never hurts to pray for other Muslims.
Where are you going to go now?
To class, and then home.
Where in Singapore do you want to go?
You're in Marine Biology, right?
That's right.
If you like fish, you'll love it there.
Oh, my God, Aisyah!
You're soulmates!
- Don't start.
- No.
A Marine Biology student
landed in a new country
despite not believing in love,
but God had other plans.
She crossed paths with a man
who loved her deeply.
Heart-melting, isn't it?
Your life is just like a movie!
Ness, I'm here to study, not to find love.
You can do both!
- Enough. You're starting to talk nonsense.
- Aisyah!
Tell me, what's his name?
His name is Liam.
Do you know him?
Maybe.
Enough. I'm going to shower.
Our partner is currently out of chicken
for this batch.
But we have two other potential partners
who meet the same quality standards.
How are we going to communicate this
to the client?
Just book me a ticket.
I'll go meet them there.
Okay, sir.
Morning.
Give this to Mr. Eddy, please.
Come in.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Why did Safira come here?
She brought me coffee.
Just be with her, Ridwan.
You're single. She's single.
And she's pretty too.
What are you talking about?
You won't look at anyone else,
but no luck with Aisyah either.
How long are you gonna keep this up?
Confess to her. If it's mutual, marry her.
And if it's not,
just forget about her.
You're talking nonsense.
Where's Aisyah now?
She's studying a master's degree
in Singapore.
That's perfect!
Can you imagine?
Under the romantic Singapore night sky,
you tell her how you feel.
That's ridiculous!
I'm going there for work.
You can do both, Ridwan!
Aisyah is pretty, smart, and nice.
And she's a student too.
Do you think male students there
are going to ignore her?
I'm from Indonesia too.
later this afternoon,
I'll have a birthday celebration.
Just hanging out with some students.
There will be some Indonesians too.
So, you have to come, okay?
Will there be other girls there?
I'm a girl.
I'm Wina.
Just relax.
There will be lots of girls.
We're leaving together later, okay?
Aisyah, you should come.
- There she is.
- Come on.
Hey!
Aisyah!
Why are you just standing there silently?
It's okay.
Now, this is the perfect song
for us to dance to.
I don't dance.
Come on, Aisyah.
No problem.
Just dance without me.
- I'm not comfortable.
- Everybody!
I'm not comfortable.
- So, you're going to have some fun too.
- Dance!
You've ruined it!
He's a wimp.
Liam.
Liam?
Why do you trust people so easily?
I live alone in Singapore.
I thought having friends from my country
wouldn't be a bad idea.
If I need something or if I need a friend
to go with, I can…
Well, you have me.
It's not that.
I've been troubling you so much.
Aisyah.
So, it's my job to take care of you.
What happened earlier…
Was it a panic attack?
Since I was a teenager,
I've had generalized anxiety disorder.
But, thankfully, I go to
cognitive behavioral therapy regularly.
And I try to live a healthy life…
so when I have a panic attack,
it won't be so bad.
- To go where?
- Singapore Oceanarium.
Seriously?
So how are your studies?
All is well?
God willing, all is well.
You still pray, right?
Yes, I still pray.
Are you cooking, Mom?
Why are you cooking?
You just got out of the hospital.
When I order food online,
it tends to have too much MSG in it.
Right?
And it's not good for my health.
You're right.
But don't tire yourself out, okay?
Okay.
I'm just gonna check the shop
for a minute after this.
You should wait
until you're feeling better.
Or you can ask Sarah to do that.
Ridwan usually helps me.
What are you cooking?
Do you wanna see?
Look.
I have rendang.
And then jackfruit curry.
And I have green chili here.
Whoa! It all looks delicious.
It makes me miss home.
Or do you want me
to make dry rendang for you?
Are you gonna send it by mail?
No, I'll ask Ridwan to bring it to you.
He said he's going to Singapore for work.
And he's also planning to visit you.
Didn't he tell you?
RIDWAN: HEADING TO SINGAPORE THIS WEEKEND
IF YOU'RE FREE, CAN WE MEET?
Yes, he's coming here.
I'll give it to him, then. Okay?
Thanks, Mom.
I need to get back to studying
so I can stay focused, Mom.
Don't forget to eat.
If something's going on, call me, okay?
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too, dear.
Forty-thousand creatures, 129 species.
All are part of
the same aquarium ecosystem.
Yes, just like us humans.
That's how it's supposed to be.
They live side by side
regardless of their differences.
They can maintain the balance
and the ecosystem.
I'm so amazed to see a rare species here.
A species I didn't even know existed.
No.
Yeah, if you want or need someone to go
somewhere with you,
don't hesitate to contact me.
I don't want to keep troubling you.
No.
It's okay.
So if you want to go to campus,
it's in the same direction.
So,
Is it…
Insya Allah.
Insya Allah means, "if God's willing."
If Allah wills it.
Amen.
Your shoes are dirty.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Yes.
Ridwan, this is Liam.
He's the volunteer guide
who helps me here.
Liam, this is Ridwan,
my friend from Indonesia.
Liam.
I can speak Indonesian a little.
Excuse me.
I arrived in Singapore a bit early,
so I decided to stop by here first.
I wanted to surprise you.
Next time, just let me know first.
I might be out.
It's okay.
I only waited a little while earlier.
Oh, by the way,
this is from your mom.
Dry rendang, your favorite.
And the second one
is from me.
I got you dates
and a book by your favorite author.
I hope you like it.
I will. Thank you so much.
Sorry for troubling you.
It's nothing.
It's my pleasure.
Every time I visit Singapore,
I always want to come to this spot.
And I finally have the chance to do it,
and with you as a company.
- Have you been here before?
- This is my first time.
Really?
Where have you been in Singapore?
My campus.
Okay.
Around campus.
And to the Singapore Oceanarium.
Typical you.
If you're here to study.
You'll likely just go to campus
and return to your apartment.
Aisyah.
Wherever you go here in Singapore,
are you always with that Liam guy?
I'm not with him now, am I?
Sorry.
Liam takes care of me.
While everything is new for me,
he knows everything I need.
I think he's one
of my trusted friends here.
Before we eat, let's pray first.
In the Sultan Mosque.
We're literally in Singapore,
and we're eating Padang food?
That's the thing.
We have to try Padang food
in every country.
Why?
So we know which one is the best.
Let's eat.
Is it good?
It's good.
Really?
So the recommendations were right.
This makes me miss Indonesia.
That's why you should come home often.
- I want to--
- I…
May I talk first?
Sure.
Actually,
I was gonna say this
after you got back to Indonesia.
But…
I can't wait any longer.
I know you always avoid this conversation.
But now, I want you to answer me.
I hope you're willing.
I…
I want you to be my wife.
Thank you so much.
You've been so helpful to Sarah,
me, and my mom.
Yeah, it's okay.
Feel free to ask me for anything.
But I don't think it's the right time.
I'm not ready.
I'm sorry.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Aisyah!
Stop it, dear!
Aisyah will hear us!
You started this.
You accused me without reason.
Who accused you?
I saw it with my own eyes.
You were at the mall with that woman.
Isn't that cheating?
She's my work colleague.
Really? What were you up to at that time?
We needed to buy something there
for the office!
While holding hands and having fun?
Playing couple?
Watch your mouth!
- That's what happened!
- How dare you!
Mom!
If you can't be a good husband,
at least don't show your daughter
that you're a bad father.
Forgive me, dear.
I'm sorry.
- Peace be upon you, Sarah.
- And you too.
Mom passed out again.
Oh, God.
Thankfully, we're already
at the hospital now.
She was in the ER earlier.
She's currently in the treatment room
getting her heart checked.
A blood vessel was found to be blocked,
so a ring needed
to be inserted immediately
to relieve the patient's shortness
of breath and chest pain.
Sarah, if something happens, let me know.
I'll try my best to come home
to Indonesia as soon as possible.
You don't need to.
I called Ridwan.
He said, after his meeting tomorrow,
he'll come back to Indonesia.
I'm sorry.
I panicked.
It's okay.
Thank God.
- Okay. Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
RIDWAN: SARAH CALLED ME JUST NOW
YOUR MOM WAS ADMITTED TO THE HOSPITAL
DON'T WORRY.
HEADING TO THE HOSPITAL ONCE I'M DONE
Let's pray for the best for your mom.
Ridwan.
Sarah just told me
that you covered my mom's hospital bill?
Sorry I didn't tell you beforehand.
I'll pay you back.
No need, it's fine.
I don't want to trouble anyone.
I'm not just anyone.
I think of you all as my family.
I understand, but…
Aisyah, it's okay.
Your mom comes first. Okay?
I think I need to go to the airport now.
I have to go.
You don't need to worry here.
Let me take care of everything in Jakarta.
Thank you so much, Ridwan.
You're welcome.
And about yesterday…
I'm sorry.
I know you need time to think about it.
And your mom isn't in good health now.
I understand.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
I think I need a job.
If you wanna work here,
you need to adapt
to the workplace.
To…
the working hours.
And
the work environment.
But my mom is ill.
if you work, it won't take up your time.
God willing.
Aisyah.
Aisyah!
So I'd like to tell you the job here.
One thing,
you have to tell them that our restaurant
serves halal food.
Yup.
This gorgeous gentleman
recommended you to me.
And of course I trust him, right?
Right.
So you work here.
But you have to work fast. I love that.
I love your smile, your eyes.
You have to work fast.
- Thank you.
You're welcome, okay.
- Aisyah!
- Yes, Chef.
Enjoy your food.
Sarah. Hey.
Relax.
God willing, your mom
is going to be okay in there.
Just pray for the best for her.
Aisyah.
Why does your face look like that?
What happened?
Don't be like that.
Smile.
Come on, show me your cute dimples.
Aisyah.
Hey.
- Peace be upon you. How is she, Sarah?
- Peace be upon you too.
Aisyah, Mom's surgery went well.
Thank God.
And?
Mom is already in the inpatient ward.
You don't need to worry too much.
Okay, then.
I'm still at work now.
Let me know the details
after I finish work.
I'll call you back later.
Okay.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Thank God!
Hey, keep your voice down.
- Sorry.
Hey. What is that?
I just…
Aisyah, I have class.
See you later.
- What is it?
- I passed.
Here. Yeah.
I'm very happy with your work.
I give you this.
Thank you so much.
Your paycheck.
Please, do take care of yourself.
Send my regards to your parents.
And the guy, Liam.
Thank you, once again.
Thank you so much.
- Please excuse me.
- Yeah.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I forgot to say this.
You did a great job, Aisyah.
Thanks to you.
No.
I know my mom has a source of income
from her shop.
But I feel like I really needed this.
Just in case.
An emergency fund.
That's why…
I'm really, really proud of you.
I bet your mom feels the same way.
I…
want…
I'm happy…
to be here for you.
Agree?
I'm
also happy you're always there for me.
I…
want to…
always be with you.
I think I'm in love with you, Aisyah.
Aisyah, wait.
I'm so sorry.
Is it too fast?
Too much? Or what?
- No. It's--
- I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
I need to go.
No. Aisyah, wait.
What's wrong?
I don't know, Liam.
I don't believe it.
But I do really love you.
That word!
Love?
I hate that word.
Aisyah.
I'm sorry.
Love only disappoints, Liam.
Are you scared of being disappointed?
No.
Love is overrated.
Anyone can say "love"
and they can leave anytime.
Liam?
Wait.
Let me be disappointed for now.
Okay?
Liam, I'm sorry.
No, you don't need to be sorry.
I just…
I love you…
and you rejected me.
I'm disappointed.
But I'm staying.
I won't leave you.
Can we still
be friends?
Please.
Yes.
Oh, my God!
I almost shit myself.
I'm sorry.
Believe me, I really wanna hug you so bad.
But I know I cannot.
I'm not your "mahran,"
so I cannot hug you.
It's mahram.
What?
Mahram, with an "M."
With an "M"?
Okay, I see.
Mahram.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too!
You're finally here.
How are you doing, Mom?
I'm good, thank God.
I feel like Iron Man now.
I've got a ring in my chest.
Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
Aisyah.
Actually,
I want you to marry Ridwan.
Because Ridwan is a really nice guy.
But I know
you can't open your heart because
of me, right?
Did my failed marriage traumatize you?
It's not that, Mom.
Forgive me, dear.
I'm not a good role model for you.
Mom.
It's not your fault.
It's not your fault,
so don't blame yourself.
Please open your heart, Aisyah.
I'm sure you can find
the best man for yourself.
The one who can make you
fall in love again.
Based on what you said, it doesn't mean
Aisyah is actually with that guy.
It's just your assumption.
Make sure first.
And what if it's true?
Stop hoping, then!
Get your feelings in order,
and manage your expectations.
But let's just make sure first.
While Aisyah is in the country.
Are you serious about this?
You got a green light from her mom, right?
Yeah.
You're halfway there.
Great!
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- It's good.
- Really?
You made the right choice.
Aisyah.
Can I confirm something?
Do I still…
Do I still have the chance
to be your life partner?
What do you say, Aisyah?
I'm afraid to hurt your feelings.
Let's give it a try first. Okay?
- Sorry.
- Aisyah.
Are you going to leave me again?
We can be open with each other, you know.
We can try to understand each other.
Please.
With all due respect to you, who's always…
always there and helping me,
Sarah, and Mom.
I've always looked up to you
as an older brother.
And it's hard to answer a question
like that with a simple yes or no,
especially since I feel like
I still need time to work on myself.
I still have so many flaws, Ridwan.
Does this have something to do
with that guy in Singapore?
I think of him as a friend.
Okay, let me rephrase the question.
This "brother" and this "friend"…
do either of them actually have a chance
at being your life partner?
Only time will tell.
Don't wait for me, Ridwan.
I'm sure there are plenty of women
out there who are better for you,
just waiting to be your life partner.
Sorry. One moment.
What's wrong with you?
Are you possessed or something?
Aisyah's answer
wasn't what you were hoping for, was it?
Just be patient.
Be patient?
Am I not patient enough?
I've done everything for her.
I've done everything for her family.
But someone new came into her life
and everything I did means nothing?
Why have you become like this?
You're the one insisting on getting close
to Aisyah.
You told me to.
I told you to?
Were you nice to her family
because I told you to?
For what, then?
To prove yourself?
To get validation?
You don't need it.
You're handsome, nice, and successful.
You're a CEO!
You have everything.
But it's pointless.
I have no family left.
You still have me.
Damn you.
You don't care about me.
But I get it.
You're looking for the warmth of a family
that you never had.
And you found it in Aisyah's family.
And you said it yourself,
you think of her family as your own.
You're a good person, Ridwan.
And you did everything
because you're a good person,
not to get Aisyah.
It wasn't transactional.
So don't stop.
Just be a good guy.
Thank you.
I love you too.
Here, let me kiss your forehead.
Nonsense.
Kiss my lips?
Kiss my hand?
You're crazy.
New semester, new energy!
Hello, Aisyah.
Hello.
Do you have the new schedule
from campus yet?
Not yet.
Why?
I want to ask you out for dinner.
What do you say?
Okay.
Hey, what's up?
How are you?
I'm fine.
No, sorry.
Where are you guys going?
We're looking for food.
- There's a really good place down there.
- Really?
- Go try it out.
- Okay, then.
- I'll see you guys soon.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- See you. Bye.
Bye.
Hey, Liam!
- Brian!
- Hey!
- Long time no see, how are you doing?
- Oh, man!
You want a beer?
Come on, man.
No, go drink it yourself.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, it's okay.
Go have fun.
Bye-bye!
Liam.
- Yeah?
- What's going on with you?
What's going on?
You're different.
You're changed.
No, I just…
I'm preparing my best version for you.
Liam.
Yes?
I wanna talk about…
what you said the other day.
Do you
still feel the same way?
I still do.
Yeah.
I feel the same way too.
But I'm scared.
I'm scared of being left.
I have past trauma that…
that makes it
hard for me to open my heart.
Aisyah.
I…
will always be by your side.
Always.
So you don't need to be worried.
Okay?
Let's go?
So, are you two getting serious now?
God willing.
Praise God!
Cool!
That happened pretty quickly.
You're meeting his parents today?
Wish me luck, okay?
Amen!
Good luck!
You look so beautiful, Aisyah.
As God has willed.
Do I look good?
You look good.
Thank you, Liam.
You're welcome.
Come on!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Liam, you said you live nearby.
Why did you bring a car, then?
So it's romantic.
Let me get you a drink.
Hot or cold?
Anything is fine, Auntie.
Dad.
This is Aisyah.
Sit down.
So,
you're the girl who changed my son
until I don't recognize him anymore?
Dad.
That's true.
I always hear him say,
"Aisyah this, Aisyah that."
He doesn't want to spend time
with us already.
No, Mom.
Yeah, he's the one
who always skips dinner with us.
Always going out,
seems so busy every day.
Busy, very busy dressing up.
And smiling a lot too,
without blur bluff face.
I think he became a better son right now.
Don't you think?
Well…
Actually, we like him better now.
Thanks to you, Aisyah.
Thank you, Mom.
Oh, you know…
This one never brings anyone before
to see us. You're the first one.
Aisyah.
What did you do to him?
I see his anxiety
is not acting up so much.
Yeah.
I'm in a better shape now.
Of course because of the therapy.
And talking to Aisyah helps too.
And you also did a great job.
Not so grumpy anymore.
I have to.
His anxiety is partly my fault.
Last time, I was too strict.
And now, you're our love.
Come on, you're always my love.
Every day, I love you.
So, who's my love, then?
Tell her then.
Thank you, Aisyah, for today.
I should be thanking you.
Because of you,
your parents accepted me.
No.
That's purely you.
Actually,
they're…
amazed by you.
- Peace be upon you.
- You too.
Aisyah, Mom's condition worsened again.
She's in the hospital.
Oh, God.
I'm coming home, okay?
No need. Ridwan is here.
Just pray for her, okay?
I just want to tell you her condition.
Sarah, I'm coming home
on the first flight tomorrow.
Okay, then.
Take care.
Let me know if anything happens, okay?
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
Aisyah, what happened?
My little sister called.
She said my mom has been admitted
to the hospital again.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Do you…
Is there anything I can do to help?
Just pray for her.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
Aisyah.
Ridwan.
Mom.
Thank you so much, Ridwan.
Aisyah.
If you don't mind,
there's something I need to ask of you.
I'm…
asking you
to marry Ridwan.
Nah, bro.
Aisyah.
I feel like
I've been troubling Ridwan
this whole time.
He's been taking me to the hospital.
He takes care
all of the hospital administration.
I know…
you've been trying to help me.
But on the other hand,
I don't want you
to sacrifice your studies.
God willing,
Ridwan is a nice guy.
Aisyah!
He's a righteous man.
And he can be a good leader
and an imam for you.
I already think of him as my own son.
And I think
he's the only one who can be by your side.
Thank you, Ridwan.
You're welcome.
The most important thing right now
is for you to rest
so you'll heal quickly.
God willing.
SARAH: THANK GOD, MOM'S DISCHARGED
RIDWAN TOOK US HOME
Who are you?
I'm a snake.
A snake?
Snake woman.
What are you doing, Ness?
Stop being weird.
- What should we eat?
- The street hawker…
Aisyah, wait!
Aisyah!
Excuse me.
Stop being like this.
Stop ignoring me.
We feel distant.
Stay away from me, Liam.
Aisyah.
If you have a problem, you can talk to me.
It's my fault.
I can't meet my mom's expectations.
And I want to cancel our wedding plan.
What?
You're suddenly like this.
That's why you should
find another girl, Liam.
A girl who can understand you.
Aisyah.
Aisyah!
Actually, I didn't want to tell you this.
A few years ago…
Liam and I dated.
But…
only for a short while.
Just two or three months.
And we didn't do anything.
We only exchanged ideas and thoughts, or…
Liam is not a guy
who'd do anything to a girl,
or play around with girls
or take advantage of them.
The point is he knows boundaries.
Liam was the one
who ended our relationship.
It's because I wasn't ready
to get serious with him.
Well, you know me, Aisyah.
I still don't think about that stuff.
And I'm not as patient and calm as you are
when it comes to his anxiety.
Well, long story short, my life
and Liam's finally went back to normal.
Until I knew he chose
to build a life with you.
That means you've given him
something special.
I'm happy to be here for you.
I want to always be with you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- How are you? Well?
- I'm well, thank God.
Thank God.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Hello, sweetie!
You showed up right on time.
Sit down, Aisyah.
I think Ridwan wants to say something.
So, here's the thing.
I'm here to pick up our conversation
from the other day.
That…
I want to officially propose to Aisyah.
Would you and Aisyah accept my proposal?
Thank God.
I super-duper agree with this.
What about you, Aisyah?
I…
I accept it.
Thank God.
I'm so glad to hear that.
I hope everything goes well.
Amen.
- In God's name.
May I come in?
Don't lie, Aisyah.
What do you mean?
About earlier.
You… actually wanted
to turn down his proposal, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Just because of my wishes,
you ended up being burdened
with a marriage you didn't want.
You should be the one who should decide
about this marriage.
Not because you feel sorry for me.
Or for Ridwan.
Don't burden yourself that much, Aisyah.
Just be honest with me.
We're family, aren't we?
I'm sorry
that I'm still unable to help you
and Sarah.
I should be the sorry one…
for burdening you.
I don't want you
to sacrifice your happiness for me.
Okay?
AISYAH: RIDWAN, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
Aisyah,
is something on your mind?
Ridwan, you're a nice guy.
In fact, you're so nice
that I can't even find a single flaw
in you.
Meanwhile, I still need a lot of time
to work on myself.
I have many flaws--
Aisyah, enough. Enough.
You don't need to go on and on
to cover up your feelings.
And you don't need to feel bad for me.
I told you,
you need to be decisive.
Because the only one who knows
what will make you happy is you.
Now,
answer me honestly.
What were you actually
trying to say yesterday?
I'm sorry, Ridwan.
I can't accept your proposal.
That's it, Aisyah.
That's what I want to hear.
Your honest answer.
I also feel
the same as you.
I can't marry you
knowing you won't be happy.
Once again, I'm sorry, Ridwan.
Yeah.
It's okay.
Actually…
I didn't want to get here late,
but I had to pick someone up
at the airport.
Just a minute.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Aisyah.
you're wrong, Aisyah.
Love is not overrated.
In fact, it was you
who understood best what love really is.
It's not about the words,
but about doing.
Like what you're doing for your mom.
What you're doing for Sarah.
Your prayers for fellow Muslims.
And
your patience with me.
Love is about
committing…
to truly being present.
Aisyah.
I'm leaving, okay.
Thank you, Ridwan.
Thanks to our meeting in Singapore,
I finally came to understand
the true meaning of love.
I now believe
that there's something much bigger
than us.
Whose love
and affection encompass
absolutely everything.
So…
if…
we wait until after I graduate…
would you agree to that?
Wait…
God willing.
For you, jasmine tea.
You don't like coffee, do you?
Thank you.
Stop looking at me.
So, are you going right back to Indo
after this?
Yes.
After that, are you getting married?
You'll be there, right?
Don't cry.
I marry you to Aisyah, daughter of Rahman,
with a dowry of a set of prayer garments,
paid in cash.
I accept the marriage and the wedding
of Aisyah, daughter of Rahman,
with the dowry paid in cash.
Witnesses?
- Valid?
- Valid!