You took her from me.
One moment she was laughing...
...the sun in her hair...
...her hands reaching for mine.
The next?
Gone.
The crimson tide pulling her
beneath the waves...
...her scream lost
in the roar of the sea.
I dove in.
But all I found was
the emptiness you left behind.
I spent my life living
off this ocean...
...reading its moods,
respecting its power.
But when it took her...
...when youtook her...
I learned something new.
The sea takes what it wants...
and leaves the rest of us
to pick up the pieces.
But I am not the sea.
I am a man.
And a man does not forget.
Hurry up, old man!
I'm gonna get naked
without you.
You're the one
who wanted more wine.
I'll be right there.
Aah!
Nik?
Nikki?! Nikki?!
No! No!
Nikki?!
This year has seen a rise in
shark attacks across the globe.
Warmer temperatures than normal
are shifting the fish population
and drawing their predators
into new territory.
From Florida to Nova Scotia,
the incidents have grown.
Drastic changes have
brought deadly encounters,
as more are drawn here
or are caught.
I'd quite like to.
It's a, it's a urine sample.
So, I'll go for it.
- All right.
For those of you
who don't know who I am,
I am Tina's
exceptionally proud father.
For those of you
who doknow who I am,
I'm the guy with the
bottomless scotch in my hand.
When Tina first told me
about this Tom character,
I must admit,
I was a bit skeptical.
And the more I heard,
the more I became suspicious.
A successful investment banker
who just happens
to volunteer at a center
for disadvantaged youths?
He did a tour with Greenpeace.
As you kids would say,
red flag-- too perfect.
But when they were hiking,
and Tina broke her leg
and Tom literally carried her
half a mile back to their car,
I knew it wasn't an act.
Tina, I'm incredibly proud
of the woman you've become.
You're smart, beautiful, kind,
and very ambitious
in the best possible way.
And she can have fun, too.
Does everybody know
in college, she won a
mechanical-bull-riding contest?
- No--
- That's right, honey.
Whoo!
Be careful what you post
on the Internet.
Whoo-hoo!
But maybe more importantly,
you always fight
for what you believe in
and what you know is right.
Our family has had
its ups and downs,
much like the beautiful island
of Malta.
It seems appropriate
to quote its motto,
"virtute et constantia."
Roughly,
"courage and consistency."
Marriage can be quite
challenging, but it's worth it.
Like everything else in life
that's worth anything,
it's worth the struggle.
It's worth the fight.
So, here's to the newlyweds.
Virtute et constantia.
Hear, hear!
Okay.
Oh. Uh...
Thirsty?
It's my party.
Yeah. Just don't come crying
to me, then.
Oh, that was really nice, Dad.
I meant every word.
Are you all right, honey?
I am...
I...am great.
You can tell me
if something's wrong, you know?
I know.
Always so stubborn.
- Oh!
- Since you were tiny.
Where do you think
I got that from?
No, no. No, Dad!
You've done enough.
This is enough!
- Stop!
Open it!
Oh, I'm gonna cry.
"Never give up on love."
Oh, wow.
Dad, that's so beautiful.
I love it.
And I love you.
Hey.
You just passed out
on the beach?
We need to talk about this.
I got nothing left to say.
But you're not the only one
in the conversation.
Jesus.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Oh.
- Hello!
- Oh.
- Wake up, lovers.
- I'll get it.
We know you're in there.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
Ah! Nice and wet--
just how I like you.
Hey, guys.
Good morning to you, too,
"Brometheus."
We have a surprise for you.
Tina?
Rise and shine,
you beautiful, blushing bride.
It's 11:00.
All right.
Just give me a minute.
Meet out front in five.
We about to get manic
in the Mediterranean.
Please... don't do that again.
That was kind of weird, right?
Eh, they're probably just
hung over.
It was a rager.
Where are they?
Probably consummating
the marriage.
Hey, there, sunshine!
Eat me.
She totally wants you.
Hi!
- Hey.
- Oh, there's our sexy newlyweds
with that adorable "just
married" glow beaming from them.
Good morning.
We know you had se-e-x.
We know you had se-e-x!
Now I'm pretty hungover.
Fun for me.
Aw! Well, maybe someone here
has a remedy for that.
I do. Industry secret.
It's called "hair of the dog."
You heard the man, babes.
Not for me.
No, thank you.
Are you ready for
your wedding present, muchacho?
Should I be nervous?
Only if you still get seasick.
Wait. What?
Let's go.
You're gonna love this.
Happy wedding,
Brotato and Mrs. Brotato.
What is this?
It's a boat, Tina.
They float on the water?
Aw, thanks, Sadie.
Good to know that even
a tropical getaway can't affect
your endless charm.
Rick got it for us today.
It is gonna be great.
I don't think so, bro. I...
I don't think we're up for this.
Dude, are you serious?
You love boats.
Didn't you, like,
live on one for six months?
That wasn't for recreation.
We were trying
to stop illegal whalers.
Tom, buddy,
this is my gift to you.
And it's much nicer
than some crusty barge.
I mean, look at it.
- We are super grateful.
It's just
I kind of hate the sea.
Then
why did you get married here?
- Sorry.
- And I get seasick.
I'm already not feeling
that great.
Come on, Tina!
The sea air will
totes make you feel amazing.
It's the number-one
hangover cure.
I can't swim.
So, what happens if I fall in?
Tom jumps in
and saves your lovely ass.
I don't see the problem.
Listen. I think we got to
sit this one out, bro.
I appreciate it,
but please go have fun.
All of you, please.
- Dude, it's a 3-hour tour.
Relax.
That's exactly
what they said to Gilligan.
- Who's Gilligan?
- Oh, Jesus.
Have I met him? Is he hot?
Bro, I'm not going to take no
for an answer.
Come on.
I feel bad about fumbling
my speech last night,
and I want to make it up to you.
- Yeah.
Thanks for calling out my
"stellar bod." Dad loved that.
How is that not a compliment?
Rick, you're an idiot.
Let's go!
You're the one who decided
to have your damn wedding
on an island.
Destination weddings
are supposed to be fun.
Dude, this thing cost me
a shit ton.
We are getting on
this catamaran,
and we're going to have fun.
Capiche?
Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun,
fun, fun!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Fun, fun, fun!
Yes! Thank you.
That is the attitude.
You got it!
Ooh, cute captain.
Boats make me want to fuck.
How does it not sink?
Boat's a-waiting.
- Thank you.
- Whoo-hoo!
All right, all right.
Welcome to my vessel,
The Tipsy Mermaid.
My name is Captain Mackey.
If there's anything I can do
to make your journey
more enjoyable,
please do not hesitate to ask.
Oh, I have a question.
Yes, beautiful?
So, what if we're,
like, really far out at sea
and oops, we fall off?
Are you going to jump in
and rescue us?
Well, it would be my duty
to do that.
So, I would.
But please stay on the boat, okay?
Aye-aye, captain. I wouldn't
want you to throw me in the...
What's it called?
- The brig?
The brig.
I'm just kidding, anyways.
There's no way
I'm getting in that water.
Sharks.
There's never been
a shark attack in these waters.
Anyhow, let's get
to what we're here for.
Let's party!
Yeah!
- Yes!
Captain, my captain!
Let's go!
Yeah! Let's do it.
Good thing I'm not driving.
Good day for sunbathers!
♪ Oh-oh, life moved on
behind my eyes ♪
♪ You pull me higher
than the skies ♪
♪ When the shadow spreads,
when the silence grows ♪
♪ You carry me
when no one knows ♪
♪ Life's a spark,
and love's a flame ♪
♪ You call me closer,
whisper my name ♪
♪ When I was frozen in the cold,
you brought the fire, I'm told ♪
♪ You say, "Hold on, hold on"
♪ When the night grows heavy
for your symphony ♪
♪ When I'm low, low
♪ Oh, I, I'll be feeling alive
and free ♪
♪ So free
- ♪ So free
♪ Oh, I
♪ Oh, I, oh, I
♪ So free, so free
♪ So free
- ♪ So free
♪ I, oh, I, oh, I
♪ Got me feeling alive
and free ♪
♪ So free
- ♪ So free
♪ Oh, I
♪ Oh, I, oh, I
♪ Now I'm burning
endlessly so free ♪
- ♪ So free
Whoo!
Tina's not innocent.
She was there.
That's what you say.
Oh!
Oh. Nice catch.
Why, thank you.
Avoiding disaster
is my specialty.
♪ Life's a river,
loves the tide ♪
♪ Rolling me deep inside
♪ You say, "Hold on, hold on"
♪ When the night grows...
That's why brides wear white.
It's science. Look it up.
Something about weddings--
they're like an aphrodisiac
for me.
Love is in the air.
I mean, I love love.
- It's natural habitat.
- You love love.
Very much so.
Very much so, yeah.
Easy there, killer.
♪ So free
I better go get a refill.
Want something?
No, I'm okay. Hurry back.
Big, huge boat.
True, I get that a lot.
And if you want
to steer the boat...
- Captain.
- Oh.
♪ Oh, I, oh, I
♪ So free
- ♪ So free
Could you just excuse me
for one second?
I'm just going to...
♪ Oh, I
♪ Oh, I, oh, I
♪ Now I'm burning endlessly
so free ♪
- ♪ So free
♪ So free
♪ That we soar beyond the sky
What's going on?
Just enjoying the sea air.
Trying to, at least.
Tom, I know we've been
at each other's throats,
but are you really ready
to give up on us...
just like that?
You're acting like
I haven't thought about this.
Is this really news to you?
I think we just want
different things.
We can make this work.
I love you.
I just need some time to think.
I'm sorry.
I need some water.
Seriously?
Uh... this isn't
where I left my dinghy.
Pardonnez-moi.
Let me just sweep past you.
Really? Rick?
What? He's harmless.
He's fun. Whatever!
Not everyone can find
the perfect man.
Hey, hey, are you okay?
- No.
- Wait. What happened?
Come sit down. Come sit down.
It's okay.
What's going on?
Um... what's going on here?
Are you okay?
No.
Tom and I
are getting an annulment.
What did he do?
No, no, it's my fault.
I...it's me.
I've been offered partner
at the firm.
That's amazing.
That's what
you've always wanted.
You've worked so hard for this.
Yeah. I've been assigned
the GoPack account.
The oil company?
They're vying
for drilling leases in Alaska.
The firm have said
that I will be fast-tracked
if I get GoPack's leases
through.
What does this
have to do with Tom?
Well, this is exactly what
Tom has spent his life
crusading against.
Wait. So, he's mad
you're taking the case?
I haven't even taken it yet.
So, what do you want, Tina?
I just don't think
it's that cut and dry, you know?
I mean,
this land is being auctioned off
by the indigenous people.
They need the income.
So, can you just tell him
that you won't take the case?
This is what I have spent
my whole career working towards.
You know, when we met,
we, like, spoke about changing
the world together as a team,
and I still want that.
But Tom is so black-and-white.
You're going to get
through this.
Um, honestly,
it's probably for the best.
Can I just have
some time with my sister?
I'm going to let you two talk.
Did I hear that correctly?
Tom and Tina are breaking up?
Rick, shut up!
Don't start with the gossip.
Why do you always root
against me?
I'm sorry,
but I've always said it.
He's too good for you.
I don't mean too
good-looking or rich or smart.
I mean, like,
too moral, too pure.
You'll never be happy
with someone like that.
Face it, Tina. You've always
been focused on getting ahead,
shedding your roots
and all that shit.
Mm.
Hey, what you guys up to?
Tom and Tina are toast.
Seriously?
What is wrong with you, Rick?!
Whoa, whoa. Wait. What?
They're getting
the marriage annulled.
O-M-G!
I knew this was gonna happen.
Rick, did I not say
this was going to happen?
What?
You told them?
No, I didn't, I swear.
No, no, no, Rick was listening.
- Oh!
- Whoa!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Dude, what the hell?
It's all right, it's all right.
Um, I think we must have hit
some rocks or something.
I'll have us smooth sailing
in a second.
It's okay. No worries.
I'd let him steer my wheel.
Get it?
- Yes.
So, like, you and Tom
are really done?
I don't know.
It's what he wants.
I don't want it.
Are you okay?
You really don't think
you guys could make it work?
I mean, you just had
this sick-ass wedding.
Tell me about it.
I'm sorry, babe.
You know, I'll be right back.
- Hey.
- Hey, there.
How you holding up?
I see word gets around quick.
Yeah, well, if you ever
need anyone to talk to...
...I'm here for you.
Really, though,
I'd love to hear you out.
Or if you ever just
want to relax.
Sometimes people just aren't,
you know, right for one another.
I, I just, um...
I just... I just think
I need some alone time.
- Sure. Of course.
- Sorry.
I'll see you up top.
- Oh!
- Whoa!
What was that?
- Aah!
- Jesus Christ, you guys okay?
Guys, what was that?
- What the hell's going on?
- You okay?
You guys okay?
This is ridiculous.
What the fuck is going on?
Uh...
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
It looks like I got snagged
on something.
- Need a hand?
- Yeah. Come here, would you?
Yeah.
All right.
Just on the count of three.
One... two... three!
Guys, come up here!
The captain went over.
What?
Oh, my God, you guys.
I don't see him.
- Sadie, stop.
- What's happening?
Wait. What?
- Rick... find him.
- Where did he go?
Bro, look for him, please.
He went off somewhere
towards the front.
He's got to be here.
- Do you see him?
- Does anyone see him?
Everybody stay back!
I think there might be
something down there.
- Some "thing"?
- Please.
Where?
Can anybody see the captain?
Yes, yes. Please, guys.
Every second counts.
Please.
- Oh, my God.
- Anybody see him?!
- No! I don't!
- He has to be here somewhere.
- Captain?
- All right.
- Aah!
- Throw it, throw it!
- He's there! He's there!
Get back, get back!
Captain,
you have to hold onto it.
Hold onto it.
We're gonna pull you in.
- Pull it in!
- I got it.
- Pull him in!
- Pull him. Pull him in!
- Pull higher!
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Go to the front.
- Come on!
What the fuck?!
Guys, guys, where'd he go?
- Oh, shit.
- Where is he?
Who sees him?
Anybody see him?
Oh, my God!
Aah!
- Aah!
- Okay, back.
Bring him in, bring him in.
Girls, go get
the first-aid supplies.
Please. Please.
- Is he okay?
He'll be okay.
Tom?! Tom,
we need to stop the bleeding.
Oh, my God,
I think I'm gonna be sick.
- Come on, Captain.
It's okay, Captain.
Stay with us.
Captain, you're gonna be okay.
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Captain, breathe in.
You're gonna be okay.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
S-shark.
- Stay with us.
- Did he just say shark?
There are no sharks
that big in this water!
We have to get out of here.
Okay, so I'm gonna see
if I can radio in for help.
Has anyone seen the shark?
This is fucked up.
- Oh, my God.
- Sadie.
Just hold my hand.
It's gonna be okay.
- Stay with us.
- Ooh, storage!
Engine. Ew!
Just hang in there, buddy.
That's a lot of blood, guys.
Mayday? May-- mayday?
It's The Tipsy Mer--
Anything yet?
It's broken.
Shit!
The signal's too...
Stay with us. Okay, Captain?
Captain.
- This has no signal.
- Guys, look what I found.
- Is that what I think it is?
I'm gonna shoot in the air.
Someone's got to see it.
They can rescue us.
No, no, let me do it.
I got it.
- Guys!
- Aah-aah!
Aah!
- Aah!
- Tina!
Oh, my God!
- Tina?!
- Tina!
- Come get her. She can't swim.
- I'm coming!
- Keep your head above the water.
Tom's coming!
Get her!
- Tom, please!
- Tina!
Please!
Come on, Tom! Tina!
- There's a shark!
- Shark!
Guys, shark! Come on!
- There's a shark!
- Guys, it's a shark. Please!
Guys! Guys, come on!
Aahhh!
- What was that?
Over there!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What was that?
- Oh, my God!
- Excuse me. Help.
Please. Help!
Sir!
Stay calm. Stay calm.
Hurry! Hurry!
Grab my hand!
Get on it! There you go.
Come on.
Come on. There you go.
Jesus! The boat's on fire!
You have to get in the water.
You have to jump off that boat.
- You gotta get off that boat!
- Sadie, get in the water!
- It's gonna blow! Come on!
- Jump! Come on!
Get in the water!
- Jump!
- Get in the water!
- Come on!
- Aah!
Keep going! Keep swimming!
Guys, swim!
- Swim, swim, swim!
- Help!
Help! Help!
Hurry up! My hand.
Come on. Get up, get up,
get up, get up.
You guys, hurry up!
Are you okay?
- Grab my hand.
You okay?
Oh, my God!
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, Sadie!
Guys!
You are my hero, dude.
- Hold on tight.
- Okay.
We made it!
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
- You guys!
- Whoa!
We could have been on there!
Oh, my God!
Wait, guys.
What about the captain?
He was already gone.
The captain?
It's my fault.
- No, it's not.
- No.
Everything that happened
was a freak accident.
It was a freak accident.
It almost looked
like it was a bull or...
It was a white.
That's impossible
in these waters.
It can't be.
Anybody hurt?
Just a little shaken up.
Thank you, again,
for saving our lives.
You were all very lucky.
Could have been a lot worse.
These tourist boats,
they just keep going further
and further than they should.
I just want to go home.
Uh, so, um, we're staying
at the Red Orchid, the resort.
Do you know it?
Would it be too much trouble
to take us back there?
I can't do that.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- It ain't safe.
What?
What do you mean it's not safe?
See that?
That's a storm headed
for the coast.
The water's going to be choppy,
low visibility.
I feel like
we could make it back in time.
You spend a lot of time
at sea, son?
Hey, wait, wait.
We're happy to go wherever
you were already going to go.
Please.
I was headed out
for my weekend run.
We can head south
around the bend.
It's going to take
a couple hours,
but there's a port there.
- Okay.
- Great.
Back to your resort.
Thank you so much.
And, obviously, we'd be happy
to compensate you for your time.
Yeah. Of course.
I need to inform the Coast
Guard about the accident.
- Okay.
- Guys, we're okay, thank God.
What I tell you guys?
Oh, my God.
We're safe. Right?
Oh, gnarly.
That was bizarre.
The dude came out of nowhere.
- Yeah.
- Something feels off.
What? Why?
I don't know, just a feeling.
He smells like fish.
He saved us all.
What does someone
have to do to earn your trust?
I know. I'm just saying.
- Projecting.
- What was that?
You don't trust people
because--
- Why?
- ...you're untrustworthy.
I'm more concerned
about that shark.
Why?
Because a shark like that
should not exist
in these waters.
Must be some kind of loner.
Oh, great.
Some aggro incel shark.
Hey, he did save us.
I know. I'll drop it.
It's...
No, I'm with you, Tina.
What's up with the cage?
He's a fisherman, dummy.
Of course,
you're afraid of anyone
who's not a member
of your country club.
Enough!
Figured you all
could use some grub.
Thank you.
It's not
the Red Orchid buffet, but...
He's a regular Guy Fieri.
He can do it all!
What did you just say?
My name is Roy.
Sorry. That's...
He's just trying
to say thank you.
Hi. Um...
Oh, I don't drink soda.
Do you have, like, a sparkling
water or maybe a Pellegrino?
Just take it.
Okay. Yeah.
Just this once.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Very kind. Appreciate you.
This boat
is not built for comfort.
Just try to relax.
It's going to take us
a couple hours, okay?
If you need anything,
I'll be in the helm.
That was pretty nuts.
Doing okay?
Nice try, Rick.
Read the room.
Mood is over.
Apparently.
C-can I sit?
I just wanted to say
thank you again for before.
Do you think
I was going to let you drown
just because we're broken up?
It was really brave, Tom,
you know,
an experience like that.
Oh! Puts things in perspective.
I know we can make this work.
I still care about you.
You know that.
But...
- But what?
Ever since you joined
this firm,
I just feel like I'm losing you
to your ambition.
It's easy for you
to be unbending
when you don't know
what it's like to struggle.
You know, if you get fired
or you choose to leave your job,
you have your family's money
to fall back on.
I told you I'd support you.
No! No, it's...
I will never be
the burden of a man. Ever.
I have worked my entire life
to be able to stand
on my own two feet.
And, you know, when
you first told me you loved me,
y-you did say that stood out
to you.
I understand,
I really do, your point.
But it only reinforces my point.
You are who you are,
but I am who I am.
There you go again.
You are so rigid and stiff
in how you think.
It's like your perspective is
the only one that has any way.
I was willing to forego
my ambition for this idea
of what is right.
Why didn't you say that?
You never let me.
And so I pushed back,
not because I thought
what you were saying is wrong.
In that moment, I realized
my opinion meant nothing to you.
Trouble in paradise, huh?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
There's no hiding on the sea.
I'm sorry.
I just don't know you.
And...
...it's hard... to talk about.
I'm not trying to intrude.
I was married once, too.
Not an easy journey.
Love is easy.
But marriage? Not so much.
That's the truth.
But it is the hard parts
that make it worth it.
Everything that is good,
everything that lasts,
everything that's real
comes from the hard parts,
getting through it together.
I know you guys are new at this.
You'll figure it out.
And the stronger you fight
through the current,
the sweeter it is to ride
through the calm.
You get all my ocean references.
And I live by the sea.
Where is your... wife,
may I ask?
She's out there somewhere...
...waiting on me.
You don't know what you got
till it's gone.
Promise you that.
Fuck this.
I'm gonna go say something.
Hey. No! Rick. No!
Hey, man, uh, no offense,
but do you know
where the hell you're going?
I was born on the sea,
pretty boy.
I'll die out here, too.
Cool.
Well, anyway, it's been about
an hour since we've been riding,
and, from my vantage point,
I haven't seen an inch
of shoreline yet.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
So, maybe it's time
you pull out your GPS or sonar
or a fucking map?
Whatever it is you use
on a dinghy like this.
And I think it's time
you take a seat.
- Sadie, you all right?
- I don't feel so good.
Tina, do you... do you feel...
Hey, guys, are you feeling...
Son... of a bitch.
Get some rest.
Tomorrow's going to be
a long day.
Sadie? Oh.
Britney!
- Oh, my God, Brit-- oh!
Wake up, Sadie.
What the fuck? What the fuck?
What's going on?
- Rick?
- Britney?
What's going on?!
Rick, are you okay?
You guys!
- Oh, my God.
- Why the fuck are my hands tied?
Get me out of here!
What the fuck is going on?!
What the fuck?!
What the fuck
is she doing in a cage?!
Help me! Help me!
Fuck! I don't want to die!
You guys, help me!
Help me!
Don't do this!
Motherfucker!
Hey! You're gonna pay for this.
Britney!
- Please. Please.
I don't want to die!
I don't want to die!! Please!
What are you doing?
Let her go.
- Roy!
- Please, please, please!
- Let her go!
Roy, what the fuck
are you doing?! Let her go.
Come on, man.
Please! Please!
I don't want to die. Please.
Let her go, dude. Roy!
I don't want to die. Please!
Please, please.
Dude, I'm loaded. Name
your price. I'll give it to you.
Aah!
What the fuck is wrong
with you?
Please. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
I understand, but just--
- Fucker!
- You fucking freak!
Aaahhhh!
Save that breath.
Help me, you guys!
Help!
You're such a fucking freak!
Help me!
Come on.
I know you're hungry.
Damn it!
Roy, Roy, bring her up, please.
Breathe, baby.
You're doing okay.
Oh, my God, Britney!
Britney!
You're okay. You're okay.
- You guys?!
- She's had enough.
- We're gonna get you out.
- There's a shark!
Roy, please!
There's a shark
in the water!
- Hey!
- Let her out! Let her out!
- Deep breath.
- Let her out of there.
Roy, don't! No, Roy!
Fuck you!
- Deep! Breathe big!
- Breathe!
Roy? Roy?!
Let her out, Roy!
Let her out!
Britney!
- Guys!
- You got to swim.
Get out of there!
Oh, my God!
- Britney!
- Come on, girl.
Come on, come on.
Keep swimming, girl.
Keep swimming.
You're almost here.
Ooh, so close. Come on.
I think it went away!
- Swim! Come on!
- Aah!
Britney!
Aah!
- Aah!
- Oh, my God!
What a waste!
So... who's next?
Bastard.
How about you, pretty boy?
Rachinda, are you okay?
What did you drug us with?
She's having
an allergic reaction.
Shit!
Not a total loss.
What's going on?
A little life left yet.
Good. Hopefully it's enough.
Roy,
you have to let me help her.
You want to help?
Your friend there
died for no good reason.
This cage is safer
than these waters.
I can tell you that for sure.
You do what I say when I say it,
and some of you
might make it home!
A few of you... at least.
Rachinda, it's gonna be okay.
Why? Why are you doing this?
You wouldn't get it.
Please, maybe we can help you.
Revenge.
That shark?
That monster?
He took my wife.
Five years back,
we were on vacation.
Nikki...
she had a beautiful heart.
And she got pulled under.
And I swam out.
Nikki! Nikki! Nikki! Nikki!
I watched the only person
who has ever loved me
torn to shreds...
...by that devil!
And I have been hunting it
ever since.
How do you know
that it's the same shark?
I tagged it,
trying to draw her in,
and I have used
all kinds of bait--
slurry, marlin chunks.
But she just doesn't respond
to the dead stuff.
So... I moved on.
Big fish, seals.
Hell, even cats and dogs.
Jesus.
See, I realized when
they get a taste of human flesh,
something changes in them.
And I've been chasing, chasing
her all over the Pacific.
And she just keeps going north.
I can't figure out why.
Climate change.
The waters are getting
warmer up here.
It doesn't matter anymore.
What did we do?
Why us?
Because you're here.
I was taking derelicts
and drifters, you know?
Folks that wouldn't have
people looking for them.
So, yesterday,
I'm out tracking her,
and--
and I see this yacht on fire,
and I see this group of panicked
tourists in need of a hand.
Tried-and-true buffet.
- Help! Help!
- Oh, my God!
Grab my hand.
Lucky for me...
Not so much for you.
It's not ideal,
but a group of entitled,
rich folks is what I got.
So, it'll have to do.
You are not going to get away
with this.
You are a weak man.
- Get off my sister!
- Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Leave her alone!
- Let her go!
Let her go!
Tom? Tom, do something!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Tom, help her! Help her!
Take me!
You want bait?
Sit down.
Hey, man.
Listen. I'll hire a crew
to get this shark for you.
You just can't do this!
You've got to be fucking
kidding me!
Son of a bitch!
You're caught.
Just give up.
We're saved.
Guys, guys, guys!
- Thank God.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
You're screwed, Captain.
Aah! Aah!
If you care about these girls,
silence is your only friend.
Get off me, you psycho!
Shut up!
You do exactly what I say,
or your sister...
Well, you get it.
Get rid of them.
You can all still make it
out of this.
You better be convincing.
Sadie, don't move. I got this.
Tina, you can do this.
Good morning, Nickina.
- Hi.
- Good morning.
Have either of you
seen a large boat,
a catamaran, out here
the last 24 hours?
No. No other boats out here.
Contained a wedding party.
About seven people,
supposed to come in last night.
Never showed.
No, officer. No.
We, uh, I'm just on a fishing
trip with my brother.
We do it every year.
We just got out here
this morning.
She's got a great cast.
It puts me to shame.
And where's your husband?
What?
Husband?
No, I'm married.
Oh, yeah. I'm married.
Um, he wasn't feeling great
this morning.
His stomach.
He definitely would
not have been able to handle
these waves out here.
Whoo! No way.
Aah!
Officer, he's completely
insane! Has us all tied up!
Freeze! Don't fucking move!
Oh, thank goodness!
You're done.
They caught you.
Yeah. Yeah.
You get the--
Aahhh!
Aah! Aah!
Sit down, you dumbass.
- Aah!
- Oh!
Waah! Aah! Oh! Aah!
Please, Roy.
The Coast Guard is coming.
They're sending more boats!
Please.
Stay put.
- Get him, Tom!
- Aah!
- Yes!
No, no!
Aahhh!
Tom?! You have to get him!
Enough! You want to join him?
Oh!
Oh. Oh!
Well, that's one less
passenger to deal with.
Sit down!
Now perhaps we
can get back to business.
I got a fish to feed.
Don't go anywhere.
Tina, try to take a breath.
It's gonna be okay.
Baby, come on.
Son of a bitch!
Stupid son of a bitch.
Hey, Tina? Tina?
Tina, look at me. Come on, Tina.
I need you here.
Come on, Rick.
Do one good thing.
Be the best man.
Captain... this can all be
water under the bridge.
We can work as a team.
We just want to live.
Listen, we can bag
this bitch together, okay?
You'll never have to see
us again.
You really don't shut up.
What are we gonna do about that?
I know you fancy fucks think
I'm some dumb redneck,
but if you don't be quiet...
Aah!
Now... unless anyone else
has something to add...
Rachinda? Are you okay?
My head.
Oh...
Hey... we'll get through this.
I know we will.
You're a survivor.
Always have been.
I'm not a survivor.
You were right before.
I'm untrustworthy.
I can't be counted on.
I was just being a bitch, Tina.
You're the strongest person
I know.
That's not true.
You've always lived life
your own way, by your own rules.
I'm pretty jealous of how
free you allow yourself to be.
Thanks.
Now let's finish this.
Come on, baby. Start for me.
Come on, baby. You got this.
That's it. Just like that.
Yeah, all right.
I see you now.
- Ow!
- Roy?
Stop!
What would your wife think?
She wouldn't want this.
Not if she's the woman
you said she was.
No.
She wouldn't.
But I do.
How many years were
you married to your wife?
Eleven years.
Long time.
You can still do
the right thing, Roy.
No shit.
You think you're clever, huh?
Yeah.
There you are.
Bitch!
Let's see you dodge this.
This is gonna get
a little messy.
Oh, shit!
I guess that didn't go
as you planned.
Damn it!
Oh! I love it!
I love you.
Yes!
I'll watch for him.
Just grab the knife real quick.
You can do it.
Yeah. Yeah, good.
Quietly.
Careful!
Okay.
Ahh!
You're way better
with this shit.
Make sure Rick's okay.
I'll take care of the captain.
Ready?
- Oh!
- Jesus! Are you okay?
Aaahhhh! Aah!
Aah!
Aah! How dare you?!
You just won't stay put,
will you?!
Aah!
Oh! Oh!
This is gonna hurt, Captain.
Not as much as this.
- Oh, my God!
- Aah! Aah-aah!
So, who wants to get
in the cage next?
Or should I choose?
I'll go.
No. Tina, you can't even swim,
and I--
You wouldn't even be here
if it wasn't for me.
I'm going.
How sweet.
You heard me. Let's go.
Unh-unh.
First... you tie her up.
Slippery, little eels.
Oh, my God.
There's got to be a radio.
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
Come in!
Does anybody out there read me?
Please, please, please.
This is dispatch.
Who am I speaking with?
This is Tom Barclay.
I'm on your boat.
Pervert.
And we are sending help
right away.
You don't understand.
This maniac has my wife.
Just follow the boat
to where I'm headed. Over.
Sir,
do not operate the vessel.
It is against the law
for civilians to operate...
Goddamn it!
She's gonna drown!
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
You know, for a shark hunter,
you're not very good at this.
Do you think you're funny?
You'll see how good
the fuck I am.
What are you doing?
Oh!
Rah!
- Get off me!
Shut up!
Stop squirming!
No, no, no, no!
Aaahhhh!
Stay still!
Tom,
I can't believe you're alive.
Had to make it back.
Couldn't leave things
on that note.
I love you, baby.
I love you.
Oh, my God, you're alive!
Where is he?
He's up there.
I think he's coming down.
What are we gonna do?
Let's kill the son of a bitch.
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Oh!
Fuck you!
Sadie, get some rope.
- Whoa!
- Fuck!
That bitch don't die easy...
kind of like the three of you.
Listen.
You got what you wanted.
The shark's dying.
Well, I guess once you get
the taste for blood,
it's hard to fucking let it go.
Hey, Roy! Catch!
Aaahhhh!
Do you know
how to drive this thing?
Yeah, I went
to boat-driving school.
Just go up to the helm
and push the throttle forward.
What's the throttle?
The lever,
just push it forward!
Okay!
Fuck!
No! Help me!
Stop!
Please don't! Stop! No!
Oh! Stop!
Come on!
Don't! Don't!
Come on! Finish him!
No! Aah!
Please don't. Stop! No!
Aah!
Aah-aah!
Help me! Help me!
Found this.
I knew you'd find
a way back to me.
As much as I hate
to break up this moment...
- Oh, my God!
- Thank God!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, guys,
this was the worst wedding ever.
They're here.
I told myself it was justice...
but it wasn't, was it?
Just a scared, old man
with a hole in his heart,
trying to fill it with something
that would never bring you back.
The pain's fading...
letting me know it's time
to follow you.
I can feel it now,
your presence.
I'm coming home, my love.
Next up,
we have the harrowing story
of a wedding party
that was attacked at sea
by a great white shark.
Elements of the story
remain unclear.
We go now to Tina Barclay,
a survivor
of the gruesome attack,
who has prepared a statement.
One of the only reasons
the shark was this far north
was because of climate change.
Climate change is something
that the big corporations
are not doing enough to fix.
Companies like GoPack
are ignoring their impact
on the environment.
I am aware
that I may be sabotaging my job
by saying this,
but I am going to tell you
what I know
so that maybe together
we can try and make a change.
Authorities surmise
the remains of the victims
have likely been eaten.
♪ I saw the moon take
a bite from the night ♪
♪ A shadow slipped past
in the dim gray light ♪
♪ Teeth like secrets,
sharp and wide ♪
♪ Something swimming
beneath the tide ♪
♪ The ocean whispered
♪ It knows my name
♪ Salt and fear
♪ It's all the sa-a-a-me
♪ Blood in the water
♪ Can you feel it rise?
♪ Crimson tide
♪ Pulling under skies
♪ You can't run,
you can't hide ♪
♪ We're dancing
with the crimson tide ♪
♪ Crimson, crimson
♪ Crimson tide
♪ Your reflection breaks
like shattered glass ♪
♪ A ripple gone,
a moment passed ♪
♪ Friends like ghosts
in the undertow ♪
♪ The deeper you dive,
the less you know ♪
♪ It's all nothing
♪ The current lies
♪ It drags you in
♪ It never di-i-i-i-es
♪ Blood in the water
♪ Can you feel it rise?
♪ Crimson tide
♪ Pulling under skies
♪ You can't run,
you can't hide ♪
♪ We're dancing
with the crimson tide ♪
♪ Crimson, crimson ti-i-i-de
♪ Crimson, crimson,
crimson ti-i-i-de ♪
♪ Oh, crimson, crimson,
crimson ti-i-i-i-de ♪