Don, Don.
Jen. Jen?
Don, Don!
Don, please!
I have to save my daughter.
Don't leave me, please!
Don, Don, Don, Don, Don, Don!
I'm so sorry.
Marcus!
It's been a while, Ms. Caroline.
Yeah, it has.
But I'm still gonna remind you.
It's Carrie.
Old Habits.
Yeah.
Hey, you look good!
You too, Miss.
Travel suited you well.
Oh, being away from him has suited me.
Car's parked here.
Can I take your bag?
You kidding me, right?
You always traveled light.
Yeah.
Hey, how's your family?
Yeah. Doing good.
Boys at uni, yeah, he's is feeling good.
Looking good.
- Mm.
We'll go on
a cruise in two weeks.
Oh, that's real nice, Marcus!
Hey, I missed you. I mean that.
Me too, Carrie.
After you, Miss.
Nervous?
How can you tell?
It's a bodyguard thing.
Well, have you ever
been to a family reunion?
Yes, but not on a secret island.
You'll be fine, Miss.
I will?
Yeah, you're a tough nut.
Yeah.
My family kind of have to be.
You're all right back there?
It's been five years and
it doesn't feel like him.
What? Your father?
This place, the island.
That's your first time here.
Yeah.
Doesn't exactly scream
"My father" does it?
That really doesn't.
I think the island prefers peace.
And he really shouldn't have bought it.
He'd be glad you got out.
Always is.
Right up until I open my mouth.
Still you can.
You cheated, Clarice.
I didn't cheat!
Yes you did.
I didn't!
Admit it.
Admit that you cheated.
Oh, fine.
Fine! I cheated!
Please, please.
I'll play the game right.
Please don't kill me. Please.
Too late. Game over.
No!
No, no!
Seriously?
Yeah, it's a bit smaller
than the New York place.
- A bit?
- Yeah.
I'll swing car around back.
- Okay.
Well, well.
Look what the tide dragged in.
Ava.
Five years and no text.
We thought you joined a cult.
Oh, I did. This is my sabbatical.
Careful, they've got
landmines for sarcasm out here.
Theo.
You look
exactly like someone who
didn't want to be here.
Yeah, you?
I'm just here for
the inheritance snacks.
Carrie.
Welcome to Dad's version of Paradise.
It's a bit rustic for a billionaire, no?
Yeah. I think it was intentional.
Something about stripping back ego.
Anyway, I give it 24 hours
before it burns down.
So this is it, then?
Full set, all the Cranes in one house?
Don't ruin the magic.
Dad's waiting.
But he wanted to see you last.
Of course he did.
Lemme show you around.
So this is the official nostalgia tour.
Living room, kitchen, panic room
disguised as a wine cellar.
Classy.
No tech, no Wi-Fi.
Dad says it clarifies the air.
Right.
I thought he'd put up cameras by now.
Samuel Jones. Motion sensors.
Yeah, he did. You just can't see 'em.
He wanted you in the East Wing,
said it suited your temperament,
whatever that means.
Yeah.
It's always hard to tell with dad.
His office.
Locked, unless you're him or Marcus.
Though they did leave
the window latch undone.
Accidentally, I assume.
Are you gonna talk to him?
Eventually.
He'll act surprised you came.
Like he didn't summon us here
like it's The Godfather.
Tell me.
You do know why she's here, don't you?
It's obligation.
Optimism, optics.
She knows Dad likes a surprise ending.
Right. Yeah.
But she hates this world.
Which is what makes her dangerous.
She's not a threat, Veronica.
She paints pictures.
She runs from responsibility.
She's...
She's a mere footnote.
Do you really think
it's gonna be that easy?
Do you think they're just
gonna hand it all to you?
Father's legacy.
It's a remote island with no plumbing,
and a sentimental complex.
I've been acting as CEO for two years now.
Nothing changes.
Let's just hope that you are right.
Let her have a moment.
'Cause when the dust settles,
I'm still gonna be in charge.
Oh, my God, oh!
Fuck!
I brought you some towels, miss.
I thought you might want them.
So what, no staff this weekend?
No, just us.
What is this, Marcus?
Austerity weekend?
Is he going outta business?
Not quite.
To be honest, over recent years,
I've not held your father's decisions.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry, miss. I've stepped a line.
No, you never, ever step a line.
I did.
♪ Deja vu ♪
- Unbelievable.
21st century exile.
Hey.
Marcus.
Ma'am.
Why is there still no signal?
I need to check in with two teams
and a pending investor call.
This place is a blackout zone!
Set by design.
No outside coms when we're on site.
Right.
Dad's whole unplugged
to reconnect fantasy.
Sorry, I can't do anything about it.
You could try harder?
I'll pass it along.
Still playing security guard
on Gilligan's Island.
Oh, is this it?
It looks amazing.
Yeah, I think so.
The guy at the cabin
wrote this is perfect.
This is just what you need
to take your mind off of things.
Hey, this is no place to be down.
Forget about him.
I can't.
No, baby. You can.
Look, I know it's a shit situation,
but the fresh air it'll clear your mind.
I guess you could say it's a shituation.
I like that.
Come on, let's get this
gearing height down there.
Did you remember to bring all the shit
you wanna burn?
Yep.
All in here.
Is not much.
This is Kyle's most
important possession.
Is Kyle who was-
Right, no. That's it.
Forget about the wedding.
Forget about him.
This is our weekend, so I
don't wanna hear his name.
And this might help.
Go on.
Cheeky bitch.
Better?
Yeah, a little bit.
Oh.
Well, let's get this shit and go.
Right, lemme just quickly call my sister
so I can tell her that we're all right.
We're leaving up because
we're burning daylight.
Sis, is me.
I'm just calling to let
you know that I'm okay.
Look, I've messaged you the address
of where we stay in, just in case
you need to get in touch with me.
Anyway, look, I'm all right.
I just need you to get
away for a little bit.
Anyway, don't worry.
I'll call again, right?
It's Kyle.
Oh no, you don't.
Wait, wait, wait!
No, this is not a getaway
to be listening to his bullshit.
But what if it's important?
Nothing he has to say is important!
Look, he had his chance and he blew it.
He didn't choose you.
So whatever he has to say is irrelevant.
Yeah. Look, it's my phone.
Yeah, well, you are my friends.
So no phones, look.
Not even mine, okay?
Yeah, what...
So what if something happens?
It won't be long.
We'll be back before it's even dark.
Lyn, no sad faces this weekend!
I mean it.
We're gonna do yoga,
we're going to eat fruit!
And we're going to burn
all of his fucking shit
and cleanse ourselves of
all the negative energies.
And drink.
Come on, let's go!
Quick, take picture.
I can't.
You took the phones, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, well.
Oh, it's beautiful!
Ah!
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Oh, my God, you fell on the mud.
Talk to me!
Oh, my God, is there blood?
Oh my God.
I think I stepped
in something gooey!
Gooey?
Oh, I thought you were gonna say
you broken your leg.
- Oh.
- Oh, my God.
I'm not cut out for popping bones
back into place.
Oh, it's a fuck ton!
Shit it's up to my knees.
What is that?
That...
Oh, that is not mud.
Well, no, it's yellow.
I don't like the sound of this.
Yeah, probably just a bird.
Okay, let's get out here.
- Let's go.
Oh, my God, no.
Let's go.
Oh, this something is not a bird.
The car, we have to go back. Come on.
Come on!
What are you doing! Get up!
My leg!
There's nothing wrong, Lyn!
Come on, get up, please!
Get up!
God!
Look, there's nothing here!
Get up now, please!
Please!
Get up, please!
I don't care how
cautious you want to be.
Begin the next phase!
They're adapting
faster than projected.
Smarter, they're testing boundaries
is not just instinct anymore.
It's calculation!
That's the point, Doctor.
We are not here to preserve instinct.
We are here to transcend it.
Proceed. That's an order.
Very well.
We'll begin testing on Alpha shortly.
And what about this IT breach?
We're not sure!
Our firewall picked up a data spike.
An attempted hack?
It was momentary.
Half a nanosecond, but it
triggered a warning flag.
Okay.
Run a full check on the firewall
system as soon as possible.
Very good.
Come in.
Hey, Dad.
Caroline.
So, this is the throne now.
Oh, don't be so dramatic.
It's just a desk.
You came.
You asked.
Ah, yes.
But I didn't think you would.
See, the others still perform.
Still posturing, calculating.
I might like it, but you,
you come empty handed.
Maybe I didn't come for anything.
That's why I prefer talking to you.
So you stayed out of it.
The noise, the power
plays, the inheritance.
Not for lack of invitations.
Oh, 'cause you are too
smart to play a rigged game.
And why bring me here.
Because someday, when the rest of 'em
have turned to dust and quarterly reports,
I thought maybe you should see
what we've done here.
- We?
- There's still time.
Maybe I should go find my appetite.
You look tired.
Even Titans get tired.
This is Marcus Holt. North perimeter.
Copy?
Warp B receiving.
This is Davidson. Go ahead.
Anything to report your end?
Quiet night so far.
Motions of sensors tripped earlier,
but probably just pause.
Nothing breached the inner perimeter.
Are you guys actually running out there?
Nothing
classified, I could discuss
over an open channel.
Is that a fancy way
of saying "Don't ask"?
Just keep
your hints quiet, Holt.
You stay in your sandbox, we stay in ours.
Copy.
North perimeter. Clear.
Copy?
Oh, you are cooking!
I know.
Brace yourself.
What even is that?
I think it was pasta,
but now it's more of a
wet existential crisis.
You didn't ask Marcus?
I did, but he said that he could make us
a ration pack stew, or a sandbag omelet.
So I declined.
Move.
You'll poison us all.
It wouldn't have killed you
to get garlic, would it?
I got salt and pepper.
I'll set the table like
we're normal people.
Sir. Dinner's ready.
Let them start without me.
They're all waiting.
Alert. Alert.
We've had a container breach.
We've lost one of our alphas and...
It's very rustic.
I feel like we should be
praying instead of eating.
Or in some weird cooking show.
Like "Billionaires eat backwards."
You'd have to start with step one.
Inherit obscene wealth.
We didn't choose to be born into it.
Some of us still act like we earned it.
And some of us pretend we resent it
while living off it.
Guilty.
Hypocrisy is expensive.
I got by without it.
You lived in a shack in
Montreal for two years.
It was a studio and it was mine.
Right.
The self-made master routine.
Better than dressing up
entitlement and ambition.
Oh, come on.
You don't have to apologize
for being a winner, sweetie.
You're quoting someone.
Is that Donald Trump?
Do you think power comes from guilt?
You're wrong, that's for peasants.
Power comes from balance.
And to quote Anthony Demouy.
Dumas, darling.
Anthony Dumas.
Human knowledge can be contained
in two words.
Hope and wisdom.
And Machiavelli said, it is better
to be feared than loved.
You are always so exhausting.
Power is only real.
It's inherited and protected.
Everything else is purely marketing.
You see,
I bought this island five years ago.
Used to be a logging territory.
Half of it I still own,
and the other half...
Well, that's under the jurisdiction
of the bio company I acquired.
Privately, quietly, and silently.
You own a biotech company?
Mm.
They operate.
And completely independent mostly.
You wouldn't know the name.
They...
They use the southern half of the island
for research, containment,
analysis, development.
I keep completely out of what they do.
Right. But you benefit from it.
That's the point.
I don't get it.
H-H-How?
I-I...
I run the day to day of
Crane Corp.
Nothing happens without my say so.
All this.
How dare you?
My husband is-
Ava, you have less to
say about the direction
of this company than anyone
else around this table.
Marcus included.
Dad.
Now.
I would guess you're wondering
why I brought you to this island.
That's a fair enough question.
You see,
Crane Corp has come to
the point of saturation.
It has too many arms.
Too many mouths.
It needs to have precision.
What does that even mean?
Well, we're selling off
several of the divisions.
Energy, logistics,
legacy, media, holdings.
That sort of thing.
Wait.
You're selling Rising West?
Oh, that's gone.
Along with Broad Bridge Freights,
and Synergy Energy.
You are dismantling the company.
I am refining it.
That's half the valuations, Dad.
You've already gutted half
the company now.
The shareholders would never agree to it.
They already have.
Last month's quarterly meeting.
Unanimously.
You got the board to agree to this?
They must think he's
positioning for something else.
Wait, what direction?
One with longevity,
scalable, protected, adaptable.
Biotechnology.
Neural development.
Regenerative medicine.
You've neutered half the company
to follow science fiction?
Will-
No, no, no. This isn't strategy data.
It's fucking suicide!
You've gutted half the
company already and now?
Now you're fucking your legacy, Dad.
My legacy isn't in what we own.
It's what we create.
To create this we need real focus.
Pinpoint focus.
No, no, no.
This can't...
This can't happen.
This, this, the board will need to vote!
And I am on the board.
Not anymore.
What?
Your seat, it's been
restructured.
Two weeks ago, the paperwork went out,
but no doubt you had it
sent to your Cayman Shell.
You are no longer a voting
member of the board.
You fired me?
No, I
restructured you.
You were
inefficient.
Inefficient?
Inefficient.
You can't be serious!
Dad, maybe we should-
William, sit down.
You senile, old bastard.
Containment Breach.
Please initiate.
What the hell is that?
Is that real?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
This is Marcus Holt. Crane house, copy.
B wall, repeat, Crane house.
We have a containment alert.
Copy.
Dad, where the hell are you going?
What's a Unit B?
What's being contained?
Dad?
Oh, this better not be
some fucked up rebranding.
Dad, is this the direction
you're talking about?
Containment Breach.
Level 4, priority.
Evacuate secure zone.
Be Walt. This is Holt.
Still no contact.
Repeat.
No response from south perimeter.
Status confirmation needed.
Over.
The alarm stopped.
'Cause I told it to.
I don't need noise.
I need clarity.
What is it?
Dad!
What the hell is going on?
Was that real? Is this a drill?
A drill? What do you mean a drill?
A drill For what?
Right. All of you, listen.
I want you to lock the windows,
lock the doors, secure the perimeter
and stay in the house.
No.
Not before you tell us what's going on.
Lock the house!
Don't bark orders at
me like I'm an intern!
Right!
Alright, sensors have
gone off on zone three.
I want you to fucking get
out there straight away.
I'll go check it out.
Yes. And take a weapon.
What will I find?
You know your orders.
What's going on?
Well, the island's secure.
For now at least.
You're lying.
You called Veronica "Ava".
At dinner.
You didn't notice, but I did.
What?
Dad, what's happening to you?
Look.
Go and check on the others.
Make sure the house is locked.
Caroline, that's an order!
Ah, likely it was just an internal glitch.
The Biotech Com here
always running these tests.
Fail saves, security tests.
They'd often forget to tell the estate.
Liar.
You know exactly what that means.
What kind of drill sets off
a containment breach alarm?
The kind that happens five minutes
after you kill your son's future.
Where's Carrie?
I think she went to find Theo.
East Wing.
So has Dad gone full Howard Hughes,
or am I the only one
not on the master plan?
I don't know.
What is it?
Nothing.
Come on, Theo. I can
read you like a book.
It's just,
you remind me of...
Is that the front door?
It's Marcus, right?
Marcus?
Just in case it's a Mormon.
Ready?
Not remotely.
Marcus?
Theo.
Theo, we need to go.
Right there!
Push, push!
The hell is going on?
You okay?
Veronica.
Where's Veronica?
We...
We moved her to one of the guest rooms.
Jesus.
What was that?
What the hell was that thing?
Dinosaur.
It was a goddamn dinosaur.
How is that even...
Marcus?
Look, I need your phones.
All your phones.
What?
I need your mobile phones,
your laptops, whatever is network enabled.
First, you bring us here.
You tear the company apart.
You fucking fired me, Dad.
And now there's prehistoric monsters.
And you want our phones.
Specimens.
Experimental.
There was a breach at
Ward B containment zone.
There, there, there, there was...
There was some sort of
hack on the firewall.
It caused the enclosures to open.
Specimens.
What were you doing anyway?
You were meant to be out
there locking it down!
It knocked on the fucking door, Dad!
What?
She's right.
We...
We thought it was...
We thought it was Marcus.
What were you doing outside?
What are you building, Dad?
Something that could change everything.
A new
regenerative biology.
A system that can outthink the disease.
Now come on. I need your phones.
All of you. Come on.
Come on!
Come on, Theo.
Theo, don't give him your fucking phone.
Theo.
Come on.
For fuck sake, Theo.
Thank you.
Was that the wind?
That wasn't the wind.
It's on the roof.
We need to check it.
I'll come with you.
Things go south, follow my lead.
That's unexpectedly noble of you.
Now it's not the time
for politics, Carrie.
Will, I'm...
I'm sorry about Veronica.
I know.
It's moving again.
Roof's weak on this side.
You see the panel, it's easy to collapse.
It is not charging anymore!
That means it's thinking.
It's testing for weak spots.
What the hell?
I dunno.
Maybe it's a signal.
Or maybe...
Maybe they're thinking out loud.
So what do we do?
We need to stop thinking like people.
Start thinking like pray.
Dad.
What are you doing?
I'm connecting the device
to the island's uplink system.
Wait.
You mean we can call out?
No, it's a closed network.
Private access only.
But, the specimens, they're fitted
with internal transmitters.
Subdermal.
Hold on.
You are not trying to communicate.
You are pinging them.
Like sonar.
Is that...
It's responding.
It's approximately a hundred
meters in that direction.
I mean, it can't give the exact location.
But
hear that, Ava?
The louder that gets, the closer it is.
It's looping the house. One direction.
Slow, deliberate.
Like it's waiting for something.
Like what?
An opening? Mistake?
One of us doing something stupid.
So any second now.
Never thought I'd be hunted
by a science experiment
my father greenlit.
You think he really means all that?
The legacy talk? Reinvention?
I think he believes the lie he needs to.
That's what Dad does.
But somewhere in there,
he's...
He's scared.
We won't last the night
unless we get ahead of it.
Then maybe stop sitting on the floor
like it's a yoga retreat.
Just waiting for the right beep.
We need to
get off this island, now.
There has to be a backup system.
Distress beacon,
satellite relay something.
There is no backup.
What?
The entire island
operates like a black site.
If there's a containment
breach, any breach,
the system initiates protocol locked down.
No outgoing signals,
no rescue, no warning.
What, we just...
We're just cut off?
That was my directive.
You. You gave those orders.
No one compromises containment.
Not even us.
It's not security. It's fucking suicide!
It's control!
So what's the plan then?
I still have a signal.
One signal.
You see two enclosures were breached.
The Avery.
The Avery?
Oh, they're flying now.
Jesus, Dad.
And the Alpha enclosure.
Well, and we're supposed
to just wait it out.
Well, there's a supply
vessel that's arriving at dawn.
Automated, minimal crew.
It docks at the north
platform for 90 minutes.
That's our window.
We just hunker down, yeah?
You hope that one of your little
Frankenstein pets doesn't
get in and kill us all!
Hope.
Vigilance.
You knew this was a possibility.
Yes.
And it's a question
between risk and reward.
Bullshit!
Bullshit, Dad!
This isn't a time to just
show your autobiography!
You stopped moving.
You still playing sonar?
Yeah.
It stopped.
It's behind there?
According to this.
A hundred meters out,
just standing there.
Shit.
It's moving.
It's coming straight forward.
Guys!
It's coming!
It's heading straight for us!
- It's Theo.
- Something's wrong.
Go!
What happened?
It stopped and
then it started moving fast.
It's adapting.
It's circling the house.
They'll be looking for another way in.
Where is it now?
Just passing the east side.
Now turning towards the north?
It's going upstairs.
- Then we go upstairs.
- Come on.
I'm not going anywhere near that thing.
Ava.
I'll stay down here!
Ava, don't be so...
I'm not!
I'm being smart.
Don't go anywhere near the windows.
Let's move.
It's still close.
And where did it go?
Fuck, it's moving fast.
And where the hell is it?
Ava.
- Shit.
- Go, go!
- Go, go.
Ava, Ava!
Ava! Ava!
He waited.
He waited until she was alone.
I told her.
I said, "Don't be a hero."
It waited.
It lured us!
It was waiting until she was alone.
Tried to isolate us, individually.
It's venomous, it's intelligent.
Dad, what did you build?
Dad.
What did you create?
Well, I...
I...
What are you waiting for?
Ray, I think I might've found
an answer to this thing.
Who the fuck is Ray?
Look, Ray. Look, look.
Ray.
Dad.
Who are you calling Ray?
Alzheimer's.
You are developing a cure for Alzheimer's.
Jesus.
I-I acquired Bio VAs
develop seven years ago,
buried the acquisition under
a dozen shell companies.
Let them work in isolation.
No oversight, no moral hand break.
Their goal, was not to build a monster.
It was to help build a miracle
of neural regeneration.
Cure all the diseases, everything!
The refocusing.
The selling of the assets.
You were...
You were plundering the company
just to save your own life.
No, save your lives.
It can be passed on.
Oh, yes, of course. If it's successful.
Ava's dead, Dad.
And if it was successful,
would you share this gift with the world?
Of course!
But at a price, right?
A cost to the consumer?
Caroline!
At least William knows what he is.
You just hide behind values and family.
She would never have let you do it!
Look, listen to me.
There is a way to try and stop this.
- How.
- The transmitter.
There's a relay beacon on
the outskirts of the island.
If we could manually connect with it,
the cell phone device might just work.
And from here I would be able
to remotely access the system.
How does that happen?
Every specimen on this site
has a transmitter linked
to the top of their heads.
Right, like how we've
been following that fucker.
Yes, and I can manually overload
the transmitter to cause
a massive overload!
Overload?
For its brain.
Will that work?
I'm certain of it.
What are you stopping for?
Think something's watching us.
What was that?
What was that!
Great.
Wait!
what the fuck was that?
Looks like a mutated bearded dragon.
- From the radiation?
- Yeah.
I think it's gone.
Here it comes.
Get down!
Go, go!
The fuck is that?
Keep it down.
They haven't seen us yet.
Been sure.
I'm scared.
Go, go!
It's fucking dark.
Theo. Theo!
Look, take this.
- What is it?
This kills raptors.
They're venomous.
This is the antidote.
I only have one dose.
But here.
Theo, hurry the fuck up!
Go on.
Keep them.
For you and Carrie.
Come on!
Boys.
The repeater looks like a computer screen.
You heard him.
You said there was a firewall breach.
Yeah.
Some sort of.
Momentarily.
Then there's some sort
of hack and now this.
Then who?
I have a long list of enemies.
Doesn't need to be that way.
Look, they'll be fine.
William is very stubborn,
and Theo is a lot more
capable than he appears.
He shouldn't have to be anything.
This was supposed to be a retreat,
and you brought us here
under the guise of family.
You came.
You could have stayed away.
Maybe I just wanted to see for myself
how far it'd gone.
She would've come, you know?
If she was still here.
No, she would've stopped you.
She was the only one who could.
I still remember how she used to sit.
Reading.
Always reading.
And this blue blanket
that she never let go of.
She always said the world was too loud.
The books made it quieter.
She made it quieter.
I see her in you, you know?
You don't get to say that.
How long until morning?
A few hours yet.
If we make it.
We will.
We have to.
Still hasn't moved.
Yeah.
That's either really fucking good.
Or really fucking bad.
It's waiting for us to get comfortable.
Just like Dad.
Hey.
Remember when he made us
dig that irrigation ditch?
Yeah.
We were, what, 11, 13?
Something like that.
He called it character building.
Character building.
It was all good until
you threw a tantrum.
And then it makes me laugh.
I did. I did.
Dad.
We're close.
Look for a narrow clearing.
You'll see a metal post, two meters high.
The relay should have a small black screen
and a manual port.
Got it.
We're in position.
We are in position.
Okay, on the screen you should see
an option labeled "Reset."
Do not hit upload. Just reset.
You hear?
I'm not fucking
getting involved in that.
What the hell?
It's fine. System's cycling.
I started.
We're in.
Now what?
Now we wait.
The system's handshake.
Once it finds the transmitter,
I can force an overload.
This is taking a while.
Theo, Theo.
Theo, I think I see something.
Will.
Get out of there!
Dad, we have to pull him out.
They're out there!
He's close. Just a few seconds.
He's gonna die out there!
He knows what's at stake.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
Dad.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
I love you.
Mom and I will be waiting.
And tell Dad...
No!
Theo!
Do you copy?
Theo.
I thought I was saving the family.
Saving myself.
Saving time.
Look what it's cost me.
I brought everyone here to
prepare them for the future.
Not dig in their graves.
For the past.
And now?
It's just us left.
I dunno what you want me to say.
Nothing.
This...
This is something I must carry now.
We need to get to the car.
We need to get to the docks
before first light.
The ship will be there?
It will be there.
I will end this tape!
No, no, no, no, no.
No, it's pinging!
It's all right.
The transmitter still sends a signal.
Even after the specimen's dead.
It's a...
It's just a residual bleed.
I'll go get the car.
Yes.
It's in the kitchen.
Don't forget it's in the kitchen.
Don't forget that.
We were in the kitchen! Kitchen.
That's the kitchen.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
So what's next for Crane
Corp and your father's legacy?
My father's legacy.
That I don't know.
I can only speak for
myself and what I will do.
- Yes?
- Are you watching this?
I am.
Looks like Crane pulled it off.
When we
attacked their firewall,
I didn't expect it.
It's fine. It's fine.
If Crane remained an equal partner,
this nightmare wouldn't have happened.
Well, besides quarantined,
the specimens are dead.
I wouldn't be
so sure. Prepare a team.
Elliot Crane was no fool.
A fishing boat was attacked two weeks ago.
What they described defies all belief.
We'll need
someone who knows the island.
What to expect.
Leave that with me.