'Nuclear Bomb!'
'The single most destructive weapon
in the whole world.'
'A weapon that will destroy
the world around us in a second.'
'The destruction it'll cause...'
'The suffering it'll rain on lives...'
'Afraid of the scars
and diseases it'll cause...'
'the world fears the Nuclear Bomb.'
'The thing we fear the most...'
'To attain that power to instil fear
is human greed.'
'The greed for power and control...'
'made man create more nuclear weapons.'
'This is the story of a team on a mission
to find those nuclear weapons.'
'And how it begins...'
'In 1964,'
'it began when China conducted
its first nuclear testing.'
'America, perturbed
by China's nuclear capability...'
'came seeking help from India.'
'A listening device was installed
on the Nanda Devi mountains,'
'located between India and China.'
'That kick-started a mission
under the code name...'
OPERATION HAT
'American CIA agents
and a climbing team from India...'
'carried the listening device
to install it on Nanda Devi mountains.'
'America hid the fact from India...'
'that they're carrying a device containing
7 radioactive plutonium capsules.'
'As the snowstorm became stronger...'
'the Indian captain
who led the expedition'
'decided to end the mission midway.'
It's not possible to go up!
Avalanche!
Everybody run!
'India later discovered
that the missing nuclear device...'
'could cause radioactive damage
lasting 200 years.'
'Many search teams were deployed.'
'But they could not find it.'
'Many stories were written based on it.'
'Chinese spies took it away.'
'It flew down the Ganga river.'
'It's buried under the glaciers.'
'But nobody knows
what happened to it until now.'
'Until now...'
'Just until now!'
"Hey!"
"Every corner of the station got a camera"
"But I'm ghost moving in the shadows,
heavy rounds pound"
"Synchronized, trigger couple rounds"
"Strike couple keys, take your final bow"
"Fury on the outside"
"Don't get fooled by the trench coat"
"Just one punch, that's all I like to push"
"Can't take you down with just my hat,
come at me now"
"Come at me now, come at me now"
"Mr. X gonna make a dent in the target"
"Daredevil, he take the spot and the mark"
"The ambulance passed,
ain't about the rust"
"To protect you, Mr. X coming for you,
this is all you get"
"This is, he is one the mission"
"This is, he's come for the revenge"
"This is... this is the one"
"This is, he is one the mission"
"This is, he's come for the revenge"
"This is... this is the one"
[radio jockey] 'Good morning, Chennai.
This is RJ Nelson!'
'Listen carefully
to what I'm about to say.'
'Don't make the mistake of going to
Mahabalipuram during the following week.'
'The security check will be high.'
'It's because the G20 Summit
is happening in Chennai.'
'You may ask, if it's a crucial matter?'
'Indeed!'
'In four days
representatives from 20 countries'
'will arrive in Mahabalipuram
for the G20 Summit.'
'This time, India will be assigned
the G20 Presidency.'
'This year, the summit led by India...'
'all the world leaders are coming together
to sign a treaty to share nuclear power.'
'This is something to be proud of.'
'So, out of habit, don't end up
in Mahabalipuram this weekend.'
'And enjoy the song
that I'm about to play.'
'Okay!'
"But he is alive"
'So, Gautham,
did you break the underwater record?'
Not yet, Madam.
But I will do it soon!
'I've sent a mission
brief to your phone.'
'It's a laundering mission.'
'Tonight at Sowcarpet,'
'laundering of 10 crore in $s
is about to go down.'
'This will be used for terror networks.'
'Sampath is the main organizer
of this laundering deal.'
'Find this network and stop them!'
'Gautham, this mission...'
'should be carried out covertly
without local police support.'
'Who do you have locally
to give you tactical support?'
'Ravindran:
He runs Dhanalakshmi Chit funds.'
'Senior Field Agent - 20 years in R&AW.'
- Where's your helmet?
- I was going nearby.
- I was wearing it earlier.
- Get off the bike!
- Pull over.
- Cut me some slack, Sir.
'Yogi:
Works in Dropido.'
'Senior Field Agent - 06 years in R&AW.'
- I'm advising for your good.
- I'm aware, Sir.
"Police are people's friends."
'Jasleen Kaur:
Weapons Expert.'
'Sheeba:
Team's Hacker.'
'There's nothing in the world
that she can't hack.'
'We'll get this done, Ma'am.'
'Okay, Gautham.
Keep me posted!'
'First, we need to find
the token he's holding.'
'It's a torn currency note.'
'Using it we can access the $s.'
'Sheeba, you monitor the CCTV
and keep guiding us.'
- I spotted Sampath.
- Okay. Watch him closely.
I'm coming your way.
34, Thulasingam Street.
'Check where is
34, Thulasingam Street.'
Yes, checking!
'Ravi and Jasleen.'
- I spotted him.
'- Check if their men are near the shop.'
Gautham, I spotted one man.
- Hey, this is the shop.
- Okay.
Hey, did a man come by
with a currency note?
Brother, here you go.
Just now, one guy went to
Thulasingam Street.
[in Hindi] Tell me.
A Police officer will arrive
with the 10 rupee currency.
Okay! I got it! I'll handle it!
Someone took away our money.
'Who took away our money?'
- Come to Thulasingam Street right away!
'- I'm coming!'
[in Hindi] Take it and escape!
Yogi!
Hey!
Hey! Run!
Pick up the bag and run!
Hey! Pass!
Hey, throw it to me!
Brother, hop on!
Ramesh, come on, hop on!
Sure! Sure!
Ramesh, he's getting in, beat him.
Hey, beat him!
Kill him!
Let it go!
Give it to me.
Hey, get up!
Hey, your arm is hurt.
Please wait, Sir.
The Doctor will attend to you shortly.
It's like a hotel room.
It's good enough to rent it out.
Eh?
"Hey, love"
How did it happen?
A cat scratched him.
- Cat?
- Hmm!
It doesn't look like it.
You need a tetanus shot.
Injection?
You're very beautiful.
"Hey, love"
What is your name, Doctor?
Sorry, I'm afraid of injections.
So, I'm making small talk.
I'm here for small talk, my friend.
Keerthana!
Keethana! Beautiful name!
Where are you from?
Remove your pants.
Remove my pants?
Hey, to give you the shot.
- Oh!
- What were you thinking?
Could you please wait outside?
I'm fine out here.
Get out, damn it!
Oh, the story is taking a different turn.
Happy Birthday!
"Hey, love"
Hey, I called you many times.
You never answered my calls.
I was sending a shipment to Dubai.
I missed your call
while I was at the container yard.
Sorry!
Hmm... You always get away
with your sweet talk.
Fine, how did you get hurt?
I fell off the bike.
Please be careful.
Gautham!
Shall we get married?
"Haiyodi,
My life is faltering"
"Your gaze is driving me crazy"
"Haiyodi,
Everything is going Topsy-Turvy"
"Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
Your smile is killing me"
"Oh, my sweetheart"
"Have I surrendered myself to you?"
"My heart dances wildly"
"My most cherished truth"
"My dear, don't hurt my heart"
"Are you the sky?
Or are you a mystery?"
"Don't turn me relentless"
"Dear, are you merciless?"
"Please don't make me plead
for my life"
"Even if time passes by..."
"one thing that wouldn't change"
"is my love for you"
"My dear, don't hurt my heart"
"Are you the sky?
Or are you a mystery?"
"Don't turn me relentless"
"Dear, are you merciless?"
"Please don't make me plead
for my life"
"Even if time passes by..."
"one thing that wouldn't change"
"is my love for you"
"Hey, love"
"Are you the heavens?
Here I am beneath you"
"Are you the moment?
I've been ensnared by the web"
"I am drawn to you completely"
"I announced me as you"
"There is an explosion
And lightning in the heart"
"When I pronounce your name"
"I seek you with my eyes
Searching everywhere for you"
"When you leave"
"I lose track of the world,
Hey my girl, I forget"
"When I stand with you"
"In love, we overlook
The season and the time"
"Oh, my sweetheart"
"Have I surrendered myself to you?"
"My heart dances wildly"
"My most cherished truth"
"My dear, don't hurt my heart"
"Are you the sky?
Or are you a mystery?"
"Don't turn me relentless"
"Dear, are you merciless?"
"Please don't make me plead
for my life"
"Even if time passes by..."
"one thing that wouldn't change"
"is my love for you"
"My dear, don't hurt my heart"
"Are you the sky?
Or are you a mystery?"
"Don't turn me relentless"
"Dear, are you merciless?"
"Please don't make me plead
for my life"
"Even if time passes by..."
"one thing that wouldn't change"
"is my love for you"
[in Hindi ]
Asif, our deal is completed here.
Transfer the balance payment
to my overseas account.
'Regal Theater Notice'
Shall I leave? Are we done?
Wait! The film isn't over yet.
Look, the Villain shoots the Hero now.
Poor Villain!
The Villain thought he had won.
But he died at the hands of the Hero.
Madam... Madam...
I don't know anything.
I am here to extract
information from them.
We've been tracking you for six months.
Twelve crores
in your offshore savings account.
Three unauthorized trips to Pakistan.
And Asif, who's lying dead out here...
We also know that you sold
the missile schematics to him.
No-- No, Madam!
Please, Madam, don't harm me.
They threatened me to do it.
I did not have another option.
Don't worry.
I won't threaten you.
Tell me.
What else do you know?
The location of
the lost nuclear device in Nanda Devi...
...is known to our enemies.
A Russian militant group
is going to excavate the device.
They've planned something massive.
What else do you know?
"Kamini will burn bright...
...wearing the hat."
They used this code while speaking.
Kamini?
Is that all?
That's it, Madam.
Saving the country is not a business.
It's a way of life.
- Prem!
- Ma'am?
Check in our database
to see if you can find information
on Kamini.
- She's a person of interest.
- Okay, Ma'am.
- It's extremely urgent.
- Sure!
Nirmala!
- I don't want to go to school.
- Chris, please don't cry.
[shushes] Hurry up!
We're running late.
Nimi, we're getting late!
Hurry up!
It's not the end of the world
if you're late one day.
Here you go!
What is so urgent at work?
- It's the end of the month.
- Don't cry.
- So?
- Nimi, you don't understand my plight.
Fine, chill!
- Bye!
- Don't forget to pick him up from school.
- Bye! Bye, okay.
- Give mum kisses.
Bye!
- I don't want to go to school.
- Bye!
- Don't cry, baby.
- Don't forget. Bye!
- Hello!
- Hey, Baby!
'Hmm, tell me!'
Hey, I called you many times.
Why didn't you answer?
Sorry, Sanjay! I was with Mom.
I miss you, Kamini.
I miss you too, Sanjay.
'As usual,
send your pictures and videos.'
I've sent them. Check it out.
Hey, Kamini.
- I want to--
'- Hold on! Mom is here.'
'- I have to go! Talk to you later.'
- Hey!
Sir!
- Ma'am is waiting.
- Yeah.
Ma'am!
How are you, Ponnusamy?
I'm good, Ma'am.
How is your wife?
Cancer 4th stage.
Chemotherapy is on.
Don't hesitate to ask for any help.
Sure, ma'am.
Ma'am, why did you summon me urgently?
'Many years ago...'
'the nuclear device
that was lost in Nanda Devi'
'was excavated yesterday
in the Ural mountains in Russia'
'by a militant group.'
'This job was carried out for Pakistan.'
'On learning this,'
'one of our operatives went to Russia
to secure the device.'
'Mr. Parameshwar Surya Pratap.'
'His code name:'
'Mr. X'
'In two days, they're going to
transfer him to Pakistan from Russia.'
'Ponnusamy, somehow, we have to
retrieve the nuclear device and him.'
How is it relevant to us when the Russians
are transferring the device to Pakistan?
It is relevant.
One of our R&AW operatives, Alexander,
gave us a decoded message.
"Kamini will burn bright wearing the hat."
We're yet to crack the significance
of Kamini in the message.
She may be a suicide bomber.
However, the "hat" mentioned is
the nuclear device we lost in Nanda Devi.
'An international Mercenary group...'
'has been trying to find this
nuclear device for years now.'
'Their leader is known as Rana.'
'Rana has many faces.'
'There are no official records
about his whereabouts.'
'Now, this group is planning
an attack in India using that device.'
If we don't secure this device...
...we can expect an attack
anywhere and anytime in India.
How can I help you, Ma'am?
In your network,
are there any local assets in Moscow?
Someone good and reliable.
I have one local asset in Moscow.
He's a bit eccentric but a great agent.
His name is Amaran.
Amaran Chakravarthy.
ID No - 1209
Code name: Lone Wolf.
'Your mission...'
'is to retrieve the device safely
held at a shipyard outside Moscow'
'and rescue Mr. X, who was safeguarding it,
and bring them to India.'
[in Hindi] You dog!
Your father is a freaking dog!
Boo!
"Witness the heist, it's crystal
clear of which way"
"Unstoppable mayhem
and the tactics are gray"
"Compose a mastermind
to have decisions made"
"You cannot hide in this match"
"You cannot win the game he plays"
"You cannot hide in any way"
"What I'm making is the masterpiece"
"What I'm attacking kind of body strapped"
"Games over when the sun sets"
"Soldier in the movies and
we're never still until it's done"
"You can never outrun the wolf's chase"
"You can never win the game he play"
"He will never stop
until the mission's raised"
"What I'm making is the masterpiece"
"What I'm attacking kind of body strapped"
"Games over when the sun sets"
"Soldier in the movies and
we're never still until it's done"
"You can never outrun the wolf's chase"
"You can never win the game he plays"
"He will never stop
until the mission's raised"
Let's go, Sir.
Who are you?
Don't worry, Sir.
I'm R&AW's local asset sent to retrieve
the device and rescue you safely.
Amaran! Amaran Chakravarthy!
You can trust me, Sir!
Until I hand over this device
to the Indian Government...
...I won't trust anyone.
I have heard a lot about you, Sir.
Legendary R&AW operative Mr. X.
Parameshwar Pratap! Right?
Why were you underground
for so many years?
And now you're back!
Why?
I've been running for twenty years.
It's enough!
I am done with all this.
I'm tired of running!
What is it, Sir? Retirement?
Any idea about your family?
Is your family still there?
Are they aware that you're still alive?
How long has it been
since you met your family?
The reunion will be freaking emotional!
I wish to witness it.
Oh, one minute.
Okay. I got the location to bring you in.
It's not far. Shall we go?
Who's on the phone, Amaran?
Sir, have you heard about Rana?
Traitor!
When I gave you the gun...
I kept a count
of how many bullets were in it.
Your services are not required anymore.
Enjoy your retirement!
That was a great movie.
Do you like movies of this genre?
James Bond, Jason Bourne, and Ethan Hunt.
Actor Vijaykanth portrayed
these characters many years ago.
The spies and agents are a hokum.
Do you really believe
that a spy lives among us?
Why not?
It's good for us!
A Hero who protects us in anonymity.
He cannot tell who
he is to his loved ones.
Moreover, he fights for the nation!
Wow! It's great!
What will you do if you encounter a spy?
You lie to the world for a living...
Is it really worth it?
I have an early morning shift.
I have to be at the hospital on time.
- Please, Sir. Don't do it.
- Hey, don't act pricey!
- Please let go of me.
- Listen to me!
- Adjust for a while.
- I'm not the girl you're looking for.
- Don't be afraid.
- Please return my bag.
We're just two guys.
No one else will join.
Please someone help!
Hey, listen to me.
Someone, please help.
Sir, please help me!
- Sir, please help me!
- Stop screaming!
- Brother!
- Who is he?
'- Brother...'
- Brother, please help me.
- Brother! Brother, please help me.
- I said quiet down!
Brother, please help me.
- Brother, please...
- I said come with me!
Brother, please help me!
Brother, please, brother!
- Stop right there.
- Please, let go of me.
Please, brother...
Brother, look at them.
Brother, please help me.
Hey, who are you?
Hey, buddy!
Go safe!
Let's go.
Goodnight!
You beat them up black and blue.
It did not feel like you were inspired
by the movie we just watched.
It felt like rage was stewing
inside you for a long time.
You're hiding something, Gautham.
Brother!
Nothing like that.
We've been in a relationship
for three years now.
You know everything about my life.
We shouldn't be having secrets, Gautham.
Are you lying to me?
Gautham, I don't care what you do.
But please don't lie to me.
Goodnight.
I'm going to quit the job.
When I got recruited in R&AW...
I thought I'd go to other countries
on missions to save the country.
But I'm running in circles in Chennai
nabbing launderers.
This job is not what
I thought it would be.
In my life, only Keerthana's relationship
feels real to me.
I don't wish to lie to her anymore.
I'm feeling guilty.
I'm planning to meet her tomorrow
and tell her the truth.
'This video was sent to us
by Pakistan Intelligence.'
'Take a look!'
My name is Parameshwar Pratap.
I work for the
Foreign Intelligence division of R&AW.
I've been arrested in Moscow
by Pakistan, ISI.
I'll be transferred to Islamabad
in the next few days.
I want our Government
to take necessary action.
Jai Hind!
Is he an Indian spy?
Was he an R&AW agent?
I cannot confirm or deny that
without the direct approval
of the Prime Minister.
Mr. Vamanamoorthy.
The G20 Summit is happening
in Chennai in a few days.
What happened is an intelligence failure.
Assassination attempt
on American President Donald Trump.
Chasing away Bangladesh's President
from the country.
These are examples
of intelligence failure across the world.
Similarly...
This will be
an international shit storm for us.
If he is transferred to Pakistan,
India will become a joke to the world.
And Indira has to take responsibility
for this mess.
Now, what is it that you're
not telling us, Indira?
This man is going to be taken
to Pakistan in the next 48 hours.
He needs to be stopped!
Can something be done?
Extraordinary Rendition Protocol.
If we can't rescue an operative alive...
we must kill them.
We kill our own man?
Once he arrives in Islamabad...
...he may expose the secrets
of the country.
So we will have to eliminate him.
As R&AW failed in this matter entirely...
I'm sending in my team
to complete this mission successfully.
Mr. Vamanamoorthy.
- Ma'am!
- You will oversee this operation.
This man should not reach Pakistan.
And this is a direct order
from the Prime Minister.
That's all for now!
What is Amaran's status?
The last update from him
was before he entered the shipyard.
As per protocol,
he should've reported it by now.
If he's silent...
...that means he's not alive.
Sorry, Madam.
I did not see this coming.
What's your next move, Madam?
I must go to Chennai.
Welcome back to India,
Mr. Ashok Kumar.
Please remove your glasses.
Please look at the camera.
How are you, Kamini?
I'm not Kamini but Nirmala.
Sorry!
Nirmala...
You asked me to honey-trap,
Captain Sanjay Mathew. And I did.
Now, he's ready to do anything I say.
All the photos and videos of him
are with me.
Let me know where to bring him
and I will bring him there.
After that,
please let me off the hook.
They're Chinese MSS agents.
They're important to me.
They wish to enter
India illegally via sea.
I need your help with it.
Arrange for a passport,
Aadhar, and identity,
posing them as spa therapists
from Manipur.
You're an expert in changing identities.
No, Amaran! I can't do it.
This I won't do it. No more!
Can you tell Rana the same in person?
You were going to die
in a prison in Pakistan.
But you were bestowed with a family life.
Learn how to protect that family...
...Nirmala!
The next three days
follow our orders diligently...
pay off your debt,
and live happily as Nirmala, Kamini.
Shall we get married?
Huh? How come suddenly
you want to get married?
What changed?
We've been in a relationship
for three years...
I'm thinking of changing the three years
into thirty years of love.
You're proposing to me at a temple
with God as a witness.
Your timing is impeccable!
Indeed, impeccable timing!
Sorry, did I interrupt?
- Erm...
- Hmm...
- Hi, Keerthana!
- Hi!
- You...
- Gautham, won't you introduce us?
She is... You know...
I'm Indira! Gautham's elder sister.
Elder sister?
I reckon he did not mention about me.
Of course, he wouldn't have.
He's a fraud!
But he told me everything about you.
- You're a doctor, right?
- Yes.
You practice at SM Hospital.
And you stay in Kilpauk.
Am I right?
Isn't your shift starting at 10:00 a.m.?
Okay, Keerthana, we'll meet later.
- Okay, I'm leaving.
- Sure!
Call me in the evening, Gautham.
Yeah, he will.
She listens to what you say.
Good girl.
Good choice, Gautham.
Watch, he'll follow me.
Ma'am! Ma'am! Sorry, Ma'am.
- I should've mentioned about Keerthana--
- Don't forget that I'm your Boss.
It's my job to know.
I had sent in my resignation.
So, you're going to resign...
get married to Keerthana
and live happily ever after.
Ma'am, I don't like to work
without a purpose.
That's why I decided to quit the job.
Here is the work you're looking for.
Read it well.
You'll understand your purpose.
'Ma'am, I lied a lot to Keerthana.'
When I'm at a point where I want to quit
this profession and start a family...
Why would you hand me this mission?
I want to start a new life
and have a family with Keerthana.
- I'm content with it--
- This is about your family.
Your father!
The mission is to save your father.
Do you know who is my father?
Do you know him?
Where was he all these years?
What else do you know about my family?
Tell me, Madam.
Do this mission.
And you'll have the answers
about your family.
Are you cornering me?
I don't care if he's alive or dead.
Let him die. I really hate him!
If he appears in front of me,
I'll kill him myself.
I'm running out of time.
Beyond saving your father...
I urge you to take on this mission
to prevent a nuclear weapon
from falling into the wrong hands
and potentially destroying our country.
I'm not here to beg or plead to you.
If you don't understand
the importance of this mission,
you're not fit to be a R&AW agent.
You might as well stay resigned!
What's it, Gautham?
All okay?
'Sir, where are you?'
I'm 10 kilometers away from the border.
Keep the boat ready.
I'll arrive shortly.
'Sir, be careful.
This area is populated with Naxals.'
Okay, noted!
We're almost there.
- We'll be there in no time.
- Okay, Dad.
- Hey!
- Dad!
Dad, what happened?
'Oh no! He killed my child'
[in Hindi] He killed my son.
He killed the kid.
Catch him!
Stay inside the car.
Dad...
Stay inside.
[in Hindi] Forgive me! Please stop!
- Let go of my Dad.
- Please forgive me.
- Forgive me!
- Dad!
- It was unintentional.
- Dad, let's go!
- Let go of my Dad.
- I did not see him coming.
Let go of my Dad.
Chief, do something.
They killed your son.
My son...
Please someone help.
Please save my child.
'My dear child.'
Dad, get inside the car.
- Dad... Dad...
- Hear me out. Spare my children.
- Step aside!
- Please hear me out.
Hear me out. Spare my children.
Please hear me out!
- Spare them! Spare them!
- Dad!
Please spare us!
Let go of me.
- Hey, please spare the kids.
- Dad!
- Let go of me.
- Let go!
Dad, please save us!
- Brother!
- Dad!
Let go of me!
[in Hindi] I made a mistake.
Please spare them.
Now, your son is my son.
You better leave.
If not, I'll kill them both.
I'm sorry, Gautham.
Dad!
Dad, please don't leave us.
Dad, please come back.
Please, Dad. Dad!
Dad, please don't leave us.
Dad!
Hey, let go of me!
- Aditi!
- Brother!
Brother, I'm hungry.
You sit over there.
Aditi, stay put until I return.
- Okay.
- Don't go anywhere.
- [in Tamil] Uncle, I'm hungry.
- [in Hindi] What do you want?
- I want an apple.
- Get lost! Scram!
Hey, take your hands off!
Uncle, my sister is hungry.
Please spare me one apple.
Do you have money?
No, right? Scram!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
He stole from me. Catch him.
Brother!
- Bloody thief!
- Brother!
- Hey, catch him!
- Hey!
Brother!
Aditi!
Hey!
- How dare you steal from me?
- Beat him up!
- Beat him!
- Aditi!
'Tell me.'
Gautham, this is a silent mission.
'Until we return to India
after completing the mission...'
'even Indira madam can't contact us.'
'I will run point.'
I will get you the necessary weapons
and make arrangements.
However, my job is off-field.
'I understand that you accepted this
mission without any personal interest.'
'But Indira Madam has faith in you.'
In 5 hours, a private jet will
be waiting to take us to Russia.
'Come to the airport
along with your team.'
The man we're about to meet is Raghu.
He arrived in Russia as a student.
His actual business is
to gather intel for R&AW.
He's well-connected.
What's up, yo?
How's it hanging, Ponnu?
Hey, sit down.
Chief, I asked how are you?
You could've asked it decently.
Instead, you're asking,
"How's it hanging?"
Get to the point!
As per Rendition Protocols...
a team from India is already here
to eliminate Mr. X.
My friend Rocky is helping them.
They're at the President Hotel.
Room - 115.
Listen, get them clean, man!
Nothing should come back to me.
Hmm... Yeah!
'Three kilometers from here, you'll find
a budget hotel named President Hotel.'
Room no - 115
The only thing they ask for...
...is Indian food.
We're going to use that to trap them.
A heavy dose of sedative.
A pinch of it will knock out a person
in 30 seconds.
'And they can't recover for 12 hours
even if electrocuted.'
[in Russian] Your order, Indian food.
Have a good meal.
Let's get to the main matter.
Where are they holding Mr. X?
They're holding him and the device
outside Moscow at an abandoned shipyard.
'But Gautham,
at least 40 men are standing guard.'
'No!'
'We won't even survive two minutes
inside the shipyard.'
If I'm not wrong, he's being
transferred to Pakistan in the morning.
Yeah!
So they will bring him
out of the shipyard.
Our only chance is
when they least expect us.
On the way to the airport.
Also, there will be fewer guards on board.
'Sheeba hack the CCTVs and monitor
if they're sending Police backup.'
Give me the list of weapons you need,
and I'll make the arrangements.
'Using Indian diplomatic pouch,'
'I'll arrange
for Mr. X and the nuclear device'
'to board the plane
without any security clearance.'
The local contacts will help us.
It's enough if you accomplish the mission
and get to the airport.
Okay.
One more thing...
The person we're going to
rescue tomorrow is my father.
Mr. Parameshwar Pratap.
I was going to kill him myself
if he appeared in front of me.
I hate that man!
Guys, I have access to visuals now.
We are following them.
'Gautham, they're about to arrive.'
It's time for some action!
"You better know who's in charge"
"And we here ready to forge"
"And those who can't hide"
"You better run, become stars"
"Adrenaline's high, every code in eye"
"Watch me install it"
"Smashing tracks on them
faces like they all-it"
"Adrenaline is the motto"
"Management that you won't see tomorrow"
"See tomorrow"
"Feed the game, feed the game"
"Feed the game"
"You won't see tomorrow"
Your private jet is ready to depart.
You have 30 minutes.
Okay.
"He'll destroy everything"
Gautham, they've called for backup.
"Don't trouble him"
"Here is the man goes to boom"
We don't have a lot of time.
The cops are nearing.
Check if the device is here.
Raghu! Raghu!
Gautham, the Police are very near.
'We don't have time left.'
- Raghu! Raghu!
- 'Gautham, can you hear me?'
'Get out of there!'
Raghu! Hey, Raghu, Raghu!
I'm sorry, Gautham.
Please don't leave us, Dad.
Dad!
Hey, who are you?
Hey, who is she?
Hey, get down!
Get inside.
Gautham, who's this girl?
Let's go! Let's go!
Start the car.
- Sir, which way?
- Gate No.2
Gautham, who is this girl?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
Instead of Parameshwar Pratap,
this girl was in the car.
We couldn't leave her behind.
So I rescued her.
You're not a cinema hero
to rescue women in distress.
We can't break the mission protocols.
Moreover, we'll be in trouble if we
bring an unidentified girl back to India.
I can't allow it.
I'll speak to Indira, madam.
We cannot leave that girl behind.
Let's go.
Kamini!
Amaran, they're here.
'There's a boat coming toward you.'
Yeah!
- Get on that.
- Okay.
Hey, hey, hey, Jackson!
Hi, Amaran!
- How are you?
- How are you, my friend?
Welcome to India!
If anyone asks,
you're a spa therapist from Manipur.
Who are you?
Are you an Indian?
Pakistani?
We can converse in Tamil.
Great, you're Tamilian.
Look, she's our girl.
As if she's his daughter.
You broke the protocols
and brought a stranger.
Expressing emotions, it seems.
How did you get caught by the Russians?
I don't know.
In the dead of night,
they kidnapped me in London.
When I woke up, I was in Moscow.
Don't worry!
Once we arrive in India,
I'll speak to my boss, Indira.
You'll be back in London soon.
Thank you!
Any idea why they kidnapped you?
My father is a R&AW agent.
R&AW agent...
Name?
Mr. Parameshwar Pratap.
Paramesh...
You?
Aditi!
Aditi Surya Pratap.
I am Gautham.
Gautham Surya Pratap.
Brother...
[news] 'Many world leaders and officials
have arrived in Chennai for G20 Summit.'
'Per this,'
'there are heavy security details
around OMR and ECR in Chennai.'
'At this Summit...'
'the world leaders will jointly sign
a treaty to share nuclear power.'
'To host and to kick start the summit...'
'the Indian Prime Minister
is about to arrive in Mahabalipuram.'
Sir, they drugged my team,
approved by you, and knocked them out.
And she executed an unauthorized mission.
She's the reason
why our Russian mission was a failure.
Yes, Sir.
I did execute an unauthorized mission.
But, respectfully...
I was not on board with the decision
to eliminate Mr. X.
Sir, I disobeyed your orders
to save the life of a good agent.
Mr. X is one of our best agents.
It's very easy to eliminate him.
But if we do,
then we can't retrieve the nuclear device.
Nuclear weapon?
It's not a weapon, Sir.
For now, it's a device
that contains 7 plutonium capsules.
But if our enemies
get their hands on these capsules...
They can turn it into a nuclear weapon
that will destroy our country.
Okay... Where's your team?
Is your mission successful?
Yes, Sir.
They're returning from Russia
as we speak.
In a short while, they'll land in Hosur.
Mr. X is with them.
Once they are here...
I can prove that I'm telling the truth.
No, Sir!
She's lying!
They recovered Mr. X's body
from a mine site in Russia.
- Ashok!
- Sir!
We have made arrangements
to bring back his body to India.
Sir, it's her team
that operated as rogue agents...
and bringing a nuclear device
into the country.
They're precisely bringing it to Tamil Nadu
during the G20 Summit.
There are chances of an attack.
I need your permission to investigate her.
Well, Indira, you'll have to step down.
I'm placing you under investigation.
- Mr. Moorthy!
- Sir!
Arrest her team
as soon as they land in Hosur.
And make sure
the nuclear device is secured.
Okay, Sir!
Nobody should know about this
until the G20 Summit is over.
Sure, Sir!
You may go now!
They're Indira madam's men.
I'll speak to them.
Hello, Sir. I'm Ponnusamy,
R&AW operative.
ID No - 2105, Chennai Division.
Sir, they've arrived.
Arrest them and get the device to safety.
Okay, Sir.
You're all under arrest!
Hey!
Hey, what are you--
Sir, what's wrong with you?
Please check the ID.
Sir, what's happening?
Hey, Gautham.
No weapons!
I'll speak to him.
Sir, please check my ID.
Sir, there's some misunderstanding.
Yes!
- Hey, stay down!
- Get down! Get down!
Stay low! Stay low!
Gautham, careful!
- Gautham!
- Hey, guys, stick together.
Stick together!
Aditi! No, Aditi!
Sir, Sir, we're all under attack.
What?
'Sir, Indira has sent force.'
'They're firing at us!'
What the heck are you doing, Indira?
Stop the car!
"Hello, Sir!"
Out!
Don't play games with me.
Shut down the airstrip!
They're armed and dangerous.
Call for backup.
Send the freaking army.
I don't care!
How is everyone doing?
I hope no one's hurt.
I informed them not to harm you people.
I reckon the brother and sister reunion
must've been very sentimental.
Who are you?
Oh!
My name is Amaran.
You're Gautham, right?
Indira sent me first
to rescue your father in Moscow.
As I had other plans in place...
I had to cut loose your father...
and steal the device instead.
But it's not an easy task
to bring a nuclear device into India.
So, through diplomatic channels,
I used you to bring in the device.
Please leave the device.
And you all are free to go.
Please hear me out.
Let her go!
I planned meticulously...
and used you to bring her to India.
Do you think
I did it without any reason?
Brother...
Do you know something, Gautham?
The incidents that'll follow after...
You'll be the villain in it.
Your game is over!
You're finished!
You, bloody-!
Moorthy, you're blabbing,
unaware of what's happening.
Hey! Careful, damn it!
Jasleen!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I want them alive!
You only need the nuclear device.
Why do you want her?
For now, you can take the device.
Hey! Stay right there!
Brother, what are you doing?
If you think
I'll consider family sentiments...
I dare you to step forward.
Brother, please, don't!
Don't do it.
What are you doing?
Please don't do it.
You're such an emotional fool.
Hey! Hey!
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
Why did you shoot her?
Amaran, let's go!
Amaran, backup is arriving.
We have the device.
Please hear me out! Let's go!
Let's go!
Madam, please put your gun down.
"I'll block the play"
I am coming for you.
Bring it on!
BAN!
BAN NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
Please calm down.
Everyone stop!
We can't shut down a nuclear plant
immediately, as you're asking.
This plant will help
increase electricity production...
not only in Tamil Nadu
but also in other states.
There will be more
employment opportunities.
There will be no power cuts.
Pollution will decrease.
Why would anyone hinder
a country's development?
Sir, this is India's largest
nuclear power plant.
In a few days,
this plant will be functional.
The past 2 years of trial runs
have caused so much damage.
I get your point.
I will ensure that your demands are
brought to the attention of my superiors.
I will give them my feedback, too.
I will do my best.
But for God's sake,
don't continue the protest.
Many officials have made
promises before.
But nothing changed.
The public is getting fooled all the time.
Until you shut down the power plant...
we will protest right here!
BAN!
BAN NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
- BAN!
- We'll handle the protest.
You please go back inside.
BAN!
BAN NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
CHARGE!
Amara!
Mother!
Amaran!
Kamini...
Go and meet Captain Sanjay Mathew,
who's in Chennai, at your request.
Before that...
I must surprise an old friend of mine.
It's time to meet them both.
Gautham, the bullet went
through and through.
The shooter knew well
not to damage the organs.
Thank you, Doctor.
I didn't know who else
to go for help at this hour.
Make sure to take her to the hospital
for treatment when you get to Chennai.
Okay, Doctor.
Is it out in the news?
As the G20 Summit is ongoing...
World leaders have arrived in Chennai.
So, for the next 48 hours, any news
that'll stir a panic won't be released.
But they will be on high alert!
Gautham, I spoke to my Chennai contacts.
They've issued an order to hold
Indira Madam is under diplomatic custody.
We all have been...
charged under the Official Secret Act.
Treason!
Are they kidding?
We did not do anything wrong.
Why should we run and hide?
It's not safe for us here.
This is Ramesh - Rural SP.
My old batch mate.
I called him to help us.
He made all the arrangements
for us to go to Chennai.
'For the G20 Summit, security...
'Karnataka Reserve Police force
is heading to Chennai.'
'We will travel along with them.
'As it's a Police convoy,
we won't face issues at the check-post.'
'Let's be careful until we enter Chennai.
Auntie! How are you?
- Who are you?
- Is Somu uncle home?
- May I come in?
- Somu!
- Who are you?
- Who are you, people?
- Don't you hear me?
- Somasundaram!
- What are you, people?
- What is happ--
Listen, who are these people?
They're barging in-
Who are you?
- Lakshmi, call the guards!
- Guards!
The guards are long dead, my dear.
Somasundaram.
Wow!
It's been ages.
I reckon it's been 15 years!
I've never met you before.
Who are you?
I want you to do me a favor.
Hey, who the hell are you?
Do you know who I am?
I know, Somu.
I'm here because I know about you.
Kamini.
Please show it to him.
'Dad, we're very scared!'
'Who are these people?'
'Please come save us, Dad.'
Please don't harm my children.
Please tell me what you want me to do.
[announcer on PA]
Change the IV for this patient.
Gautham!
It's a bullet injury, Gautham.
What do you want me to do?
Don't ask me anything now.
I will confess everything to you.
I need you to trust me.
Please give her the treatment.
Hi, Sanjay!
Shall we live together?
It's been six months since we met,
and you want to live in.
What do you know about me, Sanjay?
So what?
I can protect you forever.
Tell me, will you move in with me?
The long-range missile
you're working on right now...
Is that going to protect me, Sanjay?
The Defence Planning Committee signed on
a nuclear capability long-range missile...
Isn't it placed in your facility?
What? How do you know about it?
Come, let's talk!
Who are you?
It's not important who I am.
Intimate snapshots of us,
WhatsApp messages and video calls.
The confidential military documents
I took from you.
The Indian military authorities will want
to know how I gained access to them.
What do you say?
Shall I tell them?
What do you want?
Please...
Good
We're meeting a person now.
Until then...
...your phone will be with me.
I'll wait in the lobby.
Come soon.
Keerthana, Amaran was aware of our plans.
So, you're not able to trust anyone.
'Amaran knows everything since we
went to Russia and returned to Hosur.'
'That means there's a leak in our team.'
'I want to find the mole.'
'Until I find out, I can't trust anyone.'
Okay! What about Amaran?
Do you know what his next move will be?
He risked a lot to steal a nuclear device.
It must be for a massive attack.
There's nothing bigger than the G20 Summit.
The Presidents and Prime Ministers
of 20 countries gathered in one place...
at Mahabalipuram.
If they create an explosion
using nuclear energy...
There's no coming back for any of us.
Okay, I'll help you.
Let your sister be with me.
I'm sorry, Keerthana.
But don't worry.
My teammate Karna will be with you.
Once you arrive at your home,
he and his team will protect you.
You're asking me to trust them
when you don't.
I have sedated her.
Let her sleep for a while.
[TV] 'As the President of G20...
'Bharat extends a warm welcome to you all.
One earth!
One family!
And one future!
With this thought
let us begin the G20 Summit.
Captain Sanjay Mathews!
I'll get straight to the point.
I want the launch codes for the missile
that only you know.
Missile launch codes?
Who are you?
If I call the defence police
will be here in 10 minutes.
- Want to see?
- Oooh!
Defence Police!
Fine, go ahead!
I will tell them what you've been up to.
Dear, you may be a big shot
in the military.
But here you are, a womanizer who
can't move without my permission.
I'm a womanizer!
But I'm not a traitor to give up
the missile launch codes.
I'm a soldier!
God help me!
I ought to-
Are you going to give it up?
If you don't,
another bullet will make a hole.
I'll give it up.
I will give up the launch codes.
Now you're talking like a man, partner!
Yes, Rana!
Don't worry.
Kamini will burn bright.
'There's a Government guest house
at the end of the street.'
'They're holding Indira madam out there.'
'I'm going to break her out.'
The guards stationed are doing their duty.
So, we are not going to shoot them.
Thus, the tranquilizers and Taser guns.
This will knock them out for 30 minutes.
You guys are impossible.
They're equipped with MP5s and AK47s.
And you're going in with tranquilizers.
Do as you wish.
I can't watch you all die.
Hello!
Ah, I arrived in Chennai, Sir.
Take the ground floor.
Gautham, there are 6 men on the terrace.
And 4 on the ground floor.
'And 5 on the first floor.'
"Make it colorful"
Please start the vehicle.
"Across all worlds, his power devours"
"Across all worlds, his power controls all"
Gautham, I arranged a vehicle for you.
But all our safe houses are
being watched by the authorities.
We can't go to any safe house.
I know a safe place.
A place that no one will suspect.
You can be rest assured.
Karna, you take a team
and head to Keerthana's house.
I'll share her address with you.
- Be careful!
- Okay. I'll take care of it.
- Ashok!
- 'Sir!'
- I'm following them.
- 'Okay, Sir.'
You please wait.
- Let's give them some leeway.
- 'Sure, Sir.'
I need to find out where they're heading.
Hello, Prem!
Ma'am, we got a match for
Kamini's facial recognition.
I retrieved it from our old database.
A housewife in Chennai named Nirmala.
But until it's confirmed that she's
the Kamini we're looking for...
I've just put her on surveillance.
- Okay, keep tracking and bring her to me.
- 'Okay, ma'am.'
Ma'am, I have some questions.
Who is Amaran?
Are you playing a double game
with me and Amaran?
If I accuse you of one of the reasons
for the current happenings...
Would it be wrong?
You said I'll get my answers
once I complete the Russian mission.
It's time for some answers now.
Amaran did work for me.
But not anymore.
I know who he is working for
and what he will do.
Your father is
one of the reasons behind it.
How do you know my father?
Where is he right now?
How is he connected to all of it?
You're hiding too much from me.
Tell me where he is.
I'll meet and speak to him.
He's not alive anymore.
They killed him!
All these years,
he was protecting a nuclear device.
They killed him for the same device.
I'm sorry, Gautham!
They recovered his body in Russia.
The formalities to bring his remains
back to India is happening as we speak.
Coward! Let him die.
To you, he's a coward
who abandoned his children.
But there is another side of him
that you are not aware of.
'According to the world,'
'Parameshwar Pratap is an ordinary father
who lived for his children.'
'He recruited me in R&AW
and trained me.'
'The device that was sought after
by many countries...'
'Parmeshawar Pratap found it
and handed it to the Indian authorities.'
'To find and sell the lost nuclear device'
'the authorities did not
inform the Indian Government.'
'They tried to crack a deal
with the foreign agencies.'
'After learning this Parameshwar, sir,
'with a lot of struggle
brought the device back to safety.'
'Then, an international mercenary,
Rana, and his men'
'came looking for the device
your father brought to safety.'
'Your father realized he could trust no one,
as many officials were Rana's stooges.'
'He took the device away
and started living in shadows.'
'He moved between towns,
using different disguises.'
- Your name?
- Suriyan!
'Soon, he realized that Rana's men
were closing in on his children.'
'He decided to take the device
and you both out of the country.'
'While he was racing with the time,
an unexpected accident occurred.'
'What you witnessed that day was a father
abandoning his children to the Naxals.'
'But your father realized
that the Naxalites'
'might take the device away from him.'
- I'm sorry, Gautham.
- 'He was left with no option.'
Dad, please don't leave us.
Dad!
'A situation no father should endure.
He left you guys behind with no option
and asked me to rescue you.
Indira...
Listen carefully. My children-
We're the ones who forced the Naxal leader
to release you both.
'But before we got to the market...
'...you both were separated.'
Aditi!
'With a lot of struggle,
he took the device to Russia and hid it.'
'For years, it remained safe out there.
'Until a few days back.'
'He was away from you both
to safeguard the nuclear device.'
'And that device took his life.'
Today, you're an R&AW agent
under oath to save the country.
What would've you done differently?
Family or nation?
What would you have sacrificed?
Make up your mind and answer me.
Is he a coward or a hero?
Madam, I have saved my number
on your phone.
In an emergency, dial "1,"
and we'll be there.
- Okay.
- Please go inside.
Come.
Aditi, please wear this.
It's a new dress.
It's not my size, so I never wear it.
Thank you!
You've been following us for a while.
Have you lost your way, Sir?
Easy...
Don't worry, Indira.
If I really wanted to arrest you all...
I wouldn't have come alone over here.
I knew your team members
would come looking for you.
They did as expected!
However,
I expected you to take me to the device
once you escaped.
But none of your team members
know its whereabouts.
Right?
Amaran! It's with him.
Give me some time.
I'll find him.
Indira, I checked out
everything you mentioned.
It's all true!
I'm not here to shake hands
and make friends.
What's important now is to
find the device and stop Amaran.
Amaran knows everything beforehand.
That means one of us is working for him.
Like in the movies...
...in the end, a friend would've
backstabbed for money.
What do you say, Yogi?
My friend, money speaks everywhere.
Gautham!
Don't run your mouth
without knowing the truth.
No savings or insurance.
Neither is department allowance.
An ordinary officer
with a monthly salary of 45,000...
for his wife's cancer treatment,
How did he manage to make
a single payment of 25 lakhs?
Sheeba!
I will leave.
Let me go!
Sir, you immediately drew your gun.
When I can dig out
your illegal activities...
it's easy for me to find out
where your wife is admitted.
20 kilometers from Coorg.
Am I right?
Don't come near me.
Madam!
Please forgive me, Madam.
I had no other option.
When I was struggling to arrange money
for my wife's treatment...
they came forward and helped me.
First, they enquired
about the Russian mission.
Then, they asked about
the Hosur landing coordinates.
I did not have any other option left
to save my wife.
I became weak
and succumbed to the situation.
Please forgive me, Madam.
What else did you tell them?
They asked me for one last help.
They asked for your sister's location.
Please forgive me, Gautham.
Gautham... Aditi?
Tell me where's she?
I'll send the force.
Arrest him!
- Popcorn?
- No, thanks.
Hi beautiful. I'm Amaran.
May I?
You have a lovely garden.
A beautiful rose for you.
You don't want it?
Okay!
Your loss!
Hey! Madam is calling.
Go! Go! Go!
Did you pick up your phone?
Press "1" for help!
You must've called already.
Let them come.
Don't come near me.
I'll shoot!
Do you want to shoot me?
- Shoot!
- Please don't come near me.
Your hands save lives, darling.
You can't kill!
It's best you throw it away.
Please listen to me.
You can't even hold it right.
Don't come near me.
Don't you know how to shoot?
Keerthana...
Don't be afraid.
Keep your elbows straight.
Hold the grip straight.
Like this.
Now, relax your shoulders
and focus on the target.
Don't be afraid.
Yeah... Just relax!
Relax!
Trust me, okay.
On the count of 3...
One
Two
Three!
Oh, no!
You shot him, my dear.
You're a Doctor.
How could you kill someone?
Welcome to my club, darling!
Keerthana!
It's okay.
It's me. It's okay.
She's not my sister, Aditi.
What?
'It was too much of a coincidence for her
to be in the same vehicle as the device.'
'It seemed like
someone planted her there on purpose.'
'So, I shot her to know the truth.'
'But Amaran needs her for some reason.'
'At the moment, I can't determine
if she's a good or a bad person.'
Sheeba, I need all the details about her.
Her full history.
Do it quick!
Amaran will come looking for her.
I know it for sure.
So, I must track here.
There's a microdot inside it.
'Once you get home,
give her a dress to change into.'
'And stick the microdot on this dress.
'Please wear this.
'It's new.
'It's not my size,
so I never wear it.'
That was fun!
I don't know
why you spared her life, Amaran.
You have a soft corner for girls.
Don't be jealous, baby.
It does not matter.
In a few hours, no one will be alive.
Fine, do you have the materials you need?
So, who is this girl?
Her name is Vedha.
Vedha Narayanan.
A nuclear scientist.
'We have constantly tried to
find her details since we met her.'
'But someone shrewdly
erased all her digital records.'
'And we found that she's blacklisted
in 10 countries.'
'This nuclear generator she designed
fetched her a name in the world.'
'It's a machine that can create
a nuclear disaster.'
'It's illegal in most countries.'
How is it relevant to the device
we retrieved from Russia?
It is relevant, Sir.
It's not an easy task
to create this device.
They need two radioactive plutonium
capsules to create this device.
The device we brought from Russia
contains 7 capsules.
Using them, they can create
a nuclear disaster in our country.
How long do you need
to create the Nuclear Generator?
I need two hours!
But Amar...
...every nuclear device
consists of a heat signature.
They can use it to track us down.
If you distract them for 2 hours,
I can finish my work.
I'm speaking to you.
Not just two hours...
Shall we make them run all night
without getting anywhere near us?
- Give me the launch codes.
- I'll give it up.
AG-151-92
Jackson!
It's showtime!
'Let's do it!'
Enter the launch code.
Everyone, hack their system!
Wait and watch!
What's going on?
Sir, someone hacked our system.
"The inner-self
Ascending without descending"'
Sir, they have activated the missile.
"The universe"
Abdul, inform the Ministry.
Sir!
Sir, it's AGNI- 5.
"After burning It will subside"
Send the visuals to all the agencies.
Ma'am, a missile has been
launched from Haryana.
Take a look!
"Once the Jackal race is extinct"
Sheeba, what is AGNI-5's range?
8,000 kilometers.
It will reach Chennai in no time.
"Once life.."
G20!
"...is sacrificed"
"A new universe will be born"
"The state of the universe
Death is the answer"'
"Come to celebrate
The darkness"'
Sir, the missile is changing its direction.
"Filled with blood"
"Come to celebrate
The darkness"
It's good!
The missile changed its course
and headed to the Arabian Sea.
We are out of danger, right?
"War of the worlds"
Oh, my God!
The missile is near the Pakistan border.
We just started a war with Pakistan.
"Let the sound of blood dropping"
"Be heard
As a result of the war"'
"Let the sound of blood dropping"
"Be heard
As a result of the war"'
Ask Sheeba to track the microdot.
If Amaran is with him...
Let's go and get them.
Amaran...
I want to see my son.
Please do this as a last favor.
I'm asking this as a mother.
Oh, mother sentiment.
Reunite her with her son.
"Break them"
Good job, Amaran!
They're distracted now.
They're unaware of what Kamini is.
By the time they crack it,
you will have your revenge, Amaran.
Let's do this!
Inteqab, we're not responsible
for this attack.
Huh... really?
[in Urdu] How do I explain it to my people?
'A war is a realistic possibility.'
I'm sorry!
Sir, we have to retaliate immediately.
Rakesh, call the Chief of Defence.
We have to prepare for a war.
"My inner self burns endlessly within"
"Every world feels like a prison."
"The world will fall"
"Eliminate the anger"
"What is killing?"
"What is pain?"
"Once killed what is pain?"
The machine is ready.
We will have to calibrate it on-site.
Once it's activated...
in 20 minutes, Kamini will burn bright.
Suppose your device failed to work.
That's when we'll use this bomb.
This is a C4 explosive.
You will have to carry it inside.
That's our Plan B.
It's a suicide mission, right?
Time to play the game!
"The sound of the music"
"Is the sound of war"
"Should I generate
The darkness?"'
"I'll see you later in fury"
"And now you all will know it"
"And not a hero of today"
"I'll be your judge and jury"
What's the location on the microdot?
The microdot is still in ECR.
"Be heard
As a result of the war"'
"Let the sound of blood dropping"
"Be heard
As a result of the war"'
'Gautham, they're inside an ambulance.'
Where is the ambulance?
Erm... They're in the city
on Old Mahabalipuram road.
Okay, keep tracking them.
Don't lose it!
Oh, my God, Gautham!
The signal ping is coming
from 7 different locations.
What?
The microdot signal split into 7.
And it's moving in 7 different directions.
Look!
He found out!
He's playing us!
Sir!
As the signal is coming from 7 different
locations, it could be 7 explosives, too.
They have 7 nuclear capsules.
So, we have to assume the worst.
But why?
If there's a nuclear attack
during the G20 Summit
not just India,
but it'll be an attack on the world.
India made an unprovoked
missile attack on Pakistan.
Pakistan's reply to it
is a nuclear disaster.
The attack killed 20 world leaders.
The result will be a World War.
We are about to start a World War, Sir.
Ma'am, may I?
One of the 7 locations is already
under our surveillance, ma'am.
- What?
- Yes, Ma'am!
It's Kamini's apartment on OMR.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- 'Gautham, where are you?'
Ma'am, this is a trap!
He wants us to think
he has placed bombs in 7 locations.
'He's leading us into a goose chase
to execute his original plan.'
Also, he knows we'll eliminate
anyone who stops us.
Exactly!
Gautham, listen.
The ambulance is parked at
the ex-R&AW agent Kamini's apartment,
which is under our surveillance.
But be careful!
If Kamini is working for Amaran,
she might not cooperate.
- You have permission to engage.
- 'No, Ma'am!'
He knows what exactly we will do.
'There may be valuable intel available
inside that van.'
'Until we find out what it is...'
Please, Ma'am,
ask the commandos to stop.
I'll be there in five minutes.
Commandos will arrive in a minute, Gautham.
They have orders to shoot.
They won't wait.
Amar, I'm in position.
Gopi, you know what to do.
'Once the commandos
open the ambulance door...'
'...shoot them!'
'In a panic,
they'll fire at the people inside.'
Commander, this is a trap.
Hold on for a minute.
Commandos! Brace!
Sir, please step back!
Sir, step back!
One question: Where's Amaran?
Are you Kamini? His endgame?
I'm not. No, I'm not.
It's not me.
It's the Kalpakkam mini reactor, Kamini.
- Gautham?
- 'Ma'am!'
The code Kamini is not the girl.
It's the Kalpakkam mini reactor, Kamini.
'He's headed over there.'
'That's Amaran's endgame!'
My God, this is bigger than we thought.
I'm heading over there, Ma'am.
Gautham, this is a digital virus.
Inside the power plant
behind the server room,
there's a backup computer.
You have to connect this to it.
- Don't forget!
- Okay.
[in Hindi] Sir, how come you're
here so early in the morning?
Why this early?
You never mentioned anything.
Who are these people?
You see...
It's the new maintenance contract
for the Kamini reactor.
Technicians from Japan have arrived.
Erm, open the gate.
Sir, do they have a permit
to visit the site?
We did not receive
any official information.
[in English] I'm the Director
of this Power Plant.
And this is an undisclosed visit.
Understand?
My PA must've sent you an email.
To you... You first open the gate.
[in Hindi] Hey, open the gate!
[in English] Inform the Chief.
Mr. Somasundaram's phone is inaccessible.
And his wife was found dead.
If he's with Amaran...
then it's easy for them
to get inside the power plant.
And today is Kamini reactor's
regular maintenance day.
There will be no workers present
at the site.
'Only safety engineers
and security personnel.'
'He was aware and have planned it.'
This is utter madness!
You're playing with a nuclear power plant.
It'll cost the lives of thousands.
Sir, you're thinking small.
Thousands are merely nothing.
Now, let's say 5 million people.
No! How about 10 million people?
All die at once!
The world will talk about
the destruction by nuclear power.
It'll turn heads, Sir.
- Hey... You
- Yeah!
You're a bloody lunatic!
It's nuclear energy.
You can't control it.
It'll destroy the country with no scope
for survival or development.
Please don't do it!
Yes! You're on point, Sir.
Years ago, we said the same.
Back then,
you did tell us that nuclear energy is
good for the country's development.
But now...
you're contradicting your statement, Sir.
I think you're very confused, Mr. Somu.
Come on, let's talk.
What will be the extent
of the nuclear devastation?
Catastrophic!
If there's a meltdown or an explosion
at the core of the Kamini reactor...
'It'll kill all living beings
within 100 kilometers.'
Stop this madman!
Send the military immediately to Kalpakkam.
No, Sir!
The public will know if we send
military or air force.
It'll cause panic!
Not just that...
If Amaran senses we're sending in force...
He may activate the device anytime.
'Gautham and the team
are already at Kalpakkam.'
'I'll go there and keep you updated, Sir.
- Stay back and keep me posted.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Kamini?
She's right there, Ma'am.
Sir, you don't have permission
to enter at this time.
- You see...
- Sorry, I have the permit with me.
Jackson?
Please think about it.
The destruction will be catastrophic.
It will destroy the entire South India.
Somu, you're annoying me.
Bye for now.
Amar, the machine is ready.
Now, connect this machine
to the reactor's core.
Hey!
Mike!
Go and check.
Hey, let's go!
Security guards are aware now.
Secure the perimeter.
Stay alert!
Sheeba, it's saying 10 minutes.
I don't have 10 minutes.
Look here, Gautham.
Only if you download the virus
can I access the power plant.
So, 10 minutes!
Don't go anywhere.
Okay, I'll wait.
Any last words?
You're going to die!
What?
Ta-ta!
Amar, I'm heading to the boat.
If they prevent the meltdown,
take the bomb I gave you
inside the reactor.
"Across all worlds, his power devours"
"Across all worlds, his power controls all"
"The mastermind behind it all."
Hey, my dear launderer.
The ambulance trick was a failure.
I thought you must be
looking for the bomb all over.
Not an issue!
The reactor meltdown has begun.
Any last wishes, Gautham?
Tell me. I'd love to hear.
Because...
...we have 20 minutes left.
Your last 20 minutes...
Let it be a memorable one.
Ma'am, are you okay?
Yeah.
Ma'am, we're running out of time.
Please get to the control room quickly.
Okay.
Sheeba, it's all in Mandarin.
I can't read this.
Ma'am, I can't break their hack remotely.
What?
Ma'am, I'm going to do something.
- I'm so sorry.
- Sorry for what?
Sorry!
'Only if I create a power surge and
reboot can I gain control over the factory.'
'I had not other choice.
Ma'am, are you okay?
I'm okay!
Now, I have the control over the factory.
I have shut down the reactor meltdown.
'But their Plan B
is the bomb they're holding.'
'No matter what, the bomb
shouldn't go off inside the power plant.'
Amar!
'They stopped the reactor meltdown.
They started to override our controls.
We only have one option left.
'The bomb I gave you
should explode inside the reactor.'
'Can you hear me?
'Amar?
'Gautham what you're holding is not
a nuclear bomb but a C4 explosive.'
'If the bomb explodes anywhere
inside the factory,'
'it will cause a radiation leak.'
'Many lives will be lost.'
'So, the bomb must be taken
5 km away from the factory.'
There's a small corridor
on the side of the Kamini reactor.
That leads you to a door.
'I will open that door for you.'
'You can go to the sea in 2 minutes
through that door.'
'There we have arranged
a boat for you.'
'Sheeba I've arrived at the door.
I'm opening it now.
Oh, my God!
They're outside the reactor door.
Sheeba, open the door.
What? No!
Go ahead! Open the door!
'Please listen to me.
Open the door!
Shut the door.
Switch on the reactor.
Okay.
'Shielding people from the war upon us.'
'The people who win that war
and save the country are...'
'Spies!'
'They don't care about their lives.'
'But they strive
to save the lives of people.'
'They're the real heroes!'
He's gone, Sir.
'Who are they?
And how do they look?'
'They just disappear
from the face of the earth.'
'Today, in my opinion, Gautham is a hero.'
'And he disappeared just like that.'
'But we must protect the lives of people
he sacrificed himself for.'
Essentials documents and your passport.
He already planned to send you
to a safe location.
Keep it safe!
'Today, we stopped Amaran.'
'What about the mastermind, Rana?'
'If we don't find Rana...'
'this world will encounter
another 1000 Amaran.'
'With a motive to capture Rana...'
'I went to meet
his old loyal friend at Tihar Jail.'
Who is Rana?
What do you know about him?
Such loyalty for a faceless person?
Loyalty to an extent
to destroy the country.
When I was struggling to survive
in this nation, it did not help me.
But Rana stepped in and helped me.
Loyalty, just for that one person!
Well, then, you die here.
I don't know anything about Rana.
Never met the man.
But I know a person alive
who has seen Rana in person.
'A small village, Murthazar,
near the Pakistan Border.'
'Many years ago, when Rana was
struggling for life from a bullet wound...'
'...the village physician
treated him to health.'
'I don't know if it's the truth or a lie.'
'But this is the only option
you have to know about Rana.'
[in Hindi] Is one of them, Rana?
[in Hindi] Then, who is Rana?
'You may call it a divine intervention,'
'he gave a face to the faceless Rana.'
Your cafe latte with one sugar.
Thank you.
Gautham,
it felt like someone was following me.
Don't worry.
We are safe here.
How long do we have to
look over our shoulders, Gautham?
'You don't have to anymore!
Sorry, did I interrupt?
Keerthana,
I need to speak to Gautham privately.
Please go and enjoy your latte.
Did you spend all the laundering money
you seized from Sowcarpet...
...or is there any left?
How did you escape the blast?
Oh, yeah, you're an underwater expert.
You shrewdly made everyone
believe that you're dead.
You saved a lot of lives.
Thank you for doing it!
I know that you did not
track me down to say thanks.
Amaran and Vedha used two capsules
out of seven nuclear capsules.
Where are the rest, Gautham?
It's in a place...
...where it's safe for everyone.
I found out who is Rana.
Now looking for you...
...his men have arrived here.
Look around!
If you don't capture Rana,
then you will have to
keep running for life.
All these years,
you looked around the world for Rana.
You could not find him.
So, I took away something
he wanted the most.
Now, I made him come after me.
Rana!
'To know why Mr. X turned into Rana...'
'I retraced his path for a year,
that he chose to walk on for 20 years.'
'To the world, my father is a Hero.'
'But to me,
he's the deadliest villain I've ever met.'
'Everyone experiences
a turning point in their life.'
'The instant when
a good person becomes evil.'
'The nuclear device instigated
greed in him...'
'And the possibilities that could fetch him
money, power, control'
'When my father realized its value
turned into a different person.'
'That's when under the identity of Rana...'
'...he created an International Syndicate.'
'To conspire against India...'
'the agencies that supported
this syndicate are'
'Pakistan ISI, Chinese MSS,
and American CIA.'
'If there's a nuclear attack
during the G20 Summit...'
'...he knew it'd lead to a World War.'
'So, he secretly executed a plan.'
'This was a plan executed
to put India down'
'in front of other countries
and hinder its development.'
'My father played a genius trick by
making his identity unknown to the world.'
'Even Amaran was unaware that
the Parameshwar Pratap he rescued was Rana.'
'He learned about Amaran's background
and brainwashed him'
'and instigated him
to execute a nuclear attack in India.'
Kamini will burn bright!
'He used your trust against you.'
Mr. X is one of our best agents!
'My father is the devil who manipulated
everyone who trusted him.'
'And that devil had two faces.'
'Mr. X'
'...and Rana!
'We averted the nuclear strike
they intended to carry out.'
'My father and the syndicate
are planning another attack.'
'They will create a new world order
if they succeed.'
'Before they execute their plan,
I have to stop them.'
I'm done running, Madam.
It's time for us to hunt now.
You're right! Enough running!
Pick up the shield.
Let's fight them together!
Fight them as Mr. X!
"Hey!"
"Every corner of the station got a camera"
"But I'm ghost moving in the shadows,
heavy rounds pound"
"Synchronized, trigger couple rounds"
"Strike couple keys, take your final bow"
"Jai Hind"
"Fury on the outside"
"Don't get fooled by the trench coat"
"Just one punch, that's all I like to push"
"Can't take you down with just my hat,
come at me now"
"Come at me now, come at me now"
"Mr. X gonna make a dent in the target"
"Daredevil, he take the spot and the mark"
"The ambulance passed,
ain't about the rust"
"To protect you, Mr. X coming for you,
this is all you get"
"X-force, hit force, rush to extraction"
"Surveillance based,
operating out of faction"
"Synced up, power's mission for progress"
"Mastermind, this is the lethal artist"
"This is, he is one the mission"
"This is, he's come for the revenge"
"This is... this is the one"
"He is on the mission"
"This is, he's come for the revenge"
"This is, he is one the mission"
"This is... this is the one"