Afternoon, sir. What exactly
seems to be the problem?
Problem?
You pulled over just then
when I was behind you.
Maybe you're having
engine trouble. Is that it?
No.
I'm tired.
Thought I should rest.
What brings you to Colby?
Passing through.
Sure. Okay.
I'd like to take a look at
your license and registration.
Oh, uh... Have to find them.
I'll be right here.
Where you heading, lady?
Home. What about you?
Well, my mother always said
you shouldn't judge a book
by its cover,
but I'm guessing I'll be
running this gentleman in
on drug charges
in all of about three minutes.
You need me to stick around?
No, I've got it.
Make me a meat loaf.
What do you say?
I'm sorry, honey,
but I'll be sleeping
by the time you get in.
You run the plates?
I'm about to
if you'd let me do my job.
- Love you.
I told you I need to see
your license and registration.
Are you hard of hearing?
Dispatch, this is car 14.
- Do you even have a license?
- Go ahead, 14.
I'm with 48 on that 10-81.
Can you help me bring up
the latest bulletin
on the interstate homicides?
Didn't Denver forward a list of
stolen vehicle plates from...
No!
Oh, my God.
Mike. Mike.
Oh, my God. Mike. Okay.
10-49. 10-49.
Shots fired. Trooper is down.
Shooter is
eastbound, eastbound on 28.
Mile marker 79.
We need an ambulance.
It's Michael.
Okay.
Honey. Honey, it's Jane.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Okay?
It is. It's...
They're... They're
on their way. They're coming.
They're coming right now.
Michael.
Michael, please, please don't
do this. Please don't do this.
No,
please don't do this right now.
Please. They're coming.
They're coming.
They're coming. Just...
Please.
Dad.
He's... He's gone.
It's
day five of a wave of terror
and sudden
and unexpected violence
that literally has
a stranglehold
on the American public.
Across six states,
at least fifteen victims
have met their fates
at the hands
of the bloodthirsty killer
that many are calling
"The Satanic Slasher."
California, Nevada,
Utah, and Arizona,
as well as New Mexico
and Colorado
have seen a trail of bodies,
dismemberments, decapitations
and mutilation.
Police now confirm that
satanic symbols
and graphic slurs
were left at the scenes
of the murders,
often written
in the victims' blood.
In the next hour, we'll take
you inside the killer's mind
as we speak with a psychiatrist
who's an expert in the
psychology of mass murderers.
Oh, yeah? Do you want to trade?
Um, I will
at the house tomorrow.
Oh, okay, tomorrow. Okay.
- Okay, bye.
-  Good night.
-  Get home safe.
- You too.
Anything?
He headed south
towards Dodge City
and abandoned the sedan.
We found another victim.
A woman.
He took her ID, everything,
so there's... there's no way
to identify her yet.
There's no telling
what he's driving now.
There's a potential
emotional undercurrent here
that we haven't
touched upon yet,
and that is survivor's guilt.
As a woman
in a predominantly male field,
a field where overt masculinity
and intimidating
physical presence,
even aggressive demeanor,
can be considered virtues,
you may have already
been experiencing
occasional feelings
of inadequacy,
whether you recognize them
as such or not.
Which could add further weight
to the emotional baggage
you take away
from having been a witness
to the death of your husband.
A death for which
you seem wrongly
to be blaming yourself,
at least in part.
The reality of the situation,
what I hope to help you
come to grips with is,
no matter how many times
you replay what happened
back in your mind,
the outcome is inescapable.
You must find a way
to begin accepting that.
Are we done here?
- We are, aren't we?
- Officer Archer...
I'm only here 'cause
this is mandatory, I told you.
You've had your hour.
An hour is barely a beginning.
It hasn't even been 48 hours
since you buried your husband.
Without question,
I will be recommending
further therapy and--
I don't know what I'm gonna do
without him.
There.
Now you know.
They tell me I've got to keep
coming here, then I will,
otherwise your hour's up.
Thank you. Goodbye.
...dismembered bodies
discovered a hundred miles
east of Kansas City.
Seven people have been killed
in the state of Illinois alone.
It's believed by many
that the Slasher
is heading north
towards the Canadian border.
Authorities are cautioning
those living
in the northern Midwest
that the Slasher
may have already crossed
into Wisconsin or Michigan.
Whenever you put
that uniform on,
you might as well
become another person.
Your heart and soul
belongs to the KHP.
That's who you are, Jane.
Who you've always been.
Look who's talking.
Yeah, well, at least you know
I'm speaking from experience.
There is such a thing as
disappearing into that uniform,
or thinking that it's
some kind of suit of armor,
which it isn't.
I'll be back soon, I promise.
Took provisional leave,
two weeks.
Mike dying wasn't your fault.
Listen to me.
Nothing that
you could have done
that would have
changed anything,
nothing you could have
done differently
that would have saved him.
Yeah, I know.
So... So what then?
I mean, look, you do realize
it's crazy what you're doing?
He's not the one I'm trying
to save, all right?
Since...
...four days ago,
four days that have felt
like a lifetime,
I have thought about one thing.
The shot.
The shot I had...
and what I wouldn't give
to have it back.
'Cause you're right,
nothing'll bring Mike back.
So what's left?
Another shot... another chance.
Just one bullet could save
however many lives,
and Mike gets to rest in peace.
And I don't know,
maybe I get to sleep at night.
Look.
- You'll never find him.
- I don't have to find him.
Sooner or later,
his luck will run out
and he'll get boxed in.
And when that happens,
all I want is another shot.
- Hey, Jane, just listen--
- Dad, I'm done talking.
You know me.
Tell me again not to go,
you think that'll stop me?
Keep your gun and badge
with you at all times.
Pointless as it is,
what you're doing...
I'll admit,
if I were you,
I believe I'd also need to
find that out for myself.
The time for exploring
life's sinful perversions
is now.
The planet rapers
have got it right.
Earth is meant to have
our seed spilt upon it,
and to be trod upon
and pillaged.
Forcibly violated
and voraciously consumed.
I give thanks
to His Infernal Majesty
and his pharmaceutical empire
for their creation
of painkillers
and their almighty
erection medications.
For there is
no greater foretelling
that humankind is heading
in the right direction.
Join me, for we will rise.
Discerning believers
can find us
in the classified section
ofThe National Tribune,
if you've got the dedication.
Well, thank you,
Mr. Pendleton.
It's always very
illuminating for--
No. No.
N--
Charlie?
Help! Help me!
Help! Please!
Well, I have our case files
for Topeka. Yeah.
Uh, in the spirit
of cooperation,
maybe you could
let me take a look
at what you've got
on the Kit Carson killings.
Yeah. Well, as a professional
courtesy, I was hoping that...
Is there anyone else
that I can speak to?
And that's what my point is.
Belief is not enough
to solve this case.
Yeah. Well, any information
would be really,
really helpful.
Okay. Well, maybe
I could speak to him.
When will he next be in?
Anything would be helpful.
Any information on the Slasher
killings in Las Vegas or--
Okay. Well, maybe
I can leave my number
in case you change your mind.
Thank you.
Thanks for nothing.
Hate you all.
I want to put in
a classified ad.
How much is it for Sunday?
The national ad.
Will you take
a credit card number?
First line
of the ad is, "M N O."
Capital "M," space.
Capital "N," space.
Capital "O."
Under that,
"To those who also share faith.
Seeking our mutual friend.
Need help.
Please reply."
Let Chicago know.
So long as they're kept
in the loop,
maybe they'll stay
out of our hair.
DC gets CC'd on everything,
those SOBs.
Okay, right now I need
two equally important things
brought to me
in the next 15 minutes.
The entire forensics workup
on the Slasher
and a chicken salad sandwich.
Excuse me. Are you Agent Zolan?
Uh, sorry,
I was looking for you.
And you are?
Officer Jane Archer
of the Kansas state police.
I was told you're heading up
the Slasher investigation.
May I?
If you don't mind, I'd like to
look over your shoulder
for a day or two.
I realize it's
an unusual request.
You're joking, right?
Pretty serious, actually.
You know, the trooper
that was murdered in Kansas,
he was my husband.
I was with him when he died.
Is it so much to ask, just...
help me fill in the blanks?
I feel for you.
We're all sorry for your loss.
The KHP's loss.
But with due respect,
I don't appreciate
having my arm twisted.
What are you even looking for,
Trooper?
Take a nickel's worth
of free advice,
go home.
Hello.
Yeah, hello.
Is this Trooper Archer?
Jane Archer?
Yeah, who is this?
This is Agent Becky Collins.
We crossed paths at the FBI
field office earlier.
I'm thinking maybe
we should talk.
-  There you go.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I really appreciate
you meeting with me.
Yeah. Well, next round
is definitely on you.
If Zolan knew I was walking
you through this, he'd, uh...
Screw it.
As we know, the first killings
were 16 days ago.
Death Valley Junction.
A tiny place.
He dismembered the Durk's
Paint shopkeeper there.
Stole money,
credit card numbers,
tools, clothing, food.
The victims he chooses, there
are those of pure opportunity
and those he takes
something specific from,
like the pharmacist
from Colorado.
Yeah, he'll kill for
painkillers and psychotropics.
Percocet, Percodan, OxyContin.
We don't think he's dealing.
He's taking these drugs
himself. All of them.
And the gun shop
in, uh, Nevada, was it?
That's him.
He broke in after hours.
Got away with
at least one pistol,
a shotgun, plenty of ammo
and the shop's owner
was a collector.
He had a secret stash
of hand grenades.
Now, all missing.
- Jesus.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
And, um, the library
in Cedar City, Utah.
He killed the security guard
and the librarian.
Yeah. We got that surveillance.
What did he want
from a public library
that he couldn't get
off the Internet?
Well, if there's one
thing the FBI still does well,
it's track the Internet,
and he's not on it.
He took exactly two books
from a set of encyclopedias.
"N" and "T."
His mission,
if he even has a mission,
has him heading east
from motel to motel.
Sometimes spending whole days
in one place.
How do you know
he's been staying at motels?
I assumed he'd been living
in his vehicle.
If you want, I can show you.
He was here three days ago.
Three days after Kansas.
Checked in
in the dead of night.
On foot, paid cash.
Hotel clerk was a total stoner.
Couldn't give a description.
Didn't even have him register.
Worthless.
Middle of the next day,
the maid ignored
the "Do not disturb" sign
on the doorknob
or didn't see it somehow,
let herself in.
He used an axe,
cut her in half.
This seems to have gotten
his creative juices flowing.
This is how he leaves
all the crime scenes.
"Open the gates."
Our analysts say
he's obsessed with having
his achievements seen.
Can I use your computer?
Take a look at this.
It's from those murders
in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania.
Church killings, years ago.
He was a satanist.
Richard Reeves.
Richard Joshua Reeves.
He killed 13 people.
Similar profile.
We're aware.
Those kind of satanic symbols
and phrases do tend to overlap,
but our guy,
he's not really copycatting.
Reeves was a mass murderer,
not serial.
Maybe an admirer
of Reeves, at least.
Inspired by him.
Okay, judging by the distances
he's been traveling,
in the next day or two, this
is where he'll actually be.
Somewhere between
Columbus, Ohio,
and Wheeling, West Virginia.
110 miles, 25 exits,
give or take.
This is the best chance anyone
has of running him down.
Well, I don't know if
it's right to wish you luck,
so I'll just say be careful.
Thanks for sticking
your neck out.
I wish there was some way
I could repay the favor.
I'll pass your theories along.
For all the good that'll do.
I'm not allowed
to be telling you
what I'm about to tell you.
There's a small construction
and demolition company
near Kansas City.
A quantity of explosives
were stolen.
Explosives?
Dynamite.
About 20 pounds or so
of old-school, volatile TNT.
Enough to do
significant damage.
Manson and "The Family,"
as the cult members
called themselves,
killed seven people
in the infamous
Tate-LaBianca murders of 1969.
Messages were left written
on the walls in blood.
Devil worship was also
the motive 20 years ago,
when teenager
Richard Joshua Reeves
committed the grisly killings
at Christ Cross Church
in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania.
Reeves murdered 13 hostages
inside the church,
including a priest,
while performing
what authorities described
as a ritualistic black mass.
Slasher,
killing all those people.
When this is over, you wanna
know who's gonna be behind it?
The government.
I read on 8chan
how our government,
they've been keeping criminals
in secret military prisons
for doing experiments on.
Now one of those criminals
finally escaped.
Z100.5, we'll begin another
commercial-free block
of smooth jazz in a moment.
But first, the Satanic Slasher.
Hello?
Can I help you?
I'm listening.
I've always liked priests.
When I was just a young boy,
my priest,
he took me under his wing.
You could say
that he made me into the man
that I am today.
Oh, that's good, my son.
Very good.
And have you come to,
uh, confess?
- Not exactly.
- Pardon me?
Congratulations.
Oh. Thank you.
That reminds me, um,
could I get a glass of milk, please?
Thank you.
Jesus.
Richard Joshua Reeves
slaughtered the 13 men
and women
he briefly held hostage
inside the church
that March afternoon.
He claimed that
human sacrifice was necessary
to, quote, "fulfill
his obligation to Satan."
In a coordinated siege
upon the church,
Harrisburg police officers
managed to capture
Reeves alive.
In 2004,
facing a death sentence,
Reeves finally met his end
when he was shot and killed
while attacking a prison guard
in the federal penitentiary
where he was held.
We're asking all the major
East Coast hotel chains
to help us find the Slasher.
Yes, sir.
The suspect is almost
certainly a white male.
Above average height,
stocky build,
will be traveling alone,
pays in cash.
Whatever you do,
do not confront this man.
If you have suspicions
about a guest
you feel fits the description,
call 911.
Afternoon, sir. Officer Archer.
I'm sorry to trouble you, but
we'd actually like some help
watching out for
the interstate killer.
The Slasher.
Oh.
What little information
we have, I'd like to run by you
in case any of your guests
match the profile.
He'd be a white male, alone,
paid in cash most likely.
Police have made it sound like
he's likely not gonna
come around here.
Yeah, uh, I'm starting to think
they're probably right
about that actually.
And I wasn't working
the desk last night
so I don't know
how helpful I can be.
I...
I can check the register.
We still have
our guests sign in.
There's no one staying alone.
All right. Uh, maybe I'll just
leave you my number.
Um, thanks for your time.
Oh. There's one gentleman.
Uh...
Checked in last night. Alone.
Uh, Mr. Reeves.
What did you say?
Uh, Reeves.
Late last night. R.J. Reeves.
- May I... May I look at that?
- Yep.
Room 105?
Go down the hall,
make a left. Outside.
Okay, I'm gonna need
that key, sir.
Okay, you call the police, you
tell them the Slasher is here.
This is not a prank call.
This is for real.
Call them now.
Hello.
I saw your answer
in the newspaper.
Oh, so you're one of
our brethren, huh?
Looking for someone
to lend you a hand?
I'm looking for friends
who share my affinity
for discretion.
I need help finding someone,
but it needs to
be done discreetly.
And it needs to stay offline.
Where are you?
Pennsylvania.
Well, you're not far
from us actually.
Why don't you come
talk to us tonight?
Mr. Pendleton happens
to be hosting
some of his latest associates.
Hi, Agent Collins,
it's Jane Archer.
I'm on my way to Baltimore
tracking a 410
area code number.
If there is any way
you can help me out
by matching an address
to this number,
I'd hugely appreciate it.
Hi.
The gate's broken.
Just one sec.
It used to open
by itself, but now it doesn't.
There you go.
Let me get that for you. I--
Okey dokey.
Um, I was just gonna take it.
I was gonna put it
in the back, but...
Not a problem.
You sit right there.
Oh, uh, what did you say
your name was again?
Richard.
Well, Richard,
first I have to ask,
for my own protection
and the protection
of my employer...
are you a cop?
Policeman?
- No.
- Okay.
Because if you are
and you say you're not,
that's just, um, like...
Anyway,
I guess however we can help
a fellow believer, we will.
You know about us
using the classifieds.
We're all in this together, right?
I need information.
Yeah, well, Mr. Pendleton
will give you an earful.
Enlightenment, more like.
He is a great magus. He is.
He keeps that on the down-low
these days, obviously.
But he says he's got
a good feeling about you,
you know, good vibrations.
You are his invited guest
so he's just excited
to meet ya.
And I'm, uh, Marvin,
by the way.
Come on.
You've heard of Mr. Pendleton, right?
Yeah, he made his money
in the supermarket biz,
years ago.
You can set that down
right there if you'd like.
Or keep it with you. Whatever.
Uh... Just follow me.
Come on.
...in the middle
of the forest,
and it's on a river.
It's really--
Oh. Well, well.
Our guest has finally arrived.
Yes, please,
make yourself welcome.
If you're hungry, there's
plenty of food left over.
Yes.
So, ladies, gentlemen,
meet another traveler
on the left-hand path.
Uh, mister...
Richard.
Uh... Just Richard.
Richard. Well, okay.
- Well, thank you, Marvin.
- Yeah.
You know, my seer told me
to expect a visitor,
a visitor who would have
a profound influence
on my life.
Are you he, Richard?
You know,
it's really quite remarkable
that you're here at all,
Richard,
let me tell you.
Lucky for you, Marvin here,
he makes a hobby out of
scouring the classifieds.
Always on the lookout for
any voice in the wilderness.
I go through it all.
When he showed me your ad,
I was flabbergasted.
I need information,
information that
benefits us all...
if you are
who you claim you are.
And I don't have
the means to get it.
Oh, well, then, have Marvin
help you with that.
Easily done. Our smartest,
most committed acolyte.
Not a problem.
Now, what say, let's hear
a little about yourself.
How long have you
had the knowledge?
As long as I can remember.
Oh, splendid.
Then your family
were followers?
I have no family.
So you found the Fallen One
all on your own?
You know, I've always said
the truest believers
are not the recruits
but those who
sought out the faith.
Hail, Satan!
- Hail, Satan.
I live to serve him,
and I'll die to serve him.
Wonderful.
You know,
there are those who say
that the party's over for us.
The reality is, my friend,
the party has just begun.
I mean, look around.
Turn on the television.
Satan rules over this world.
I mean, can there be any doubt?
The oil conglomerates
and the government
work hand in glove to wage war
and to drain the planet of
every last vestige of life...
Human beings will,
you know, soon have devolved
into pod-dwelling,
cyber cavemen...
A wizened, naked old man
with his engorged cock
fairly vibrating...
The time for exploring
life's sinful perversions
is now,
the golden age
of human depravity.
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah!
Any more sweet 'n sour?
That was a vibrant speech
from Mr. Pendleton.
You can tell
Mr. Pendleton likes you.
It's this way.
This is your room.
Anyway,
what was this information
you keep asking about?
Someone I need to find.
Okeydokey. Fine.
Well, there is this detective
that Mr. Pendleton uses
from time to time.
Good,
then he's a man of discretion.
Well, you can
probably imagine Mr. P's
need to protect himself
from his enemies.
What's the name of the person
that you're looking for?
Looking to, uh,
put a hex on them?
I don't know their name.
Right, well, uh, how am I
supposed to find them?
I know what they do.
Well, you've lost me.
I know what city they're in.
Okay.
I... I still don't follow.
There's a certain city.
I need to know
who there does this job,
who they are,
where they live.
Right.
...facing
accusations of vigilantism
earlier in the week
since Officer Archer's husband,
also a Kansas state trooper,
was slain in cold blood
by the Slasher.
I said everything
I've got to say
at the FBI press briefing
so please leave me alone.
Listen, he's still out there,
killing every chance he gets.
If I have the chance
to somehow help track him down,
then why wouldn't I do
exactly that?
We looked into
the newspaper ads weeks ago,
Trooper Archer.
There's no evidence connecting
them to the Slasher.
Anyone could be responsible.
We're not wasting manpower
on a hunch.
I'll advise you again,
go back to Kansas
before you get yourself killed.
The FBI's got this, and you're
way out of your lane.
You've reached 555-0324.
Leave a message.
Officer Archer,
we bumped into each other
at the motel the other day.
I'm flattered you've been
following my work.
I'll be leaving you
some new pieces along the way.
On the 28th,
we will open the gates.
Give my regards
to your husband.
Fiat voluntas eius.
Carnem eius
cum carne celebremus.
We call thee forth
to bear witness
to our carnal devotions.
Let others celebrate the death
of their hippie superhero.
We celebrate the life
and infernal majesty
of Lord of the Flies.
Hail, Abaddon.
Hail, Satan!
Hello? Uh...
Oh. Hey, there you are.
Listen, uh,
got what you wanted.
Our private detective guy,
he came through.
Seems like it was no biggie.
You're welcome.
Hey! Uh...
What? So-- So that's it?
You're leaving?
Hey.
Look...  ...I really
think that you should wait
and say goodbye to
Mr. Pendleton, don't you?
I mean, that's the least
that you could do.
Come on. He's going to wonder
why you left all of a sudden
without saying "thank you."
It just...
It's kind of a common courtesy.
That's all it really is. I...
I... Look...
What are you doing?
Your friends are going to hell
ahead of schedule.
What the hell?
You're not like them.
I believe you believe.
Are you... You're him.
You're the Slasher.
Leave.
Never look back.
Keep silence...
...or I'll find you.
I will.
Whoa, whoa, wait!
No, no, no.
Pazuzu.
Pazuzu, be gone.
They are seven.
Fuck! Fuck!
What I had,
I gave to you Feds
and to everyone and anyone
who would listen.
I gave you everything.
Everything.
So, where the fuck
was everyone?
I got here!
Where the fuck were you?
We don't know.
We don't have any evidence
of what went down here.
I saw him. I told you.
It was him.
I mean, you do realize
we're fielding something like
two dozen bogus leads
by the hour?
Just listen to me.
Twenty years ago,
devil-worshipper
Richard Joshua Reeves
committed the church killings
in Harrisburg.
A few years later, the satanic
metal band Demon Fist
started writing songs
about Reeves inspired by him.
They even posed
for one of their album covers
in front of
the abandoned church
where the murders took place.
Now, because of Reeves,
and probably
because of those albums,
that church,
Christ Cross Church,
is a mecca
for would-be satanists.
Reeves inspires Demon Fist.
Demon Fist and Reeves
inspire the Slasher.
He is quoting titles
and lyrics from these albums.
And the whole time,
the Slasher
is using Reeves's name,
maybe even thinks he is Reeves.
I'm telling you, the psycho
wants to finish it there.
The Slasher
is going to Harrisburg.
In other news
outside the Slasher killings,
today marks
the 28th anniversary
of Three Mile Island,
the worst civilian nuclear
disaster in American history.
We were
outside early that morning,
March 28th.
And the ground
started to shake.
My sister says,
"That's an earthquake."
And I said, "It don't feel
like an earthquake.
An earthquake, it don't
make sounds like that."
I said,
"I think something happened
at Three Mile Island."
They told us we had to
evacuate our homes immediately
before a hole got burned down
to the center of the Earth.
We abandoned everything.
Our homes, our belongings.
We were terrified.
Well,
since we're on the subject,
I firmly believe that it's
important to remember history,
even if it's dark
or unpleasant.
Maybe especially
if it's dark and unpleasant,
because we have to learn
from our mistakes.
I'm not arguing with that,
but sometimes
we just have to let things go.
So, why don't you call her
and find out?
She's your sister, isn't she?
If she's my sister,
that makes her your sister too.
I'm aware. I'm well aware.
- Leonard Wilkes.
- Oh, fuck!
Do you love your wife?
Well, look who finally decided
to show up.
But where are you?
"3M1.
3MI."
Today marks
the March 28th anniversary
of Three Mile Island,
the worst civilian nuclear
disaster in American history.
What did he want
from a public library?
He took exactly
two books. "N" and "T."
...when the uranium core
of the Harrisburg power plant
partially melted down,
spewing radiation
over Pennsylvania
and neighboring states.
A quantity of explosives
was stolen.
Old-school, volatile TNT.
They told us we had to
evacuate our homes immediately,
before a hole got burned down
to the center of the Earth.
Oh, my God.
Christ, Leo.
Didn't you work already?
Just got called back in
by Kreiger, so it's, uh...
It's urgent, so...
Yeah.
Pop the back.
Hurry up. Come on. Let's go.
You know the drill.
All right, let him through.
We're almost there. Please.
Keep going.
This is not a joke. You need
to send officers right away.
Do you understand?
There's going to be an attack
on Three Mile Island.
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm so sorry.
You'll be okay, okay?
I'll be back. I promise, okay?
You'll be okay.
I love you. I'll be back.
No, no. Please. No.
Please.
No, please. Please. Please.
Please. Please,
you don't need me anymore.
You can let me go.
You don't have to do this.
Just let me go.
No, no, no.
How you help me now
decides who lives or dies.
I'm Highway Patrol Officer
Jane Archer.
Listen to me.
I have every reason to believe
there's about to be
an attack on this plant.
What are you talking about?
He's here. He's already here.
There's something going on
at control reactor one.
Open the gates! Do it!
- You, ride with me.
- Hold on. Just hold on.
Look, I know who he is.
I can help you stop him,
but we need to move.
Okay.
Let us through, then
lock it down and call it in.
Get out.
Jesus!
Come on.
Spread out. Go, go, go.
I got your six.
Come on.
-  Let's go.
-  We're in. Hup!
-  Move it, move it.
-  Go, go, go.
On me, on me.
Go!
Watch it. Here we go.
-  Stay close.
-  Yeah.
Go, go, go.
He's locked
in the control room.
He's taken Leo hostage.
I need this hallway, people.
Everyone, back the hell off.
Anyone from operations
or engineering, follow me.
Do this one last thing,
and I'll let you out.
Your wife's waiting for you.
Or don't do it.
And I'll kill you.
What have we got?
Reactor one's operating at 75%.
The problem is
Leo's flushing the core.
He overrode the system. He's...
He's purging the coolant.
All of it.
Water levels are plummeting.
The emergency system
will kick in
once the core temperature
rises above nominal.
He's gonna kill that man. Leo.
This isn't a hostage situation.
There's not gonna be
a negotiation.
Look, I know how this sounds,
but the guy in there,
that's the Slasher.
I've been following him,
and this has been his plan
all along.
His suicide.
He's very dangerous.
He has explosives.
He will have brought them.
If he blows up
the IC system, we're done.
No, no, no. Please, no.
Please, please, please.
He's gonna use the grenade
as a detonator.
That much TNT...
It can take out
the entire control room.
Well, can't you just shut it
down before he does anything?
You must be able to do that.
Not from outside
the control room, no.
He's gonna fucking
melt us down.
He's gonna take out
a city full of people.
More like
the entire East Coast.
Security,
you've got to get in there
right now.
You have to get in there
and stop him.
Is there another way
into the control room?
The ventilation system?
It's secure.
That's the whole point.
It's even designed
to keep a radiation leak out.
All right, people.
Listen up.
Notify the NRC
and Civil Defense.
Tell them Three Mile Island
is on the verge
of catastrophic failure.
If we're lucky, they've got
two, maybe three hours
to try to evacuate
all of central Pennsylvania.
There might be a way. Come on.
This has been closed since...
...forever.
It's plexi.
It's bulletproof, I'm sure.
Stop!
Hey!
It's over. There's no way. I...
Sorry, but fuck this.
Hail Satan!
Welcome your servant
into the kingdom of hell.
All in your name,
Almighty Diabolus.
Open the gates!
Go to hell, psycho.
Authorities
are remaining tight-lipped
about the status
of the investigation.
Why are
there Satanic Slashers?
Is it Richard Joshua Reeves?
There's no doubt in my mind
that the
Three Mile Island killer
is in fact The Satanic Slasher.
There
is speculation over whether
the Three Mile Island killer
may still be alive.
See, I told you.
Our government
is creating human monsters
and releasing them
back into the world.
Shown here on archival footage
is Richard Joshua Reeves's
1999 arrest
and conviction for
the Christ Cross mass murder,
which was thought to
have brought an end
to his killing spree.
That tragedy now
pales in comparison
to the trail of death
he left in his wake
in the past few weeks
as The Satanic Slasher.
At a minimum,
he is responsible for 48 deaths
on his recent murder spree.
And some claim
that he may have survived
his suicide run
at Three Mile Island.
A spokesperson for the FBI
denies those claims,
insisting Reeves suffered
several gunshot wounds
including one to the head,
which ultimately proved fatal.
Welcome home, Reeves.
Yeah,
Death Valley missed you.