"Ain't nobody gonna make me fall?"
'Sattendru Maarudhu Vaanilai'
'Sudden Winds Of Change'
Where is Janaki?
'What are you doing
in the room given to Janaki?'
'All of us are waiting
for her in the wedding hall'
'Everyone is furious
after what you did last night'
'Janu?'
'I can see Janaki's novel'
She isn't here
She must be there, go and check
'Chee! I don't consider you
as a human being at all'
'Minister Boovaragasamy inaugurates
Grand Flower Show in Kodaikanal'
Young girl kidnapped and killed
[Young girl kidnapped and killed]
Chandru, don't come here
and make a scene unnecessarily
You better leave from here
Where is Janu?
Are you asking me the same question
I asked you a while ago?
Didn't you see her
after that issue last night?
She didn't come back to her room
What did you do to her?
'She lost her peace of mind
the moment she set eyes on you'
- Wait, Raghavi
- You bloody rascal!
'How will I know?'
- Hey! Don't try to escape
- 'He's likely the culprit'
- 'Don't let him get away
- Come
- Check where Janu is
- That's our duty, come
Hey! Confess
[screaming in pain]
- Thrash him
- Cough up the truth
Confess
Spit it out
Tell... tell us now
'If we wish something
with all our heart'
'If our wish is fair and just'
'This universe will make
that wish come true'
- Hello?
- 'Where are you, sir?'
Pizza Hut in ECR
I'm standing opposite that
in front of Coffee Crush
'Okay, sir
I'm coming'
Party Working President Eashwaraiya
He has been asking for a long time
to marry our daughter Janaki
Isn't your daughter at home?
She has gone out
Didn't I inform you of my visit?
Kindly listen
'She isn't the least bit
interested in marrying you'
Please understand, as if
you can't find any other bride?
You listen to me, I don't want to marry
your daughter for want of any other bride
'If I marry your daughter'
My astrologer said, that groom
will reach the pinnacle of fame
That's why I want to drive away
my wife and take Janaki as my 2nd wife
That's the only reason
you got MLA seat and ministership
I have elevated your status
to my level, for your information
If you want, take back the posts
you gave with strings attached
My daughter's happiness is priority for me
Forget my daughter
- What the hell, man?
- Sir
Are you treating me disgracefully
for reaching out like this, huh?
- Keep this in mind
- No, sir
This ministership
is mere alms I gave you
Don't forget you have
2 murder cases against you
Don't force me to pull those dusty files
Your life will reek!
- Please be patient
- Fix the wedding date soon
Sir... leader, I will somehow convinc-
- Just do as I say
- Don't be angry
Or you'll be counting bars!
He wants to throw
our pet parakeet to a monkey!
'Move it'
He will sell his soul
for a damn post or seat
Selvi
'Selvi'
Sir, madam is on the terrace
drying the clothes
She will see my Hyde side today
Bloody roadside mongrels!
Mother and daughter trying to insult me?
Oh God! Madam
Aiyo! Ma
- How could you, sir?
- Hey listen
She accidentally slipped and fell into
the swimming pool while drying clothes here
Oh God! Poor madam
Janaki
Where is Janaki?
Upstairs in her room, sir
She hasn't stepped out
for nearly a week, sir
Isn't the minister at home?
Sir has gone to Delhi
with Party leader
[knocking]
Janu
How can you lock yourself up like this?
Come out
'At least go and stay in a hostel'
I'll take care of the expenses
'Will you open up a make-up studio?'
'Do it as a challenge'
I'll invest for you
'Every problem has a solution, Janu'
'Please just come out, no?'
This is the right time
for you to leave, Janu
Your dad is in Delhi
'Do not stay in this hell-hole'
'You be happy somewhere else'
I've got my hands into this mess
I shouldn't miss the 'Miss'!
'She seems to be
a carbon copy of Nayanthara'
'What to do if every newcomer
competes with Lady Superstar?'
Aiyo!
'I feel like getting
into action right now'!
You look so dazzling bright
Is your hubby out of town?
- Chandru?
- Who asked you to mail our boss?
Complaining about Yogi
stealing and selling laptops?
You added his mail Id in CC
which is totally unconnected to our mail
I forwarded like I do usually
Someone has tagged him
in the previous office mail
Automatically his ID also got added to CC
If you can get Yogi out of
his cabin for just 2 minutes
I can easily delete that mail
from his laptop
You help all those orphans in Anbu Illam
I'm also an orphaned youngster
unloved by any girl
Won't you help me?
I'll zip my lips
Let me see what she's doing
Picking her phone, huh?
Take Swapna's audio clip
I am not good at mimicry
Pick an audio note from your WhatsApp
'Sorry, Kathir'
'I couldn't attend the meeting today'
'Please manage somehow'
You are copying Arjun in 'Irumbu Thirai'?
He can hear whatever I intend saying
in Swapna's voice
Will you imitate Swapna?
I get an adrenalin rush if I hear her voice
You do the honors please
[telephone ringing]
Someone is calling me from our office?
Has that 'shovel head' snitched
to my boss about me?
- Hello?
- 'Hellllo'
Hello, who is this?
"Find out..find out.."
"Who is talking to you?
Try and guess, dude?"
Sopppppuuuu!
'How did you identify immediately?'
Can your sweet lips
Can your sweet voice
slip out of my mind?
The moment I wake up
I listen only to your voice
Whether I listen to sacred chant or not
I listen only to Swapna
like the dog in His Master's Voice!
HMV, huh?
If her husband finds out
that dog will be slippered!
He may hear you
How come this sudden surprise call?
- 'Will you come to my room?'
- HUH?!
Midnight?
Naughty!
- Where?
- Here
For what?
'For THAT!'
That...!
Hello...?
Hello... Soppu... Soppu?
We can hear him drooling here
- 'Drooler of the year!'
- Thank God everyone is cat-napping
[song from 'Kolamaavu Kokila']
"Time to get married, find a soul mate"
"Your time has passed expiry date"
Never mind
I'll renew it
Bro, coffee?
I don't like 'Bro' coffee
I drink only Bru coffee
Don't bug me, go
Shut up! Bad enough
your original voice is annoying
Give us access, bro
You have no idea of my needs, get lost!
Soppu darling
'List out your craving'
I chased those immature boys
just like you wanted me to
I've come alone
- Shall we go to 'Gulfothri'?
- For what?
To play mummy-daddy game
- For 'that'!
- 'That' means what?
I don't get it, Yogi
Lunatic lady!
You called me here over the phone
I called you?
When did I talk to you?
Didn't you sing like Trisha in 'Thug Life'?
- We'll get an intruder soon
- 'Kamal or Simbu?'
'I am a combo of both the hero'
"Here is Swapna baby
I am singing her a lullaby"
- You enticed me and deceived me
- Yogi, what are you doing here?
Swapna has only a sharpener
She doesn't have a pencil
One look at your shifty eyes, I know
How can you barge into a girl's cabin?
She called and asked for my pencil, sir
I never called, sir
You called me here
- Get out!
- Trust me
Get out, I say
She's changing words
like changing spouses!
Go and wipe the benches
'Complaining like LKG kids
of missing stationery'
'Is he giving her a rubber or what?!'
Soppu
You asked me to come
and made me last in your list
- 'I knew it'
- I am the MD-
Sir, if all of you hit on me
I'll complain in 'Me too'!
- Down here
- Let go of my sari, sir
My dear, I came here
only because you called me
Get up, sir
If my wife got to know
she'll shoo me out of the office
I am going
'Preacher outside
Playboy inside'
- I gave her a rubber
- Fell at her feet in a jiffy
Don't give a detailed account
to anyone out here
- You'll give me a promotion?
- Go, 'tell' my wife
'Shameless fellow!'
Soppu, didn't you call
asking me to come?
I told you I didn't call you
Then who the hell called me?
- 'Hi Ranesh'
- Hi dad
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, dad
Has Janaki given the green signal?
I convinced her to leave her home
I made her stay in a hostel
Hey dumbo
I told you to make her
flip for you and marry her
What are you doing instead?
Only now she's getting back to normalcy
She's worth 3 billion
Don't let go of her
'I am banking on her assets
to repay our bank loans'
Before her father finds her a lousy groom
make sure you tie the knot round her neck
Try to brainwash her by giving her
a taste of high society, pub, party, club
Don't sit on this and drag it
We don't want some chap
barging in, whisking her away
- 'Did she say where she was going?
- No, sir'
- Why did you let her go in my absence?
- I wasn't at home, sir
Hey Commissioner
I have sent you my daughter Janaki's photo
She walked out of the house
Order your staff to silently track
her whereabouts and tell me
Yes
You think I can't find you, damn you!
Why did you bring me to this pub?
We can booze on our terrace
and give this wasted expense to a beggar
Like our beloved 'Captain sir'
donate your money to 'Anbu Illam'
Get tanked without a sermon
like actor Sivakumar sir
- My treat today
- Machan, thanks
Aiyo! All those girls are stunning
- Don't know which one to hit on
- Served starters
- Starters seem like main course
- Just eat, dude
Thank you
I'm better off working here
- Cheers!
- Cheers for juice?!
Enough, dude
I can't believe so many pretty girls
live in our town?
Yes, Quad-eyes!
Only if we come to
pubs like this
We realize we've missed out
on such pretty girls!
How come we never
see them during the day?
They will be suffering from hangovers!
And relaxing in some
beach house or farm house
We can also booze at night
and chillax daytime
Of course we can
and end up being jobless
'Is that okay?
Shut up, drink'
[Hindi] Look now
[Telugu] I'll show you
- I am rich
- So what?
Wording on your T-shirt
Richardson
Friends call me 'Rich'
If you stir with your finger
you can drink and be merry
Chee!
Look at that, dude
She doesn't even consider me
as an appetizer!
Wow!
A dreamboat head turner like this girl
Cha... cha... no
She's the one I would like to marry
Who is that?
We can look at a BMW and drool
But we shouldn't wish to drive it!
Even the Pulsar bike
we ride daily will ditch us
Hey!
'First we must ask the universe
with all our heart to grant our wish'
'If our wish is fair and just'
'This universe will make
that wish come true'
You read 'The Secret'
by that Rhonda lady, bro?
I have asked the universe 10,000 odd times
Not once has my wish been granted!
Go ahead, ask, let me see
if it gifts you on a golden platter!
Shall I ask?
Buddy?
1 minute
'Coming, sir'
Why are you asking him
instead of the universe?
- Yes, sir?
- That girl in a black dress over there
Tell her I'm buying her a drink
If she asks why, tell her
it is my birthday today
She should buy for you
Go on, universe
Proceed with your plan
That gentleman over there is offering
to pay for the drinks you order
Why?
His birthday it seems
He's throwing a party for everyone here
Oh! No, thanks
I am here with my friend
- It's okay
- Thanks, madam
Okay, buddy?
No, sir, she declined your offer
She's with a friend it seems
'Your plan failed, eh?'
- Hi
- Sorry, I'm late
- No worries
What's up?
'You are always late'
Ma'am?
He's offering to buy
a drink for your friend too
- Because-
- I told you I don't want
Can't you take 'no' for an answer?
What's the issue here?
His birthday it seems
He's offering a free drink
Doesn't seem to get it
when I declined firmly
Okay
That's okay
It's free
Instead of hooking that girl
...you're happily showing
Thumbs Up, Coco-Cola to her guy
He's agreeing to a free booze
with no hang-ups!
- Next move
- 'Getting his driver a drink?'
I want to dance with her, bro
She should first agree, no?
I will make her say 'yes', bro
- How, bro?
- Like this, bro!
"Hey! Akka-di"
"Fire it up, buddy"
"Everyone tonight
Tanked so tight"
"Whatever said in stupor is right"
"Gin & Sprite
Fried anchovies delight"
"Dress sparkling white
No need to fight"
"This club lacks light
Take peanut bar & bite"
"We can roll the vibe"
"No cash, no bribe"
"Still we stand, strong tribe"
"With AI's aid a song I penned
Uploaded on Insta as per the trend"
"Inbox on fire
System to rewire"
"To text you a Hi, all of a sudden
I slid into your inbox then"
"K_420687"
"Helium balloon with love
floats high there above"
"I was footloose and fancy free
Caught in her web; I can't flee"
"It was love at first sight for me
I sent her a hello-drink happily"
"I want to clone your genes specially"
"Hey glam doll girlie
My fair lady"
"Pause the melody
Fire it up, buddy"
"Hey lovely lassie
No sister to me"
"Stop the melody
Kindle the kicks, buddy"
"Glam doll fiery"
"Go on a spirit spree"
"Ring-a ring-a rose
Titanic Jack's chapter close"
"Even if that ship sank into the sea
I'm a shark, I can swim to safety"
"My wallet is empty, sorry
No booze to make merry"
"If I ride my bike, cops will catch me"
"Even when the night is gone
my feet will dance on and on"
"I am not suspicious, just not my style
When it's romance, I'm lost by a mile"
"Like Chris Nolan, director of repute
I came here to confuse you, dude"
"With a swag I walked in here"
"Why don't you tag me, my deer?"
"Without any lag I streamed
'live', my dear"
"Helium balloon with love
floats high there above"
"I was footloose and fancy free
Caught in her web; I can't flee"
"It was love at first sight for me
I sent her a hello-drink happily"
"I want to clone your genes specially"
"Hey glam doll girlie
My fair lady"
"Pause the melody
Fire it up, buddy"
"Hey lovely lassie
No sister to me"
"Stop the melody
Kindle the kicks, buddy"
"Glam doll fiery"
"Go on a spirit spree"
"Fire it up, buddy"
Akka-di
Phew!
99-41-00
Easy to remember
I mean... in case
you break up with your guy
Consider me as follow-up
- What's your name?
- For what?
- Janaki
- [Hindi] Who's that?
Hey Pakkadi
Give your # and go
Tata
This evening was a bit different
and actually awesome, right?
Do you know him from before?
No
- Why should I know?
- I meant
We didn't go to our usual bar
Here we come and some random chap
offers to buy us a drink
You danced with him
I saw you talking to him
Come on, I say
I don't know him from Adam
And
His songs were local and crass
Nowadays girls prefer such local boys
Hey! What's up with you?
Where are we going?
The Dublin Bar
Hey Ranesh, I'm tired
Just drop me in the hostel
So... you'll accept a drink
from a random stranger
You won't even accept the same offer
when I do the same, right?
Hey!
Just stop this nonsense, okay?
Of course I said 'no'
You accepted the freebies coolly
Are you accusing me
of being a free loader?
From the car you're sitting in now
Food, travel, life style
I am the one who spends
for everything, A to Z
Mind it!
I said I'll take up a job as
a bridal make up artist
You wanted both of us
to start a business
And offered to
take care of my expenses
Now you're insulting me
as if I'm living off you!
Aren't you ashamed?
You coward!
Coward? Yeah?!
I'm the coward?
Get the hell out of the car
'Doesn't look like one of us'
She got out of a car
Wonder what's her problem?
If some chap sees her with us
she will be in trouble
Hey dude!
Different colored doves are waiting for us
- Let's feed the birdies
- Look, they are here
Buddy, they are a different kind of bird
'Just a make-up'
- Let's go
- Make-up or pack-up
I want to make out
with that low hip now, da
Here comes the 'roadside Romeo'!
Why are you standing
silent and shy, darling?
- I am in a randy mood, no?
- I told you not to come near me
She isn't available
If you want, I'll come
I don't want you
I want only that chick
She isn't that kind of girl, hands off
Hey!
Don't come up with excuses
to hike up her rate!
Sky is the limit
Ask whatever amount
I want her this very minute
- Are you deaf or what?
- Why are you backing off?
- Listen to me
- Wondering if I can afford only an auto?
Just nod your head and say 'yes'
We can unzip in an Audi
as we zip zap zoom
- Help!
- I'm ready to help you
Help me please
- Chuck him out
- Don't know who this is
'Shall I call my boys?'
First you 'help' me
Next will be my turn to 'help' you!
Brother
My friend has booked that girl
Be patient and wait
Hey! Careful
'Move, they will fall on us'
'Go, thrash him!'
'Looks like he is a fan of Thalapathy'
Thrash him, man
Come, let's bring our gang
Why this unnecessary violence?
I can wait
'Scoot before your nose bleeds!'
Get back to the auto
'He ran for his life, di'
You broke my nose
without knowing who I am
Rascal! I'll wreck her in front of you
- Start the auto
- 'Get lost, junk of a jerk!'
What are you doing here?
I was...
Girl, do you know him?
I am...
You shouldn't be hovering around here
Leave this place right away, okay?
If a policeman catches you
he will put you behind bars along with us
'He will assault and abuse us'
You don't hold a chance in hell
Just go with him now
Go, I say
Come
They may come back
Why are you hesitating?
Get on to his bike
Don't waste time
Where should I drop you?
Angel Ladies' Hostel
- Careful
- 'You take care, brother'
This is Robert D'Souza
He will take all our videos
Via Cryptographic software
Upload in Dark Web
and broadcast 'live'
- Super
- Cheers!
You don't even have
a single security chap
In my profession
I need to make deals in absolute secrecy
Through any security
No one else should be privy to it, right?
But still how do you manage
all by yourself in such a huge place?
Alone, huh?
Not even a fly can enter this compound
without my permission!
'I have surveillance cameras all around'
To live alone
It's a thrill
Only those I want can enter my darbar!
Because
I am Chakravarthy!
Great
Your demand
It's way too much
Come up
Welcome, Robert
Have a seat and relax
Thank you
And I will show you how to make
Easy money
Here we go
Robert
I own a chain of 100 hotels and resorts
under the name 'Moonstay' throughout India
In 1 hotel
If 50 rooms are booked
On an average 5000 rooms
I give an offer of 50%
for couples to choose my resort
Wow!
Booking is full all the time
Even if you take into account
just 50% booking
2500 videos in 1 day
That too, 'live' visuals
'...will be uploaded
in your organic sex website'
'To watch 1 'live' video'
Even if you charge minimum $2
If 1000 viewers worldwide
watch 1 video, on an average
You make 200 million per day
In our Indian currency
Approximately 60 BILLION per annum
'Live' videos will stay uploaded
in your website even after that
Videos will be watched on loop mode
Revenue will flow in
with every repeat watch
Now tell me
All I am asking
for this humongous deal
Just 5 billion
That's it
Easy money, man
Great!
When will we start the streaming?
I will forward my account ♪
Transfer the amount via crypto currency
Will it leak anywhere else?
I have installed a software in my laptop
Without my permission
No video can be streamed
'Entire backup will be intact'
Deal, okay?
Okay, see you, Robert
- Thank you
- Take care
- Dai
- Yes, Bonda
We were the ones who emptied
the whole jug, dude
He was simply a spectator
He's passed out like the hero in 'Master'
Wonder where he was
gallivanting last night
Buddy, plan to come with us to the office?
- Not coming
- Seriously?
All that's fine
Last night, you ate till you burped
Just when we had to pay the bill
You scooted like a female using
a phone call as excuse, where did you go?
Bike ride
With Janu
You mean that 'BMW'?
Did you have a go
at 'test drive' in the night?
I had a blast with 'BMW'
on my bike last night
Pcccht! That's a unique feeling
'Lucky fellow!'
What about that freebie boozo!
Was that moron Richie Rich
pushing your bike?
I bashed up that 'sim' card last night
Watch it, bro
May be a mobile with dual sim
Nowadays that's the trend!
- 'What say you?'
- I know to cuss you in the morning too
Please scoot and save yourself grief
I am floating in a good mood
He's in a zip zap whizzing mood it seems
He wants us to zip our lips and leave
Let's leave him to lie
on his tummy to tango!
Because he's Thalapathy fan
we have to grin & bear it
'Sorry n Thanks'?
Who is she?
Janu!
Janu?
I'll call her now?
Not like this
I'll freshen up and call
[mobile ringing]
Janu is calling me?
This pain, huh?
Chandru, come over to
the office right away
'Boss is waiting for you'
I can't come immediately
'What is the matter?'
I think it is something very important
That mongoose-mouth fellow
has asked thrice
'No need to shower
Just wash your face and land up'
Okay, I am ready
On the way
Come soon
I got ready for your sake
That effort didn't go waste
Thank you, Janu
Bye, bro
'Everyone is waiting
Giving this chap too much importance'
Vodka-ing last night?
Your face is shining bright
'This rubber mouth chap
is staring daggers at her'
As if he is 'Thalapathy 2.0'
Chandru, you made
even our boss wait for you
Hey!
Bad enough he is at his wife's mercy
lounging with legs crossed
He's holding on to his seat
He can afford to wait
for Chandru, no harm at all
No one here is working for anyone else
We work for our own benefit
We can work if we want
Or else we can just quit
That's my policy
Now only the coat is missing
I have to go to Panaiyur,
beg him somehow to act again
Otherwise everyone will
wear a steel cuff-bracelet
I don't take too much time
Because already the time is going
I'm going to announce the new branch head
- Nice preparation
- 2 days practice
That's no one else
But yours truly!
Soppu, you and I will be
sharing the same cabin
- Jolly times
- Thank you
Come on, sir
Hurry up and give me the post
Dream of a decade
My neck is waiting, sir
[overlap of surprised voices]
It's me!
You didn't bend enough
so he's the chosen one!
'Thank you, sir'
What, bro?
It's very wrong, bro
I got to know via E-mail
the external business you are into
If my chairman father-in-law gets to know
You will be totally jobless
So... zip your lips
and be quiet
Follow Chandru's good example at work
I have the last word!
Chandru
- Thank you
- Thanks, buddy
You snitched on me
and moved up the ladder, eh?
I swear, either stand
on that side of the road
Or on this side
If you stand right in the middle
A lorry won't hit you
My car will do the hit-and-run!
- Can even be AK's car!
- Okay
Merge with your 'bonda' boss
happily from now on
Soppu, I am feeling tense
Let's go and discuss
I won't come
Get lost, da!
What disrespect!
Uncle, your ID
'Uncle'
Stupid pig!
Congrats
Attend office regularly
and do your job properly
'Go back to your seats'
- Give us a treat for sure
- Yeah, sure... sure
I have to share this news with her
Where is she likely to be now?
I had enquired about a job
for bridal make-up artist
- Any leads?
- 'If there's anything I'll let you know'
Ya, please let me know, thank you
Hi, Janu
Really sorry for yesterday
No thanks
I've already apologized to you
Last night I was boozed
That word 'coward' triggered me
in the most terrible way
'Sorry'
Can we break up
with one stray incident?
Who are you?
Who are you to me first?
Okay... okay
Tell me what I should do
for your anger to subside?
I'll do it
Whatever it is
Kindly leave this place
Do not disturb me, please
Fair enough
But before that meet
my parents once before you go
- For what?
- You will soon be their daughter-in-law
Shouldn't they give the green signal?
Did I ever tell you
I wish to marry you?
In fact I never thought of you in that way
You said we can both start
a chain of beauty parlors
So I walked out of my house, that's all
You didn't come because you love me?
You want to start a business with my money
You wanted to marry some other chap
who is better than me, so you walked out
Correct?
Ranesh
You are behaving badly once more
You went with some chap last night
Did he behave properly?
Janu... Janu?
We need to talk?
That chap or me?
Decide right now
- 'Hi'
- Ja-
'You had asked him to come?'
'He's also here'
Hey! Janu
- Oh god!
- Are you okay?
Sorry
Will you marry me?
Hey! How dare you ask her to marry you!
Do you know who she is?
I don't know details of your family
- What's your status vs ours?
- I am not bothered?
I'm an orphan too
- Will you marry me?
- Bloody orphan!
I'll take good care
of you come what may
Big shot or what?
Now
'Janu, he is an orphan
with no proper family'
In the world, only love
is a solitary feeling
'So what? Will you trust him
and walk away with him?'
He stood by me
and sorted out my problem
He didn't hide behind
like the coward you were
'He is what I call 'man'
Any girl will wish to
marry an alpha male
"I just got lost somewhere"
"Don't search for me anywhere"
Buddy, gift voucher
Enjoy the honeymoon package
in Moonstay resort in Kodaikanal
Thanks, dude
"Something stirs in my heart
slitting my soul apart"
"Aeons shrink, seconds play
Time just melts away"
Love you, my wifey
"My world dissolves, a fading haze
I feel lost inside your blinding gaze"
Love you, my hubby
"No gentle tease, no soft embrace
My mind's aflame at a scorching pace"
"Neither night nor day"
"Sudden winds of change blow my way"
"Neither before nor after"
"Only today, this brand new chapter"
"No grey clouds in sight
No flash of lightning bright"
"Sudden winds of change in my sight"
"Winds of change all of a sudden"
"Honeyed drizzles softly unburden"
"The weather changes all of a sudden"
"A bud blooms in my heart unbidden"
"Even when you are not near me
I feel your presence within, soulfully"
"Not a single word you speak to me
I can still hear your lingo A to Z"
"I merge with your shadow, to be true
I get tanked with my love for you"
"I will chat with your body, mind and heart
Finally conquer my soul; never drift apart"
"You tease my dawn's cool breeze
into a blazing flame with ease"
"Where will I go, dear
without you here?"
"No gentle tease, no soft embrace
My mind's aflame at a scorching pace"
"Neither night nor day"
"Sudden winds of change blow my way"
"Neither before nor after"
"Only today, this brand new chapter"
"No grey clouds in sight
No flash of lightning bright"
"Sudden winds of change in my sight"
"The weather changes all of a sudden"
"A bud blooms in my heart unbidden"
Congratulations for
the newly married couple
Thank you so much, sir
Welcome
We were told all the couples
have been invited for dinner
No one else is here
I have already seen them yesterday
I wanted to see you in person
Aah... I mean
I hosted a candle light dinner
last night for the others
Mr Ramachandran
Yesterday was your birthday, right?
Sir
How do you know my birthday, sir?
I know everything about
my guests in my resort
A to Z
First cut the cake
Happy birthday to you
- Sir, first for my wife
- Please
My turn
You haven't registered your marriage yet?
Yes, sir
Sudden marriage
We have registered it
- Oh!
- So
We came on our honeymoon right away
Okay... okay
I'll just use the restroom and come
Looks like you have to
face a lot of problems
Sir?
- Take good care of her
- Sure, sir
Hey!
Only 2 chapters left
I'll finish reading and give it
Will anyone read detective novels
during their honeymoon?
We have to read something else now
Secrets of romance
Don't you have the habit of reading books?
I used to when I was in college
Rajesh Kumar, SuBa,
Pattukottai Prabhakar
I am mad about
Agatha Christie novels
If I start reading her book, I won't
put it down till I reach the last page
Very interesting plots
I just can't believe this, Janu
That everything will be over in a jiffy
Why?
- 'Why' means?
- Why did you say yes when I proposed?
Because you are fresh!
Whaaaat?!
Just kidding
Your approach was fresh
I saw a flash of truth in your eyes
Pcccht! Oh!
Okay, fine, shall we continue?
- Show me
- Started your play?
You wouldn't have loved
any other girl to this extent
Your eyes told me
Was it 'love at first sight'
when you saw me in the pub?
Hey! I didn't see you
in that bar for the first time
- Fraud
- Ouch!
So did you follow me to that pub?
You got me wrong
I didn't follow you
I was sitting in that club
even before you came
I saw you for the second time, that's all
But when I saw you for the first time
I thought I should marry
a girl just like you
Why?
Am I so good-looking?
You have a golden heart
I told you I saw you for the first time
in a coffee shop in ECR?
You were sharing a table
with 4 beggars and eating
We generally give alms to beggars
'Or we will buy them some food'
You sat there
treating them as equals
I have never met anyone like you
To an orphan like me
Only such a heart
will sparkle like gold
My beloved hubby
You didn't hide anything from me
The first day you met me
You opened your heart to me
The very next day after a boy meets a girl
If he proposes to her
clueless about her
Imagine what a genuine guy he must be
Will anyone miss such a trusting chap?
That's why
I trusted you and said 'yes'
I need to talk to you
from dawn to dusk
About what?
About you
About me
We can catch up tomorrow with all that
I want to talk to you today
We'll be talking lifelong
Fraud hubby
First tell me about you
The boy's name is Ramachandran
He's called Chandru
'He grew up in 'Anbu Illam'
an orphanage in Tiruvanmaiyur'
Has computer knowledge
to a certain extent
Claiming to be a software engineer
He got a job in a big firm
My parents passed away
when I was just 8 years old
After that
A man called Gopi anna
Started 'Anbu Illam'
and raised us there
To collect donation
He went to Andhra
When he was returning with the money
Some greedy fellow
Grabbed all the money he had
Pushed him from the train
Gopi anna died on the spot
Then
Railway Police
Retained his body for 2 weeks
Since no one came to claim
They cremated him
As soon as I knew
Gopi anna had died
I got really stressed
After that
I was affected mentally for 6 months
I was admitted in a rehab center
under the supervision of a psychiatrist
I was treated
That boy has taken
psychiatric treatment for 6 months
What do you mean?
Is he a mental case?
What?
Are your eyes sweating?
Ignore that, dear
That's normal sweat now and then
Okay
Don't you want to know about me?
Do you know why
I'm staying in a hostel?
You must be from a slightly
affluent family down south
So you have come to this hostel
No
I was born and brought up in Chennai
- Chennai?
- 'Yes'
Why are you in a hostel
when your family is in Chennai?
My dad decided to get me married
to a man as his second wife
My mother and I didn't agree
Next day when I wasn't at home
I got a call saying my mother fell
into the swimming pool and died
My dad killed her
Is your dad in jail now?
No
He is a minister
My dad is minister Boovaragasamy
'Your daughter has married this boy'
First day she fell in love
2nd day got married and 3rd day
they are on their honeymoon
Cha! So what?
How can I let her get away?
I'll slice every organ in her body
- Minister's son-in-law
- Didn't tell me
Akka, pure water
No, thanks
If you don't take it I will cry
'Minister's daughter is acting pricey'
- Is that a 'namaz'?
- Islamic prayer?
'He's wondering what to do
if he is subjected to an ED raid'
Whatever is destined to happen, so be it
What is destined?
Everyone will be behind bars!
Aiyo! Akka, if that happens
my fragile body can't take the torture
Why are you falling at everyone's feet?
- White skin, no?
- So what?
Her husband is right here, go away
She's glaring
Chandru, what next?
What's next?
I have to leave Janu in her hostel
Hostel? Then why did you get married?
They were supposed to stay with me
When my house owner got to know
her background, he shooed them away
We are staying up here
in our office
'Good time'
'Chandru, I have an idea'
Rent out a bungalow
fit enough for her lifestyle
Let her stay there
If in case her dad visits
He will know his daughter
is well-settled, no?
If she stays in this son of a gun's office
he will be Peeping Tom in your absence!
Where do I go for that kind of money?
Then why the eff did you
get married so impulsively?
Thanks to your rash decision
all of us are care of platform!
Ignore negativity
I know a dependable financier
He will listen to whatever I say
I can get you a loan
of any amount
'He resembles Santhana Bharati's uncle'
But you know what he will do?
He lent money to a textile shop
and when the owner did not pay up
He stripped the mannequin's sari!
Your wife looks sleek
like a mannequin doll
'He will grab her
to adorn his showcase!'
This is very risky, Chandru
Nothing can be a bigger risk
than getting married to you
You have to send money
to your orphanage every month too
You came with full faith in me
You are my only life
I can take any risk for you, don't worry
I'll take care
Getting a loan for you
isn't that tough
But you know his mannerism?
I have to go to Panaiyur for sure
Do it elsewhere, go
Egg-head, he has signed
Push the cash
- Here
- Thank you, bro
'This Govt claims to be cashless!'
This cash was the cause
of downfall for many, da
'Egg-head, am I right?'
You counted?
Amount is okay?
- Okay, buddy
- I kept up my word?
Go and settle your wife in cool comfort
Swapna's house is nearby
She got tanked, fell off her bed it seems
I'll drop in and see her
Thank you
What do you think?
Will he repay properly?
I can assure you he won't!
Are you joking?
I lent the money
on your reference
'You said he has a good paying job?'
Of course, a good job
I was supposed to get!
He snatched it from my hand
Will I twiddle my thumbs and watch?
That's why I made him borrow money
That too, from you, no?
His peace of mind has
gone for a toss now
'Why are you still as a statue?'
Smile like that Laughing Buddha
Perfect with a capital P!
'Tell me if you get any stolen laptops?'
I can refurbish, fix it, change password
and sell it for a good price
[mobile ringing]
Boss... good morning, sir
What's the update
on your daughter?
- What's your plan?
- That's why I'm in Kodaikanal now
I'll kill the boy and drag
my daughter back home
Don't do something rash and crazy
If your daughter squeals to the media
this problem will boomerang
Drag your daughter back home
and foist a case on that boy
Try and solve this problem
Okay, boss
[heaving a huge sigh]
He dumped his mobile with me
- Pcccht!
- Sir?
- Cha!
- Tea
I'm planning to buy 4 cars
and start a Travel Agency, sir
I am a little short of money, sir
'Please be large hearted
and help me out'
You told me last time
this is final
Sir, you pushed your wife
from the top of the stairs
If I had snitched you would have
lost your post and been counting bars!
- Who kept the 'bread bundle' here?
- I saw it in the car, sir
You deserve to die!
Sirrrrr...!
- Catch
- Sir
- 'Give it to Yogi bro
- Keep the key and scoot'
Don't you laugh!
Why do we need to host this party?
Tomorrow is your first birthday, no?
First birthday?
- Tomorrow is your 1st birthday as my wife?
- So what?
We went for our honeymoon
in a tearing hurry
My friends want a wedding treat
So I thought of this idea
Birthday and wedding treat combo
I've been trying to hack it for so long
What is the darn password?
[password alert tone]
Shall I share the password?
How is this laptop speaking?
'From my own hotel'
'Sitting in my car, are you
trying to steal my laptop?'
'5 Star Supermarket in ECR'
'You are sitting in the car
right in front of that parking lot'
'Behind your car'
'Turn your head and see a girl
in a pink T-shirt smoking'
'Correct?'
Hey!
Who is this saying it on the dot?
Hey Maruti
This laptop has a GPS
- I can follow you wherever you go
- Laptop belongs to your boss?
If you place it back
right where you took it from
'Good for your health'
Good for my wealth!
My boss has found out
Let's return it
- I'll lose my job
- Hey!
Are you the MD of Maruti company?
You'll be jobless if you get caught
He would have complained
to the police by now
I don't know what I'm in for
That chap has EPS or OPS
inside this laptop it seems
- EPS...OPS?
- Must be a politician
It's called GPS, you brainless fool!
- Who is he?
- You're part of Beetroot's hang
This is how dumb you'll be
Play some song
See that chap coming out
- 'Yes
- He's known to me'
Get our bags
He and I have a dealing
to sort out for a long time
I'll deal with him
You remember what we did
in Spencer's Plaza?
Just copy it to that girl
I'll handle the rest
Okay, bro
Watch me in action
- Aiyo!
- Hey!
- Bad time for you hereafter
- Brainless or what?
Are your eyes at the back of your head?
'Sorry, Chandru'
Birthday party, huh?
Are you flicking from my own car?
Key?
I'll kill you if you touch my stuff
Not me, sir
That new recruit
Shut your gob!
Whose laptop is this?
'Mr Ramachandran'
'How did you get this laptop?'
Er... who is this?
I can hear only a voice
I can't see your face
'I own the resort you stayed in
for your honeymoon in Kodaikanal'
Chakravarthy
Sir...?
Is it really you?
How did your laptop
land up in my car?
'Are you coming from
ECR 5 Star Supermarket?'
- Yes
- 'Did you see any chap?'
'Wearing a floral T-shirt
totally unconnected to that spot?'
100% right, sir
Were you also there?
'No, he stole my laptop'
'Then got cold feet he may get caught'
'He dumped it in your car and escaped'
You are lucky, sir
He left it in my car
Don't worry, sir
I'll return your laptop tomorrow, sir
'No... no... no'
'I have a very important Zoom meeting'
'I need my laptop immediately'
Okay, sir
Tell me where
I'll come and give it
'I have shared my location
in your mobile'
- 'Come there'
- Sir...?
How do you know my mobile #?
'I will never forget any couple
who has stayed in my resort'
'I know A to Z about them'
'Top to bottom'
You are razor sharp, sir
I'll come and give it
within an hour, sir
Okay then
Let's meet there
Okay, sir
Thank you
[humming]
- How long, da?
- Janu darling
A laptop got misplaced in our car
'So...?'
Shall I go and return it
in Sneha Garden?
Hey! I am so sleepy, da
To sleep alone in this new flat
'I am feeling scared'
Okay, you go to bed
'I have a spare key
I'll come soon'
Only thing is I wanted to see you
at 12 midnight as 'birthday baby'
- 'I will be back'
- Naughty fellow!
'Press 725829'
Come up
'Come to first floor'
He seems to be super tech-savvy
Sir
- Thank you, Mr Ramachandran
- It's alright, sir
Ramachandran, I have an important
video conference now
Please don't mind
- Take it
- Sir
Thank God
Sir, why are you giving me so much money?
This is much more than
the cost of your laptop
I can afford to buy another laptop
The data in this
It's my life
Excuse me
It's okay, sir
I don't want this cash
I'll take leave, sir
They just slept
instead of making out, shit!
Hey... did you come just to sleep
on your wedding night?
Get up, both of you
Key
Pcccht!
- 'Yes, sir'
- Yov!
'Go to room # 303'
Give them a wine bottle, cake and fruits
If they ask why
Tell it's our compliment
for honeymoon couples in our resort
- Okay, sir
- Sir?
I came to collect my car
keys I left behind
HEY!
See you, sir
'Press 5436'
- 'Escalation of cyber crimes'
- TV is still on
'Innocent people are victims'
'A young couple in Gujarat
were intimate in their bedroom'
'Hackers recorded this via Smart TV Camera
recorded and uploaded the video online'
'The husband's friends
who watched it on porn sites'
'...informed their friend'
'The young couple unable to bear
the humiliation, committed suicide'
'HEY!'
'You can watch a special interview by
police officer Mr Panneerselvam about this'
'In this AI age'
'All communication and electronic
devices we use on a daily basis'
'Showcase our personal life
and details to others via pictures'
'Especially wifi enabled
Smart TV, computer, laptop
'Can be hacked via camera in mobiles'
'Perpetrators can monitor
all your activities without your knowledge'
'This couple's tragic end
is a standing example'
'In your intimate private moments
is the wifi switched off?'
'Smart TV, laptop, mobile'
'Care should be taken to ensure
these devices are switched off'
'Most importantly
in public places'
'In hotels, bedrooms, spa, resorts'
'While in the toilet and washroom
you should take extra precautions'
'I have already seen them yesterday'
'I know everything about
my guests in my resort'
'I know A to Z about them
Top to bottom'
'The data in this'
'It's my life'
[startled gasp]
[telephone ringing]
- Hello?
- 'Yes, sir'
Can you connect me to room # 303?
Sorry, sir
Untimely hour
I can't disturb our guests now
'Can you try his mobile?'
He is my friend
He said you sent up
wine and cake just now
- 'Yes'
- While we were talking
We got cut off
That's why I called your line
Can you connect me, please?
Okay, sir
1 minute
I'll connect now
[telephone ringing]
'Which idiot is calling me now?'
Pccht!
Hello?
You got the wine and cake?
Yes, sir
Thanks a lot, sir
Looks like you slept early
Yes, sir
We went to bed early
because we travelled from Trichy
Thank God you sent us wine and fruits
- 'Otherwise tonight-'
- Sir
You're wrong in assuming
I'm calling from the resort
Like you, I am also
'I was a guest who stayed there'
Listen carefully
to what I'm about to share
'Your activities now'
Everything you are doing
Through that Smart TV in your room
'One fellow is watching you 'live' now'
Without telling anyone
Silently check out in the morning
- 'Sir, what are you saying?'
- I'll tell you the rest later
- 'Oh gawd! We are doomed
- What happened, da?'
'Who was it on the phone?'
'Someone is watching us
through this Smart TV camera'
What do you mean?
I'll complain to Cyber Crime immediately
- If my father gets to know we are here
- Doesn't matter
[mobile ringing]
If you complain to the cops now
The very next minute
'Your making out video'
'...will go viral on all WhatsApp groups
in Srirangam temple neighborhood'
'Seduction sensation by
priest's daughter and flower stall boy'
That will be the Breaking News
'Your various poses and positions'
Everyone will drool over
it on social media
And follow suit
We got trapped here
What will we do?
Watch us die also
Wow!
Interesting
'Live' suicide video
Finish!
[telephone ringing]
- Hello?
- Yov!
- 'Sir?'
- Room 303 got a call now
'What is that number?'
'1 minute, sir'
Ramachandran
I will close your chapter
once and for all tonight
I'll perform her funeral rites
like I did for her mother
If you come to my place
of your own accord quietly
It is good for everyone
[mobile ringing]
- Hello?
- Yov!
Why are you dragging that case?
Finish him off and close the case
Hey! I can't dance to your tune
'You are also under strong suspicion'
He has given a statement
you have killed your wife
Nothing can be done with that statement
Before you take action
I'll ensure you're sacked
Sir, phone
Wonder who this surprise element is!
- Hello
- 'Sir, SI speaking'
On Pallangi mountain peak
we have found the corpse of a girl
She has a ring with
the initials JC, sir
You there!
Is your wife wearing any ring?
Yes
Janaki Chandru
She wears a ring with JC engraved on it
Why, sir?
Nothing
Okay, I'll come over there right away
You fell in love and
got married, that's fine
Why did you both fight?
Back to Kodaikanal
Why did you land there?
'It was Janaki's birthday party'
Last we saw Janaki was at work
Then you have hidden her from us
I think bro has her locked up
till she is 3 months pregnant
That's called 'work from home'
Am I right, Soppu?
Hey!
Why did you call us
when you both have long faces?
- I know
- Any issue?
He went out last night
and returned only this morning
He went out again
and came back just now
'Is that so?'
He has this doleful look on his face
He hasn't even wished me
since this morning
Bro, what's up?
Nothing
Work pressure
Boss called me this morning
and screamed his throat hoarse
Who?
That chap who said you should keep
this company's flag flying high?
That zipper-mouth chap?
'So...?'
Couldn't he even wish me
for my birthday?
Bro, a boss is a like
a pet dog in a bungalow
Barking at every passer-by
except the owner
'Why be upset about this triviality?'
Wish her for her birthday, bro
Happy birthday
Did he wish his wife?
Sounded more like wishing you!
Let's celebrate
He's wished her, no?
Get the cake
Come on, make merry
Jumping to booze! She's the light
of her house, poor husband of hers!
Sitting like the captain who has lost
the Finals, come on, bro
- Happy birthday to you
- Go closer to her
'Cake looks delicious'
'Patched up!'
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday to Janu
'May God bless you, Janu'
Happy birthday to you
'May God bless you, dear'
Bro
Cheers!
You're downing it like
'omam' water in a single gulp?
Does your husband know?
He's a teetotaler
Good for nothing!
Useless, eh?
Then for 'that'...?
- Even for that
- Then what do you-
'Who is that?'
Who is it?
Happy birthday wishes
'Already in a chaotic mess'
Come in, boys
Flat bought with our loan
Enjoy yourselves
Let's see who stops us
Beetroot head!
Why did you barge in here?
Hey! Move aside
- Get up
- It's too quiet
- Play some song
- Doing, man
Beer isn't even cool
'Ask that to the Govt, egg-head!'
Chandru
Why did they come here?
They must have joined
your wife's birthday party
Sir, this is my home
Not a bar for some random rowdies
'How dare you!'
You took an advance
from me to buy this flat
You are splurging my money right from
the bed you make out to your swanky car
How dare you insult by
calling us 'random rowdies'
Aren't you taking interest for your loan?
My foot!
He promised to repay in 3 months
'Last month I bought a car
This month I bought beer'
'He hasn't even
paid up the interest'
Ask him to pay back
interest + capital
I will leave immediately
If he doesn't pay
we will camp here
Yov! Egg-head
Continue, boys
- 'Listen to me
- Play the song'
'You were too rude
and spoke in haste, Chandru
'You keep quiet
I'll handle this'
Hi Raghavi
'Hi Janu, happy birthday'
'Where's the party?'
Don't rub it in!
I'm wishing I hadn't been born!
Hereafter this is my house
Ask all the free-loaders to get out
'You're in such a royal mess
Won't you ask us for help?'
'Hang up'
Hey Beetroot!
Why are you hassling us
on a special day?
Get out of here
Yogi, listen carefully
You referred him to me
You make him pay
and I'll gladly leave
Please listen to me
Leave now, we'll discuss later
What did you tell me that day?
You wanted to take revenge on him
for snatching your promotion
- You ensnared him in my trap
- Shut up, man
You pay up
I'll leave
We'll discuss it
Not today, go now
If a husband lacks the ability
to keep his wife happy
- Ask him to gift her to someone
- Watch your tongue!
[overlap pf angry voices]
'Why is he coming here?'
- How much is due to you?
- 12 lakhs
Will you hand it now?
Who is this?
He seems to be a bigger financier than me
Janaki's ex boyfriend
You can take up any amount of loans
You can rock & roll with
anyone you like and have fun
Your wife has
...a good back-up!
Hey! You got your money, right?
Better move your butt at once
Hey! Collect the cash
Even if you had told me
when I came to wish you at 12 midnight
I wouldn't have let it get this ugly
What is he saying?
Did you call him?
No, I told Raghavi-
You were in a tearing hurry
You are suffering now
Not even bothered
today is my birthday
You hit me in front of our guests
You will regret this a lot
Janaki
Chandru has come
Ignore him
Focus on your work
What, Chandru?
You hid it from us all along
- What did I hide?
- Boss wants to see you
He will inform you
Why does the boss want to see me?
Sir, why is my cabin locked?
I was asked to sack you
Take
Termination order
Sir, why did you terminate me?
What wrong did I do?
You know how many will support me?
Security, be near me
For 6 months you have
taken psychiatric treatment
You have hidden it in your resume
You know how big a crime this is?
That happened long ago
Why bring it up now?
Look here, IT employees are already
affected by work pressure and depression
'You have taken treatment
with a psychiatrist for 6 months'
You can stoop to any extent of brutality
I even gave you a promotion
If chairman knows this
I'll lose my seat of power
Sir, don't blabber like a lunatic
- Yes, I am a lunatic!
- Everyone knows that
- You want coffee, sir?
- Get me ginger tea
- Where did I pause?
- You are a loose!
- Yes, I l(o)ose!
- Tell this to him
That's right
I am a lunatic
'He's glaring at you
with his eyes shut'
Don't play the fool with me
- Sir
- Yes?
Tell me if you can
fault me in my work, sir
- Catch him
- Don't tie up unrelated stuff
Sir, you're making a huge blunder
We should sack this lunatic
and occupy his seat
- I am the MD
- 'I am back'
Hold him tight
Chandru
Let go of him
Hey let him go
Hands off
Move aside, da
Are you brainless?
Is this how you treat a person?
Bro
We are your friends
and we knew only now
Who could have snitched?
'Under the supervision of a psychiatrist'
'I was treated'
I shared it only with Janaki
- Janu
- Janaki?
'You hit me in front of our guests'
'You will regret this a lot'
You are in a confused state
Go to your room
I'll find out the truth
Go, bro
"Don't follow me
O' love, just let me be"
You trusted me whole heartedly
Shouldn't I take good care of you?
"Don't spread tender love & care
as memories everywhere"
"My bond, my soul-companion
Don't melt into oblivion"
Where is Chandru?
What happened to him?
Why are you bothered?
You branded him as mad
and wrecked his life
I gave up everything, trusting him
Chandru was wrong to have hit you
Accusing him as psycho,
will you sack him?
Janaki did not squeal about Chandru
Her minister father
All of you ganged up
and separated us, no?
"Our life illusive
Like a mirage elusive?"
Sorry, Chandru
Your profile is already blacklisted
I don't think, going forward,
you'll get a job in any company
"I wanted you as a blessing in my life
Yet you gifted me only pain and strife"
"A boon from above
My one & only love"
"Don't follow me
O' love, just let me be"
"Don't spread tender love & care
as memories everywhere"
- Hey get out... go
- Throw all their belongings on the road
Shut the gate and lock it
Yov Beetroot!
Do you have a conscience?
Where will these orphan kids go?
You steal laptops
and sells it on the sly
You're talking about 'conscience'?
Get lost!
Correct indeed
Let's go
Won't you pick up Janaki's call?
She was chucked out of your flat
She has gone back to her hostel
Chandru bro, after this weekend
the school will work as usual
'I will lose my job along with you
if they find out I sheltered these kids'
'What do we do now?'
"Only when buried deep below
seed and root will sprout and grow"
Take this money and arrange
for a proper orphanage for the children
If you do as I say
I'll give you some more money
You know very well
You end what you began
"Only from old leaves dried and dead"
What should I do?
"Fresh new branches sprout and spread"
'Divorce deed'
You sign this, augur well for
your orphan siblings and Janaki
"Can the heart endure the pain?"
If you want her to be happy
get out of her life, da
"Can hearts endure this weary quest
with deep wounds as Fate's fiery test?"
"Even when endless pain does not heal
my mind and heart cling to that feel"
Why should we both sign-
Chandru
I'll sign the divorce deed
as per the minister's wish
Think deep and make the right decision
"Stand and fly, beyond the blue"
At least let her be happy
Janaki, will you go for
a bridal make up in Kodaikanal?
"You changed your direction for me"
They are willing to pay 1 lakh
"To distance yourself from our journey?
To change into a cloud cottony?"
"A rain of fire falls on my soul"
"A burning cold that takes its toll"
"I can hear Love's lament"
"In the bleary distance; insistent"
"I am not by your side now
You are not far away anyhow"
Chandru
"We merge as one
to be lost in this confusion"
Chandru
"Don't follow me
O' love, just let me be"
"Don't spread tender love & care
as memories everywhere"
"My bond, my soul-companion
Don't melt into oblivion"
"Like distant dreams
Don't hide from life's streams"
"Like tales burning in the breeze
inscribed by Time with gentle ease"
"Will you and me be apart?
Love confined to our heart"
"Our life illusive
Like a mirage elusive?"
Bro... bro... bro
Take it slow and easy
Drinking for the first time
You've crossed 3 beers!
I sold my soul
I have settled my children
I'm not worried even if I die now
If such a situation arises
it will be a great loss
to Thalapathy fans!
Forgive me
I am the sole cause for your misery
You got into this mess
because you got the promotion meant for me
'You know why I got mad at you?'
My laptop dealing-wheeling
You mailed our boss
You stopped my promotion
and I wanted to take revenge
I urged you take a loan
I wanted to make that loan-shark
hike up the interest rates
And humiliate you
in front of everyone
I wanted to pour
diluted cow dung on your head!
But that Ranesh found out about your loan
He brought that beetroot head
into your house
And created friction
between you and your wife
'Ranesh planned and drove
a wedge between you both'
Your wife is not at fault
I am to blame for everything
Please forgive me
- You are the reason for everything
- Yes
But you are wrong about the reason, bro
- Correct
- I don't get it
You are the reason for everything
But not for the reason
you have in your mind
Why are you quoting 'Thug Life' to me?!
- All over
- Finished 4 bottles?
Hiding the bottle at his feet
and trying to fool me
You brought a beer bottle in your pant?
Booze it!
- Hey!
- Bitter? Not cool enough?
Who do I get a burning sensation?
Garnish with some snacks
My stomach is burning, da
- What is this brand?
- Phenyl
Hey!
Bro, he drank phenyl
instead of beer
- Floor cleaner?
- Don't know what will happen to him
Are you brainless or what?
Can't tell beer from phenyl?
Why do you even booze then?
- How will I know-
- So you'll gulp it down?
Now you're hiccupping like
a python that swallowed a cow
Will you jinx me by inviting
Saturn with its rings?
I was forced to vacate
2 houses due to your ruckus
I am choking, save me
Am I the bait, caught between
repentance and dying of mistaken intake?
My house owner is already crucifying me
- Like mishandling a wife!
- I'll bring a few boys
No, I'll bring 4 boys to lift him
- Keep an eye on him
- Call the ambulance
Forgive me, Janu
Forget Janu, you madcap
If you save me
I'll bring you a Jessi!
'6 demons are dancing on my throat'
'I am going to Kodaikanal
for a bridal make-up assignment'
'Same Moonstay resort
we went for our honeymoon'
- 'Same room
- Same room, huh?'
'I have to tell you something
very important in person'
'Meet me there, please'
Buddy... hey
6 demons have escalated to 8 now
None of the boys are willing to help
You go by yourself to the graveyard
Like how I got VTV Ganesh's voice
You should get Mottai Rajendran's voice
I didn't expect you
to come for this wedding, Janu
If I knew this was
Ranesh's cousin's wedding
I wouldn't have accepted this booking
I think you're done
Will you come along?
In case of any touch-up?
Sure
You look lovely
- Hi
- Just a minute
Okay
I'll wait over there
Call me if you need help
'Hey Chandru'
'What is this new habit?'
'If his daughter marries
the guy she has fallen for'
'The father will summon his henchmen
and kill the poor guy'
'Your father has too much
weight and pull'
- 'Minister!
- Shut up! Come'
Hi Janu
Ranesh, please stop following me
You did us a great favor!
- I am not denying it
- Janu, listen to me
- I'll somehow repay you
- Just hear me out
If we meet again
my life will be ruined, Ranesh
- Hey
- Janu... Janu... Janu
- Let go of me
- I should've ousted you when you barged in
Why are you here?
Uncle, he's hitting Ranesh
- 'Grab him
- Chandru, what are you doing?'
- Chandru'
- Someone, hit him
- Let go of him
'Chandru'
Let go of me
Bloody tramp!
- Chandru, what are you doing?
- Drunken dog!
How dare you hit our Ranesh
at our wedding venue?
Hey! Mind your language
He didn't know
Sorry
Let's go
I didn't hit him unknowingly
I knew what I was doing
- You didn't expect me here, right?
- Chandru
Let's stop everything with this
What do we stop?
- Who is he?
- Sir
Janu is my wife
He is her friend
He wanted to somehow marry her
But I married Janu
the next day after we met
He's trying to split us
Fraud!
Ranesh, what the hell is this, man?
You told me Janaki is divorced
You want to marry her
Okay, she's a minister's daughter
We agreed because
this is common nowadays
How disgusting can this get!
'Is she divorced or now?'
Ranesh, what is this?
- Is it true?
- Yes, Janu
I can't bear to see you suffer
'I'm willing to marry you anytime'
That's why I asked my cousin
to specially book you and bring you here
All lies
Father and son are scheming
For your money
You're right, da
So be it
You took the money from me
promising to divorce and left
Chandru?
Did you ask me for a divorce
after taking money from him?
Yes
How much
I loved you
You settled for money
You too?!
'All of you joined hands
and killed a girl so unjustly'
- Make way for him
- Okay, sir
Push everyone aside
'Ask the Press people to move'
'Sir... sir, did the police hit you?'
Sir... sir
- Janu... Janu
- Don't come near
Janu... Janu
Janu
- 'Move aside
- Why are you pushing us, sir?'
'Allow us inside, sir'
'We need to go in and enquire'
'We need to know what happened'
- This isn't my Janaki
- Why do you say so?
She has a tattoo of Lord Rama on her wrist
- 'What?'
- This is NOT my Janaki
'If she isn't Janaki'
Who is this girl?
They have kidnapped my wife
claiming some corpse to be Janaki
Hand in glove with the minister
the police force is trying to frame me
Somehow find my Janaki for me
- Save her
- Take him away
He is speaking the truth
- Another body has been found here
- That's right, man
That's minister Boovaragasamy's driver
Is that murder or suicide, sir?
We have just now started
our investigation, be patient
- Move
- Give us an update, sir
'I told you these cops
are hiding something'
'Like Chandru said
the minister is the culprit'
'He pushed the driver, da'
All of us have got a video
from the dead driver's mobile, sir
The dead man's mobile
is with the sender of this video
- 'Whaaat?'
- Come here
'Vanakkam'
I shot the video of minister Boovaragasamy
pushing the driver to his death
- What is he saying?
- I don't understand
By resorting to pride-driven killing
of his own daughter
Minister framed that innocent chap
I saw Chandru sob inconsolably
That's why I've come to
extend maximum help from my side
Is the minister linked with this case, sir?
Is it a case of 'conceited homicide', sir?
Have you arrested Chandru
to cover up his crime?
Is the Police Propoganda wing
for politicians?
Minister has been dismissed from his post
A team has been sent to arrest him
We have asked them to check
all the CC TV cameras in Kodaikanal
If we get any other information
we will inform you
[overlap of queries]
'Breaking News'
'Minister Boovaragasamy has
been ousted from his post'
Sir, let go of him
Sir, did you kill your daughter?
My daughter is my whole world
I killed my wife and my driver
But I didn't kill my daughter
Please save her
Do you know who the murderer is?
Move, I say
This huge a bungalow
to stay for 10 days in a year!
- When is your owner expected, man?
- Only next month, sir
- This is the cam here?
- Yes, sir
TN 09 BV 0001
- Isn't that the minister's daughter?
- Yes, sir
Search for owner's detail
in Vahan portal
1 minute
This is Moonstay Resort owner
Chakravarthy's car, sir
- Are you sure?
- Yes, sir
The case is taking a different turn
- I must inform this to SP office at once
- Yes, sir
- Bring the laptop
- Okay, sir
[mobile ringing]
Start the jeep
'Raman searches for Sita'
'They exchanged mutual glances of love'
'Love marriage in 1 day
is entangled in a mess now'
'Has Janaki been kidnapped or killed?'
- 'Kaliyuga Ramayan returns'
- Heard the News?
'What will happen now?'
What next?
All of us joined hands
in getting them married
We will be put behind bars
and beaten black and blue
That's why I booked a room and
boozing by myself while I'm still free
Where are you?
'I'm going to my parents' house'
'It is good to get married, no?'
To get married is good news
But it should be managed properly
Otherwise a whole lifetime
will be damaged!
'I had chest pain whole of last night
Chest pain?
Did you consult a doctor?
'Hmmm, I did'
What did the doctor say?
Doctor said 'wow!'
'Doctor said 'wow?!'
Is the doctor a male or a female?
'Obviously male!'
Hereditary practitioner of Siddha medicine
'Hey chee!
The doctor is my husband'
Huh? He came back?
You said 'husband'
He said 'wow' as if
it was a first time for him?
- Reason for that?
- 'Naughty!'
Move, I say
Sir, look on all sides
They are refusing to let us enter
Hey come... come
Let's tag along with the police
'Hey, stay behind'
- 'You can't go there'
- This way, sir
- 'Where are you coming? Move
- Stop them'
- Where?
- Here, sir
Praise be to Lord Shiva
'Manager is fleeing'
- 'Move aside, sir
- Let me take a video'
Who is the manager here?
I'm in no way
connected to this, sir
I was transferred here
because the former managed embezzled
Where is the owner's house?
I was told he lives
near the lake area, sir
- No one knows his whereabouts, sir
- Where did you say?
I said 'lake area', sir
Come, sir
I know
How does he know?
Sir, Chakravarthy and I
got divorced 6 years ago
Why did you call me for an inquiry?
Aren't you the only relation
of Mr Chakravarthy?
A couple staying at his resort
have been killed
He has hidden the body in the premises
We suspect he may have pushed
another girl from the mountain top
We found a Benz symbol
next to this body
Doesn't Chakravarthy own a Benz car?
Minister's daughter is also missing
May I know the reason for your divorce?
I am not compelling you
But the smallest piece of information
you give may help us crack this case
He is a psycho, sir
He likes to see everything
in 'Live' action
He took a video of us being intimate
without my knowledge
He will be watching it secretly, sir
When I am in the shower
Even when I use the restroom
When my younger sister visited us
he did the same to her
I hit him with my slipper
and walked out of the house
Did you tell this in court?
'I will grant you divorce'
If I tell this in court
He threatened
...to upload all our videos, sir
My sister had just got engaged
That's why
I kept this information to myself
I got my divorce
and distanced myself silently
Good morning, sir
Have you traced
Chakaravarthy's call history?
Yes, sir, 2 weeks ago
He has called the resort manager
in Kodaikanal from that mobile
It was switched off
And is activated again
in Dubai this morning
Dubai?
Chakravarthy's mobile
...has been slipped into the luggage
of a plumber Abdullah without his knowledge
Did you enquire about Abdullah?
Yes, sir
Completely enquired about him
Clean history
Any information about Chakravarthy's car?
Yes, sir, his car is parked
on the roadside near Madurai airport
Check all passenger lists
in all airports for his name
Pass on the News formally to Interpol
- Yes, sir
- Inform the Press also
'Breaking News'
'Shocking twist in the disappearance
of minister's daughter'
'Moonstay resort Chakravarthy is a culprit'
'Serial killings in a resort in Kodaikanal'
'Is Moonstay resort owner a serial killer?'
'A separate task force
to nab killer Chakravarthy'
'Announcement by Commissioner'
If you look at it fair and square
Ranesh kidnapped Janaki
But the police claim it is Chakravarthy
The cops always finds out
only in the climax
But I cracked it before them
Come
See this
Look
That Nick-Nose has stalked Janaki
and taken photos and videos
Next
He has taken a snap
of himself in his jockey!
- See
- Is this Ranesh's Apple Laptop?
Yes, da
Take a good look
How did you open without a password?
Hey! I am an expert in that
You could've told me lying down
Murugadoss sir told Vijay sir
to stand up and say it
- Why are you saying it?
- His assistant told me, so I'm saying
Come to the point
Ranesh's long standing wish
is to marry Janaki
- Yes
- Janaki is worth 3 billion
Somehow he wanted to grab
So he paid Beetroot
And conspired to split Chandru and Janaki
He made her come to Kodaikanal
Made the police nab Chandru
He kidnapped Janaki
This is the synopsis
Boss, then this Chakravarthy?
He's as innocent as a child!
He is not connected with this case at all
The cops went in search
of Janaki to his resort, no?
He got caught in that scenario
- That's all
- You know so much, right?
Inform the police and get
award and acclaim
Listen
All this name & fame, function
Public events, audio function
I won't even step out of this bungalow
I'm steeped in pressure
Should Janaki die
because you are busy?
I will definitely inform the police
You intend snitching?
Kathir, hold this gun
- This is a cell phone
- Imagine it is a gun!
You have to handle everything
See you?
Okay, bye
- Sir, 1 minute
- What is it?
You have a more important job
than this, I think
We will spin a tale and pin it on you
and usurp your position
How many hurdles would I have crossed
to reach this Hall of Fame!
I won't die so soon, da
Where are you going now?
To have a beer, brainless fellow
You fall for beer
I'll call the cops
- Hello?
- Sir, are you brain-dead or what?
'Won't you nab the original culprit?'
Do you know the main culprit in
minister's daughter Janaki's case?
Janaki's friend Ranesh
What do you mean?
I've sent all the photos
from Ranesh's laptop, kindly check
How do you know his laptop password?
Our man's speciality is hacking
laptops belonging to others
That's why our boss
deprived him of a promotion
'If you are so doubtful
I'll share my location'
Come and check for yourself
Yes, 'live' location
He isn't believing me?
- Whom did you call?
- I called the police
- To save Janaki
- Who will save us?
- Rascal!
- Don't hit me
- Did he ask you?
- Take back your gun
You misused my gun
- Come out now
- 'Live' location will go wrong
Go and hide in Swapna's house
Do you already know
resort owner Chakravarthy?
Yes, sir
You never told me till now
You never asked me
Oho!
'Will you tell only if asked?'
How do you know him?
Sir, when we were staying in his resort
He called us to his guest house for dinner
I met him then
Then?
Then the night before Janu's birthday
He called me
Why?
He said it was simply to wish Janu
You should have told me
all this much earlier
Sir, how will I know he will follow
all his guests and meet them?
Do you know who made you lose your job?
I know, sir
- Who?
- Janu's father, the minister
He threatened my boss
and made him sack me
He snitched about my personal life too
Listening to your story
I feel sad
Sorry
Knowing I did my bit of thrashing
'I feel even more sad'
Pull over to the side
I need to smoke a cigarette
Don't worry about anything
'I'm like your own brother'
Like Hanuman to Lord Rama
This Hanumanth is for Ramchandran
Even if you kill hereafter
Come to me
I'll protect you
How much
I loved you
You too?!
Hey!
What's your problem?
You are hiding something from me
Deny it by swearing
on our baby in my womb!
I wanted to share this
with you face to face
We've made a baby, da
'I have made a grave blunder, Janu
The biggest blunder ever'
'If you come to my place
of your own accord quietly'
'It is good for everyone'
I'm coming
'What shall we do now?'
After indulging in such heinous crimes
Are you asking me what to do?
If what I am doing is wicked
What about your misdeeds?
If a girl somewhere bends
If her dress shifts a bit
don't you ogle shifty eyed?
Don't you get pleasure viewing
stories of celebrities' private lives?
Aren't you curious to know
what would have happened?
When it is gossip about others
'Sticking out your tongue'
'Don't you yap asking for more?'
Porn sites are the most viewed world over
Then all the viewers are culprits, no?
I have the same crooked mind
common in everyone
Are you justifying yourself
after playing dirty?
I could have easily gone to the police now
But 1000s of couples
are staying in your resort
Not wanting to expose your shameful crime
and rob them of mental peace, I didn't go
If you continue this crime
I won't even let you think, da
Then for your crime?
'If you hadn't warned them
they would have made out one more time'
'And slept blissfully in ignorance'
Your phone call compelled them
to hang themselves
Now tell me, Mr Ramachandran
'Who is the bigger culprit?'
You or me?
Hey! Why are you getting so tense?
Already this video will be
uploaded in Dark Web
'For 'live' streaming'
I've clinched a deal for 5 billion
Now your video will go worldwide
And viewers will enjoy in the web site
A small surprise for you
'Goodbye'
This should not be exposed
to the outside world
If it is, many couples
will lose their peace of mind
"Like many risible people"
"Like many men and women comical"
"Like so many absurd people"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to the foolish games they play?"
"Like many risible people"
"Like many men and women comical"
"Like so many absurd people"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to their follies in any which way?"
"Did you think that of me?"
"Will I be so stupid and silly?"
"Did you belittle me really
thinking so little of me?"
"Come on"
"I'm da illest in the business
Its a battle of resistance"
"Got ur name inside my hit list
I'll be brutal I'll be vicious"
"I'm the kraken I'm malicious"
"I'll be crackin' apparitions"
"Gotchu lock up now submission"
"Gotch your aim & I'm not missin'"
"Hey man! Are you ready to play?"
"Cuz I'm-a burn you into ashes
If you come in my way"
"Pray"
"I'll be coming back for all of you all"
"Ain't nobody gonna
Gonna gonna make me fall"
"In directions eight I held sway
You fell into a death trap as my prey"
"I have no army to back my play
I'll fight this battle in my own way"
"Even if hurt, I stand relentless
Not fall to the ground defenseless"
"I decided to close the chapter
of this senseless beast forever"
"Like many risible people"
"Like many men and women comical"
"Like so many absurd people"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to the foolish games they play?"
"Like many risible people"
"Like many men and women comical"
"Like so many absurd people"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to their follies in any which way?"
[Telugu] Bro, 1 quarter
Cash... cash
"Ain't nobody gonna
Gonna gonna make me fall"
- I don't have lesser denomination
- It's okay
"Did you think I would fall prey
to their follies in any which way?"
to the foolish games they play?"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to their follies in any which way?"
"Ain't nobody gonna
Gonna gonna make me fall"
"People whose only goal
is to search for their next meal"
"Those who indulge in gossip
With petty talk upon their lip"
"As a result their weary minds so wilted
Left in constant mental despair silted"
"Savoring cruel deeds
to cause others pain"
"They grew old and grey
with nothing to gain"
"Then succumb and slip
into Fate's death-grip"
"Like so many absurd people"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to the foolish games they play?"
"Did you think that of me?"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to their follies in any which way?"
"With skill & logic, I'll plan your downfall
I'll close your chapter once and for all"
"Mercilessly I'll hunt you down"
"I have a plan to bury you underground
I'll make you nameless, no trace found"
"No mercy for you; relentless"
"I'll negate the curses
of your sins countless"
"I planned to kill, fueled by fury
You fell into the trap voluntary"
"Your atrocious antics I'll wipe away
Double-fold a price you will pay"
"For a man who sold his soul guiltlessly
Your body will float in a crimson sea"
"No way can you save your head
In bits & pieces rest in peace-ful dread"
"I'm da wrath and I'm da
Karma that come around you"
"Now better be careful
I'm above people"
"I'm grim reaper 4 u
I am the last that you will see"
"So pray to God 4 mercy"
"Killing the sentiment
All of a sudden now (hey)"
"Ain't nobody gonna make me fall"
"Did you think I would fall prey?"
"Ain't nobody gonna make me fall?"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to the foolish games they play?"
to their follies in any which way?"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to the foolish games they play?"
to their follies in any which way?"
"Will I be so stupid and silly?"
"Did you think I would fall prey
to the foolish games they play?"
Hey Chandru
Where did you disappear whole night?
You didn't pick my call either?
Chandru
Sorry, Janu
I'm not in a state of mind
to talk to you
Chandru
Chandru!
'I have to talk to you'
Wait, 1 minute
'Chandru'
'I wanted it to be
just you and me on my birthday'
Good morning, sir
All that's fine
I presume you are alone
Yes, sir
The couple who stayed in our resort #303
'Committed suicide'
[in Chakravarthy's voice]
- What are you saying, sir?
- They are related to me
I was the one who got them married
without their parents' knowledge
That's why I sent them wine and cake
'As soon as their parents knew
they sent me a voice message last night'
'And hanged themselves'
'I saw the message only this morning'
'That's why I called you immediately'
'Sir, if this leaks out
we will be in solid trouble'
'Resort's reputation will be ruined, sir'
What do you suggest?
'I can lug the bodies tonight and
push them from the mountain top'
Stupid
'Then post post-mortem will reveal
they died last night'
'The police will trace them
to our resort easily'
'Everything will be publicized
including their suicide'
- 'What should I do, sir?
- Listen
Place that boy's body in the freezer
in our resort without anyone knowing
'Shift that girl's body into
the freezer in my guest house tonight'
If the police get wind of this
I will be behind bars, sir
I will handle all that
Update in our system as if
the couple checked out this morning
Just take the money
from the counter
Don't whisper a word to anyone
Go into hiding for a month
I will handle everything else
I'll do as you say, sir
Then
Sack my security at home,
servants, entire staff
Okay, sir
If I go to the police station
The cops will want to know my motive
I cannot confess the bare truth!
'If I spill the beans'
I will be ruining the peace of mind
of all the couples in the resort
Carrying this huge guilt within me
I can't live with you happily
When the children in the orphanage
were ousted out
I needed money to
settle them comfortably somewhere
That's why I took the money from Ranesh
That wasn't the sole reason
I thought you'll be safe with him
'I thought he would've reformed'
But he joined hands with that financier
greedy to grab your inheritance
And created a furore
He used that cousin who got married now,
sacked me and also blacklisted me
He threatened the financier
and bought the orphanage
And made the children homeless
That's why I came here and hit him
What else could I do? Tell me
Hey!
I flipped for your unconditional affection
Add love of the purest kind, da
Not knowing how to
demonstrate your affection
You were trying to express it
by buying me a flat and car
Those times, I knew only your love
instead of the debt we were steeped in
Even now
Everyone around you should be happy
You want me to be happy
This is what you are thinking even now
How can I be happy
if I am away from you?
Listen
Whom did you kill?
A thug who films couple's intimate moments
without their knowledge and mints money
A criminal with a crooked bent of mind
A murderer who forced an innocent couple
ruthlessly to hang themselves to death
Had he been alive, he would've
exposed all these private videos online
Many more couples would've resorted
to suicide unable to bear the shame
You have saved all of them
Why should you be branded a murderer for
weeding out a poisonous plant from society?
He has to pay for his sins
We should reveal to this society
his true colors of being a cruel beast
Everyone should hunt him down to kill him
Think how we can change
this killing to serve our purpose
Won't Andhra Railway Police
identify his body?
'Railway Police held on for 2 weeks'
And then presuming it
to be an orphan cremated him
Will no one search for Chakravarthy?
That's why I have placed
a dead body in his resort
And one at his residence
Chakravarthy is missing
So everyone will assume he killed
this couple and went into hiding
Some random dead couple
Chakravarthy missing
This won't do to cover your tracks
If the police find out
Chakravarthy is dead
...all the guests at
the resort will be in trouble
'No one should trace Chakravarthy'
What if the minister's
daughter is missing?
If her kidnapper is Chakravarthy?
If Chakravarthy is branded
as a serial killer?
If we make the entire police department
hunt high and low for him?
Only then we can live in peace
That girl has to wear your dress
You change now
'That house is monitored by CCTV'
'You walk past and
I'll shove you into the car'
Do you have the key?
'I took the key from
his house on that day itself'
- This is the girl who committed suicide
- My God!
You exchange your dress
with that corpse
- You want me to?
- Hurry up!
Remember we came here for our honeymoon?
- Did you take your mobile?
- Yes, I did
Give me your mobile
- What are you doing?
- Mercedes symbol
Clue to show Chakravarthy was here
Remove your ring
Take
Take your wedding chain off
No, I don't want to
Okay, leave it
Hold her feet
Sorry
'Don't be scared
I'll lock up the house'
No one can enter
I'll go to the resort after parking
the car near Madurai airport
I'll come and rescue you
within 24 hours, I promise
Love you, my wifey
Love you, my hubby
'Someone will come in search
of Janaki for the bridal make-up'
'Someone has to'
'Where is Janaki?'
'What are you doing
in the room meant for Janaki?'
'All of us are waiting
for her in the wedding hall'
'Everyone is furious
after what you did last night'
'Janu?'
'I can see Janaki's novel'
Hey! She isn't here
She must be at the hall
Go and see properly
'Chee! Fraud'
"Ain't nobody gonna make me fall?"
"Did you think I would fall prey?"
subtitled by rekhs
calibrated at APInternational
Tell me what happened?
Record
That night, Chandru and I
got into a huge fight
I was feeling miserable
I got so fed up and
I walked out in a huff
As I was walking,
a white Benz car halted next to me
Someone got out of the car
Sprayed something on my face
He dragged me into the car
I fainted almost immediately
When I opened my eyes...
I had been kidnapped
and held captive for 2 days
I knew only now when Chandru told me
Can you identify the kidnapper?
No, sir
He was masked
I couldn't see his face
Have you nabbed my kidnapper, sir?
He parked the car at the airport and
escaped abroad on a duplicate passport
We will nab that serial killer very soon
Framed as the killer
Chandru took a terrible beating
Poor man!
It's okay, sir
'Sorry, Chandru'
You seem to be a loving couple
Look forward to a new future together
pushing the past behind as a nightmare
- All the best
- Thank you, sir
Thank you, sir
Love you, my hubby
Love you, my wifey
"Sudden winds of change in my sight"
"Honeyed drizzles softly unburden"
"The weather changes all of a sudden"
"A bud blooms in my heart unbidden"
"Even when you are not near me
I feel your presence within, soulfully"
"Not a single word you speak to me
I can still hear your lingo A to Z"
"I merge with your shadow, to be true
I get tanked with my love for you"
"I will chat with your body, mind and heart
Finally conquer my soul; never drift apart"
"You tease my dawn's cool breeze
into a blazing flame with ease"
"Where will I go, dear
without you here?"
"No gentle tease, no soft embrace
My mind's aflame at a scorching pace"
"Neither night nor day"
"Sudden winds of change blow my way"
"Neither before nor after"
"Only today, this brand new chapter"
"No grey clouds in sight
No flash of lightning bright"
"Sudden winds of change in my sight"
"The weather changes all of a sudden"
"A bud blooms in my heart unbidden"
"Sudden winds of change in my sight"