Daniel, I know.
I know you are doing something.
You ain't doing that much entertaining.
What are you doing?
I know you were doing something.
Night after night.
What are you doing?
Wait, no.
Okay.
Am I crazy?
Maybe I'm crazy.
What are you doing!
Job was a man who
knew what suffering was.
But yet his faith was not cast away.
That's right, that's right.
We must learn to endure hardship
and trust God through
every single situation.
Like the word, the word says, be watchful.
Stand firm in your faith.
Act like men and be strong.
Don't allow opposition
and distress to take hold of your life.
Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
Remain faithful and never waver.
Yes, sir.
Stand firm in your faith.
Praise the Lord.
Hey.
Just wanted to let the
kids see you before we go.
Papa!
Hey.
Thank you, Viv.
You know it's the holiest of pleasures
to see you and my grand babies.
Of course.
Great sermon today!
How are you doing?
I'm good, I'm good! - That's good.
Sir.
Give me a minute, V.
I'll be right outside.
Oh, Pops we can...
No, no. - We can go.
No, let the kids play.
That's why the toys are over here for them.
Okay.
You wanna color?
Yeah.
Are you ready?
What you got?
Oh my god.
Oh, you've already started.
How may I help you, Mathis?
Yeah, well listen.
The church has seen much growth
since Anthony has taken
over the youth ministry.
Yeah.
Five baptisms last month.
My son is doing very well.
Yeah.
However, with these bills stacking up,
how are we supposed to keep the doors open
for our younger generation, hm?
And you know they don't give.
Financially.
Minister, what does
test all things mean to you?
The Lord is my shepherd I shall not want.
Okay? What does that mean?
More importantly, how are we supposed
to get them to act accordingly?
Accordingly?
Yeah, yeah.
With a young men coming in here
and making all that
ruckus and smelling like...
Smelling like weed?
Yes!
Yes.
Psh, and...
And the young women, their
outfit choices are inappropriate.
Ha.
I told you not to get
rid of those choir robes.
Look, I'm serious, Pastor.
How are we supposed to
secure the future of Mount Zion?
Hm?
You see, we don't.
God has it all figured out.
Gary.
Pastor.
Uh, Pastor.
Deacon Mathis, with all due respect,
I would like to spend the rest of my Sunday
with my grand babies.
And we can resume this
conversation tomorrow.
God bless you.
Yeah.
God bless you too.
Did you see how fine
Minister Harris looked today?
Girl, he could be your dad.
Like that would stop her.
I wouldn't mind calling him daddy.
Zooey!
Ugh, what? I'm just saying.
Man, I can't wait 'til I turn 18 next year.
And what would you do to Minister Harris
when you do turn 18?
Girl, don't you answer that question.
We are still at church.
Crazy self.
Hey, Deacon Mathis.
Zooey.
Luke.
Hey, Mrs. Mathis.
Cara, come on, we're leaving.
Bye, guys.
And don't forget to call me tonight.
See ya next Sunday.
What did I tell you about
hanging out with those two?
Dad!
Don't Dad me.
Cara, your father's right.
Okay, we have an image to uphold
and with him being the
church's future pastor,
you cannot be hanging around those two.
Look, I know every church
has charity case families,
but you, you're not one.
Fix your face and come on.
Get in the car.
Honey, how do you
feel about ribs tonight?
I found this delicious recipe
and I'd really like to try it.
Oh baby, I'm sorry.
I have this, uh, dinner meeting
with some of the other deacons tonight.
I... I totally forgot.
Okay, well, you know
Cara, she can just order in
and I can come with.
Thanks, Mom.
Uh, no.
No, no, no.
We're just gonna be
talking about business stuff.
Eh, boring.
Okay, well...
I guess if you insist.
Yeah.
Marshall.
Marshall!
Hello?
Oh! - Whoa.
Oh man, what's going on?
What do you mean?
That's my stuff.
Hey man, I got orders.
I gotta go.
Where have you been?
I tried calling you all weekend.
Betty, what the hell is going on?
Ugh.
Marshall!
My office, now.
Shut the door.
No thanks, I've had enough.
Come on, take it.
Have a seat.
So, Bill.
What's going on, huh?
Why was that guy moving
stuff outta my office?
Why don't you calm down?
You haven't been around here all week long
and you're not returning anyone's calls.
Yeah, well, I couldn't find my phone.
That's a little
concerning, don't you think?
Yeah, tell me about it.
You know, I don't know how
to tell you this Marshall, okay.
But things aren't looking
up for the business.
Okay?
We're being investigated.
Investigated?
For what?
You don't need to worry
about that right now, okay.
I just need you to lay low
for a little while, all right?
Lay...
Low.
Wait!
Am I being accused of something?
No, no, no, no!
Look, it's not like that.
I just want you to lay low for awhile.
You and I, we started
this business together.
Have I ever let ya down?
No, you haven't let me down.
Then you need to trust me.
Take a little vacation.
A vacation?
I took a pay cut for the last six months.
I can't afford a vacation.
And besides, I'm still
on thin ice with Brooke.
This is for your own good.
I promise.
Do ya trust me?
Yeah, I do.
Okay, good.
Betty has a check for ya.
Don't cash it until Friday.
I've gotta move some money around.
Now get out.
So what on god's green earth
are we being investigated for anyway, huh?
All we do is help people find love.
Have you ever heard the term,
sometimes love isn't good enough?
Heard it?
Yeah! I'm living it right now.
Well, sometimes doing the
right thing isn't good enough.
Now get out.
What does that even mean?
Exactly.
It's not going our way.
Things aren't going our way.
They're going all over the place.
Go home! I'll call ya.
Ugh.
And shut the door!
He leaves it open.
Bye, Marshall.
All right, Betty, I'm
heading out to lunch.
All right, Katie.
You good? - Mm-hm.
All right, I'll see you in about an hour.
Okay. - All right.
Bring me coffee.
Okay, you got it.
Okay.
Hi.
Hi!
I'm Elizabeth.
Hi.
I have an audition with Bill.
An audition?
Yeah, to be your next cover girl.
Oh.
Um...
Elizabeth.
Oh.
Over here, honey. - Thank you.
Hi, Bill.
Well, hello! How are you?
Can I see a little spin, please?
Very nice.
Let's go to my office.
Mm, mm.
Hey, come on, buddy.
You gotta eat all your food
if you wanna grow big and strong.
I don't wanna grow big.
I wanna be little forever.
I remember Ma used to get on me
about not eating my vegetables.
It wasn't until I got in the 5th grade
when she told me girls
liked boys with muscles.
Now you know how you get some muscles, son?
Ya gotta eat those greens, huh?
Ha, ha, ha.
Mom!
Well, he's not at that age where he needs
to be worried about what girls think yet.
Right, babe?
I'm gonna get them ready for bed.
Come on, kids.
Come on.
Crazy.
Man, I'm so proud of you, son.
And you should be, too.
You've got a beautiful family.
You have a beautiful life.
I appreciate it, Pop.
There's something I've been wanting
to talk to you about.
Is it church related?
Yes.
Pop, can it wait?
Tomorrow's not a promise, son.
All right, at least let me help out
by taking these dishes in.
Let me help you out.
Pop!
You're a guest, man.
I don't mind. - I know, relax.
I know, I know.
Ow!
You all right?
Just let me sit.
Let me sit for a minute.
Ow!
Pop.
Are you all right?
Pop, come on, man!
Vivica, call the ambulance now!
Pop, come on, Pop.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Can you breathe?
You gotta talk to me, Pop.
Come on, lean back.
You gotta talk to me. Talk to me, Pop.
Call 911!
I'm calling
'em, I'm calling 'em.
Well, uh...
Well, look who's here.
The man of the hour has finally showed up.
George, what are you doing here?
Oo, hey, Marshall.
Veronika?
What are you both doing here?
What do you mean
what are they doing here?
We're having dinner
with the Smiths tonight.
Uh.
Oh.
Oh, I am so sorry.
I've had things going on at work.
Just my mind has been...
Uh, elsewhere.
I'll go freshen up real quick and uh...
Where's the wine?
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
Okay, just forget about it.
Just go clean up.
Brush your hair.
You look like a slob.
Uh.
Yeah.
Well, I hope you guys love tea.
Ha.
Marshall didn't leave us much choice.
Oh.
Well.
Shall we go to the dining room?
Sure. - Come on.
Why not?
Hey you.
Hey, baby doll.
I'm sorry, I was trying not to wake you up.
Oh.
No, it's okay, because I've actually,
I've been waiting up for you.
Oh, have you?
Yes.
Ah, oh baby.
What?
Are you too tired?
Yeah, I'm...
This meeting kinda wiped me out.
Okay.
Yeah.
I love you, though.
Muah. Goodnight.
So, Marshall, how's business?
Uh, business is...
It's okay.
Good, good.
No, he's just being modest.
It's doing amazing.
Oh, so, Brooke was
telling me how you guys
had met on that website.
I just think it's beautiful.
Yes.
Right, right?
Of all the men that I could
have met that weekend in Rome,
I mean who knew that I would have met
and fallen in love with one of the founders
of Love Meet Up Worldwide.
Ha, ha!
Oh, I just think it's great that y'all
created that website.
You know, if I didn't
marry George, who knows.
The love of my life could be in Spain.
And thanks to you for creating the website,
the choices are all around
for everyone across the globe.
Well, that is our goal to connect people.
Oh, oh.
Wait, wait!
Honey, Veronika is on the
board at the country club
and she can vouch for me so that I can join
faster than the normal enrollment process.
Plus, the joining fee is
at a discount right now.
It's only 4,000.
So, give me your credit card
so I can sign up right now.
Can we discuss this later, Brooke?
What's there to discuss?
I wanna join.
All the other wives in
the neighborhood go there.
Marshall,
give her your credit card.
Babe, not right now, okay?
Marshall, just give me your card.
Ha.
Brooke.
What?
Why are you making this so complicated?
Because I lost my job today, Brooke.
That's why.
Well.
I can even...
I can go ahead and give you
that same deal in September.
Um, it might be even a little cheaper.
Yeah, cheaper.
Uh-huh, yes.
Oh, great.
Thank you.
We have a choice in our suffering.
Going through our suffering
produces perseverance.
We have a choice in our suffering.
Knowing that our suffering
produces perseverance.
He that endures.
Dad!
To the end.
Shall be saved.
Dad!
No one but you can run my Zion, Anthony.
Dad.
Anthony.
Vivica where are you?
Vivica?
Anthony.
Vivica!
Dad.
He's gone, baby.
I'm sorry.
I don't have any parents anymore.
Guys.
Listen, um...
After the passing of our
dear shepherd and pastor,
Franklin Harris III, we elders and deacons
of Mount Zion Baptist Church
must start seeking candidates
for our new senior.
And who could possibly take his place?
Well, I...
I don't mind stepping in.
I mean, I believe it's
time that we have a pastor
who embodies the church's values.
And who can take us to the future.
Yes, Missionairy Byers?
I think his boy, Anthony,
should take the lead.
Uh...
He's been primed for it.
Plus, he's bringing in
a younger generation.
Yeah, and you know what?
My son tells me that he's teaching
real good Baptist doctrine.
And plus, he got style.
It can't be all that good
if they're coming in here
wearing everything off the street.
And they don't give no offering, either.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
They ain't got no job.
And plus, I don't see
you giving anything either
with your tight ass.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I give every week.
Every single Sunday your...
No, I have been here the longest.
Everyone, please!
I would be honored to step in and fill
the shoes my father left behind.
And I also believe this is
what he would have wanted.
For me.
That sounds like nepotism to me.
See, there you go with that nepotism.
Well, what do you want?
What are you talking about?
I, I'm...
Okay, time out. Time out.
Time out!
Let's just take a vote to
make Anthony interim pastor.
Let's just pray about it and vote yes or no
and send the email to
Marsha, our secretary.
Now, excuse me.
I've got a game to go watch.
Hey wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Listen, I'm sorry things
didn't go your way.
But you know, if Anthony wasn't around
and you weren't such a
jerk, you would have my vote
and everybody else's vote.
But you know Franklin, you know,
he thought really highly of Anthony.
So, don't worry about it.
Okay, kids, we'll see y'all later.
Bye. - Bye.
Are they gone?
I feel so bad for Minister Harris.
Maybe if I just gave him a kiss,
that would take away all of his problems.
You are something else, you know that?
Zooey! You have got to
stop making those jokes.
Not only is he married,
but you are under age.
Uh-uh, correction.
You're the one that's
underage, miss 16-year-old.
You would get in trouble if you
and him did something, not me.
Well, that would never happen.
But in all seriousness though.
If he takes over and
becomes new head honcho,
we're gonna have to get a new minister.
I can't think of anyone
else who would deserve it,
to be honest.
If
Anthony wasn't around,
you would have my vote
and everybody else's vote.
Bill.
This is my fourth time calling you.
All right, you told me to
call when I found my phone.
Like, I still don't understand
what happened, all right?
Why are we really being investigated?
Look, my bills are stacking up.
My wife won't even let me touch her.
The well wives always runs dry
for whatever reason they choose.
That's why you always have
a spare horse in your stable.
A horse?
A whore.
Shivers.
Well, I don't want a whore.
I want my wife!
What's the difference?
Do you realize you purchased that woman?
Look at how much she's costing you.
Making you pay for sex.
Sounds like a whore to me.
Yeah, well, what am
I supposed to do, huh?
I resigned just like you asked.
Listen, Marshall, I
understand how you feel.
No, I don't think you understand, Bill!
I have to choose between
gas money and feeding my wife.
If you'd just let me finish.
I'll wire you some money from
one of our offshore accounts.
Just give me a day.
Offshore accounts?
Do you want the money, Marshall?
Yes!
Yes, yeah, and...
Anything helps.
Okay, I got you, Marshall.
Now, enjoy your mini vacation
because when you return
I'm gonna be putting
you through the ringer.
All right, thanks, thanks.
Thanks, Bill.
Daniel, change of plans.
Dad, is everything okay?
Yeah, baby girl.
Uh...
Daddy's just really sad.
Why?
Listen, um...
If I asked you to do something for me,
would you do it?
Of course.
And not just for me.
For your mother and you and...
Well, for all three of us.
Yes, Dad, anything.
Come here.
Sit next to me.
Listen to me.
This is what I need from you.
And don't tell anyone.
Girl, I don't even see
her car parked out here.
I mean, she just texted me.
She said she was on the street, so.
Girl, guess who just texted me.
Let me guess. Scotty?
He's lame, bro!
He's not lame.
You're lame for saying that, bro.
He's lame. - Like, what?
Girl, let's get out of here.
Why?
Shut up!
Please!
Who are you?
Uh, Alicia.
You?
Elizabeth.
Don't worry.
It gets easier the more you do it.
Do... do what?
Here.
Please, miss, just let me go home.
You need to get in there
and take a shower right now.
I wanna go home, please.
As long as you do what I tell you to do,
you'll be just fine.
I wanna go home, please.
No, you're not going anywhere!
Ah! Please, please!
No, get in there and
get to showering, now!
Mr. Bill said he had an
awesome time with you last night.
Did you have a good time with him?
Yes, Miss Bertha.
That's what I like to hear, thank you.
Hey, Brooke.
Are you here, baby?
Of course not.
Mm.
I got 20 missed calls.
2.3 million?
Transferred to your account?
What the hell, Bill?
Ah.
Who is it?
It's your
neighbor, man, open up.
Hey boss, how you doing today?
George?
Is that you?
Yeah, man.
Who else do I look like?
Ugh. Ha.
So, what brings ya by?
Listen, Marshall.
Your wife has been talking to my wife.
And Veronika wants me
to come get ya to hang out
from time to time.
Man, what are you talking about?
Your wife says you have no friends.
No, I... I got lots of friends.
Yeah, whatever, listen.
My boys and I are going down to the state
to watch a game this week.
You wanna come?
I'm sorry, I don't watch football.
Hey, Marshall.
Are you all right? What's going on, man?
What's wrong?
What's up?
Who's that? - Who?
Marshall Shepherds?
Yeah, who wants to know?
Sir, you're under arrest
for human trafficking.
Go ahead and turn around,
put your hands behind your back.
Wait... what?
For what? Huh?
Ah!
Marshall, I'll call Brooke, all right?
No, no.
Don't call Brooke.
Ah!
Don't call her.
Hey, Cara.
What are you doing here so late?
Hi, Sister Stacy.
I was wondering if Minister
Harris was in his office.
I believe so.
Thank you.
Mm-hm.
Cara.
It's late, what are you still doing here?
I was just... confused on some stuff
and hoping that you could give
me more of an understanding.
Such as?
Just, um...
Thoughts.
Human thoughts.
I'm not sure how I
can help you with that,
but come on, sit down.
Let's give it a shot.
Morning, baby.
Morning.
Is this for me?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
You woke up pretty late this morning.
Talking to the big man.
So, how are you coping?
I wouldn't be able to get
through any of this without you.
Thank you, Vivica, for loving me.
Anthony, you don't have
to thank me for anything.
No, but I do, though.
I mean, who's going to love
me more than my parents?
God really blessed me by giving me you.
God is good, babe.
Always.
Are you expecting somebody this morning?
No.
Probably another one of
your Amazon deliveries.
You know me too well. - Mm-hm.
Amazon deliver faster
than Jesus, don't they.
Morning, officers, how can I help you?
Anthony Jamal Harris?
Yeah, is there an issue?
Yes, sir.
You're under arrest for a
sexual assault on a minor.
What?
What are you talking about?
Anthony, what's going on?
I haven't assaulted anybody!
Ma'am, come over here for me.
Wait, no, you've got the wrong person.
Wait!
Call my lawyer.
It's okay, baby, go upstairs.
Where are they taking daddy?
It's okay, baby girl,
just go upstairs, okay?
Listen to me, wait, wait! What happened?
Call him!
Daddy!
It's okay, baby.
Come on, dark skin.
You see, Turner.
These men are monsters.
Must be detained at all costs.
Some need to be locked up forever.
Or even killed.
Dun, dun, dun.
Especially ones that abuse little girls.
Enjoy your stay.
No continental breakfast.
Hey!
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
What's your deal?
I'm sorry.
What'd you do?
Nothing.
Yeah.
Yeah, me neither.
Ha.
Everyone's innocent in here, right?
Hey, I know that look.
That was me last night.
Are you worried?
Not at all.
Why is that?
Because God is on my side.
God?
Yeah.
Just look around.
This is a county jail.
God ain't here.
And if God was on our side,
I wouldn't be in this shit hole.
I hope my wife hurries up and posts bail.
Vivica.
Ha, yeah.
If God is real.
He sure ain't fair.
Oh, just lets us all destroy each other
and he just sits up in the clouds watching
like it's some kind of
messed up reality show.
It's sick.
Stop molesting our kids.
Enough is enough!
Sister Hatch, I...
I'm so glad you called.
I'm waiting for him, the
church isn't answering
any of my phone calls.
I didn't...
I dropped the kids off at my mom's house.
I'm a mess.
I... I just don't know what to do.
Okay.
It's um... it's just
Anthony's lawyer, Matthew.
Let me call you back.
Thank you, Sister Hatch.
Stop molesting our kids!
Enough is enough!
Any good news, Matthew?
Yes, he's been approved for bail.
Let's go get your husband.
Thank you, Jesus.
Okay, let me, uh, grab my purse.
Whatever you do, stay looking down.
Don't give them an
ounce of attention, okay?
Okay.
Stay with me, here we go.
All right.
Okay.
Stop molesting our kids.
Enough is enough!
Stop molesting our kids!
I know everybody
is so concerned about Cara.
Even my mother.
I just feel like I failed as a parent.
As a mother.
I'm supposed to protect my daughter.
And I didn't even see
that disgusting pedophile
eyeing my daughter.
Baby, baby.
Don't do yourself like that.
Hey, dark skin!
Harris!
You posted bail.
Come on, get off your bunk.
You're free to go.
Congratulations.
Not you.
Come on.
That was fast.
Good luck to you, Marshall.
Ha. Thanks.
Well.
Maybe God was on his side.
Thanks for everything, Matthew.
It's not over yet, Anthony.
You got a long road ahead of you.
I'm innocent.
God and my wife knows that.
That's all that matters right now.
All right, let's get ya outta here.
Before the news you're out on bail hits.
Good idea.
All right.
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah, it's just been
a long night, Anthony.
A lot to take in.
Viv, you do believe me, right?
Yeah, of course.
Let's go.
It's getting late.
We wouldn't want to keep Matthew waiting.
Ha.
Ah! Brooke!
Brooke.
Oh, baby.
Am I ever glad to see you.
Hello, Marshall.
What?
Hey... what's wrong?
Oh, I don't know.
Um, maybe it's my husband being locked up
and all of our assets being investigated.
Which means I have no money.
Hey, hey.
As soon as the lawyer gets hold of my case,
I'll be outta here.
Did you... did you call him?
That's why I'm here.
Steve is not coming.
He wants money, which you don't have.
Damn it!
Damn lawyers.
But hey, I am really glad to see you.
That's cute.
I'm selling the house, Marshall.
What?
No, no, no.
Wait.
You... you can't do that.
That... that's my home!
I can do whatever I want with your assets
that aren't being investigated,
because am your wife.
Remember?
You don't really think I
did all that stuff, do you?
Look, Bill screwed me, okay?
He set me up to take the fall.
I had no idea what they
were doing with that business.
It doesn't matter what I think.
I'm not helping you.
Get yourself a court appointed lawyer.
Goodbye, Marshall.
Wait, wait, wait.
Brooke.
Wait, Brooke!
Brooke!
After everything I did
for you, come on, Brooke!
Don't leave me like this!
Brooke!
Oh my gosh.
Hey, Marsha.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe it!
Marsha.
Anthony.
You have some nerve
showing your face around here.
Mathis.
I didn't touch your daughter.
You're no longer welcome around here.
Nor around my daughter, ever again.
Your daddy would have
been so disappointed...
Don't you bring my father into this.
Why?
You tried to use him to
become the new pastor.
But guess what, little boy,
I'm the new pastor now.
And you will forever be
that disappointment what if.
Jimmy, escort Anthony outta here.
We'll have the rest of your
stuff shipped to your home.
That's if you ever get a
chance to see it again.
Yeah, you might be serving life,
after my lawyers get through with you.
I didn't touch your daughter.
Get him outta here.
Anthony, I'm sorry, I have to...
Get your hands off of me!
Give it back!
You give it back!
I'm the new pastor now.
Okay, what would you like, I'm buying.
Oh, I'm all right.
I just...
I can't stop thinking about it, sister.
Last night I poured a whole glass of wine
and just stared at it.
I don't know what to do.
Do you think he did it?
No.
I... I know him better than anyone.
For 15 years.
Then again, everyone has their secrets.
I just can't see it.
What does God say? Hm?
Have you been praying at all?
This is a test, beloved.
Now, as Anthony's help mate,
you need to figure out
a way how to help him.
How?
Well, you're a woman.
God gave us intuition.
He didn't give it to men.
He gave it to woman.
So, you would have known something.
You would have felt something.
Am I right?
Yeah, you're right.
Women do have intuition, they just choose
to black it out until it's too late.
But I can honestly say
I haven't seen one hint
of this from Anthony.
Give me your hand.
You need to learn to stand, beloved.
How are you gonna win this battle
when you don't talk to
your strongest warrior, hm?
Let's hope this works.
Yeah.
Hold it.
Hey.
Hi.
Hi, Matthew.
Well, I hope you got
some good news for us today.
Not quite, but not bad news.
Just briefing Anthony on what
to expect in court on Monday.
Well, thank you for everything.
Absolutely.
All right, have a good one, man.
All right.
I just... - Now, look.
Before you say anything.
I just want you to know that I'm here
and I'm with you.
And I know the man that I married,
but what they're saying out there
and who they think you are.
I know isn't true.
I just...
I just love you, Anthony.
I love you too, Vivica.
And I didn't touch that girl.
Heck, I make it a point
to not touch any woman
unless I'm in a crowd of people.
I know what the world thinks of men.
Especially those that look like me.
I believe you.
I just can't wrap my head around
why Cara would come up
with such a huge lie like that.
Maybe she was forced to.
By who?
Her father.
Deacon Mathis?
Why would he do that to you?
He wants to be the pastor of this church.
He thinks its his god given right.
You shoulda seen the way he looked at me
at the church today.
Now, Anthony, I know
you didn't go to that church.
I know, it was a mistake.
So, how are we gonna get through to Cara?
She's a child and you or I
can't be seen around her.
Well, I uh, gave this theory to Matthew.
I know Cara.
She's a kind hearted girl.
I don't see her letting
this go on too much longer.
Yeah?
Unless she's being fed lies by her father.
That's my biggest fear.
We all want to please our parents.
Look, I know you're
scared and that's okay.
But God is gonna be by
your side through all of this.
Okay?
I know.
I know, baby.
Oh no.
Oh, no, no, not again.
Ah!
What did I do to deserve this?
God.
Since you make all powerful decisions, huh?
What did I do to deserve it? What did I do!
Don't blame God for all
your decisions, old man.
Who's that?
Eddie. I'm in the cell next to ya.
Well, if I don't blame
God, then who do I blame?
Because I sure as hell didn't do anything
to deserve being in here.
Yeah, are you sure about that?
Just leave me alone, man.
All right.
But...
Before you place the blame
on God for your hardships,
why don't you try
getting to know him first?
Where am I supposed to do that here, huh?
Bible study every night in room seven.
Have a good night.
Ah.
Uh, church, um...
We must understand that
God makes no mistakes.
Amen?
Amen! - Amen.
Amen.
Yeah, although our timing
may not be his timing,
we still have to trust and believe in him.
Uh, where does the Bible say, uh...
When a man...
When a man, when a man...
What?
Huh?
That's a lie.
My good man.
No.
Nah, I don't think it say that.
What?
Um, you are not alone.
We are here to stay.
Well, listen Mount Vine, Zion.
I um, well listen, Mount Zion.
I understand that we
all have our challenges.
And they come unexpectedly.
But they are no surprise to God.
Amen.
So we have to trust him and lean
not into our own understanding,
but acknowledge him.
That's right, come on.
Acknowledge him like, for one,
that we did not appoint
that demon in that position.
Yes, I'm gonna call him out,
because only a demon would
do what he did to my daughter.
What?
Oh my.
So, God sees everything.
And knows everything.
And we just stay prayed
up and this too shall pass.
Amen?
Yeah.
Amen!
Amen?
Amen, amen!
Your father sends his love.
You know, that new
position just has him so busy.
Mom.
I need to tell you something.
Okay, baby girl, what is it?
Anything.
You promise to just keep it between us?
Of course.
And you won't tell dad, either?
Mom.
Cara.
You are scaring me.
Look, I didn't wanna do it.
But Dad looked so
defeated, he was drinking,
and he never drinks.
He said you both were
on the verge of divorce
and that we would lose everything
if he didn't secure the position as pastor.
And there was only one
way to secure the position.
So he told me to lie and
say that Minister Harris
sexually harassed me.
But I thought he would just
lose his job at the church.
I didn't think the cops would be involved.
And I don't want to talk
to the cops and lie again.
God says that it's not good to sin,
and that's all I've been
doing this past week.
Mom.
Say something, Mom.
There has to be a way to prove
that you're innocent in all of this.
What if we get one of
Cara's friends to talk to her?
I don't want to get anyone else involved.
Especially children.
Yeah, you're right.
If only there was a hidden camera
in there somewhere, you know?
Camera?
Wait...
Oh, pops!
What?
You remember that
time last year you wanted
to get a little naughty in my office?
Yeah?
But you were totally against the idea,
because you said big brother was watching.
Which he was!
Pops made me install a
nanny cam in my office.
Why?
Because as he put it, for my protection.
As a black man, your word is never enough.
You always have to have proof.
And plus, he thought someone
was snooping around the office.
So...
Oh!
So, all we have to
do is get in your office
and get the footage.
She said it happened that
night in your office, right?
Exactly, but how are we gonna get it?
It's not like we're exactly
welcome in the church right now.
Sister Hatch.
Everyone respects her.
She can get me in and out of the church
without anybody kicking me out.
Let me call her.
Pops, if you can get me outta this one.
Thank you.
Sister Hatch, I want to thank you
for this opportunity to
speak to the inmates today.
Hey guys, I wanted to
speak briefly on repentance.
I came through Sister Hatch
program about five years ago.
What the hell are you
doing? Get your ass in there.
Ah!
Remember not to start any problems
in there for me, old man.
If you run your mouth,
I'll let your little friends
come and play again.
He took me to repent
to him for all of my sins.
I didn't know what was gonna happen.
But you know what?
Something sparked in me.
And it helped me.
Now I have a loving family.
I have three children now.
I have a wife and I'm happy.
Due to this program Sister Hatch gave me.
And I know if I can do it, you can do it.
Thank you, Sister Hatch.
Amen.
Listen.
Not everyday is gonna be a great day,
because there's gonna be days that
I could be a real bah...
That's witch with a B.
But I always turn to God.
God is my helper, and
I'm never alone with God.
And I know that.
And I thank him everyday.
Even if I'm having a bad day,
I thank him for that day.
And I also thank him for the opportunity
to share the very next
day and start all over again.
So, I find him.
Yes, Nathan.
Sister Hatch, why must I keep praying?
Even though I don't feel
like God is ever listening?
Listen to?
Well, sometimes when I pray,
not all the times, just sometimes.
I ask for things.
And well...
I don't think God has
ever given me one thing.
Well, my sweet Nathan,
he can't hold your hand
and do it for you.
Now, he has given you a
key to this amazing world.
But it's up to you to find the right chest
and unlock that chest.
Okay?
Ha!
I got this, Doug.
Is there anything you would
like to share with this class?
Uh...
No, no.
I'll just keep my mouth shut.
No, actually.
You know what?
I'm not going to keep my mouth shut.
No, I mean, when I first
came to this shit hole
all I heard was God this, God that.
Well, God is so mighty.
Well, this has been the
worst month of my entire life.
And if God is so wonderful,
how come he chose now to come into my life.
When it's completely fallen apart?
Are you calm now?
Yeah, I'm calm.
Lessons.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
I said, lessons.
What is your name?
Marshall.
Well, Marshall, it's nice to meet you.
Now, I'm Sister Hatch.
Well, Sister Hatch, I...
I'm still a little confused about what
you said about lessons.
I mean, I'm a successful grown man.
I mean, what lessons
do I need to be taught?
Sister, I can't in good
faith let you near these men.
Doug Forrest.
Or as they call you, Officer Forrest.
Now, the only people I
need to be afraid of in here
is you two.
God sees everything, don't you forget it.
Now, these are all God's
children, not just you and yours.
Got it?
May I have your hand?
Yeah, I guess so.
God is trying to teach
you something, Marshall.
Now, you may not understand,
but there's always a reason.
And yours might just be a lesson.
Think about that.
Oh.
Hi, Mom. Hi, Dad.
Hey, Cara, can you please take a seat?
Okay.
Listen, um, your mother informed me
that you told her what
you and I had discussed.
Look, I'm sorry, Dad, okay?
It was so hard keeping it from Mom.
Especially when I have to see her everyday.
Nah, no, no, I understand.
It's okay.
My concern is that if you continue
to open your mouth to other
people outside our household
we can't trust.
Well, I haven't.
You haven't yet.
Cara, your father did what
was best for all three of us.
Do you understand me?
Do you understand?
Good.
Now what we are about to tell you
is going to be the best
thing for your wellbeing.
What are you talking about?
Well, if you're thinking about telling
the truth at this point,
it's not gonna matter about your age.
Because you're gonna be locked up,
because ya lied to the police.
And the fact that you didn't
do a rape kit examination,
that's further proof that you're
making the whole thing up.
But Dad, this was your idea!
But you went along with it.
And the words came out
of your mouth, not mine.
And the fact that you said what you said,
Anthony is going to be sent to prison soon.
There has to be some
way that we can tell the truth
and not get in trouble.
Cara!
Did you just ignore
everything your father said?
There is no longer a we in this.
This is your problem.
You will be the only one facing the judge
and I don't wanna see my
16-year-old daughter go to prison.
Look.
If we just stick to the plan, hm?
Everything is gonna be okay.
Cara.
Yes, father.
Do we have your word?
Cara Nicole Mathis.
That is not good enough.
Your father and I need
to hear you verbally agree.
You have my word,
I will stick to the plan.
Thank you, honey.
You can go ahead and go to your room now.
I'm gonna go ahead
and get started on dinner.
Oh, baby, I have
another dinner obligation.
Again?
Sweetheart, you know
what it entails to be a pastor.
Now, if the church is fundraising
and they need me to
entertain, well, so be it.
I understand.
Breaking
news, now at 10:00 A.M.
Where is Elizabeth Peters?
It has been over a week since anyone
has seen the 22-year-old Elizabeth Peters.
Who was reported missing by her roommate
in Dallas, Texas on June 12th.
And this morning
investigators are now saying
that they cannot rule out
foul play in her disappearance.
Elizabeth's disappearance comes along...
Hey, Matthew.
Yeah, Vivica's on her way
to the church right now.
Let's pray this all works out.
Later.
And sometimes
too trusting to strangers
as she has a huge heart.
If you have any information,
please dial the number on the screen.
Okay, okay.
Wait, wait, wait!
Please, Lord forgive me
for what we're about to do.
Sister Hatch, come on.
We don't have all day. Go, go.
Vivica!
Vivica, what are you doing here?
You know that you're not allowed here.
Patrice, how are you?
No, don't Patrice me.
Sister Hatch, really?
How dare you bring her into this church!
Knowing what her husband
has done to my daughter
and then doing it in the church.
The disrespect!
Patrice.
It's okay, Sister Hatch.
I got this.
Patrice, now I know we haven't seen
eye to eye on everything.
I don't hear a lie.
But you can't sit here and tell me
that you believe that Anthony
would do such a thing to Cara.
So are you calling my daughter a liar?
Patrice, inside voices.
No.
But what I am saying is
that she was put up to it
and was scared to say no.
You know what?
You need to leave right now.
Now look.
I'm a child of God first
and a woman second.
And about my family,
we'll fight to the death.
Now if you ain't gonna physically
pull me outta this church,
which I would love to see you try,
I highly suggest you move outta my way.
Now, I'm going in my husband's
office to get something.
So back up.
I said, no.
Patrice.
I got saved a long time ago.
But I ain't too sure I'm delivered yet.
I'm getting security.
We've got like three minutes, dear.
Go, go.
Eagle eye, eagle eye, where are you?
Gotcha.
Please, Jimmy.
I've known you since you were knee high,
my knee high stockings.
I'm sorry, Sister Hatch.
I'm just doing my job.
It's just, can you please step aside...
You.
Really?
I'll open it myself.
I'm so sorry, Vivica.
I tried to stall 'em as long as I could.
I'm just not a good accomplice.
It's okay, Sister Hatch.
I got what I needed.
Let's go.
Hi.
Hey!
Patrice, how are you?
Oh, it's so good to see you.
It was so good to see Deacon
Mathis last night at the Omni.
Yes, he has been working a
lot of dinners for the church.
Oh? He was working?
Okay, I thought he was
just showing his beautiful,
young niece Elizabeth around town.
He did say that she had
just moved into the city.
But anyway, it really doesn't matter.
But uh, I didn't know
Deacon Mathis was half white.
Half white?
Yes.
You...
Yes, he is half white.
Ha! I'm sorry.
And our little niece,
Elizabeth, I just love her.
Lizzie poo.
Well, anyway, give Deacon Mathis my love
and I hope to see you both
at Wednesday's night service.
Yes, ma'am.
Good to see you, lady.
Good to see you too, bye Miss Mary Anne.
Anthony.
I assume you already saw the footage?
Yeah!
I knew you were innocent, I knew it.
Oh, I miss your smile.
You have to call Matthew
and get this settled now.
And I'm gonna call my Mom
and check on the kids, okay?
Okay.
Okay, I love you.
I love you, I love you!
I love you too. - Muah!
Okay!
Matthew!
We got it! We got it!
Yeah, she just came in with it.
Okay.
Okay!
Woo-hoo, hoo!
Daniel, I know.
I know you are doing something.
You ain't doing that much entertaining.
What are you doing?
I know you were doing something.
Night after night!
You're not coming home!
What are you doing?
You don't want to be
intimate with your own wife!
What are you doing?
Who are you with, Daniel?
Not with me!
I'm your family.
I know you are doing something.
I know it.
Wait.
Okay.
Am I crazy?
Maybe I'm crazy.
Okay, maybe...
Maybe I...
Maybe I haven't met
one of his nieces before.
I mean, it's possible.
Are you stupid, Patricia?
You know all of his nieces.
And they all live in San Diego.
And no, Miss Mary Anne, he ain't white!
What are you doing!
Harry Hines.
Uh, hi.
Uh...
Hello.
Sorry, I...
I haven't done this since, uh...
I lost my mother.
And I don't think I was
particularly nice to you then.
I'm not asking for a miracle.
I think Sister was right.
Being here has given me time.
To think about all my damn decisions.
Sorry, sorry, I didn't
mean to speak out of turn.
But yeah, uh...
I wasn't the smartest.
But...
If I get to get out of here,
I will start thinking.
And not just quickly jumping into things.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, thank you.
Uh...
For the time here.
I really needed it.
Mom!
Dad?
I need to talk to y'all!
Hey, how fast can you get
me and take me to the church?
Thank you.
I'll see you soon.
This is the right thing to do.
Ma'am, can I help you?
Hi, yes, um...
My girlfriend, she sent me here
to ask for more information.
What do you guys do exactly?
Well, this is our headquarters.
We have agents working
like around the time,
sending updates around the world,
for people of all walks of life.
For example, if you're in New York,
you can travel to like England, or Dubai,
or Germany, and then
find the love of your life.
Okay, so...
I see.
You are in the business
of setting people up.
Yes.
Sleepy Hollow. Elizabeth.
Ma'am?
Excuse me, ma'am.
What was that?
Yeah.
Of course, yes.
Um, I just want to thank you
so much for this, Sister Hatch.
Yeah, and whatever happens in court,
I know God is gonna be by our side.
Amen.
Uh.
Hold on, hold on, Sister Hatch.
Let me, uh, let me call you back, okay?
Okay.
Matthew, hi, how are you?
Oh.
We're needed at the church?
Right now?
Oh, okay. We can be
there in a couple minutes.
All right.
Okay, see you soon, bye-bye.
Anthony!
1106 Sleepy Hollow.
How's it going?
Oh my gosh! Get out of here!
Go!
Can I help you?
Hi, I'm...
I'm here to see Daniel.
There's no Daniel here.
You must be Elizabeth.
Look, I know my husband comes here.
I don't know what
you're talking about, lady.
Then why is your address here?
Daniel!
Please, please. I don't want no trouble.
I don't either, look,
all I need is confirmation.
Confirmation on what?
Oh my god.
Oh.
Please.
They say if we're good we can go home.
They?
Who did this to you?
Who did this to you!
Cara.
Cara, baby, I cannot talk right now.
Look, I'm in...
Cara.
Cara, baby, what's wrong?
Where are you?
Okay, I'm on my way right now.
I'm so sorry.
I am so sorry, but I have to go.
No, don't go.
I'll be back though, I promise.
I'll be back.
And then everything will be okay.
God led me here for a reason.
And I'm not the bad guy.
I'll be back, okay?
Zooey.
Zooey, where is Cara?
She called me on the phone crying,
saying get here as soon as possible.
Zooey.
She, she's okay.
Okay, I mean physically she is.
Wait a minute.
Physically, like...
What do you mean by physically?
Mrs. Mathis, please
don't be mad at her, okay?
It was really eating her up inside.
Zooey!
Where is my daughter!
She's in the conference room.
Searches of personal property
and restricted access to all...
I'll telling ya. You're making a mistake.
I'm not the guy. I didn't do anything!
Let go of me!
Unhand me now!
I've been a member of Baptist...
You're gonna be a great
asset to the company,
I tell ya, because you're sexy
and I'm in the sexy business.
We're gonna make a lot of money together.
Bill.
Bill!
Bill. - What?
There's people out there.
Oh!
Bill Schneider?
Yeah, who are you?
You're under arrest
for human trafficking.
What?
Anything you say can and
will be used against you...
No, no, no I'm not that...
Hey!
You've already got that guy he's in jail.
Don't make things more
difficult than they already are.
Hey, Betty!
Get my attorney on the phone.
Ow!
I'm innocent!
Yeah, all right.
Betty, get my attorney on the phone.
I'm innocent, I tell ya!
I didn't do this!
I am so sorry.
Let's just get out of here.
Yeah.
We all need help in
these last days, amen?
Amen.
So please, come.
Come to Jesus today!
You're free, my friend.
Let Jesus set you free!
With God all things are possible!
He made the lame man walk!
And the blind man see!
He resurrects the dead to life!
The Bible says, let us
rejoice in our suffering!
Knowing that suffering
produces perseverance.
And knowing that we
must hold unto our faith.
So that he could provide
you with the strength!
The strength to stand.
Amen.
Stand!
Amen!
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Believe it ♪
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Believe it ♪
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Believe it ♪
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Believe it ♪
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Believe it ♪
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Believe it ♪
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Believe it ♪
♪ Receive it ♪
♪ Claim it ♪
♪ Walk in it ♪
♪ Yes ♪