Fm Movie
Hey!
What's wrong?
Puncture!
BIRTHDAY
Hey, Bablu, tell me something.
How do people take a dump in a plane?
Everyone has a remote.
The moment you need to go,
just press the button.
Suddenly, the window opens!
Automatic.
You just need to stick your butt
out of the window.
There will be a nice, cool breeze
and you're all set!
- And then? -Then what?
Just do your business.
Damn it!
Then it'll fall down!
Yeah, it does.
- What if it falls on us?
- That's why I'm telling you,
'Cover your head, Mannu'!
Damn it!
It's coming!
- So, do it.
- The plane, bro!
Hey, Bablu, wait up!
Come on, run faster!
- There it goes!
- Hey, wait up...
One, two, three!
Jump, Mannu!
- Look, it's flying away!
- Wow!
Mannu's down!
Mannu's down.
Bablu!
Look, there it is!
- Look, there it is!
- Wow...
Beep! Beep! Beep!
Plane!
Mannu?
Hey, Mannu!
Are you taking a dump inside?
Mannu?
Mannu.
Hey, Mannu!
Mannu!
3 DAYS LATER
- Mannu!
- Sister...
- Sister, stop...
Please listen to me... -Mannu!
Mannu...
Mannu!
15 children have lost their lives
in the last year.
Why has this river become
a burial ground for children?
Is there a ghost or...
Hey, move!
Hey, Mannu.
My child...
- Come on... Wake up!
- It wants the blood of children.
Bablu, please wake Mannu up.
- Why are you crying?
- That's the question...
Wake him up gently.
- But before any action is taken...
- Come on, wake up!
- Krishna...
- Live on our channel...
Look, your maternal uncle is here!
Uncle Krishna!
Tomorrow is Sunday.
Your uncle will take you to watch a movie.
- The entire village is gathered here.
- Wake up! Wake him up...
- Someone please wake him up!
- What happened...
Why the hell did the body
have to float up today?
It didn't float here.
The machine dug deep under the water
and the body came up
to the surface, along with the sand.
- Do you see who's here with me?
- Who?
Remember?
I told you,
Prince Bhaiya will celebrate his birthday
on the riverbank today.
And what did Bhaiya tell you?
That all the arrangements
have to be top-notch.
'Top-notch?'
If the body isn't disposed off by evening,
I'll light a fire under your bottom.
- Stop the truck...
- Top-notch...
Stop the truck! Today, there will be
two dead bodies, not one!
Go see what happened there.
Hey!
- Hey! Where are you guys going?
Go away from here! -Mannu...
- What the hell...
- We won't budge...
Didi, there's a problem at the riverbank.
Where is Prince?
Come on, Guddu, let me go!
Let me go, Guddu...
No, Bhaiya, no!
No, Prince Bhaiya!
Let me go, Guddu...
No!
Bhaiya...
That was amazing, Bhaiya!
Absolutely fantastic!
- Bloody asshole...
- What a grand entry, Prince Bhaiya!
Returning is not my style
I'm the bullet that doesn't turn back
once I fly
I wished the gun goodbye
Just coming to meet my love to say 'hi'
Show it to me.
- Bhaiya, you're rocking it.
- Call him.
- Hey, idiot! Come here!
- What...
- Me?
- How do I look?
- You're looking good, Bhaiya.
- I look like an asshole.
No, Bhaiya.
- You're looking good, Bhaiya.
- What?
You thought I didn't hear what you said
because of the water?
- No, Bhaiya! I was referring
to Guddu, not you! -Guddu?
He called you an asshole.
- Sorry...
- Hey!
- Why are you being so gentle?
- No, Bhaiya...
Hit him harder.
Good job!
- Sorry, Bhaiya...
- What?
I just blurted it out...
- What if my gun too blurts out?
- No, Bhaiya...
Sorry, Bhaiya!
- Should I shoot him? Should I?
- No, Bhaiya! No, Bhaiya...
- I'll die, Bhaiya...
- Shoot him...
- Shoot him, Bhaiya...
- Come on, you shoot me.
- No, Bhaiya... I can't do it... -Why?
You were trying to be a hot-shot, right?
- No, Bhaiya... -Go ahead.
Come on, shoot me! Shoot!
- Shoot! Shoot me.
- Bloody assholes...
Assholes like us
don't deserve to live, right?
- Move aside! Give me the gun!
- The hell!
What's going on?
Get lost, you fucker!
Hey, Guddu!
Get lost!
I was talking to him, Softy.
- Give me the gun. The hell...
- Talk to Didi.
Give me the gun!
'Talk to Didi!'
- Come on, I have something important
to discuss with you. -So do I.
Shoot this.
- Softy... -We'll have to cancel
tonight's party.
There's been a problem at the riverbank.
What are your demands
from the district administration?
They should come
and launch an investigation.
15 children have died in a year.
How?
These machines that you see here
dig up sand from the middle of the river,
resulting in deep pits.
Coming to those pits,
children and animals
drown and die in them.
- Who is behind all this mining?
- Hey, Krishna.
- Krishna, let's go...
- There's only one mafia in this district.
Babli Didi.
She's in jail, with three murder cases
pending against her.
All the work that's going on here
is managed by Softy
and Didi's brother, Prince,
aka Shashikant, the main perpetrator!
Run...
- Run...
- Come on...
- Come with me.
- Let me go!
- Come on... Hey...
- Let go!
Come here, boy.
Hey!
- Go on, drive your truck over me!
- Stop this drama.
- Go on! Let there be
two dead bodies here today! -Get up.
- Get up. Hey--
- Run me over!
Move!
Take him away!
- No, don't--
- Should I shoot her? Should I?
No, Bhaiya, she's a woman...
What's wrong?
Dance.
Didn't you get paid to perform?
ANNIVERSARY
Hello, Mr. Prabhakar.
A FEW DAYS LATER
I'm handing over the car.
Why haven't you come?
Okay, no problem.
I'll call you back.
Clean India!
Great, Subedaarji.
Great!
Your wife had told me,
'Vinay, it's our silver jubilee.
We've been married for 25 years.
Even if we have to go see 25,000 cars,
Subedaarji should have
no reason to complain'.
May her soul rest in peace.
Mom wanted a photo with the car.
Sit inside.
This is the least you can do.
Rest your arm on the car
so that you look like the owner.
Mom had one more condition.
- Mansion... He's built a mansion
high above... -Let's go.
- Wear your seatbelt, Shyama.
- Mansion...
- No one here wears a seatbelt.
- Now, it's time to be patient, my love
Now, it's time to be patient, my love
- Be patient, my love
- SOLDIER
Be patient, my love
The entire village salutes me
when I pass by
I call him Mr. Chaudhary, oh, my!
He has a government job,
his work is risky
My lover, the cop, drives a Gypsy
He's built his home where the judges stay
He walks and talks like a Subedaar, I say
He's also got reach in the government
Walks and talks like a Subedaar, I say
Stealing sand, are you?
Just wait, I'll teach you a lesson...
What are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Stealing sand, bloody thieves!
- Hey...
Hey...
Get rid of the cars...
- Hey... There's enough place...
- Move the cars...
What's the matter, mister?
Did your new car break down?
Want help?
- Sound the horn...
- Go on, mister.
No one here stops at the red signals.
Get going.
Keep moving--
SHEEL COLLEGE, BHETOD
Happy anniversary, dad.
Thank you.
My daughter is getting married--
- And you'll let me withdraw
only 50,000? -Not allowed...
- I'm tired of your ranting...
- I'll set myself on fire!
You've filled out the wrong form!
Go fill it up again!
- Come back tomorrow.
- I won't leave till I'm done!
- I want to talk to the officer!
- That guy seems mad--
- What's going on--
- What the hell--
Hey, get this fiery woman out of here!
Want to set yourself on fire? I'll pay
for the petrol! Go torch yourself!
- How can you throw me out like this?
How can you do this? -Just leave!
She's been screaming nonstop!
Ill-mannered woman! Get lost!
So, what did you say your name was, sir?
Subedaar Arjun Maurya.
Retired.
Subedaarji, why on earth have you
deposited your money here?
My wife used to run
a small pickle-making business.
- How the hell can you--
- It was her account.
- Oh, come on...
- I want to close it now.
- When did she die?
- Hey... How can...
It's been three months.
Go ahead, shoot me!
I'll sit right here! Shoot!
- I won't leave! Do whatever
you want to! -Move!
Someone get this woman
to shut up! Rubbish!
Crazy woman!
I got transferred
to this god-forsaken place! The heck!
I'm so irritated.
I can't even find your closure form!
Look at this. One guy
had come here yesterday.
One such 'customer is king'. Have a look,
he ripped up all these papers!
I think your form was one of them.
Here's what you can do, sir...
- Take this form and come back tomorrow.
- You don't understand...
I've already filled up this form thrice.
What's the big deal, sir?
- Fill it up a fourth time!
- Just hear me out...
- Want me to beg?
- Just leave...
- I've been transferred here
by the authorities. -Move!
I'm not one of the locals,
who's going to clean up your... shit!
Please leave and come back tomorrow!
- Go away...
- I won't leave.
Then please come and sit here, sir.
Tell me your war stories
and let me tell you mine.
Please have a seat.
Sit down.
Have a seat.
FRIEND
You're looking fit, pal.
Please don't mind.
I couldn't be there
when the car was delivered.
Your daughter had called me up
and asked me to come
but I couldn't muster
the courage to do so.
Your wife's face kept flashing
in front of my eyes.
She was really thrilled
when she booked this car.
She called me up and said, 'Mr. Prabhakar,
I'm buying a Gypsy for Subedaarji.
He'll look good driving it'.
And then...
Okay.
Life has to go on, buddy.
- It doesn't add up...
- Hey...
Here they come.
That's Softy Bhaiya.
Have you seen the banks of River Kokh?
Didi controls five such riverbanks.
Softy Bhaiya manages all of them for her.
Understood?
They supply sand to the entire country.
They earn around 7.5 million
from each riverbank every day.
Even if you and I work together
for 75 years,
we won't be able to earn
that kind of money.
You done?
Not yet.
Wait till I introduce you to them.
Look, these people like
to show off having retired soldiers
as their bodyguards.
Please don't do anything untoward today.
If we make a good impression,
they'll recruit
at least 25 watchmen from us
- for their leather factory in Kanpur.
- You've been called inside!
Yes, coming.
Let's go. At least wear a fake smile.
Even I've swallowed my pride.
- For shame, old man.
- As you say.
Prabhakar Security Services.
Will he be able to protect himself?
So, old man,
you don't have any ailments, do you?
- BP? Gout? Blood sugar?
- No.
No, Softy Bhaiya,
he has no such problems. None at all.
What was your rank?
Subedaar.
Subedaar...
- Hey.
- Yes, Bhaiya?
What was Shyamcharan's bodyguard's rank?
Bhaiya, he said he was
a Subedaar-Major.
- Major? Doesn't look like a Major
at all. -That's right.
More like a minor.
This man is a Major.
Tell me, which rank is higher?
Subedaar or Subedaar-Major?
Major.
Prabhakar...
- You've failed, man.
- Why, Softy Bhaiya?
Who have you brought?
What did I tell you?
I wanted someone senior, not older.
Where are his badges and medals?
What will he hang on his chest?
Shyamcharan's guy
used to hang five of them.
Even he has them.
He does, Softy Bhaiya. Many.
He doesn't show them off
because he's a bit shy.
From now on,
if anyone asks you your rank,
you need to say you're a Subedaar-Major.
Stay alert.
Ranju!
Madam Ranju is being very wise!
She's acting brave and wants to testify!
Get lost!
Want me to get you a lawyer?
You'll testify in court?
You'll file a case?
What do you think will happen?
You should've come to me.
I would've got you justice
the way I did your brother.
Should I?
Well?
'No...'
What is this?
- What is this? -My brother was shot
right in front of me.
- What is this? -Prince, Softy...
They were all there.
- Forgive me.
- 'Forgive me...'
- You guys love being on TV,
don't you? -Forgive me...
- You like being on TV?
- Forgive me...
I should've shot you right there
but these idiots said, 'Let her go!
She's a woman'! The hell!
My bad!
It's because I'm a good man!
Take her inside!
And don't let her out till I tell you to!
You're our bloody servants!
You live off our scraps
yet you dare challenge us!
I'll bury the whole lot of you
in the sand!
Take her inside!
Red Gypsy with number plate 2109!
Whose is it?
Mine.
How can it be yours?
- Move it...
- 21-09 is my birthday.
So, it belongs to me.
Give me the keys.
Come on.
- Move it...
- Hey!
What the hell are you staring at?
- Who are these people?
- Why are you irritating him?
He's a bodyguard.
Military.
Didi.
Yes, Didi?
- Where are you? -Let's go.
We leave in ten minutes.
- At the quarters.
- Will he come dressed like this?
- Make him wear a uniform.
Safari suit. -Okay.
Let's go!
At ease, soldier.
I'm reminding you...
Please don't do anything untoward today.
I'm going to Kanpur.
I'll be back tomorrow.
And don't create any trouble
till then, please.
- Come on...
- You nitwit!
Bang!
Bang.
Stop crying!
Walk straight.
Go in!
- Come, kiddo, I'll give you candy.
- Hey, Subedaar!
- Let's go!
- Come on! Get in!
I said be quiet!
Just go in!
Keep quiet!
How did you get a new number
without an ID?
Why are you so scared?
Ranveer.
I need to talk to you.
It's okay, sit.
The videos you send me,
those ones...
My inbox is full.
So, I was thinking...
Should we watch it together?
- With your mother?
- The hell--
Got it?
Got it now.
This is Ranveer,
a 2nd year student at Sheel College,
who studies B.Com.
- He sends me obscene videos
every single day. -Hey...
I've told him a thousand times
not to do so but he just doesn't get it--
- Stop recording this, Kajal.
- That's why I...
- Stop recording or I'll break the phone!
- That's why I'm making this video!
- Sit down! Sit!
- Can't you understand? Just stop!
Let's go!
- Ranveer...
- Shut up!
Tell me, Subedaar.
What's your favourite song?
Let me guess.
The entire village salutes me
when I pass by!
I call him Mr. Chaudhary, oh, my!
My lover, the cop, drives a Gypsy!
My lover-- Hey...
Why are you honking?
Use the hooter!
Spray this every day.
Big enjoy!
Hey, why are you irritating him?
'Irritating him?'
I'm thinking
of stirring him up completely.
You had stirred things up two months back.
We all saw the result.
The riverbank was closed for two weeks.
We lost millions.
- We also had to deal
with court cases. -Hey, Softy!
Don't try to father me.
Stop the car.
Stop the car!
Fucker...
Who the hell hired this oldie as a driver?
I'll show you how it's done.
Get out!
Now this is what we call speed!
You should meet the 5th gear sometime.
Understood, Subedaar?
Open the glove box.
Prepare my tobacco mix.
- I don't know how to.
- Then what the hell do you know?
You don't know how to drive,
how to prepare the mix...
Do you even know how to salute?
You better get used to it.
Open that and rub
the masala.
O my lover, the cop,
hurry up and mix the masala
Hurry up...
Gypsy...
Gypsy.
Gypsy... Hurry up...
Hurry up...
WOMEN'S PRISON
(DISTRICT KOKH, MAHAPRADESH)
Didi.
I've rounded up both the mother and son.
Just give me the order.
I'll bury them inside the warehouse.
- Avdhesh.
- Yes, Didi?
Since how many months have I been here?
Didi, I'm trying my level best.
Really?
You just sit in court all day,
in your stupid black coat.
You'll be more useful as a scarecrow
scaring away crows in my fields.
Think you can try that?
Well, Didi, the gun you used is missing.
I had asked for bail based on that.
But the boy, whom Prince Bhaiya
shot at the riverbank...
The same gun was used in that incident.
I'm not saying that.
That's what's written in the report.
That's the problem.
What's the point of being a lawyer, then?
Change the report!
- It's no big deal--
- Say 'keep quiet'.
Softy.
No.
Say, 'Keep quiet, asshole'.
Keep quiet, asshole.
Hey, scarecrow.
You give it a try.
- Keep quiet, asshole!
- Smashing!
So, what did you understand,
bloody asshole?
It takes just a few seconds
for fortune to change.
If you weren't my late father
Lallan Singh's illegitimate child,
I'd have thrashed you right here!
Did you have to use the same gun?
I don't want any more trouble
until my court hearing!
Don't touch the mother and son.
And don't let them escape either.
You scrawny little fellow,
where did you get so much courage from?
Bhaiya, I got carried away.
- 'Carried away?' You brewed up
a storm! -I didn't mean it.
Here you go.
Six. Your turn.
- Hold on, I'll make my move.
Why the rush? -Come on, roll.
Today, I'm going to beat you for sure.
Go on, it's your turn.
- Guddu!
- Yes, Bhaiya?
- Where's the soldier?
- He left.
He said his hand was itching.
I'll take your leave.
- Mr. Avdhesh!
- Yes, Bhaiya?
- Where are you going?
- Just around the corner.
Come with me.
I'll drop you wherever you like.
- No, it's okay, Bhaiya.
I'm better off on my cycle-- -No?
- You're going to turn me down?
Come on! -No, Bhaiya--
Actually, Bhaiya,
I'm scared of riding in cars. Bhaiya!
Too many incidents of cars
flipping over nowadays...
Untie me!
Bhaiya!
Untie me! I'm scared!
I said it by mistake!
Untie me! Bhaiya!
- Bhaiya! Please come back!
Untie me! -Hey, scarecrow!
SUDHA NIVAS
The government is mired in the controversy
following the Krishna murder case
in Bhetod district
and its links to the sand mafia.
The court has strongly reprimanded
the administration.
There are two questions
that the administration must answer.
First, where has the eye-witness,
Ranju Devi, been for the past two days?
And second,
where is the murder weapon?
My brother was shot right in front of me.
Prince, Softy...
They were all there.
Will Ranju Devi be able
to appear in court?
PARKING
The inter-university tournament
will start the day-after-tomorrow.
I'll have to stay in Kanpur for two days.
The soles of your shoes are coming off.
Come to the military store
with me tomorrow.
Why don't you sell
these leftover pickle bottles
at Mr. Lahori's shop?
Drink the milk.
Mom used to add almond powder.
Hey...
Stop...
Hey, old man!
Move your car right now.
Bhaiya's car will be parked here.
Hurry up.
I think he got offended!
He got offended!
Come, Bhaiya!
Come! Come... Come!
What happened, old man?
Move your car.
I'm getting late.
Me too.
I need to get my hair styled.
The hair on my head.
You're too funny, Bhaiya!
Park your car somewhere else.
This is my parking spot.
What happened?
Where are you off to?
Yesterday, you left without informing me.
Do you think I'll bite you or what?
Sudha Devi.
Your wife?
Your wife or someone else's?
Big enjoy.
Arjun Maurya.
Take the keys and move your car.
Bless you... not.
- Move aside.
- The hell!
I'm being respectful
because you're my father's age
but you don't seem to care.
What's the name... of your father?
Are you pulling my leg?
Fine.
Late Lallan Pratap Singh.
Does this road
legally belong to your father,
- Lallan Pratap Singh?
- No, don't...
You can go, Subedaar.
You've rendered me emotional.
Move.
And make sure
nothing happens to Subedaar's Gypsy!
Don't get carried away
and make scratches on it,
or vandalize the car
or puncture the tires...
Don't do any of these things!
Got it?
Hey, old man!
- Why such drama... Just kill me...
- Oh, stop it... Get out of here...
- Just end it once and for all...
It's my money... -Sir...
- Bring your officer here... This is
going overboard... -You don't get it...
- I don't care! It's my money!
Give me my money! -Get her out of here!
This is my final warning!
I'm going to call the police!
Oh, no!
Sir, please come back tomorrow.
I can't deal with this today.
Hey!
What are you staring at?
It's tea. It got spilled!
Here, take this form.
Fill it up and come back again.
Please leave!
You fill up the form.
What!
What did you say?
You fill up the form, sir.
Subedaar, you're going to
fill up the form yourself!
And get it back tomorrow.
You said the same thing yesterday.
Did I tell you not to come?
I'm just telling you to come again!
It's positive.
With positive energy, got it?
Come tomorrow!
Positive energy...
Don't you understand?
Come on, leave!
Mommy...
- Can you hear me? Hey, stop her!
- I'll set myself on fire!
- I'll set myself on fire! -Crazy woman!
What the hell are you doing?
- Have you lost your mind...
Get the hell out... -It's my money...
Your wife?
Did I tell you not to come?
Take the keys and move your car.
I'm just telling you to come again!
Come tomorrow!
With positive energy, got it?
Don't get carried away
and make scratches on it,
or vandalize the car
or puncture the tires...
- Don't you understand?
- Hey, old man!
Sorry, old man.
Please look away, Ms. Sudha.
Hey...
What's wrong, old man?
You look pissed.
Should we get him wet too?
The hell...
Bhaiya...
Prince Bhaiya...
Prince Bhaiya!
Bhaiya!
Bhaiya! Prince Bhaiya...
Were you missing me terribly?
SUBEDAAR
Keep the change ready.
Take it!
Let's go!
Get up.
Take off your clothes.
Clean it.
I'll be back.
Listen up, old man!
I'll come after you.
Go straight from Chaurangi Gali
station crossing,
right after the fourth lane,
behind Lahori General Store,
Plot No. 144, Sudha Nivas.
And if you still get lost,
just ask anyone,
'Where does the mustached soldier live'?
That person will escort you personally.
Kiddo... go home.
Your mother must be waiting for you.
Bhaiya...
Hey, come on...
Hey, kabaddi champion!
Listen carefully.
Don't even dare to think
of uploading that video.
This time, it was water.
You know what it'll be the next time.
You know, right?
Understood, everyone?
Hello, Romeo.
- Your timing is superb.
- Take your hands off me.
Juliet is completely wet.
Go make the most of it.
- Why, you... -You asshole...
Let go of my collar!
- Rajan...
- Got mad, did you?
- Rajan!
- Leave him...
- Listen to her.
- This is my fight!
Listen to what Juliet is saying...
You don't need to act like a hot-shot.
- Did you hear that?
- This iron lady will deal with them.
- This is her fight.
- Get lost!
I know that 22 trucks have left.
I'll call you back.
What happened?
What do you want to eat?
- What happened?
- Just tell me what you want to eat!
What's up, oldie?
- Bhaiya... Sorry...
- You think it's funny?
Big enjoy?
Bhaiya, please let dad go.
- Staring and laughing at me!
- Please stop, Bhaiya...
Where's the gun?
Guddu, where's the gun?
Why did you have to get involved in this?
You could've just parked your car
somewhere else. It was no big deal.
I'm talking to you.
You're behaving as if nothing happened.
You beat up Babli Didi's brother
in the middle of a street.
What else should I have done?
Clean his piss?
Do you have any idea
who these people are?
They aren't small-time hooligans.
They're a part of a gang.
Seems like you know them well.
Yet you want to work with them.
Despite getting humiliated, you still
want me to be a part of the circus!
Of course! Seems like
you're the only one around here
who's wearing his pride loud and proud.
And I do no such thing.
Sorry.
I never said that.
You feel so.
Arjun, all I'm saying is
that our families, our children,
they all live here.
And this is where we have to live.
And this isn't the border, it's the city!
I took a bullet for these people
but I won't put up with these insults.
You have to change your ways, pal.
Forget you were a soldier once.
Welcome to real life.
9,125.
What!
9,125 days add up to 25 years.
I gave 25 years of my life to the army.
But how many days did Sudha
and my family get?
700 days.
I could never repay her
for that.
She sold pickles and sewed clothes
so that Subedaar could own a Gypsy.
If anyone...
If anyone touches the car,
I'll rip him apart!
At ease, soldier.
These guys are extremely dangerous.
And I always thought that the ones
across the border are our enemies!
Arjun, please.
Make peace with them.
Softy has called me up twice already.
Those rascals are just mooching off
what their forefathers built!
I refuse to speak to them!
Take a little hit
in your business, Prabhakar.
I'll make it up to you someday.
Take this.
This is all that's left.
Mr. Prabhakar?
Hello, champion.
What's up?
- When did you arrive?
- He's leaving.
Dinner?
I've had enough.
Softy and Prince's men
might attack tonight.
Let me know if you need back-up.
Did I ever ask for back-up on the border?
- Hero...
- Get lost!
Hero...
And I'm a big zero...
I've made an advance payment
for the Gypsy, Subedaarji.
And now, I'm making
stuffed-chili pickle.
It's so spicy!
Just like me.
Want to taste it?
- No, everything's great.
- 'Great?'
Rubbish!
But the sari that I'm wearing
is great!
The blouse strings
need to be tied at the back.
- If you pull them--
- How is Shyama?
Why are you changing the topic?
Are you feeling shy?
Yes, it's quite hot.
Come over, then.
I'll help you cool down.
Yes, I'll come over soon.
Come on, say it once...
'I love you, Sudha.'
I've been waiting
to hear that for 25 years.
Say it once.
Er...
What happened?
Not 'what happened'!
Say, 'I love you, Sudha'!
- Say it or I'll jump!
- Yes... No...
Come on, just say it, Subedaarji.
Just say, 'I love you', sir.
Er...
I'll call you later.
I love you, Sudha.
Sudha...
Is everything fine?
How about you?
All good.
FEAR
Box!
Who threw this net so wide?
A fish got caught
The boy and girl's stars shine bright
Who threw this net so wide?
A fish got caught
Box!
When I walk around exuding my swag
The style quotient goes up high!
When the fire spreads all around
The speed shoots up, it can't be bound!
Who here's got the guts to fight?
No one, my friend.
I own the night!
The father-in-law
asks the daughter-in-law...
Where is the tobacco box?
The father-in-law asks
the servant named Raju...
Where is the tobacco...
Where is the tobacco box?
Tobacco...
He's here.
He's here!
- Who's the guy with a knife?
- He's here...
The old man is here!
He looks very angry!
Hey, old man!
- Is the knife still sharp?
- Come on!
We're coming!
- Hey, Shyama!
We're here.
Should we come inside?
Take your dad away!
He ran away...
Parade...
Shyama, come outside!
We're here...
- Kabaddi...
- Come outside...
We're here!
This is my last warning, Shyama.
Don't you dare upload the video.
Do you understand?
What happened, Shyama?
Shyama, are you okay?
Shyama!
Shyama...
Shyama, open the door.
Shyama!
Shyama...
Ranveer!
- Ranveer.
- Yes, mom?
What are you doing here?
She says she's here to meet the groom!
I'll be right there, mom!
Wait!
I couldn't wait to tell you, ma'am.
Our Ranveer is about to become famous
in the next hour.
I thought his family should know
about his antics first, am I right?
What's she talking about?
I can't understand a thing.
Our relationship is complicated, ma'am.
He had shown up last night.
He left something behind this morning.
So, even I wanted to give him something.
Return gift.
'Gift?'
One hour to go, ma'am.
Before the video premieres.
- 'Video?' Video...
- Bye.
Video...
I'll see her off.
Hey, Shyama. Stop!
Careful with your towel, boy.
Had I met him earlier,
you'd have been the uncle to the kids
of this guy and mine,
- Shashikant.
- Give it to me...
What?
You got beaten up
in the middle of a street
yet you're acting all macho.
So, Softy...
We've lost face
and our gun as well.
Didi, I'll get the gun back.
I'm working on it.
I request you to please let me
handle this my way.
It'll be in everyone's best interest.
- What do you mean?
- Didn't he tell you
that he threw bottles of piss
at the army man's house?
Should I have given him sweets instead?
Not everything is directed
as a personal attack on you!
'Personal attack...'
I have to manage Didi's bail,
the riverbanks and other things.
So? Have I stopped you
from doing your work?
Just do as you're told!
- Am I your bloody servant?
- What nonsense!
Don't pick it up, Fatima.
You can leave.
Your brother will do the needful.
After my mother died,
our father had her silver jewelry melted
and embossed on the gun in her memory!
Then he got his name
engraved on it! Lallan Singh!
Of course you won't understand this.
She wasn't your mother.
I want that gun back.
End of story!
And if you fail to bring it,
I'll strip you naked
and plaster your posters
all over the town!
Now, get lost.
- Hey, Manoj.
- Yes, sir?
Has anyone lodged an FIR on Didi's behalf?
No.
Then why are you here, sir?
It's a good thing you beat him up.
That rascal has made
all our lives a living hell!
There are two cases of murder
filed against him.
Sir.
Please lodge the FIR.
Mr. Prabhakar, you tell me what to write.
I told you before...
There's no point
coming down to the police station.
Now, he's calling me up.
Softy!
Do you have the gun?
If you do, return it.
It's a gun, not a loan
that it needs to be returned.
Hero...
Listen, I'm going to the military store.
Let me know if you need anything.
- Get a pair of shoes for Shyama.
- Okay. Size?
Never mind, I'll figure it out.
Hey, start the car!
Hello?
What is it?
Can't get your car out?
Look to your right, this way.
Munna here.
Care of Didi.
You look very angry.
Move your car.
And if I don't?
He'll beat you up, Munna.
What else can he possibly do?
Really?
Move your car, sonny boy.
Damn it! He's made you
his family now, Munna!
He called you sonny boy!
I keep calling him 'old man'
but he keeps ignoring this kiddo!
I hope the cops at the police station
didn't ignore you.
Did they write down the FIR
or should I talk to them?
What did you think would happen, Subedaar?
That you'll beat me up
in front of everyone
and I'll just let it go?
Move the car.
First, return the gun.
Why?
Did you lose the gun?
You have contacts
in the police department.
Go... lodge an FIR.
- Hey!
- Wait...
Jewelry suits queens and swag suits kings.
This line hit me when I saw you
and I'll dedicate it to you
posthumously!
Move the car!
- Make sure there aren't any scratches!
- Moving it...
My lover, Subedaar, drives a Gypsy.
Hey, old man!
ANGER
No... Spare me...
I didn't do anything!
- Subedaarji, my keys...
Well... -Come tomorrow.
The hell...
...who studies B.Com.
He sends me obscene videos
every single day.
I've told him a thousand times
not to do so but he just doesn't get it--
- Stop recording this, Kajal.
- That's why I...
- Stop recording or I'll break the phone!
- That's why I'm making this video!
- Sit down! Sit!
- Can't you understand? Just stop!
What is your name?
Ranveer.
And yours?
- Sir, Ranbir.
- What!
- Sir, with a 'B'.
- Okay...
- And are you Vicky?
- No, Kaushal.
Sir, Rajpal.
Ask your guardians to come meet me!
Even they should know
what their wards are up to!
Get out!
I'll take the necessary
disciplinary action against them, but
please delete the video, Shyama.
It's maligning the reputation
of our college.
Please delete the video.
Please.
And you all!
Bloody rascals!
Get out!
Wait, let me drop you at the stadium.
Why?
Are you my bodyguard?
- Something like that.
- Fine, follow me, then.
Shyama.
Don't be angry.
Why just grab my hand?
Hug me while you're at it.
I might just do it.
Let go of my hand.
- Listen to me. -Let go.
I'm not in the mood for this.
- Come on... -Let go... Let go of my hand.
Just let go of my hand!
I'll follow you!
Why the hell do you get so mad?
Hey, Shyama.
What were you talking to Shyama about?
Why do you care?
Hey...
- Hey...
- You dare stop her!
- Hey! Have you lost it?
- You dare hold her hand!
- Leave him!
- Let go!
Get lost!
Sir...
- Hey... Stop... -Rascal!
If I see you anywhere near her again,
- I'll bury you alive!
- Mind your business!
I'll bury you alive! -Let's go...
Sir...
Please... Let's go...
Let go of me!
- Hey...
- You dare stop her!
- Hey! Have you lost it?
- You dare hold her hand!
- Leave him!
- Let go!
What happened?
Get lost!
Hey...
Stop...
Mr. Prabhakar,
does he have mental health issues?
No, nothing of that sort, sir.
It was a mistake.
From a distance,
it seemed as if Prince's goon
was troubling his daughter.
That's why he beat him up.
- Please let this slide...
- No way.
I can't do anything in this case.
It's up to the boy's family now.
All I'm saying is,
- don't get the family involved--
- Where is he?
His daughter is here.
- Why did you beat up Rajan?
Hold on... -Why are you here?
- Let me talk... Why did you beat Rajan?
- Listen to me...
- One second, let me speak...
- Listen to me.
- Hey...
- He's been hospitalized!
- He has a head injury!
- Hey!
- Will you please say something?
- Shut the hell up!
- Listen... -Dad...
He's my friend...
Friend!
Any lady constable around?
Send her here!
Prabhakar, take her away.
- Prabhakar.
- Let's go home and talk. Let's go.
- He has a head injury...
- Sorry... Let's go...
What's there to talk about?
Has he ever explained anything?
Bhaiya, we didn't find the gun.
Look behind the sofa.
Hey, Subedaar,
why are you getting involved in this?
Be like me.
See very little and forget everything.
- What do you say, Manoj?
- Yes, sir.
You're right.
Sign here.
It's a good thing the boy's family
didn't file an FIR.
You got lucky this time.
This isn't the border,
where you start a war
over the smallest of issues.
Go home and enjoy your freedom.
Shyama had told me, 'Dad is very strict'.
But I hadn't imagined
that I'd get beaten up so badly.
Your daughter said she won't go
to play the match.
She was here last night.
I had to scold her and send her away.
Why don't you talk to her once?
Why did those dreams,
like pearls so bright,
Slip from my eyes and fade from sight?
They were here once, in some quiet place
Why has our bond of love lost its grace?
This distance feels lonely and bare
Lying between us, just sitting there
Bring me your sorrows
Every tear,
I'll make it fade and disappear
O dear friend
My beloved has come home
Blessings have entered
My courtyard
Blessings have entered my courtyard...
Do you still have nothing to say?
I'm talking to you.
O dear friend
My beloved has come home
O dear friend, my beloved has come home
O dear friend
O dear friend...
What are you waiting for, Subedaar?
Go.
I WAS HERE
Take these shoes.
Who told you my size?
Mr. Prabhakar?
Dad, whatever you've done,
whatever you're doing,
whatever you're about to do...
I have absolutely no idea about it.
Not today...
Not then...
- We'll talk once you're back.
- Talk about what?
What?
That day, I kept calling you up
but you didn't answer...
I had to take mom on a stretcher... alone.
There were tubes
inside her nose and mouth...
Shyama.
Coming...
Dad, what do you even know about me?
My likes, my dislikes...
Do you know anything?
Mom would go on and on about you.
Even your war stories
were told to me by someone else.
Be it at the border
or in the city.
I'm talking too much, aren't I?
I know.
Mom used to say,
'You're just like your dad.
Always speaking bitterly'.
Go, they're waiting for you.
I'll be back
the day-after-tomorrow, in the morning.
I'll be staying at the hostel from now on.
You do what you want to.
I'll do the same.
A TRUCK RAMS INTO A SCOOTY
47 YEAR OLD SUDHA MAURYA DIES
OF RELATED INJURIES.
O husband of mine...
TRUCE
Sit.
He's a soldier.
He's used to standing for hours.
I had gone to your house.
You weren't there.
So, I left you a present.
Did you see it?
Greetings, Didi.
Let me see him.
Hmm...
This mustache is my weakness.
Tell me, soldier.
Does your gun still fire or is it empty?
I heard that your wife is no more.
Are you looking for a new one?
So, you won't feel shy
or smile either, then?
Quickly tell me what you want
and end this matter.
It's time for me to sleep... alone.
Didi, we're here to settle the matter.
All of a sudden!
That day, you were all charged up,
acting like a superhero!
Shashikant, let me speak.
- Don't interrupt!
- 'Let me speak...'
Subedaar, he's young.
That's why he's hot-headed.
You should've known better.
You should've thought it through
before raising your hand.
Did you think
you'd insult me
and I wouldn't take revenge--
Just ask him where the gun is!
You had come to look for it.
Didn't you find it?
That's right, Didi.
Prince Bhaiya went to his house
and ransacked the place.
We thought he took the gun.
Would I have called for this meeting
if he had taken it?
I want the gun.
I don't have it.
Just look at his attitude!
This is what I was telling you about.
Subedaar!
If you wanted to show us attitude,
why come for the meeting?
To end this.
'End this?'
And who started it?
You know that very well.
I did?
Who did, then?
Tell me, who pissed in the car?
So, you'll beat up the child
just because he pissed somewhere?
Hey!
I'm not a child!
I'm a soldier.
I can take a bullet to the chest
but not an insult.
Old man, I have both.
Should I give them to you?
Kiddo,
I'm giving you some advice.
Swallow your pride
and stop all this.
You think I'll stop because you said so?
Shut the door.
Subedaar, you're here for a compromise.
Just apologize and leave.
- I won't apologize.
- Then?
I'm ready to forget whatever happened.
I don't want to drag this issue anymore.
- But I want to. -Hey!
He just told you what he wants!
Even you need to do the same
and end this matter!
We're dealing with shit here but you are
going on and on like a broken record.
Fine, Didi.
I'll end this matter.
What I did on his car
is what I'll do on his face now.
And... it'll be in front of everyone.
Then we'll call it quits, okay?
Okay.
Do whatever you have to
but just end it quickly.
I'm sleepy.
Sweet dreams, Mr. Mustache.
Let's leave, Prabhakar.
- This is wrong.
- Prabhakar...
- Go stop him.
- You should've stopped him instead!
- We were here to settle the matter!
- Stop him.
- This is entirely your fault,
Softy Bhaiya. -Let's go, Prabhakar!
He literally pissed on all our efforts!
He loves to piss!
- Hey... -So, why the hell
are you calling him back?
You know what?
Your father had come to meet me.
Honest.
He stood here and said,
'Sonny boy, I beat you.
I'm sorry'.
Rajan.
I don't want to talk about him.
Bye.
It's time for my flight.
Listen.
Please take care.
You need to take care of yourself first.
Go straight home once you're back.
Don't act like you're my dad!
- This isn't done, Softy Bhaiya...
He pissed... -Don't you dare...
Hey!
Enough of standing at ease.
So much for making peace...
Hey!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me
But you didn't listen, no way
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way
Understood?
- Just see what you can do.
- Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me...
But you didn't listen, no way...
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me...
Welcome, kids.
Use of weapons inside the school premises
is prohibited.
Listen carefully.
If you want a long and healthy life,
keep reciting the prayer.
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me...
- But you didn't listen, no way...
- Louder!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me
But you didn't listen, no way...
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me...
Kiddo,
don't complain later
that the old man took your gun.
Why isn't he answering his phone?
Hey, kiddo!
I told you...
Be careful!
Hey, boy!
I told you...
You better listen!
Little boy, you better stay away
Or this fire will burn you, okay?
Don't poke your finger into the burrow!
There's a mouse inside...
It'll bite!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way!
Take them with you.
I'll join you.
Stay out of my way!
Let's go, Arjun!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way!
Stay out of my way!
Hey, oldie!
Oldie!
BEWARE
You are my only refuge, O Lord
O Lord...
Don't be scared.
No one will come here.
No one comes to this village.
Outsiders refuse to come here.
Why are you saving us?
Wait till morning.
Then we'll talk.
Drop us off at our village in the morning.
You're not safe there
till the court hearing.
'Safe?'
Where are we remotely safe?
Tell me.
What!
Both mother and son escaped!
When they were here to talk,
he should've made peace.
But no, he had to act all macho!
They've taken her away.
Now, we'll have to clean up this mess!
You expect me to clean it?
Both of you need to take your shoes off.
Take them off.
Now!
And hit each other with them!
We've already taken a hit, Didi.
You rascal!
You're the one who insisted
on making peace!
That woman escaped because of you!
- Bhaiya, please listen...
- Shut up!
You're going to make me understand?
You're on Softy's team now?
- I'm... I'm on your team...
- Shut the hell up!
Didi, just look at the assholes
Softy has hired!
Now, I'll show them how it's done!
Asshole!
Have you spoken to Shyama?
She's angry with me.
She isn't answering her phone.
Give her some time.
She'll understand.
It's my mistake, not hers.
I could never make her understand.
Come on, move it!
Secure this rascal.
- I'll go speak with Major.
- Yes, sir.
Go inside!
Hey, stop!
Don't move!
The hell!
Hey!
Dad... Dad,
mom met with an accident!
Please call me back.
Mr. Prabhakar is out of town.
Please call me, dad.
I don't know what to do!
Call me, dad...
I've brought mom to the hospital.
She's unconscious, dad.
The doctor said
mom's condition is very serious.
I'm very scared, dad...
Please call me...
Hey!
Mom is no more, dad...
Mom is no more...
Soldier.
Ready?
Attention.
- All the best.
- Bye!
Prabhakar, I'm going to the bus stand
to pick up Shyama.
You'll see...
Today, the father will make peace
with his daughter.
If I don't return,
don't receive my calls.
And don't call me up
until everything is ready.
The passengers are requested to...
- Come on! Come on!
- Shyama! Shyama!
Hey!
Shyama!
- Shyama!
- Move it!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Move it! Move it!
Hey!
Shyama!
Hello?
I want to speak to Prince Bhaiya.
Shut up!
Want to fight back?
The hell!
Who's in that car?
Who's following us?
Faster!
Shyama...
He's alive!
Get her out.
Hold her.
Kaushal, hold her.
Come on.
- Time to give you a medal.
- Move it!
Shut up and walk!
You refused to understand.
Now, wait and watch
how I make your video go viral.
She's been humiliated enough.
Stop now.
- Or we'll be in trouble--
- What! 'Humiliated enough?'
Just shut up!
If you're so scared,
go stand guard outside!
Have you lost your mind?
- What if she goes back
and testifies against us? -Quiet!
'Goes back...'
Why the hell are you so scared?
We'll take turns to enjoy ourselves.
We'll throw her in the furnace
when we're done.
I refuse to be a part of this!
Hey!
Rajpal!
Hey, Ranveer.
Let's go convince him.
- If he blabs, we'll be in trouble!
- Damn it...
- He'll be back.
- Let's go, guys.
- Let's go!
So, Subedaar...
Should I piss on you now?
Nice and warm!
Answer me, oldie,
or I'll tear you to pieces.
Tell me!
Hey, don't take this gun of mine.
I'm asking you one last time...
Where have you hidden the mother and son?
- Where is Shyama?
- What!
Where is Shyama?
Who's that?
Who is it?
Did you hit your head
or something, Subedaar?
Don't stare.
Tell me.
Don't stare!
Tell me!
- Where is Ranju?
- Where is my daughter?
Where is Ranju...
Where the hell is Ranju?
Take her clothes off.
Come on, take them off.
Take them off!
You think you're strong?
Catch her!
Why, you... Catch her...
Grab her legs...
The hell...
Just grab her god-damn legs!
- Grab them...
The hell... -Hold this.
- We'll kill you... Grab her arms...
- I'll kill you! Shut up! Shut up!
Grab her!
Come on!
- Shut up!
- Come on!
Get up!
The bitch has gone mad!
Kill the bitch!
Kill her!
You're going to make a video?
You bitch!
Come on, rip her clothes off!
Catch her!
Look!
I'm Ranveer!
Sheel College, B.Com, 2nd year!
And now, I'll get you liked,
shared and subscribed as well!
- Shoot the video.
- Sure.
Take them off!
Hey, Shyama!
Hey!
Get her!
She's getting away!
Stop!
Get her!
Where did she go?
Hey, stop!
Where do you think you're going?
- Catch her!
- Stop!
Ranveer, catch her!
Hey!
Hey...
Catch her!
Catch her! Hey!
Catch her! Quick!
Catch her...
What now, kiddo?
Should I open fire?
I told you
- to untie her--
- Hey! Sit!
Hey...
Hurry up... Run...
Didi.
I've been working with you for years.
Have I ever stopped you
from doing anything?
Tell me.
Don't try these emotional tactics with me.
If you want to ask something,
ask directly.
Okay, I'll be direct.
- Did you get his daughter kidnapped?
- Whose?
Didi, things are very tense right now.
I've already told you, you don't have
the administration's support!
So?
Big deal.
Even you can leave.
Take her as well.
Both of you can go hide behind a veil.
I am Lallan Singh's daughter.
My father taught me only one thing...
Once the fear is gone, the game is over.
Didi, you're being unreasonable.
And Prince is like a bull on the loose.
This is my last warning. Get that
asshole brother of yours to surrender.
- Hey!
- Enough, Babli!
I may no longer be a goon
but I haven't forgotten it.
Take care.
What are you staring at?
Get out!
Leave!
Hey.
If I don't return,
don't receive my calls.
And don't call me up
until everything is ready.
Your friend isn't receiving your calls.
Shyama?
Dad?
- Hello?
- My child...
Who's this?
Your dad met with an accident, my child.
- What!
- He was asking for you.
Should I send a car for you?
Where is he?
Where is dad?
Where are you?
Get in!
Move it!
Come on!
WINNER
- Hello?
- I want to speak to Subedaar.
- Here.
- Soldier, is everything okay?
All good.
Should I come?
- Or will you?
- You come.
With Subedaar.
ATTACK
Dad, mom met with an accident!
Please call me back.
The doctor said
mom's condition is very serious.
I'm very scared, dad...
I've brought mom to the hospital.
Mom is no more, dad...
My phone was right there, my child...
Dad...
Mom always used to say,
'Your dad is a troublemaker'.
Your mom was no less.
She used to say the same thing about you.
You think all this is
a part of mom's plan?
She's probably getting bored up there.
Maybe that's why she wants us up there.
Want to go?
One by one,
I'll bury them all!
Puncture...
Ten minutes...
TEN MINUTES
Where is Softy?
He said his car broke down.
Hey!
Quiet!
Let Didi come online.
I'll kill you all in front of her.
What do you say, Subedaar?
'Safe?'
Where are we remotely safe?
I'll be back.
Hey, Subedaar!
Hey!
Hey, old man!
- Where do you think you're going?
- Hey, Subedaar!
Stop!
Or I'll shoot you!
Wait.
Are you running away like a coward?
- Shyama...
- Bhaiya...
Hey, stop!
Hey...
- Kabaddi...
- Shyama...
- Ten minutes...
- Kabaddi... Hey...
You still up for a fight?
Bhaiya...
Big enjoy!
Hero...
- Hero!
- Mr. Prabhakar...
Mr. Prabhakar...
Where are you off to, Subedaar?
Left, right, left, right.
Stop!
Hey, old man.
FIVE MINUTES
Turn around!
Old man, you just wouldn't let things be!
Old man, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Today is the old man's last day!
First, drink my piss.
Then I'll kill you.
Soldier, are you ready?
- Hey! -Hey!
I'll crack your dad's skull open!
Quiet!
Sit!
- Soldier is ready...
- What!
What are you mumbling?
Soldier is ready.
Say it loudly.
Don't make me say it.
Old man.
Say it loudly.
Soldier is ready!
Puncture!
I purposely didn't hit the target!
That was a warning shot!
You don't deserve a soldier's bullet!
You, scrawny brat!
You think you can piss on Subedaar?
If I don't send you all to your graves,
you can call Nana Waghmare
by any name you like!
I'm a retired soldier,
not a tired one!
Got it?
Look around you!
You'll spot a retired soldier
atop every single hill!
It took me a little longer, kiddo,
because I was putting together
a battalion, not a mob.
Soldiers, ready?
Lance Naik Nana Waghmare ready, sir!
Lance Naik Ram Avatar Singh ready, sir!
Havildar Bhupender Singh ready, sir!
Subedaar Ramadheer Singh ready, sir!
Hey, Guddu!
Call...
Call up Softy!
Guddu, leave.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Hey, Guddu!
Is that Softy?
Softy Bhaiya said...
'This guy wanted to drown him in his piss.
Now, let him drown in it!'
What did you say?
Boys, let's go!
Big enjoy!
Stop!
Hey, Guddu!
I, Prince, swear I'll get you for this!
- Get lost.
- Shyama...
I can fire this
but I won't.
This is where you and I are different.
Let's go.
You want everyone to bow down before you
while we just want to live
with our heads held high.
Let us live.
Let us live!
Let us live...
Mannu!
What happened to Prince after that?
Prince?
And Subedaar?
Hey, Subedaar!
What did you think?
That it's all over?
I've brought you a gift!
Join hands with me or die.
With love!
Yours, Softy!
BEGINNING
Hey, kiddo!
I told you...
Be careful!
Hey, boy!
I told you...
You better listen!
Little boy, you better stay away
Or this fire will burn you, okay?
Don't poke your finger into the burrow!
There's a mouse inside...
It'll bite!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way!
Hey, boy!
It was you, wasn't it?
Stay the hell away, you're garbage!
I told you...
I spoke in your language!
Didn't you get it?
Pay attention, you twit!
Didn't you hear it?
You better head to your estate!
It's getting late!
Got it?
If you trip and fall,
you'll get injured and all!
For you, your mother will wait and fret!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way!
Kiddo, you just wouldn't let things be!
Kiddo, I warned you not to cross me!
But you didn't listen, no way!
Kiddo, you best stay out of my way!
Stay out of my way!