Whether or not a person
commits a crime,
no one cares...
If the crime can be proven,
then they're guilty.
Otherwise, they're not.
I'm innocent, Mr. Shyam.
You know that, right?
I was just doing my job.
Don't lose hope.
We'll appeal to the High Court.
But how?
How will I afford it?
It's over for me.
SYSTEM
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Neha Ma'am...
Thank you.
Sorry.
Thanks.
STATE VS JAGDISH SINGH
Hi, Atmaram.
Hi, Neha...
Sorry, I...
The first day of trial...
feels like an exam.
Aren't you nervous?
People get nervous before the results.
You're already panicking!
It looks like the defence
has done all their homework...
Four times over!
Chill, dude. Relax.
Have some water.
Ahlawat Sir is here.
All rise.
Honourable Judge presiding.
Matter of State versus Jagdish Singh
is now in session.
Sir, on the night
of 3rd October
an informant called me.
He told me that there's a nightclub
called Eclipse in our jurisdiction...
where illegal drugs
are consumed and sold.
So, at 11:30 that night,
with a full police convoy in tow...
I raided the nightclub.
What did you find during that raid?
The club was mostly empty.
But then I checked the bathroom...
The real party was there!
One of the cubicles was locked.
We knocked the door.
I told the person to come out.
The person inside didn't respond,
so, we broke open the door.
And who was this person sitting inside?
He's sitting right here.
Mr. Jagdish Singh.
The owner of Eclipse bar.
So as per due process,
did you take the accused
for a medical test?
Of course.
Cocaine was detected
in the blood test.
Did your team collect any
other evidence during the raid?
Yes, during the search,
we found 100 grams of cocaine
in one of the bar drawers.
Thank you. No further
questions, Your Honour.
Inspector Rathi,
if I heard correctly,
you said that you found
my client in the bathroom.
You have sharp ears!
You heard me right.
When you knocked on the bathroom door,
did you say that
you're the police?
Of course!
Why would I feel shy saying 'police'!
Silence, please.
May I ask you a personal question?
-Be my guest.
-If you're in the toilet,
and someone knocks the door,
do you just open it?
I'm not into that kind
of public service, sir!
Silence.
As per your report, you found
100 grams of cocaine at the club.
103 grams, to be exact.
But you found the cocaine
in the bar area, right?
-Yes.
-Isn't it possible that someone
from the staff was dealing
in drugs?
Did you find my client's fingerprints
on the packet?
-No.
-Was my client Jagdish Singh
found anywhere near the drugs?
No, sir.
So, anyone could
have put the packet there.
You included, Inspector Rathi.
-Objection.
-Overruled.
Overruled.
Mr. Singh, who all have access
to your back office?
It's not a restricted area, ma'am.
It's open to everyone.
You're welcome too!
But I hardly go there these days.
Sometimes for weeks.
Surely you have a way
to keep tabs on your staff?
We have CCTV cameras,
but they've been defunct for a while.
I've been meaning to fix them,
but I'm so busy I keep forgetting.
I have so many businesses, you see.
Of course.
Your Honour, it's so funny...
Whenever CCTV cameras
are needed, they never work.
So Mr. Singh,
there's no way to know
if you went to the bar area that day?
-Objection, Your Honour.
-Sustained.
Sustained.
It's not enough
for the prosecution to show
that the defendant
possibly committed the crime.
You must prove that he
has committed the crime.
No further questions, Your Honour.
We'll adjourn for the day,
and the court will resume
tomorrow at 9,
for the closing arguments.
-Neha!
-Hello, sir.
I'm taking over this case from you.
Sir...
Please don't do this.
Let me fight.
We can still win this!
Forget winning,
even getting Jaggi into rehab
looks tough now.
Sir, please, sir. One last chance.
I won't disappoint you.
Let me think about it.
Sir!
Don't take his words to heart.
He's just a grump.
Chill.
Thank you, Ravi.
Brilliant as always.
Yes. The look on their faces!
And you handled him well.
Thanks!
Sir, sir...
Just a question!
One by one, please.
One at a time.
Mr. Rajvansh,
What would you like to say
about today's judgment?
I'm really happy that my client,
Mr. Vikram Bajral
has been given a clean chit
by the court.
This judgment is proof
that courts are indeed
temples of justice.
But sir, this isn't a first.
Your client has been accused
of land-grabbing many times.
You know why our country
still lags behind?
Because people here
aren't inspired
seeing others succeed.
They're envious.
The root of this case
was nothing but envy.
Thank you. Excuse me.
No more questions, please.
Thank you.
Your dad is next level, man.
Never lost a case to date!
What's the criteria
to work under him?
First prove yourself by winning
enough cases for the prosecution...
Then he might consider you.
If you talk to him,
maybe there's a way.
This criteria even applies
to his own daughter.
Being my friend is hardly a boost.
Come, let's go.
-How are you, my little glitterbug?
-Mummy!
-There comes our boss.
-Auntie?
Oh, you're here!
How was your day?
Any problems?
No, nothing at all!
Everyone was watching TV
and enjoying themselves...
Right?
By the way,
I've cooked Rajma.
I'll send some over
once it's done.
-Thanks, auntie!
-Okay.
Kusum, is your science test
result out yet?
Yes, 96!
Really? Show me!
Wait, grab this!
What are you hiding?
This? Nothing, just
the science fair form.
The teacher asked us
to get our parents' signatures.
You were selected for this?
Yes, but I'm not
in the mood for it.
Heard her?
She's not in the mood!
No, it's too expensive.
Besides, it's in Pune.
I won't be able to sleep there,
without Dad around.
I'll feel scared.
Even ghosts would be scared of you!
Let me worry about the expenses.
Focus on your studies!
And you?
God knows what nonsense
you two are cooking up.
Story? Listen!
You think she scored 96
without studying?
Scold her later.
She deserves a prize first.
Kusum, take this.
What prize?
Ice-cream?
-Ice-cream!
-How about ice-cream?
Using her as an excuse to have it!
-You know you can't!
-Once in a while is okay, right?
Really?
Are you a doctor now?
Here.
Get a chocolate bar for you,
and a mango bar for Dad.
-Okay.
-Is that right?
Yes.
Go.
Please, sir,
I can win this case...
No reply.
Madam, it's closing time!
Take your selfie later.
I'll miss my train home.
Guys...
Ladies and gentlemen,
I really want to thank you all
for being here today.
Today, our law firm, Rajvansh Legal,
completes 25 years!
And in these 25 years,
our firm's biggest achievement
is that we have no clients at this party.
Only friends and well-wishers!
My family and I...
We want to thank you.
Doing this without you all
wasn't impossible,
but would've been tougher.
-Absolutely.
-So...
-Cheers!
-Where's my glass?
Cheers!
I hope you're enjoying here.
Hi.
You're looking sexy!
Sexy?
Please! I just hope
I'm not stinking!
The Public Prosecutor's office
doesn't even have an AC.
-Can you beat that?
-Really?
To me, you smell just fine!
You're the government school type.
That's why you find
government lawyers sexy.
-Let's go.
-Sure.
-How are you doing, Sarita?
-Fine.
-How are you?
-Well...
How was your day,
Miss Public Prosecutor?
So bad...
That I want to forget all about it.
Princess! There you are.
Hi, Dad.
Sorry. I'm late.
Congratulations!
Thank you, and to you too.
Thank you!
I was just telling Neha
how much we miss her here.
Before becoming a partner,
you must stand on your own feet.
Absolutely.
I myself worked as a
prosecutor for many years.
Here we go again.
Sir, I...
-I'll go get myself a drink.
-Sure.
-Will you have something, sir?
-No, thank you.
Okay.
What was that, Dad?
Some sort of reverse nepotism?
Because I'm your daughter,
things should be
more difficult for me?
They shouldn't be too easy either.
When you get things
too easily in life,
you don't learn to value them.
You know, Neha...
The greatest emperors in history
spent their lifetimes
building huge empires.
And then, their heirs
just destroyed it.
What do you mean?
That I'm not worthy of your legacy?
Not at all.
Just that you haven't earned it yet.
My wish is that
when you join this firm as a partner,
everyone should feel
it's because you deserve it.
And according to you,
when do I deserve it?
Are we negotiating?
As always.
Fine.
Ten cases.
Win ten cases.
Deal.
Without losing a single one.
Knew there was a catch...
As always.
Deal.
Okay.
So, how was your day at court?
Good.
-Great, actually.
-Well, I heard otherwise...
Hey, Sis!
Hi.
You know, a little birdie
came and told me
that this case is also...
Is it?
Don't we always find a way?
Yeah.
-We do.
-I specifically told you, two ice cubes!
How many are these?
-Can you count?
-Sorry, sir.
Ravi!
These dimwits cannot take
one single order, I'm telling you...
But Mr. Rajvansh...
In the last 25 years,
how many cases have you won?
To tell you the truth,
and nothing but the truth...
It's easier to count
the ones I've lost!
Vikram Uncle,
you may not know this...
But you were the first and the most
important client of our law firm!
Am I right, Dad?
Absolutely, yes.
I thought you had many other
important cases going on?
Hey, I hope you're
not complaining!
That I cannot!
So what I'm saying is,
two cubes ice in a...
Vikram, Vikram...
You should call it a night.
-Akshay.
-Sir.
-No.
-Come with me, sir.
Let me ask...
Who's he?
Where's Pooja?
Hey, why didn't you tell me
you're here?
Mom, I was going to come to you, but...
But then you lawyers started arguing.
Save the arguments for court.
Come, let's have a family photo.
-It's your Dad's special day today.
-Yes.
Smile, please!
And that's their gorgeous burger.
But what I wanna show you
is my current favourite:
Their Chai latte.
It's to die for.
Cafe Roasted Chai Latte,
Inaaya Kataria approved, okay!
Roasted Cafe Latte...
"The fox remains undefeated in court..."
"Rajvansh's daughter having a
poor run as a prosecutor..."
I've a name, you idiot.
"Raghav Srivastav."
-Careful...
-Sorry, ma'am.
She popped out of nowhere!
-Are you okay?
-Sorry, madam.
I was in a rush. My bus was delayed...
No problem. Come, I'm going to court too.
I'm Sarika.
Sarika Rawat.
Neha Rajvansh.
How's it going in the Prosecution?
How's it going, well...
It's different, for sure.
-And a bit tough, too.
-That's true.
It's a little easier for the defence.
They don't have to prove
their clients innocent.
They just have to show that
the evidence isn't adequate.
Prosecution bears the burden
of proving the crime,
that too,
beyond reasonable doubt.
It's certainly tough.
So even if you lose,
don't take it to heart.
You think I'm going to
lose this case?
Well...
The judge will decide that.
When the judgment will be passed
two days later.
Sir, please stop on the left.
May I say something, ma'am?
Prosecutors often focus on
what the criminal did...
they tend to overlook
what they didn't do.
Thanks for the lift.
Only one CCTV was out of order.
Your Honour.
The defence says the Eclipse Bar's owner,
Mr. Jagdish Singh
neither knew that drugs
were being sold on his premises,
nor that 103 grams of cocaine
were found in his office.
Mr. Jagdish Singh has admitted
that the bar area CCTV camera
has been out of order for a while.
Despite knowing this,
he did nothing about it.
Under The Food Safety
and Standards Act of 2006,
Section 66 states that:
If an offense is committed
in a company or restaurant
and the offense is caused
by the owner's carelessness,
then the owner
will be held liable,
and be punished accordingly.
That's all, Your Honour.
Based on the evidences and testimonies,
this court finds defendant Mr. Jagdish
guilty of both,
drug possession and trafficking.
This court also believes that
the CCTV cameras not working
was a deliberate tactic
to enable the usage and sale
of drugs in the club.
The court sentences Jagdish Singh
to ten years imprisonment
and a fine of two lakh rupees.
Your Honour!
I've been framed!
I had nothing to do with them.
Do something, Malhotra.
-Say something!
-I'll handle it.
Hi.
Congratulations.
Well, all thanks to you!
Why me?
Your suggestion worked!
I really owe you one.
If that's the case,
you can buy me
a cup of tea.
But not today...
-I've got to run!
-That's not done! You just said...
Not so fast, Ms. Sarika!
Tell me...
What's the latest from court?
Any untoward incidents or violence?
Oh, Ms. Rajvansh?
Hello. I'm Raghav.
Court reporter.
Next time you ask for a transcript,
pay for the previous two.
Ms. Sarika, India is going digital.
Check your UPI!
Ms. Rajvansh, why do I get the feeling
that you didn't like my article?
One look at the headline,
I knew it's not worth reading.
Do something that's worth writing about,
the right headline will follow.
How about that?
So tea later, then?
-Yes.
-Tea?
What's the occasion?
Check the transcript.
You don't know how to write
but I hope you can read.
Okay, bye.
Ms. Sarika,
treat her to lemonade, not tea.
-Leave!
-It'll cool her down.
Hello, People.
Hello, My Darling.
Come. Sit.
Someone seems to have
had a good day.
Don't tell me you won.
Yeah, I did.
I guess for Delhi courts,
the Rajvansh name is enough.
Right, Dad?
Have some, Mom.
It's Friday. I'm fasting today.
It's Friday already?
Now that you've tasted success,
make it a habit.
That's the plan.
I want to get out of there soon.
It's really filthy.
Oh please!
I worked there,
before becoming a partner here.
It's different for you.
You're a guy.
You women... On one
hand, you demand equality,
but make such excuses.
What's different?
You pee standing up.
Please.
These talks are not for the dinner table!
-Then tell him!
-Oh God!
I read the court transcripts.
You argued well, Princess.
But your closing argument...
That was the clincher.
The defence wouldn't have expected
you'd go after them for negligence,
not drug trafficking.
There's a saying in boxing,
that, "the punch that
hurts you the most
is the one that
you don't see coming."
Well played.
Will you have some? Raita?
Take some salad.
Madam, could you move aside?
Tell me something...
Why did you help me?
What help?
It was just a small advice.
There's no law against that, right?
Still...
Even big lawyers
often use technical arguments
to save their clients.
If it helps to serve justice,
what's wrong with that?
Why? Don't you think,
the court delivers justice?
Justice, ma'am...
is like God.
Very hard to find.
Courts don't give justice...
Just a chance to appeal.
Feels like I'm talking
to my Dad!
I must've heard from him.
I've seen him in court
many times.
It's good, right?
Inaaya Kothari has given
this restaurant 5 stars.
-Who?
-Inaaya Kothari.
Social media influencer.
I follow her.
Never mind.
Will you help me
with a case?
Pramod Mishra.
He's a government official.
The charge is soliciting a prostitute.
I can't help you, ma'am.
I've a life outside of court.
I have a young daughter.
I have to spend time
with her too.
Well, to give her a good life,
you need money, isn't it?
10,000 per case?
Why does a Rajvansh need
an ordinary stenographer's help?
No help is ordinary
if it helps win the case.
Is it just to win
or to get someone justice?
To win.
My future depends on it.
Besides, justice is like God, right?
Difficult to find.
But why me?
You've seen high-profile cases,
from the prosecution's
and defence's point of view.
That kind of experience is rare.
And if I can buy that experience,
what's the harm?
20,000.
We'll work after court.
Till 7 p.m.
And weekends off.
Works for me.
But, madam... if anyone
at the court gets to know,
I'll lose my job.
Trust me.
No one will know.
Did you not like the Chai Latte?
It's kind of bitter.
-Bitter?
-I've got to run home now. Sorry...
Thanks for the tea!
Are you sure?
Sarika, your phone!
-Sorry.
-File.
So shady!
Is this the only place you got?
What if someone
calls the cops?
So, what will they do?
Threaten us with Section 294?
"Obscene Act in Public"?
I'll tell the cops...
There's just obscenity here...
No public!
So shameless!
Do you feel like... only in cars?
No.
Buses, trains, planes...
You make me very happy.
And you make me happier.
Darling.
She's gone to her parents'.
I'm all yours for the next 2-3 months.
Just give me a call
whenever you're free.
What do you want?
A son or a daughter?
My wife wants a son.
But boys are a handful.
Girls are simpler.
I think they're adorable.
When you have a daughter,
you'll eat your words.
Stay a bit longer?
Your wife isn't home,
but my husband is.
Then let me drop you home...
I'll be with you a bit longer.
You're a man. And a cop.
Your neighbours won't
talk shit about you.
But my neighbours...
Their tongues
won't stop wagging.
Come on, I've got to go.
Well then at least
text me when you reach...
If it's not too much trouble,
darling?
I'll text you.
I'll text you. Sarika.
I want to make a name for myself,
not just be known as Rajvansh's daughter.
"Neha Rajvansh pulls
rabbit out of hat to win case..."
Well argued!
The official time is 3:30.
Please come tomorrow.
Ruksana.
I'm Neha.
Can I ask you some questions?
How old are you?
Nineteen years.
And is Pinky really your aunt?
Ruksana, I want to help you.
If you answer my questions...
Please, ma'am,
I want to go home.
Please send me home!
I don't want to stay here.
Please, ma'am!
Please, ma'am.
Please send me home.
- Yes, Neha Ma'am?
-Sarika...
-Can you come to my place now?
- Sure.
-I'll send you the address.
- I'll be there.
Thanks.
Kaka, can you get us some tea?
I've seen such houses many times,
just from the outside.
But it's the first time
I've come in.
It's lovely.
I think
you'll like the tea too.
This time, no Latte.
Thank you.
That girl Ruksana
she seems quite scared.
That purported sex worker?
Can she be of use to us?
-What?
-Madam, your vocabulary needs work.
Not "madam", call me Neha.
Wait, I know what this means.
"Purported" means alleged, right?
But why do you say "alleged"?
Prostitution, "the oldest profession"...
Laws around it is a bit strange.
Your Honour, even if we accept
that my client, Mr. Pramod Mishra,
and this girl
were physically involved...
It's simply a private matter
between the two of them.
There's nothing illegal here.
It doesn't merit
a public solicitation charges.
The defence's argument
is totally baseless.
They were found at a brothel
at KPKG Road.
How will you prove
that it was a brothel?
Fifteen garlands, please.
Give me a good rate.
The investigating officer's testimony
mentions, it is a brothel.
No.
He believes it was a brothel.
Quick.
Madam will pay.
120 rupees, ma'am.
Your Honour,
the documents on your screen
are of the house
the police raided.
And according to these documents,
the owner of that house
is Ms. Pinky,
Ruksana's aunt.
A man and a woman.
Both adults.
In their spare time...
In a closed room...
whether they pray, watch TV,
or play cards...
Or do anything else.
How is that against the law?
These aren't enough.
We need more.
Hurry up.
That girl...
Can she help us?
There is one thing.
I think that girl is underage.
But her birth certificate states
that she is 19.
It's easy to get fake documents.
Isn't it?
How's my gang?
They're all good.
-You're back!
-Yes.
Come out soon.
How was the day?
Exhausting.
Walked around all day.
I just got home.
Such lovely flowers!
You must be working
at the same office.
Neha, come in.
That's my husband, Lakshman.
And that's my daughter,
my glitterbug, Kusum.
-What bug?
-Glitterbug!
-Hi.
Wow, that's so cool.
Who painted that?
Life's drab, but at least
the walls are colourful.
I'll bring the  pakodas .
-Just  pakodas ♪
-Yes.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
What happened to him?
It was an accident.
Kusum!
It wasn't his fault.
Here.
No one would guess
how much you're juggling.
I see why family time
is so important to you.
I'm doing what I can.
Kusum should've a better life.
That's all I want.
-Here, Dad.
-Thank you.
She's so young,
yet she takes such
good care of her dad.
Whoa, you look so cool!
I'll be back in 15 minutes!
All right.
-Jai mata di.
Take some of the holy offering.
We only have a case
if we prove the girl's underage.
I'm already on it.
Doctor, can an X-ray
determine a person's age?
Children's bones,
especially the wrist and fingers
have growing zones
on both sides,
which we call "growth plates"
in medical terms.
As children grow older,
these growth plates get thinner.
And when they become adults,
they disappear completely.
As you can see here,
growth plates are visible.
According to you,
based on this X-ray,
how old would this person be?
Going by this, I'd say
in their late teens.
Around 16.
Thank you, Doctor.
That's all, Your Honour.
Doctor...
Can a patient's bone development
tell you everything about them?
I mean,
the exact date of birth?
Isn't it possible that at times,
the bones don't indicate
the age of the person?
Yes, it's possible.
-It's quite rare.
-There's a chance, right?
Yes, if the bone growth is slow,
it is possible.
So you accept that if
her bone development is slow,
Ruksana could be 19?
-Yes...
-That's all, Your Honour.
Raghav, what the hell!
Have you lost it?
-What have you sent me?
- Hello, hello...
It's not what you think it is.
Just check it once.
Don't cry!
There's no need to cry.
Please! I don't want to...
Don't be scared!
You'll enjoy it.
-How old are you?
-15.
That's the age to have fun!
But I don't want to...
You'll enjoy it, trust me!
Please uncle,
please let me go.
Want some sweets?
Please, Uncle,
I don't want to...
- Come to me, Sweetie.
- Please let me go.
Objection, Your Honour.
The evidence is late.
Objection overruled.
Just sit down!
This court
finds Pramod Mishra guilty,
under IPC section 375,
for rape of a minor,
sentences him to 20 years,
and under IPC section 377,
for unnatural sex,
sentences him to 10 years
rigorous imprisonment.
Both these jail terms
shall be served concurrently.
Sarika.
Yes?
Think again.
About what?
Working with Rajvansh's daughter...
Don't worry so much.
I know what I'm doing.
Careful.
And if I can earn us some
extra money, what's the harm?
I want Kusum to go
for the science fair.
Do you ever feel like?
Go to sleep.
Looks like silver.
Finished ma'am.
Okay, done for the day.
Read every question two times.
All the best!
-Thank you, ma'am. Bye.
-Bye.
Hello, madam.
I'm reaching in just a bit.
Neha, you're looking
like a movie star today.
Cheers to that!
Cheers!
Tell me something...
Where did you get the video?
Whatever you may think of us,
we're not so unethical
as to reveal our sources!
And anyway, these days, from
hotel rooms to changing rooms,
there are spy-cams everywhere.
That's true.
Sarika!
Whoa, you guys are
friends already?
If he keeps writing
good things about me,
the friendship might even last!
-Such a tiny glass of water?
-It's not water!
That's tequila!
Have another one, it'll help.
It's Neha's success party, after all!
Are you okay?
-My insides are on fire.
-It is okay.
-I'm on fire!
-Careful!
♪ You are my mirror ♪
♪ You are my reflection ♪
♪ Yes, you are.. ♪
♪ You are my mirror ♪
♪ Through the soul's eye,
Let's see the world anew ♪
♪ Even with eyes closed,
I can recognize you ♪
♪ One earth, one sky ♪
♪ So many worlds in one world ♪
♪ Through the soul's eye,
let's see the world anew ♪
♪ The same shared rivers ♪
♪ The same sunlit paths ♪
♪ The same two eyes ♪
♪ Just a different view ♪
♪ We swat the same mosquitoes ♪
♪ We count the same stars ♪
♪ With no imagined borders ♪
♪ We're all the same ♪
♪ Through the soul's eye,
let's see the world anew ♪
♪ Even with eyes closed,
I can recognize you ♪
♪ One earth, one sky ♪
♪ So many worlds in one world ♪
♪ You are my mirror ♪
♪ You are my reflection ♪
♪ Yes, you are ♪
♪ You are my mirror ♪
♪ When you came,
My world opened up ♪
♪ The same shared rivers ♪
♪ The same sunlit paths ♪
♪ The same two eyes ♪
♪ Just a different view ♪
-Hi, Mummy.
-Hi.
Kusum, shoes...
She didn't greet me!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, Mom!
Hey, Mom can't digest
so many thank-yous.
Say thanks to Neha.
She got you the books.
Thank you, Ms. Neha.
Go ace the science fair.
I really hope you win.
Yes.
I really hope you win too, Neha.
♪ The same shared rivers ♪
♪ The same sunlit paths ♪
♪ The same two eyes ♪
♪ Just a different view ♪
♪ We swat the same mosquitoes ♪
♪ We count the same stars ♪
♪ With no imagined borders ♪
♪ We're all the same ♪
Sir, can you just take your line
with a little more energy?
Sure, I'll do it.
Please don't fumble on your line.
Okay, action.
Dedicated to building better lives.
Cut!
-Clap. For this.
-Yes.
Hi.
You look wonderful today!
Thank you for this opportunity.
It means the world to me.
Are we meeting this evening?
Thank me then?
What time, sir?
Mr. Bajral?
Time?
Reyaan!
Ms. Sarika.
You're early today.
Now that I'm here,
let's start the class?
-But, ma'am...
-You can play cricket later.
We'll end class ten minutes early today.
-Okay.
-Come.
Bye, Guys. See you later.
Ravi, come home, man.
Things are not
what they look like.
Hi.
So late at night?
-What's up?
-Where's the police report, Akshay?
We need to rush.
Yes, sir.
Celebrating again, are we?
If I partied after every win
I'd never have reached here.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'm just one case away
from winning ten in a row.
Don't be so sure
that the next case
will be as easy to win.
Goodnight.
Justice for Inaaya
is trending on social media.
Inaaya Kothari has been found dead
at Surya Niwas Tower, East Delhi.
Inaaya Kothari was a social media
influencer and food critic.
Reports say that Inaaya
committed suicide
by hanging herself
from a ceiling fan.
She died because of a failed
love affair.
RIP Inaaya,
you brought flavour
to lots of lives.
Neha!
Mr. Ahlawat is calling you.
Coming.
-Yes, sir?
-Have a seat.
What do you know about
the Inaaya Kothari case?
Only what I've seen
on the news.
ACP Kumar.
Oh, hello, sir.
He's handling the case.
I used to follow Inaaya online.
I never thought
she could commit suicide.
It wasn't a suicide.
It was a murder.
According to our investigation,
the suicide is staged.
Sir, I want this case.
That's why I called you.
Are there any suspects?
Yes.
Vikram Bajral.
That builder.
Vikram uncle.
Any problem?
No, sir.
I think you know
who is fighting Bajral's case.
Let's talk tomorrow.
You can't take this case.
Simple.
I don't think you realise
that I don't work for you.
I don't need your permission.
Neha... Are you crazy?
You'll fight against
your father?
Please, stay out of it.
What do you mean?
I can understand that
it's a high profile case.
And you can be a part
of this case.
Join in as my co-counsel.
You've proved yourself.
Are we negotiating?
What?
What do you want
to prove, Neha?
That you can go up
against me in court?
You don't think
I'm good enough?
Come on, Neha.
I thought you were smarter!
Can't you see what's happening?
Ahlawat, himself a public prosecutor,
is afraid to go up against me.
That's why he's pushing you forward.
He thinks putting you against me
will make me weak.
It's a cheap trick.
Typical of Ahlawat.
What do you mean,
a cheap trick?
Give me some credit, Dad.
Do you have no faith in me?
Think about it, Neha.
Giving such a high profile case, to
an inexperienced lawyer...
Why?
Unbelievable!
Here I'm on a winning streak,
and you still don't think
I'm deserving.
Everyone can
hear you guys outside.
What are you both
fighting about now?
Dad doesn't think
I'm a good lawyer.
Of course you are!
You're my daughter...
Don't try to take credit!
You never had time for me?
-It was Mom...
-Stop it!
Enough!
You know what?
Before coming here,
I was unsure about
taking up the case.
But now I'm dead sure.
I'll fight this case!
You want to do this?
You'll fight me in court?
Ravi, you're talking
to your daughter!
No, I'm talking
to a public prosecutor!
So, Ms. Prosecutor...
Be sure,
that compared to others,
I'm going to be tougher on you.
Because as a senior lawyer,
I need to
teach you law.
And as a father,
teach you respect.
See you in the court.
Neha... Listen to me.
Can we get back to work, Alok?
Yeah, Dad.
Like father, like daughter.
Come on, you don't need
to move out!
Your father and you
keep having arguments.
And you always make us patch up.
It isn't a little argument.
This could get ugly,
and I don't want you
to get caught up in it.
That's why I'm leaving.
Ravi, stop her please.
Tell her,
it's just a professional rivalry,
that she shouldn't
take it personally.
Rivalry?
Between her and me?
She won a few cases,
and now she thinks
she can go up against me?
You don't worry, Renuka.
Once her delusions
break in court,
after that, I assure you,
she'll be back home
in no time.
♪ Come softly, chiming like the stars ♪
♪ Glow like a tiny firefly ♪
♪ Walk along, humming a tune ♪
Neha!
♪ As the whole world sleeps.. ♪
♪ Till the morning breaks.. ♪
♪ My eyes.. ♪
♪ Talk through the night ♪
♪ That letter burned in your heat ♪
♪ I sigh all through the night ♪
Yes, Mom.
Take care of yourself.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
♪ O Life ♪
♪ Shake me awake ♪
♪ Neither sleep nor peace will come ♪
♪ Till the morning breaks ♪
♪ My eyes.. ♪
That door over there.
-How much is it?
-Ninety five rupees.
Come on, help!
♪ Until morning.. ♪
♪ All my dreams have turned away ♪
♪ Tonight they question me ♪
♪ How do I find the answers? ♪
This is the best I could arrange
at a short notice.
I hope it's all right?
Yes, it's good.
You're not used to this, right?
I'm not used to
being a Prosecutor either.
♪ Till the morning breaks.. ♪
♪ My eyes. ♪
♪ Talk through the night ♪
We love you, sweetheart.
I love you too, Mom.
♪ Neither sleep nor peace will come ♪
♪ Till the morning breaks ♪
The man you'll face in the court...
You've probably never met him before.
It's not about winning cases...
Mr. Rajvansh's goal is to crush
the opposing counsel so badly,
that they can never recover.
Don't worry, sir.
I won't disappoint you.
You better be fully prepared.
♪ Bless us tonight ♪
♪ Let the night keep burning ♪
♪ O Life ♪
♪ Shake me awake ♪
♪ Neither sleep nor peace will come ♪
♪ Till the morning breaks ♪
♪ My eyes.. ♪
♪ Talk through the night ♪
Why do you think
Inaaya's death wasn't suicide?
Two reasons...
Firstly, there was
no suicide note.
Suicide victims usually
leave behind a note.
And secondly,
these ligature marks.
In cases of suicide,
the marks usually form
at points bearing maximum pressure
of body...
Such as the sides
and back of the neck.
But the suspension marks on her
are all around her neck.
This is usually
a sign of strangulation.
And why has Bajral been arrested?
While searching Inaaya's place,
we found these pictures.
We couldn't find the phone
used to click these photos
or the one through which
Bajral was being blackmailed.
Obviously, Bajral either broke it,
or got rid of it.
God knows.
Obviously, he runs
such a huge business.
He wouldn't be so stupid.
Good for us that he didn't find
the physical photos.
Any other evidence that links
Bajral to the crime scene?
Yes, we got this picture
of a broken glass.
It must've broken during
the struggle.
It has Bajral's fingerprints.
Other than CCTV footage,
we also have eyewitnesses
who confirmed Bajral's presence
at the time of the murder.
Vikram Bajral has handed
this case to us on a platter.
You just prepare the opening
and closing statements.
What does Bajral
say about all of this?
I've got nothing to do with this.
I'm being framed.
Okay.
So what were you doing
at that apartment complex?
Check my messages.
I was told to bring money
to the terrace of that
apartment complex.
So I went.
Were there no other instructions?
I was there for half an hour.
No one came. In fact,
there was no message either.
So I left.
I swear on God,
the whole time,
I was on the terrace.
Trust me.
According to the police report...
You've destroyed evidence too.
And the phone that was used
to message you
wasn't found
even at the blackmailer's house.
Now answer me carefully...
I'm not interested in
how you might know this.
But do you have any idea
where that phone might be?
I have no freaking idea
who was blackmailing me...
How the hell would I know
where the phone is?
Please trust me on this.
All right, all right.
All I'm saying is,
whatever you say
will stay between us...
But please,
be absolutely honest with me.
Ravi, for how many years
have you known me?
I didn't even know the girl!
Why would I kill her?
Please get me out of this.
Now please get me out of this!
Even the police couldn't
find the phone...
Someone must have it.
It's crucial that we
find that phone, Akshay.
Put your best detectives on it.
We have to know
whose phone it was,
and who was sending
those messages to Vikram.
All right, sir.
What do you think? Is
Vikram Bajral telling the truth?
He did accept the blackmail angle.
He's refusing involvement
but has a motive.
Isn't it strange?
He can't hide the blackmail.
The police found photographs
on the crime scene, right?
He's just making up a story
about how he was framed.
He's an old friend of my Dad's.
His vibe was always off,
but he never came across
as the murderer type.
Did he seem the type
who would have an affair?
Come on! Anyone can
have an affair. Even you!
I mean...
I mean you can't compare
an affair to a murder.
No...
I just mean to say that...
All of us hide our real face
from the world
-Add it to the tab.
-Sure.
Police...
Undercover police!
Un...
Come on,
it wasn't such a bad joke.
Give me your phone.
Come on!
What?
This thing between us?
It's over now.
What?
Even the police warn you
before shooting.
You shot me straight in
the chest without warning!
It's not like we started
with an application.
Did I do something wrong, tell me?
Both of us are at fault.
We're both married.
And you just realised this?
Listen...
Our marriages will carry on.
Let this continue too, please.
Were you using me?
Think whatever you want.
Case no. 112.
Delhi Court versus Vikram Bajral.
On the charges of culpable homicide.
-Who's representing the defendant?
-I am.
Ravi Rajvansh, Your Honour.
And Prosecution?
Neha Rajvansh.
Okay, let's proceed.
How does the defendant plead?
Not guilty, Your Honour.
The defence has applied for bail.
Your Honour, with all due respect,
bail is out of the question.
The defendant is accused of a murder.
An accused and a criminal
are not the same, Your Honour.
If basics of the law need to
be explained to the Prosecution,
it will be a waste
of the court's time.
If the prosecution is worried
that my client will leave India
if bail is granted,
then let me assure the court
Mr. Vikram Bajral is a respected
and law abiding citizen...
-Your Honour--
-Who has total faith
in this country's justice system.
Your Honour, the prosecution
is also aware
that Mr. Bajral is a popular
and well connected man.
Yes.
If he is granted bail,
he could influence
the investigation.
Yes, he is a big businessman.
That's not a crime.
In fact, it means
that his responsibilities are not
limited to just his family.
He has responsibilities towards
his employees and home buyers.
-Your Honour--
-These responsibilities
cannot be handled from jail.
This is a huge risk, Your Honour.
Enough.
This court accepts the defendant's
bail application,
and sets the bail
at 2 lakh rupees.
Along with that, Mr. Vikram Bajral
is ordered to surrender
his passport to the court.
Princess.
Sir, big fan of yours.
Atma!
Sir...
She used to like me
calling her Princess.
She used to like you too, Dad.
-Okay.
-Anita, update the calendar.
Sir?
The SIM card from which Mr. Bajral
was getting the blackmail messages
has been deactivated for a while.
We are trying to track down
the IMEI number.
But it is not showing up.
Either the phone is switched off.
Or it has been destroyed.
Who does it belong to?
Did we find out?
It's registered to some
Abdullah Sheikh
who lives around Khidki village.
But he said his phone
was stolen last year.
-Vikram...
-Yes?
Do you suspect anyone?
Who could be doing this?
No, Ravi.
All right.
Any man you've ever
had a clash with,
any woman you've ever
had anything with...
We need to make
a list of everyone.
Are you serious?
Everyone?
Oh, God! Are you okay?
25 minutes.
Vikram Bajral's version is that
he waited her for 45 minutes.
In our version, he went
down the stairs during this time
to the 8th floor,
murdered Inaaya there,
and then climbed back up the stairs.
How?
Is he Virat Kohli or something?
You have a point.
Bajral is double his age
and a heart patient too.
See this.
He doesn't look tired at all.
And if he indeed
went down 20 floors,
killed her,
then climbed up the stairs...
We'd be discussing his autopsy report
along with Inaaya's.
Let's go.
According to the CCTV footage,
He was right here
from 5:30 to 6:15 p.m.
And according to Inaaya's
autopsy report,
she was murdered
in this time frame.
How much do you think
a house here would cost?
Must be 50, or 60 thousand?
Thousand?
To buy, not rent!
40 million.
With my salary,
I can't even dream of buying.
40 million!
Are you thinking of buying a house?
Our salaries aren't all that different.
This was Inaaya's house.
She owned it.
How can a small-time blogger
afford such an expensive house?
It's simple...
By blackmailing rich men
like Vikram Bajral.
Come on, let's go.
All set for tomorrow?
I went to Surya Niwas towers today.
You have a tutoring job there?
I saw your poster there.
Yes, I have a student there.
Reyaan.
Very sweet boy.
But really bad at maths!
Did you ever see Inaaya around?
Even if I did,
I wouldn't have realised.
I don't know much
about these blogger types.
Nervous about tomorrow?
Honestly...
I am, a little.
That's why I'm reworking
my opening statement
It will all be okay,
don't worry.
Your Honour, Inaaya Kothari
was a social media influencer.
Apart from food blogging,
she uploaded scandalous stories
on her social media.
One of these stories was
that of Mr. Vikram Bajral's affair.
As soon as Inaaya got to know
about Mr. Bajral's affair,
she started blackmailing him.
In the world of real estate,
Mr. Bajral has a formidable reputation.
It's said that
whenever he enters a deal,
and the other party
refuses his terms,
they're left in no position
to do business at all.
In this case,
we will be presenting
evidence to prove...
That something similar
happened to Inaaya.
In this secret deal
with Mr. Vikram Bajral,
Inaaya Kothari was the one
setting the terms.
And being true to his nature,
Mr. Bajral got rid of her.
This, Your Honour,
is a case of cold-blooded,
premeditated murder.
That's all.
Your Honour,
I paid close attention
to the prosecution's
opening statement.
As a defence lawyer,
to disprove every claim
of the prosecution
is my job.
But I'd like to compliment them.
That in their opening statement
they've been rather truthful.
I agree with the prosecution
that Mr. Vikram Bajral
is a very reputed businessman.
He is aggressive and ruthless,
as he should be.
After all,
he's running a business.
Not an orphanage or old age home.
As the prosecution has stated,
despite being married,
Mr. Vikram Bajral had
an extramarital relationship.
Is that true?
Absolutely.
He's definitely guilty
of cheating on his wife.
Does this affect his reputation?
Sure, it does.
But just to save his reputation,
to murder Inaaya Kothari
is something that he's not guilty of.
Mr. Vikram Bajral
is not a criminal,
and he is definitely
not a murderer.
And the botched up way
Inaaya Kothari's murder
was staged as a suicide...
It looks like the work of
a very careless and stupid person.
And me and my client...
We take offense to that.
Because my client Mr. Vikram Bajral
might be many things...
But he is neither
careless nor stupid.
That's all, Your Honour.
Sir, the evidence is circumstantial
but the motive is clear.
We found Mr. Bajral's photographs
in Inaaya's apartment.
The prosecution perhaps
didn't pay as much attention
as I did during
their opening statement.
That picture,
and the rest of the evidence
has been planted.
The photos were found,
but why wasn't the phone?
The one used to click the pictures,
and blackmail?
Possibly, after the murder,
Mr. Bajral destroyed the phone.
"Possibly?"
Possibly.
The prosecution's entire case
is built on a vague possibility.
But the fact is
that Mr. Vikram Bajral
didn't even know Inaaya Kothari.
The fact is
that the building CCTV camera footage
shows Mr. Vikram Bajral
entering and exiting.
That complex has 150 other flats,
not just Inaaya's.
Fact.
And it is also a fact
that Mr. Vikram Bajral was
instructed by the kidnapper
to come to the terrace
But he went to Inaaya's apartment.
That's not a fact,
but pure conjecture.
Mr. Bajral's fingerprints
were found at the crime scene.
There was a huge confrontation
before the murder...
And in the entire house, only one
glass had Mr. Bajral's fingerprints.
Don't you think
this glass could be
planted evidence?
Your Honour,
from the defence's arguments,
it seems, Mr. Vikram
neither killed her,
nor was Inaaya Kothari
blackmailing him.
Your Honour,
even after Inaaya Kothari's death
the way she is being maligned
as a blackmailer...
It's... rather unfortunate.
The defence contends
and we will prove
that behind this murder
and blackmail,
there is a single person
who has conspired
to frame my client.
I would like to
request the police too
to reopen this investigation
with a renewed perspective
so that the deceased and her family
can actually get justice.
That's all, Your Honour.
"David versus Goliath"
"Daughter and father
go head to head."
This is Inaaya's bank statement
from 2016.
The year she bought the house.
You were right.
And she only had
3 lakhs in the bank?
With 3 lakhs in the bank,
she bought a 40 million house!
The proof of funds letter
that the bank should've issued...
That didn't happen either.
Maybe her family paid for it?
Not everyone is born poor like me.
Her dad is a government
school teacher in Bareilly.
So maybe a builder gifted it?
Hey, Girl, you look needy.
Here's an apartment, keep it.
Maybe the builder
was the one in need.
Who was the builder?
Bajral?
Correct.
Why would he gift her a flat?
Ever heard of the Twisted Bar case?
Yes?
Hi.
Hope I'm not disturbing you.
Working?
I'm surprised you're not.
We haven't met in so long...
I was worried you'd stopped eating
because you missed me.
So I came over.
And I brought dinner.
So...
How's it going?
Are you here to talk about work?
Akshay!
What the hell!
What are you doing?
Stealing information to give to my dad?
You think this will earn you a promotion?
Sick!
What will you say?
How did you get
this information?
What do you think...
Whose idea was this?
Your Honour, the messages that
were sent to Mr. Vikram Bajral...
We traced them.
First we found the SIM card,
and through that, this phone.
Using cellular tower triangulation,
we figured out the location
of the phone
We found out
that at the time those
blackmail messages were sent
where this phone was located.
Basically, the location
of the blackmailer.
To put it simply,
Your Honour...
If Inaaya was using this phone
to blackmail Mr. Bajral,
she would've been very careful
that this phone always be with her.
But that wasn't the case.
Most of the time,
the phone's location was
far from Inaaya's home.
Even at nights,
when she was presumably home...
The location of this phone
was often RK Puram.
Especially at nights.
So it's clear that it wasn't
Inaaya, but someone else
who was blackmailing
Mr. Vikram Bajral.
Your Honour, the defence
is using this blackmail theory
to try and distract
from the actual murder.
It's also possible that
Inaaya had an accomplice
and they were blackmailing
Mr. Bajral together.
Anyway,
the fact of the matter is
at the time of Inaaya's murder
Mr. Bajral was in the building,
and he had a very strong motive
for this murder.
The evidence is in front of you.
You can take a look.
How can there be a motive?
When my client and the victim
never had any connection.
There was a connection.
Nine years ago, at a restaurant
and hookah bar called Twisted,
there was a huge fire,
and four people died.
The owner was charged
with negligence amounting
to culpable homicide.
That owner was none other than
Mr. Vikram Bajral.
-That..
-Yes.
Objection.
What is the connection
between these two cases?
There's a connection.
That was nine years ago,
and my client was acquitted
in that case.
Will prosecution please get
to the point if there is one?
Your Honour, Inaaya Kothari
was a key witness in that case.
But she wasn't the only witness.
There were other people.
That doesn't mean that my client was
in contact with all the witnesses.
I don't know about all,
but we have strong reason to believe
he was definitely in touch
with Inaaya Kothari.
Inaaya's Surya Niwas apartment
was gifted to her by Mr. Vikram Bajral
in return for a favour.
Your Honour, this is a request petition
to the Honourable High Court
that in the years 2016 and 2017
from Mr. Bajral's office
any official communication,
any documents,
any mails or messages
should all be requisitioned.
It is an extraordinary request,
Your Honour.
Murder is also not an ordinary crime,
Does the defence have any objection in
submitting the documents?
These documents are all
8-9 years old, Your Honour.
The records are maintained.
I don't think there's a problem
in sharing them.
Your Honour, just yesterday,
Mr. Suresh Nayyar
called up Mr. Bajral's office...
I mean, Surya Niwas Tower's office,
because his conveyance deed was lost.
And I must compliment Mr. Bajral
and his team,
because within a day,
they emailed this deed to Mr. Nayyar.
And the notable thing is
Mr. Nayyar bought his flat
in August 2016,
which was one month
before Inaaya Kothari.
I'm presenting all these
in the court so that
the defence has no doubt
about their record maintenance.
We have no problem
sharing the documents.
We just request the court
to give us some time.
The defence must present
these documents in court
at the earliest.
Thank you, Your Honour.
Halwa ♪
I made it specially for you,
with dry fruits.
Here are the papers for Twisted Bar
that the ACP gave.
"Parties of the Twisted Bar case."
"Vikram Bajral, owner."
"Jagdish Singh, manager."
"Ramnath Dhami, supervisor."
"Inaaya Kothari,
eyewitness."
"Ramnath hung himself in jail."
How did all these cases
come to me?
They're all connected
to Twisted bar.
And all these cases
came to me.
Don't you find it strange
that all these cases came to me?
Such things happen.
No big deal.
No, I mean...
These three people and Inaaya...
They were all connected
to the Twisted Bar case.
Vikram Bajral was also involved
and my father
was the defence lawyer.
And nine years later,
I'm prosecuting all of them.
This can't be
a coincidence, right?
Do you realise what
you're accusing Ahlawat of?
I think you should not over think
and focus on the case.
Dad.
Yes.
-What is this?
-Mr. Vikram's phone records...
Right after the 2016 Twisted Bar case...
They belong to Inaaya.
These numbers...
Here, here, and here...
These are all Inaaya's number.
And these other numbers...
They're from sir's office.
From his personal line.
And you won't believe this, Dad.
The sale deed of the flat.
That fool!
I warned him so many times
to avoid direct contact
with the witnesses!
Dad, you knew about this?
You think Mr. Vikram murdered Inaaya?
The question isn't whether
he committed the murder,
but whether or not
the prosecution can prove it.
This sales deed is clear evidence
of a financial transaction between
him and Inaaya.
Neha cannot find out
about this document.
We've the court's orders.
We've to share the evidences.
We will...
But if we do, it's game over.
What has the court ordered?
That all official documents
from that time period
must be shared.
And we will.
Each and every bill,
each and every memo,
each and every piece of
official communication...
So that...
In this barrage of documents,
the one document,
that will clinch the case
will effectively get lost.
That's it!
What do you think?
I came here to become a lawyer,
but your dad has made me a clerk.
There's nothing of use here.
And there are so many more boxes.
The evidence we're looking for
is hidden somewhere.
I'm the one looking!
You're leaving!
Sorry.
I would've loved to help,
but I've to meet someone important.
Fine, go.
But remember,
this is the spot
where you have left me,
you'll find me right here
when you return.
All right, Atmaram.
You got to do what you have to.
Atma, where is Neha?
It's crystal clear that
this is the company's fault.
Just be aware, it'll probably take
years to fight this in court.
The company lacks neither money,
nor lawyers.
Whatever compensation you get
won't even cover the time
and money you'll spend.
Think about it.
Okay.
Mr. Shyam?
Ramnath was a very sincere
and honest young boy.
He was just doing his duty.
They made him the scapegoat.
I tried my very best.
But high profile lawyers
like your father
played dirty.
From pushing the dates
to buying witnesses...
What hope did Ramnath have for justice?
His entire family was destroyed.
His brother-in-law
also worked there.
What was his name?
It's not like I've jumped
into the depths of hopelessness
but it's impossible to find
that little piece of paper.
Hey, Sis.
Move!
-How are you doing?
-All good.
Hi.
All this was your idea?
I'll go and get some tea.
You already know
who calls the shots.
So Dad sent you here?
No, Mom did.
Why didn't she come?
Dad was home.
She made your favourite dish.
I'm just the delivery guy.
You're the delivery boy
and I'm the customer.
I'd been craving homemade food
for quite a while anyway.
Return the tiffin box!
Yeah, I don't want to
piss her off!
You know how possessive mom is
about these boxes.
I know.
If you leave any here by mistake
she'll miss these boxes more than me.
You're right.
Sometimes I feel Mom
loves these containers more than us.
I really miss her.
How do you manage here?
Here you go.
Okay, I'll see you.
See you.
Can I say something?
I'm really jealous of you.
The way you've stood up
to Dad...
It's not easy.
I can't even dream of it.
Really?
Actually, I do think about it often.
But I don't have the courage.
I'm really proud of you...
for standing up to him like this.
All the best!
Don't smoke so much!
Take care of yourself.
This file...
How did this file end up here?
Found it.
I found it!
Vikram Bajral just got
a fast track ticket to jail!
What happened?
You don't seem happy.
No, I'm happy.
Just a little bit tired.
Tomorrow is a big day.
Let's call it a day.
I've been calling you forever!
Why didn't you pick up?
Vikram Bajral knew Inaaya.
We found the evidence.
Really?
Then we will be able
to prove the motive.
You wanted to tell me in person?
That's why you didn't pick the call.
There's more.
And what's that?
Vikram Bajral
didn't murder Inaaya.
What?
Mom, Dad's calling you.
And I'm off to dance class.
Here's your tea.
Thank you!
Neha, come.
Here's your tea.
Come, have a seat.
If not Vikram Bajral,
who's the murderer?
You are.
What rubbish!
Why will I do this?
You're making no sense.
Sarika, I just met Mr. Shyam.
His brother-in-law
worked there as well.
And what was his name?
Lakshman.
He was disabled in the same accident.
And Ramnath's poor sister...
She moved heaven and earth
to save her brother
But
as usual, the voice of the poor gets lost
in the noise of the rich.
Sir!
I know you implicated Jagdish Singh
in the drug.
What did she tell you?
I planted the evidence
because she asked!
I put the drugs in the drawer
I helped her when she needed it.
And now she's talking too much.
I'm heart-broken.
And that video
condemning Pramod Mishra...
You gave it to Raghav.
I asked Sarika where
she got the video from.
But she repeated my own line to me.
"I don't reveal my sources."
If you know all of this
then you must know why I did it too?
I know.
I've read the case files.
Case files.
This isn't fiction!
And neither are we
characters from a book.
Now that you know everything
and everyone gets it!
From here, quickly!
Go out this way, quickly!
My brother was a living,
breathing person
who did his duty
with honesty.
Jaggi and Bajral were at fault...
But who went to jail?
His poverty was his doom.
They framed him easily.
Your Honour,
I clearly instructed Ramnath
to keep the fire exit clear.
But as I left, he set up tables
there. He didn't follow orders!
I was right there
It was Jaggi who asked him
to set up the tables.
Sir, the tables will block
the fire exit.
Don't teach me how to run my
business. Do as I say or leave!
Fool! He'll instruct me!
Sir, we can't block the fire exit.
The license Bajral had from the MCD
only allowed a third of the ceiling
to be covered.
The rest had to be left open.
But even on the other two thirds
he had illegally erected structures.
Ramnath, from here.
Get them out from here.
Let's get out that way
Be careful! Quickly! Quickly!
Move this way.
That exit is shut,
go this way!
Run, quick!
Come on, hurry!
He didn't care for his employees.
Nor did he care for his customers.
All Vikram Bajral cared about
was profit.
So you framed all of them
in false cases.
They framed my brother!
He killed himself in jail!
You think any of them
gave a damn?
It took me years...
I followed every one of them.
Figured out their weaknesses...
And then made a plan
to trap and frame them.
I'll make sure they rot in jail.
How many are these,
can you count?
Sorry sir, I'll change it.
Sarika, your work is done.
You killed Inaaya!
What was her crime?
What was her crime, you ask?
Vikram Bajral had bought off
all the other witnesses.
All our hopes,
the prosecution's entire case
depended on Inaaya's testimony.
Sarika was pregnant with Kusum...
Inaaya swore on our unborn child.
That she would tell
the truth in the court.
So, Ms. Inaaya Kothari
what did you see?
I saw Mr. Jagdish Singh scolding Ramnath.
The club was completely packed
and he had set up tables
blocking the fire exit.
Mr. Jagdish told him
to remove the tables.
And did he remove them?
Or not?
Jagdish Singh left the club minutes later.
Ramnath didn't remove the tables.
This is wrong.
Our home was destroyed.
And Inaaya got
a fancy apartment
from Vikram Bajral.
Ramnath saved her life,
and in return...
Then why did you let Bajral go?
Why not murder him too?
No.
He framed my brother
to save his reputation.
I have to ensure his downfall.
His family deserves to suffer too.
The way we have been suffering.
So you framed him in a murder case?
Working in the court for many years
one thing is clear to me
that only serious crimes
of the rich matter.
So to frame Vikram Bajral
you killed Inaaya Kothari
with your bare hands.
It doesn't matter
if I committed the crime or not.
It only matters
if the crime can be proven.
And if not
then I haven't committed any crime.
You were blackmailing Bajral, not Inaaya.
You planted the photographs
of his affair at Inaaya's house.
You planted the motive
for the murder.
You asked Vikram Bajral
to come to Inaaya's terrace.
Full marks for the planning.
You work in the building as a tutor.
So no one would've paid
much attention to you.
Reyaan.
Ms. Sarika,
you're here early today.
Now that I'm here,
let's start the class.
And today, we can end
ten minutes early.
Okay.
Then you went straight
to the 13th floor
to Reyaan's house.
After the class, you went
to the 8th floor through the
fire exit, to Inaaya's home.
Yeah, the lunch was really good.
I met Medha and I'm...
You knew the CCTV cameras
were out of order.
So there would be no recording
But you entering
and exiting the building
I have that footage.
And you have a motive for murder.
I'll get some water.
Are you okay?
All the evidence is circumstantial.
How will you prove that I murdered her?
So to frame Vikram Bajral
you killed Inaaya Kothari
with your bare hands.
It doesn't matter if I committed
the crime or not.
It only cares if the crime
can be proven.
And if it cannot
then I haven't committed a crime.
Neha...
Giving you these cases was risky.
I made a mistake.
I underestimated you.
You are your father's daughter.
You used me to take
revenge on my father.
I'll remember that.
Honestly speaking,
you were never a part of the plan.
All the pieces were in place
but when I found out
that Rajvansh's daughter
has joined the prosecution,
it felt like a sign from God.
And when you approached me
for help in Mishra's case,
I became sure
that this wasn't
just a sign,
but an opportunity...
To settle scores with Rajvansh.
I don't understand one thing...
How did you ensure that
all the cases came to me?
Along with Rathi, were you sleeping
with Ahlawat as well?
I don't have the money
to bribe people.
I use what I have.
Aren't you disgusted by yourself?
How do you sleep at night?
Why don't you ask
Vikram Bajral this?
And why just Bajral...
Why don't you ask your father?
I agree, I used you.
But I have nothing
against you, Neha.
Please, Sarika...
No more lies.
It is the truth.
What you do now is up to you.
You know everything now.
What's your plan?
I thought you would only come home.
When the case was closed.
Well...
Welcome home.
This isn't me returning home.
I just had a question for you.
Who's asking the question...
My daughter,
or a public prosecutor?
Both.
Sit.
Do you remember the Twisted Bar case?
What about it?
Was he guilty?
Who? Vikram Bajral?
You know he was acquitted.
I know what the court said.
But was he responsible
for the accident?
I don't get paid
to judge my clients.
I get paid to prove them innocent.
To win their cases.
As a lawyer,
fairness, justice
don't you have any duty towards it?
Don't be so naive, Neha.
Real life isn't a moral science class.
Where right and wrong
are all that matter.
Whether or not someone
has committed a crime...
that is immaterial.
If the crime can be proved,
then the person is guilty...
Or else they aren't.
All rise.
Honourable Judge presiding.
Prosecution may please continue
with the questioning
of the accused.
How are you, Neha?
Mr. Vikram Bajral,
Bajral Builders' project
Surya Niwas Towers
is one of the largest housing societies
in the real estate sector. Am I correct?
Correct.
And I'm very, very proud of it.
As you should be.
It's so hard to get to the top,
in any field.
You must have faced
many hardships too.
I mean, if I'm not wrong,
there are some 12 civil cases
against you.
Well, as they say,
the success of a business
is judged not by the number
of its well wishers,
but the number of its rivals.
By the way,
in all of these cases,
the charges against me
have not been proven.
So you mean all those
accusations were false,
and according to the defence,
the murder charges in this case
are false too.
Absolutely.
As I have stated earlier,
I didn't even know the deceased...
To claim I murdered her
is outrageous.
By deceased,
do you mean Inaaya Kothari?
Yes. Inaaya Kothari.
Your Honour, these are Mr. Vikram Bajral's
phone records
from 2016 and 2017,
which prove that for many days
after the Twisted Bar case,
he was in touch with Inaaya Kothari.
These, Your Honour, are
Inaaya Kothari's bank statements.
They show that she only had about
3 lakh rupees in her account.
There was no way
she could afford this flat.
Just two weeks
after the Twisted Bar case,
she moved into her new flat.
Your Honour,
these are the property papers
which prove that the owner
of Bajral builders,
Mr. Vikram Bajral,
personally gifted Inaaya Kothari
the Surya Niwas flat.
This proves without a doubt
that Mr. Vikram Bajral
knew Inaaya Kothari.
Mr. Rajvansh, does the defence
have any questions?
No, Your Honour.
No further questions,
Your Honour.
Considering all the evidence
presented to this court,
this court finds defendant Vikram Bajral
guilty of the murder of Inaaya Kothari,
and under the Indian Penal Code
Section 302,
he is awarded life imprisonment.
And in light of
the new evidence presented,
this court orders that
the Twisted Bar case be re-opened
and reinvestigated, afresh.
It's all your fault
if I go down,
I'll take you with me.
You're all hand-in-glove.
Leave me!
My name is Vikram Bajral!
Neha...
Hello, sir.
Bye, Neha.
Dad, I'll see you in the car.
Yeah.
Smile!
You just won your 10th case!
If you hadn't saved Bajral
in the Twisted Bar case,
we wouldn't be on opposing sides.
I'm actually glad...
That I lost my first ever case
to my daughter.
I want to thank you.
You've unburdened me
of the mistake I made.
All thanks to you.
Some burdens cannot be eased, Dad.
They are someone else's now.
Was Bajral threatening you in the court?
Let him try.
What will he do?
File a case against me?
I now have a better lawyer to defend me!
I have a new partner at Rajvansh Legal.
I don't know, Dad...
I don't know where I'll go
from here. I'm just not sure.
Whatever path you choose,
I will be proud of you.
Go.
The reporters are
waiting for you.
Ms. Neha, one question!
Go! Enjoy your win.
I don't know if I should
thank you or apologise...
No need to say anything.
You got the revenge you wanted.
The court may have ruled
in my favour
but you got me justice, Neha.
This isn't justice, Sarika.
You, my father, and Vikram Bajral...
You all are similar.
Just like them,
you too exploited the law.
Perhaps you are right.
Why did you let me off?
The way my father's crimes
have shamed me...
I don't want Kusum
to go through the same.
It should stop somewhere.
So, congratulations.
You got what you wanted.
I've lost so much.
First my brother...
And now a friend.
You're a Rajvansh.
I thought that,
just like your father
winning was more important
than justice for you...
But what you've done today...
You've made a name for yourself.
Independent of your hallowed surname.
Neha.
Thank you.
Ma'am, I can't believe it...
You want to fight for
a poor woman like me?
Why not?
Rich or poor,
everyone deserves justice.