Fm Movie
Are human penises getting smaller?
I chose to be an obstetrician because
everything begins at birth.
Every time a child is born,
it's a new world
that opens up on the horizon.
Strong. Strong. Strong.
Very good.
The moment when you see
your son or daughter for the first time,
all the neurotransmitters
inside your head, inside your body,
in fractions of a second,
when you see your child, they change.
It's an explosion.
My God!
Congrats, Vane.
Go ahead, take him.
My love.
He looks like his father, once again!
Everything is concluded in a single word…
Joy.
When I first saw plastic
inside the human placenta,
I didn't feel joy.
Quite the opposite.
We asked mothers
to donate their placentas,
being careful
not to corrupt them with plastic.
ELECTRONIC MICROSCOPY LABORATORY
So, can you show me
if we got good results?
In my opinion,
we found something interesting.
We found this object.
We see that it has multiple layers,
like other microplastics described.
We analyzed the samples
and in some of them
we found microplastics.
And we found various types of plastics.
Polypropylene, polyethylene and so on.
Sit.
We thought,
"If microplastics are in the placenta,
perhaps they are in other places as well."
The movement is this and this.
We asked mothers to donate milk.
Excellent.
And we saw that
in many of these samples,
there are plastics.
Well, today I decided to take
a pregnancy test, another one,
and I'm going to share with you.
We never know, right?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
What does it mean?
It's not a joke, is it?
It's not a joke, right? This can't be.
There are two.
I'm not trusting this test, no.
Okay, hold it here.
I'll use another one now.
Oh, my love.