Motherfucker! What are you looking at?
Get lost!
Weren't you supposed to just deflower her?
She wasn't letting me do it.
She was acting as if she was some heroine.
I tried, but she started screaming.
I tried to gag her with my hand,
but the bloody thing bit my finger.
Then?
Then what?
It pissed me off.
What did you do then?
Then I got mad, went into the kitchen,
brought chili powder,
and shoved it up her...
Motherfucker.
Do you think it's funny?
Hello, doctor.
Sonu here.
You know that idiot Pappu Thekedar.
He was trying to deflower a girl.
But things went a little south
and he stuffed chili powder in her...
Who's going to get ice at 3:00 a.m.?
I'll bring her over.
What did the doctor say?
Hold her tight. Grab her properly.
Be quiet!
Hey, Dom!
What?
Come here.
There's a girl's body in the boot.
Cremate the body quickly.
What is her name?
Who will light the pyre?
He will. He has got a fire burning inside.
Why would I?
I won't cremate her.
Will anyone tell me
what caste or clan she belongs to?
She's an orphan, motherfucker.
Cremate the body. I'll pay for it.
Listen, Dom.
This is Mr. Bansi's property.
We never came here,
nor did you cremate any girl.
Understood?
Yes, Guptaji.
Hello, madam.
Meet me under the Rajendra Nagar flyover
in 30 minutes.
At this hour--
Hello?
Good morning, madam.
Here you go.
What is this?
This news is worth chasing.
What do you mean?
It's a social audit report.
A survey was conducted
in the state's children's shelter homes.
There's a report of girls
being physically abused
in the girls' shelter home of Munawwarpur.
See if this news is of any good to you.
Come on, Guptaji.
You woke me up in the morning for this?
Keep it.
This is the problem
with reporters like you.
If you knew,
you would be a national-level reporter.
I'm handing you
the state government's head on a platter,
but you don't get it.
I am a reporter, Guptaji, not a cop.
Understood?
But if the cops had taken action,
we wouldn't have to do anything.
What do you mean?
It has been two months
since the report is out.
The government, police, and administration
won't lift a finger.
You can take this news
or I'll give it to the BND News channel.
What are you thinking, madam?
What if it's fake?
You can investigate first and pay later.
How much?
51,000 rupees.
Have you lost your mind, Guptaji?
Where will I get 51,000? You keep it.
- Madam...
- No, I don't want it.
Money isn't a factor between us.
We'll discuss it later. Take it.
And if this news is fake,
then you better say your prayers.
I am not going anywhere.
During the social audit
of all the shelter homes in our state,
we took a closer look at all
the children's shelter homes in the state.
That's when the girls' shelter home
in Munawwarpur drew our attention.
We request the state government
to form an investigation committee
to bring about reforms
in their management and conditions.
But where did you find Gupta?
He's a big-time scoundrel.
Bloody Traitor.
Remember how he gave you that fake news
against the chief minister last time?
And also charged you 10,000 rupees.
You've got it easy.
You are a female reporter.
Anything you say slides with the audience.
I almost got thrashed last time.
Are you even listening
to what I am saying?
I am, Mr. Bhaskar, but unfortunately,
the way things are going,
we'll have to shut down
the studio in six months.
Then we'll both be sitting idle.
Now, are you listening to what I'm saying?
Do I have a choice?
Look, Mr. Bhaskar, I am making an effort.
And making an effort
is better than just sitting idle.
Did you find a news reader?
Do we have tea leaves?
I am asking you
if you found a news reader.
This is an office, not a kitchen.
I'll find someone soon.
You've been giving that excuse
for a week now.
If you're done eating,
can we do some work?
What?
No, I'll wait.
- I'm all ready.
- No, it's all right.
Wait just a minute.
- Wait, look here. Look this way.
- Okay.
Is my face too glossy?
Not at all.
Okay.
What do I do about these headphones?
I'm using wires from the table lamp
to keep it together.
Only one side works.
Now say "hello".
Hello! One-two...
- Can you hear me?
- Loud and clear.
Much better.
- Okay...
- Roll.
Action.
Hello! This is Vaishali Singh
from Koshish News, Patna.
Firstly, the headlines for today.
Patna Police have seized
large amounts of fake liquor last night.
Two brothers in Darbhanga
shot each other over a property row.
A dog and a bitch got married in Munger,
and the guests were overjoyed.
Why haven't you started yet?
Vaishali.
Will you pay the electricity bill
or should I?
I'll pay for it.
Just give me the money.
Okay.
What's new in the state, madam reporter?
Winter has set in.
Oranges have arrived in the market,
unemployment among youth
is on the rise, and--
And the government is silent.
I've been hearing this
since my college days.
You reported this three years ago.
The government stayed silent back then
and even now.
We give five years to the government
to bring some change.
I'll get only three?
What will I achieve in three years?
Look, Vaishali,
you said this three years ago.
That you'll set up your channel
in two years.
Now we're in the fourth year.
I know this is the fourth year, Arvind.
What should I do?
Take up a job in some big channel again?
Suck up to everyone?
Wait for that big scoop to arrive?
I can't do all this.
You're not getting anywhere
in this job either.
Okay. Stop.
Stop.
This seems to be the place.
I'll ask that tea vendor.
GIRLS' SHELTER HOME, MUNAWWARPUR
JAN SEVA DAL
Hey!
What are you doing?
Why are you taking pictures?
Mister.
Which way is Amar Cinema?
It has been five years
since Amar Cinema shut down.
Well, I was looking for a tour and travel...
This is a private lane, understood?
Trespassers are not allowed.
- Now leave.
- What?
I said leave.
Why is this a private lane?
I'll serve it.
Here.
What number is it on, Vaishali?
My brother-in-law,
you only watch my channel when I am here.
It's 603 in Patna,
you'd know what number it is out here.
It must be 603 here too.
It's not like that...
Scan the channels.
Let's meet the students and the teachers.
Are you the teacher?
No, sir, I'm a student.
What are you studying?
I'm pursuing my graduation.
Home Science, second year.
And he's your son?
- Are you here to meet your dad?
- No, he's my classmate.
The state government's love
for the youth is pretty unique.
Normally, it takes three years
to complete graduation in other states.
But sometimes in our State University,
it takes six to seven years.
It is good
when the youngsters
won't remain in their youth phase anymore.
There won't be
any youth unemployment left.
The youth of Bihar
have so much time to spare,
they are following us around.
You seem pretty concerned
about unemployed young men.
What is your opinion about yourself?
I mean, who's going to watch your channel
for this kind of news?
What suddenly brings you to Munawwarpur?
I had some work.
I had to meet someone.
How are your studies coming along?
Good.
She misses you.
Even I miss her.
She's like my daughter.
She's like your daughter,
but she's my daughter.
When will you decide
on expanding your family?
Madam Vaishali,
I'll wait outside in the car.
There are complications in getting
pregnant after a certain age, Vaishali.
And you've been married for six years.
I'll wait for a couple more years
and set up my work.
Then we'll see.
It's not like I am missing some train.
The thing about work is that
you can set it up at any time.
And it doesn't matter even if you don't.
You must have a baby.
She's acting like a baby herself.
Imagine your life without a child.
Listen.
I have no information
about any such report.
What are you trying to do, Vaishali?
I am just trying to find out.
It has been two months
since the report is out.
Why is the government tight-lipped?
The government--
I mean, when the state government
has ordered this audit,
then why hasn't any investigation
been carried out?
Don't you find it strange, Mr. Mithilesh?
I think CWC should verify this report.
This is your responsibility too.
Of course.
This is our responsibility as well.
I am not running away from it.
Look, Vaishali, I'm not saying
there shouldn't be any investigation.
In fact, there should be an investigation.
An open, serious investigation.
But there is a system for everything.
And the government is bound
by its formalities.
First, an investigation will happen,
and then the government
will complete its formalities
and send the file to us.
How long will it take
to complete these formalities?
Young girls are being exploited.
It's right in front of you.
You have read it.
Read what?
You brought this.
The government didn't send me this.
When the government sends me the file
and if after reading that file, I feel
the children are being treated unfairly,
then I won't just sit quietly.
I have two cute little daughters.
I am a dad myself.
Have faith in time. Be patient.
And watch the administration
work its magic.
These things take time,
but everything is fixed
in the end. Goodbye.
I've given you my card.
Please inform us if you find out anything.
Hello.
Am I talking to Arvind?
Yes.
Hello! This is Bansi Sahu,
from Munawwarpur.
Yes, hello! Sorry, I didn't recognize you.
You didn't?
Never mind.
I don't know you so well either.
My goodness.
Did the sun rise from the west today?
Did you come to welcome me?
What are you reporting lately?
What is this girls' shelter home
that you are investigating?
You thought I wouldn't find out?
Some Bansi Sahu had called me.
Who is Bansi Sahu?
You don't get it, Vaishali.
I've asked my brother-in-law
and he said that guy is a bastard.
Tell me what you wish to do.
Arvind, I don't know
which Bansi Sahu called you
and what he said.
I'm just doing my job, that's all.
- Doing your job?
- Yes.
Vaishali, I've always supported you.
I am an ordinary man.
I can't take on these people.
- Understood?
- Why are you getting mad at me, Arvind?
I don't understand what's wrong.
Give me the car keys.
Keys.
You won't take the car starting tomorrow.
I don't want your car.
Vaishali!
ONLY RASCALS SPIT HERE
Bansi Sahu runs three newspapers.
Navyug, Munawwarpur.
News, Munawwarpur.
And Siyasat-e-Bihar.
The majority
of the state government's official ads
are published in his newspapers.
Fun fact, he takes 60,000 papers
from the state government
on subsidized rates
and prints only three copies.
It's a total scam.
The shelter home in Munawwarpur
belongs to him
and he's also connected with several NGOs.
Also, the chief minister
attended his son's birthday party.
He has contested the elections twice
but never won.
Don't you think you should have
informed me about this earlier, Guptaji?
He has already called my husband
because of you.
And the point is,
if all this is government-affiliated,
then he must have
the government's support.
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
That's why he has suppressed the report.
Once his secret is exposed,
everyone will get looped in.
Each and every one.
What are you reporters for?
Expose them.
Yes. Expose them? Upon your order?
And challenge the government?
Then why don't you sell some snacks
on the streets instead
or open a grocery store?
- Why bother with journalism?
- Don't teach us
- what we must do!
- Mr. Bhaskar!
- He's being absurd.
Deposit 25,000 in his account.
25,000 is too little, madam.
I know, Guptaji. But soon.
Right now, take this.
My wedding date is close.
Are you getting married at this age?
Any kind of pressure?
Is someone forcing you to get married?
- I need it, sir.
- Look, Guptaji, we're quite stressed.
The conditions of the girls living
in Munawwarpur is a matter of concern.
Deep gashes can be seen
on some of the girls living there.
When we spoke with the girls,
some of them told us
about the physical abuse they faced.
Several of them
were so afraid of the management
that they didn't even speak.
The girls living there told us
that they have been
physically abused several times.
And they see no signs of help.
Many of them believed that several girls
who were living with them had disappeared
or maybe they were killed.
JAN SEVA DAL
KHUSHI SHELTER HOME, PATNA,
ANUMAYA HUMAN RESOURCE FOUNDATION
Even our organization is recognized
by the state government.
Through the police or any other medium,
when we learn there is
some helpless girl in the area,
or alone,
or battling some kind of a problem,
then we rescue her.
We'll bring her here, counsel her,
and get a medical checkup done.
We'll send the medical report
to the Child Welfare Committee.
The girl is our responsibility.
Food, clothing, education, and medical...
We take on all these responsibilities
and spend from the funds
we get from the government.
Up to what age can these girls stay here?
I mean...
Is there any rule or age limit?
We can only keep those
under the age of 18.
When they are old enough
to go someplace else,
we either shift them
or send them to a different shelter home
for various other reasons.
Do girls from other shelter homes
come here?
Yes, girls from Gaya, Bihar Sharif...
And Munawwarpur?
No, we never had any case
from Munawwarpur.
Where are the girls from
the Munawwarpur girls' shelter home sent?
Try to understand the chronology here.
All these little organizations
are governed by one ministry or another.
Do you understand?
And the one we're examining,
the girls' shelter home,
comes under social welfare.
They monitor it
and provide them with enough funds.
I have an idea.
The Social Welfare Department minister
is Rajni Singh.
Her office is in the Secretariat.
Let's go pay her a visit. Finish your tea.
- How's the idea?
- It's stupid.
Why is it stupid?
Don't you think the Social Welfare
Department already has this report?
The report arrived two months ago
and they haven't done a thing.
Why will they act now upon our request?
Think of something else, Mr. Bhaskar.
This world is a complicated place.
I can't think of anything else.
You have to come up with something.
Where do we go from here?
KOSHISH NEWS
Mr. Bhaskar...
Would you like to have tea
with Bansi Sahu?
In October 2017,
the state government
officially appointed NISS,
the Noble Institute of Social Studies,
to conduct a social audit
of all shelter homes that come
under the Social Welfare Department.
NISS has mentioned several
shelter homes in their report,
but their main focus was
on the girls' shelter home of Munawwarpur.
What needs attention is that NISS
submitted the report two months ago,
and the state government
hasn't taken any action in this matter.
We're curious to know
if there's any truth in the NISS report.
Is the state government's
silence justified?
This is Vaishali Singh with the cameraman,
Bhaskar Sinha, for Koshish News, Patna.
Look, he's doing yoga.
It's not yoga.
It's a votive for the goddess.
Stay seated.
You're embarrassing me.
So...
Yes.
She's my daughter, Puja.
- Say hello.
- Hello.
She's a popular reporter in Patna.
She's doing her BA in English.
Go, child.
You've been targeting me.
I am not targeting you, sir.
I'm trying to find out the truth
and there's nothing wrong with that.
Define wrong.
Every wrong thing in this world
is right in their own opinion.
There is no such thing as wrong.
Wrong is when you
intentionally malign someone,
which you're doing.
I knew it the day
when you were asking about me in the city.
Mithilesh informed me.
You went to the CWC?
I called your husband directly.
He seemed like a decent man.
It was a pleasure talking to him.
Arvind works at the post office,
doesn't he?
Six years of marriage, imagine.
It doesn't look that way.
You still look so young.
Although I don't call anyone so soon,
but I did.
I clearly told him
that if you have any questions,
you could ask me directly.
But madam, you went two steps ahead of me.
You broadcast the news last night.
How many people watch your news anyway?
In fact,
I've watched the repeat show myself.
Why are you doing this?
I am a reporter.
If I see something that's not right,
then it's my duty to follow up on it
and that's what I am doing.
Why are you getting annoyed, madam?
Even I am a reporter.
If I publish something
in the newspaper about you,
you won't be worth anything.
My newspaper
has a bigger reach than yours.
And I'll publish it
in all three languages.
Hindi, Urdu, English.
You see, Vaishali,
if some cyclist gets run over
by an oncoming truck,
then that's an accident.
But if someone
throws himself under the truck,
then that's suicide.
You have other members in your family.
Why do you wish to get into trouble?
My name is Bansi.
I'm not a flute that you'll play.
Next time when you come over,
you can also have some tea.
- Sonu.
- Yes.
Show madam reporter the way out.
Come.
See you tomorrow.
What time is it?
I've been waiting
for over two hours, Vaishali,
and I haven't had a morsel of food.
Give me five minutes.
I'll make some porridge.
This is great!
Work hard the entire day
and eat porridge at night.
Just tell me what you want to eat.
I'll make it.
Make what?
Have you lost your mind?
Have you seen the time?
You're always busy working!
You don't care about your family.
Why are you yelling?
What do you expect me to do?
- Rub your feet?
- Did I ask you to rub my feet?
I don't have a problem with your job.
But I have a problem with your methods.
I make enough money,
- so you don't have to do such petty work--
- Don't call my work petty, Arvind.
I do it for my passion, not for the money.
Get that straight!
- Have you fulfilled your passion?
- No, I haven't! Tell me!
Bansi Sahu is abusing those girls.
Why don't you understand, Arvind?
Is anyone abusing our child? No!
Then why are you getting emotional?
Do you know what the problem is?
People like you
with such disgusting mentality.
- That's the problem.
- Be quiet!
I won't stay quiet. You be quiet!
No one speaks up
when someone else is being mistreated.
But remember, Arvind,
that someday,
your child will get abused too.
So we must speak up, Arvind!
You can wait until you are victimized,
but I won't!
And if you are hungry,
is it my fault that you haven't eaten?
All you have to do is boil a cup of rice
and lentils in the pressure cooker.
Can't you do that much? Are you a child?
If you feel hungry,
then better learn to cook, Arvind.
You and your family
keep persuading me to have a child
and expand the family.
I beg you to stop urging me.
I will have a child
when I am ready for it.
I won't quit everything for it.
If you're getting desperate
to have a child,
then marry someone else, but spare me!
When did I nag you about having a child?
Madam, I've checked the entire register.
There's no one from Munawwarpur.
You know what?
There's Mary Welfare Society in Darbhanga
and Umeed Gruh in Motihari.
O, Lord.
- O, Lord.
It's your grace...
- It's your grace...
- And not our capability...
Did you ever come across any girl
from the Munawwarpur shelter home?
We had a girl two years ago.
She stayed here for a couple of months.
Later, she was transferred to Hajipur.
Why?
She was insane.
She would bite the other girls.
How old was she?
Close to 11 or 12 years.
We never had anyone after that.
We came all the way from Patna.
See my card. We're from the media.
Call your owner. We'll talk to him.
The owner isn't here. How can I call him?
No one's allowed inside
without permission.
Did you get permission
to come into this world?
I didn't, so what?
You're irritating me early in the morning.
How dare you talk like that?
Show some respect.
Idiot!
Shut up.
- You're an idiot.
- Get lost.
Madam, let's leave all of this.
Let's give this news
to some bigger channel.
When it becomes national news,
the government will deal with it.
At least we'll get a break.
We don't have to talk to such idiots.
Not a single girl from Munawwarpur.
We had two girls a year ago.
But we had sent them to Motihari.
The Motihari person said
they haven't had any new girls.
Maybe they sent her someplace else.
No idea.
One thing is confirmed.
There is no one here.
There is a girl who cooks for us.
She used to cook at the Munawwarpur
girls' shelter home earlier.
Do you want to speak to her?
Yes, please.
Guddan.
Yes, ma'am.
Call Sudha.
Sudha!
Ma'am is calling you.
Coming!
Come, my child.
Come on, don't be scared.
She is Sudha. That's Vaishali.
She wanted to know something
about the Munawwarpur girls' shelter home.
Talk to her.
Madam, can we please get some tea?
Of course. I'll send some right away.
Relax.
She was kneading dough to make bread.
- Why are you standing?
- Wait.
Have a seat, dear.
Sudha, I am Vaishali Singh,
and that's Mr. Bhaskar Sinha.
We're from Patna.
We work for the media.
Ms. Shobha was telling us
you've worked at the Munawwarpur
girls' shelter home before this.
If you remember anything,
if you can tell us anything...
I don't know anything.
Anything, good or bad. Anything at all.
Sudha, I've heard
that girls are being abused over there.
Did you see anything?
No. I don't know anything.
What will be the outcome
if you don't tell us what you know?
You'll be a part of this crime in the end.
Say something.
Sudha, I'm only trying
to help those girls.
You must remember something.
I can't force you to speak to me.
I've left my number with Ms. Shobha.
In case you remember anything at all,
give me a call.
Okay?
She was speaking
in the interest of those girls.
Think about it.
Wait.
If I tell you anything,
will my identity remain a secret?
I swear
I'll never let your name be revealed.
Have faith in me.
- Can I record--
- Please don't do that.
Whenever you're ready.
December 2016 was the first time
I went to the girls' shelter home.
My dad got me a job over there.
He said Bansi Sahu is a very nice man.
And I could learn a lot under him.
Fine, I'll send four.
There, I met Sonu first.
Sudha...
- Your age?
- I'm 21.
You're 21?
- Sonu was the caretaker of the place.
- Here.
Press harder.
Yes.
Baby, where are you?
Come downstairs.
After meeting Sonu, he sent me inside.
That was when I first met Baby Rani.
Baby Rani was the warden
of the shelter home.
She looked quite ordinary.
But she was nothing the way she looked.
What is your name?
Sudha.
Sudha...
What does Sudha mean?
Nectar.
You've been appointed as the cook.
So stick to cooking.
You have no business
with who or what anyone's up to.
Okay?
- At first, I didn't understand
- Come.
what Baby Rani had said.
Come.
I went into the girls' room
with Baby Rani.
Leave it.
What, leave it?
Give it back to her.
Why are you fighting?
Sit down!
Or else, you'll get a tight slap.
There were no rooms, just one large hall.
There were mattresses
spread out on the floor.
There wasn't even a single window.
Around 40 to 45 girls of the shelter home
were seated on the floor.
Look here.
She is Sudha.
Starting today,
she will cook for all of you.
Some of these girls are insane.
They bite.
If anyone tries to bite you,
then give a tight slap.
Come on, let's go.
Listen, girl...
Don't bite me or I will hit you.
I am not insane to bite you.
I just came to tell you
that you should run away
as soon as you can.
They are not nice people.
- Why are you trying to scare me?
- I am telling the truth.
What are you gossiping about?
I was hungry,
so I came to ask if the food was ready.
Is it time yet, princess?
How many times have I told you
not to enter the kitchen?
Get lost!
They are rude. Don't talk to them.
Talk to me as much as you like.
Motherfucker! You guys make a mess
and disrupt my sleep!
Now you're trying to run away?
I wasn't running away, sir.
She's heavy. Please help.
What heavy, asshole? I'll break your head!
Pick it up!
He's telling me she's heavy.
Asshole!
And you, bring her along!
You'll understand
when I kick your ass in the morning.
Come on.
Dom, it's Sonu speaking.
I'm bringing a girl over. Stay awake.
Yes, we'll be there soon.
Come on.
Haul her in quick.
It's the same drama every day.
I'm tired of explaining.
But nothing gets in your thick head!
I'll show you tomorrow
when you wake up, bitch.
You'll realize when I keep you
locked up in the dark room for three days.
You will neither get food nor water.
Just rot in there!
Have you lost your mind?
How can you be so stupid?
Will you understand
when they strip you naked?
And if you don't comply,
they will bury you alive
without any trace.
Look.
Do you want to see more?
They took me yesterday.
When I yelled and screamed,
they beat me up and left me here.
They took two more girls today.
Tomorrow, it will be your turn.
So listen to me
and get out of here while you still can.
Otherwise, you won't be able to leave.
Understood?
And if you didn't, then you don't have to.
Just save yourself and run away.
Go out after five minutes.
Lock the door.
That bloody Neeraj!
I wonder what he did with that girl
after watching that porn flick.
She has been screaming for five days.
I've locked her up in the room.
- I wonder what she will do if I go in.
- You're such a coward.
Strangle her to death.
And then?
Then what?
Who is she?
Is her name mentioned in the register?
Does CWC know about her?
No one knows whether she exists or not.
I'm fasting today.
Otherwise, I would've killed her myself.
You know what?
Remember that thin, dark-skinned girl
we brought from Samastipur?
Tell her to strangle that girl
and we'll set her free.
We will let her go?
I am just joking, you fool.
- Do you think I'll let her go?
- Goodness!
It's hard to tell when you're joking
and when you're serious.
Who are you?
I...
She is Sudha.
She is the new cook here.
Sudha.
Sudha. Nice.
What do you cook?
Never mind her, sir.
She's going to be around.
You can check her out later.
Mr. Sinha has been sleeping here
since last night.
Take a look at him.
That bloody Mithilesh...
Kick him in the ass.
Nice.
Your hair is all wet.
You'll catch a cold.
Take care.
Don't you carry a veil?
Drink some hot tea.
And get one cup for me as well.
That's Mr. Bansi.
The master, owner, he's everything.
If you keep him happy,
you'll be happy.
Go. Make some tea.
Doctor, what are you thinking?
This master has made things tough for me.
The injury is pretty serious.
Please tell that Baby,
girls are for satisfying your desires,
not for putting out cigarettes.
She could've bought an ashtray instead.
Why waste something that's worth millions?
Ask him.
Do cigarettes cause injuries,
wounds, or burn marks?
Master, it's injury.
It burns.
You're unbelievable.
What medicine did you give her?
They just don't get it.
That Pappu Thekedar
took Gudiya to the hotel.
When Gudiya started screaming,
he shoved chili powder up hers.
That motherfucker...
Doctor is completely drunk.
You handle it now.
What should I do?
Take a look.
Save her if you can.
Otherwise, just choke her to death.
- And Mr. Bansi?
- I will deal with him. Go.
Had I not escaped that night,
maybe I'd never get another chance.
GIRLS' SHELTER HOME, MUNAWWARPUR
At least Sudha should have spoken up
and taken a stand.
Why hasn't she? It's wrong.
It's not Sudha's fault.
Our society has made
girls like her helpless.
She can't speak up,
but we can.
What will you say and to whom?
They'll ask on what grounds
we made these claims.
What are you going to say?
We have nothing to show.
There is a difference
between humans and animals.
Humans can use their minds and speak up.
If we cannot do that,
then we should consider ourselves animals.
We must use every ounce
of our strength, Mr. Bhaskar.
To get those girls justice.
Let's go.
O' River Ganga, you've witnessed
Everything on your shores
O' Ganga, you've witnessed
Let's go.
Haven't you frozen?
You're absolutely right.
How could you still flow
Slowly
O' Ganga
O' Ganga, you've witnessed
Everything on your shores
Why don't you talk to her?
That Bansi Sahu is not a good guy.
And the way Vaishali
has been pursuing him to run her news
could prove her wrong.
I know. I've spoken to Vaishali about it.
I know what you've been telling her.
If I knew you would change
so drastically after marriage,
I would've never let you marry this girl.
Bring some fritters.
Your dad had asked me
before consenting to this relationship.
It's too late anyway.
What's the point now?
- No point in crying over--
- Hello, my sister-in-law.
God bless you.
Greetings, my brother-in-law.
Where are you coming from?
I was on a tour of Bihar.
Looking for Bansi Sahu's playground.
You're still fixated on that, aren't you?
I am, my brother-in-law.
And I will only move on
once Bansi Sahu gets capital punishment.
It's not right
to be so fixated on something.
If I was fixated on everything,
then we wouldn't be sharing a snack today.
I would've been
a national-level reporter, wouldn't I?
Be thankful for what you have.
Don't be a sour lemon.
If you're so hung up on right and wrong,
then don't just show
what a reporter can do.
Go to the court and file a case.
There's a system in place for everything.
How does news reporting fit into all this?
And you call yourself a journalist.
My brother-in-law, that reminds me.
To file a case,
I'll need a lawyer, won't I?
And you are a lawyer.
How long will you keep
making birth certificates?
I want to file a PIL. Will you do it?
I mean, donning the black coat alone
doesn't make you a lawyer.
Please say yes only if you genuinely
want to help, my brother-in-law.
Dozens of lawyers stand outside the court.
I'll find someone else.
What are you looking at?
Eat those fritters!
GIRLS' SHELTER HOME, MUNAWWARPUR
No, mister.
You dance well to the songs,
but always miss the words.
It's not "Whack! Whack!",
it's "Smack! Smack!"
What is this?
PIL.
PIL for what?
Someone has filed a PIL
in Patna High Court.
PIL for what?
It's against the state government.
It's about why they aren't taking any
action against our girls' shelter home!
Who the fuck has filed this?
I am trying to find out.
Still trying to find out?
What were you doing until now?
What do you think, master?
Sir...
Only someone who knows about the report
and wants the case to be reopened
will file a PIL.
That reporter. What was her name?
Vaishali.
But there is no name on it.
It was filed anonymously.
Remember Brij Bihari's case?
- Yes.
- First, the PIL was filed.
He took it lightly and later got screwed.
The same thing happened
with Chandrashekhar, right?
That was a murder case.
302 is different and a PIL is different.
- You see, a PIL is--
- Shut up.
Don't be a wise guy.
If you know so much,
why didn't you become a lawyer?
Dial Patna.
And tell Brijmohan I want to meet.
I said I'll deal with it.
Listen, I'll call you back sometime.
Okay.
Now hang up.
What's the matter, Bansi?
Why are you so stressed?
Don't worry, Mr. Singh.
I won't be stressed alone.
I know.
Don't fret over these little things.
Find a bigger topic for the election.
Does this look like a little thing to you?
Well?
Remember what you said?
"Don't worry,
the media will never find out.
Even if they do, I'll manage them."
Now, someone has filed a PIL!
Did you manage this?
Don't just stand there.
Get something for him.
Are you an approver?
- No, I'll get something.
- Go!
I am managing it.
Did any big players come in?
And there won't be anyone
in the future as well.
This Vaishali is no big deal.
No one in the media even knows about her.
It's not about known or unknown,
Mr. Singh.
We must stop her,
no matter how insignificant she is.
What if they become significant tomorrow?
Then what?
Did anyone tell you to interfere?
I am talking to him.
- I am just--
- If he doesn't stop barking,
someday he will get you in trouble.
What did you say?
I am barking?
You mean, I am a dog?
Yes, I am barking because I am loyal.
What do you have to say?
Dogs like him will get you in trouble.
She can do nothing. Nothing!
You know what, Mr. Singh?
You are responsible
for a couple of things,
but it doesn't mean I'll watch silently
when someone throws shit on my face.
If you don't stop her, then I will.
I won't hold back.
Hey! Don't talk rubbish.
Don't lay a finger on her.
Not a finger.
Orders are from above.
She's a reporter and a woman too.
If you even put a scratch on her,
all of the media fraternity
will come after us.
Who will be accountable then?
Who?
I've put the entire state government
on your security
and you're worried sick.
I am quiet because she is a reporter.
Otherwise, I would've beheaded her
and thrown her body on the railway tracks!
Nonsense.
And the state government is saving itself,
not me. Even you know that.
Don't make me lose my temper
for your own good.
Understood?
You're a smart man yourself.
He only looks like one.
These things
won't make a difference, Mr. Bhaskar.
Our channel isn't reaching many people.
And until our channel
doesn't have a wide reach,
how will they see our news?
Suggest something.
What should we do? Tell me.
We'll have to go viral, Bhaskar.
What does that mean?
Facebook, WhatsApp, Twitter.
We'll try everything
we can get our hands on.
Something will definitely work out.
These are a few things
I know nothing about.
Madam, Ajit's always on the phone at home.
I'll call him over.
Let him look after this. What do you say?
Yes.
Mr. Bhaskar, starting tomorrow,
we'll do a 30-minute show every day.
I'll do live reporting
on the Munawwarpur case.
I'll speak about everything.
NISS report, Bansi Sahu,
why the government isn't taking action.
We'll disclose everything.
Okay.
Great. Absolutely correct.
Nice.
I've picked you from the streets.
How can you forget?
I gave you a roof, food and clothes.
Does all this come for free?
Do you know what orphan means?
Someone who has been abandoned.
No one to look up to.
No one knows whether you exist or not.
Only I do.
I am your master.
You'll do as I say.
Or else, I'll stub you with this cigarette
until you're dead.
Will you do it?
What's the matter?
I can't find the guy who filed the PIL.
I gave you a small job.
Don't you get it?
I suspect a guy.
He's Vaishali's brother-in-law.
Suresh Singh.
He's a bloody lawyer.
I think he's involved in all this.
He practices in Munawwarpur court.
He lives in Brahampura with his wife.
I'll go deal with him if you want.
Take your belt out.
Let me go!
What are you looking up for?
Do you want to go?
Forgive me.
Understood?
My sister-in-law!
Is he all right?
What are you here for now?
You've already done what you wanted.
What are you saying, my sister-in-law?
He was badly beaten up.
He has serious head injuries.
He lost a lot of blood.
The doctor has taken him inside,
he's bandaging him up.
You must know already.
They were Bansi Sahu's men.
The police didn't even file an FIR.
Are you happy now?
No, my sister-in-law...
Who attacked your brother-in-law?
Bansi Sahu.
Bansi Sahu?
He lives on Sahu Road.
The reporter?
He's not a reporter.
Have you ever met him?
How does that matter?
It doesn't matter,
but you should know the man
you're filing a complaint against.
As far as I know,
it's hard to find a man like him.
- He's such a decent--
- I run a news channel.
Bansi Sahu has been in the headlines.
He warned me, threatened me.
- But you see--
- Wait a second, madam?
Did he warn you or threaten you?
What's your question?
A warning is like a request
not to broadcast anything
against him on TV.
And threat means that
her life's in danger.
Bravo, Dheeraj! You are pretty smart.
This is a serious matter, sir.
You're treating it too lightly.
Take my complaint.
Well, madam, I don't know why Mr. Bansi
has been in the headlines on your channel.
But I have a question.
If he was snuffed with you,
then why did he beat up
your brother-in-law and not you?
How can you talk to me like this?
My family has been attacked.
I'm here to file a complaint.
Take my complaint.
Since you're a woman
and a reporter at that,
I'll file a complaint
of violence for your sake.
Take it down, Dheeraj.
But I won't write anyone's name.
Why wouldn't you?
What do you mean?
Someone will walk right in
and file a complaint against any guy,
and I'll accept it?
The law has a system, madam.
I get it, sir.
Thank you.
What has gotten into her?
It's bad enough they beat me up,
but they also badgered my motorcycle.
Your dad had gifted me.
Aunt is here.
Here comes the princess.
You're pretty seriously injured,
my brother-in-law.
Why didn't you tell me?
- If you were filing the PIL--
- PIL?
I am not crazy to file the PIL.
I haven't filed any PIL.
PIL, my foot!
If you didn't file the PIL,
then why did Bansi Sahu's men--
Bansi Sahu's man, Sonu, came to badger me.
He beat me up outside the court.
He told me to get this through to you
or else,
you'll face the same consequences.
What did you think?
You will change the society?
Change the system?
You're trying to be a hero!
I didn't know this would happen,
my brother-in-law.
If you pinch their nerves,
they won't let it go.
You think I'm an asshole
because I don't say anything.
- No--
- You think I'm an asshole.
- No, don't say that.
- Do you know why we keep quiet?
Because we want to stay safe.
We have a family.
Today, they just beat me up.
Tomorrow, they can even slit my throat
and the police won't do a thing.
I went to file an FIR.
How can you be that stupid?
Don't you have brains?
I don't want to get into your mess!
I told you once! Why don't you get it?
Get her out of here...
Stop putting us in trouble...
There's no hope from anyone
Even our joy is short-lived
Our troubles keep growing
With every moment
My heart longs for
A single ray of hope
Please show us the light
At the end of the tunnel
- O' Ganga
- How you keep flowing
- Slowly
Why are you so worried?
What can we do?
We live in a male-dominated society.
If the wife sets out to do some good
and the husband supports her,
it is tough to see.
Forgive me.
It doesn't matter.
How does it not matter?
And you came from Patna
to Munawwarpur on a scooter.
You should've taken the car.
I look better going to the office
on the scooter.
I like the fresh breeze on my face.
Let's go get something to eat.
I am hungry.
There's nothing I can do about
my brother-in-law's injuries, Arvind.
But I can put his injuries to better use.
And maybe he might earn some merits.
I don't understand. What do you mean?
Will you do something for me?
It has been a while since
the social audit report in connection
with Munawwarpur's shelter homes
was published.
Seems like the state government
is still sleeping over it.
None of the media houses,
be it print or TV,
is shedding any light on it,
nor is it being investigated.
Remember, we brought this news
to you first.
A lawyer from Munawwarpur court
filed a PIL
in the Patna High Court
after hearing this news.
Today, this lawyer was brutally attacked
by a person named Sonu,
who fatally injured him
right outside the court.
That's not all.
Munawwarpur Police
expressed their hesitation
in mentioning any names
in their complaint.
Maybe they are under
some kind of pressure, but we are not.
Starting today,
we'll broadcast a special program
on our channel every day called Bhakshak.
Through this report,
we'll bring all the information to you,
and we'll keep doing it
until this case isn't tried
and the people connected
aren't brought to justice.
Remember, one person
cannot bring about a change.
We need your help.
- What are you looking at?
- I am...
That we only got 400 views so far.
Soon, we'll get 1,000 views,
wait and watch. Only 400.
Madam, who do you think filed the PIL?
I don't know yet, Mr. Bhaskar,
but I feel terrible
about what happened
with my brother-in-law.
- I mean, he is still my family member.
- Of course.
He's your brother-in-law.
Don't be sad.
There are always two perspectives
to look at things.
Good and bad.
What if we look at it the other way?
He kept sticking his foot in your matters.
As a result,
someone broke his legs.
Broke his legs...
I imagined his face.
He's your brother-in-law. Sorry.
Do you know where's today's newspaper?
Hey! Get up!
You're sitting on today's newspaper!
You have no manners at all.
This is called manners.
SSP Jasmeet Gaur. See!
IPS from Punjab.
This is her first posting here.
She's the first lady SP
in the history of Munawwarpur.
She taught them a good lesson.
I have her number.
You can speak to her if you want
or go meet her.
What do you say?
You aren't saying anything.
That means we are visiting her.
Did you notice something, madam?
- Tell me.
- Ladies have really done a good job.
Let's ask over there.
Hello, madam.
We have a meeting with madam.
I am from Patna. Vaishali Singh.
Hello.
Vaishali. Come in.
How do you know my name?
I saw your video. Have a seat.
- And you?
- I am Bhaskar, her colleague.
Koshish News.
Vaishali, I apologize for what happened
with your brother-in-law.
You stated in the video
that Munawwarpur Police
is not filing your complaint.
Yes, madam.
I personally went there to file an FIR.
- Was it the Town Police Station?
- Yes.
Do you remember who was on duty?
Prabhat Kumar, madam.
Cancel Town Police Station in charge,
Prabhat Kumar's duty roster,
and tell him to meet me tomorrow.
Don't worry. I will look into it.
You were talking about some discrepancies
at the shelter home in your video.
Yes, madam.
The social audit states that the girls
in the shelter homes are abused.
The case comes under POCSO.
Yes, Protection of Children
Against Sexual Offences, madam.
Many big people will get exposed,
that's why they are suppressing the names.
Yes.
Don't get me wrong.
But this report could be wrong too.
The media shouldn't run anything
without firm evidence.
I mean, you cannot act
or pass judgment like the court, right?
You're right, madam.
I'm not trying to act
or pass any verdict like the court.
I'm only raising a question.
If this report has been published
for so long,
then why hasn't it been investigated yet?
I mean, does the government believe
this report is wrong?
I'll talk to you later. Hang up.
You were saying?
How can we believe it's wrong
until it's not investigated?
Why didn't you file an FIR, Vaishali?
Every common man has this right.
I didn't file an FIR,
but someone has filed a PIL.
And the results are in front of you.
I'll talk to my superiors
and see what I can do.
His zipper was stuck.
Both Sinha and Mohan
were running for life!
Master.
GIRLS' SHELTER HOME,
MUNAWWARPUR
JAN SEVA DAL
Hello, inspector.
Did you take a wrong turn?
Why would I miss a turn?
Is Sonu here?
Who?
Sonu.
I have an arrest warrant against him.
So what?
What else? I've come to arrest him.
Go check inside.
Hey! Back off!
Did you drink too much last night?
We'll take a look around
and leave if he isn't here.
I said there's no Sonu here.
Don't you get it?
Sir, greetings.
Hello.
SSP Madam is looking into
this matter personally.
I'll have to arrest him.
Tell her he isn't here.
She's the SSP.
I would've managed it
if it was just the station in charge.
Hop in your car and get out.
What?
I won't repeat myself. Understood?
Hey! Get in the car!
See you.
Is this a circus going on here?
Get lost!
If I had given this same news
to some other reporters,
he would've given me 500,000 rupees.
Here, I'm getting paid far less
and not even on time.
We already paid you half the sum.
You'll get the rest
when madam comes back. Leave.
I should've given you only half the news.
People like you should be given leads
only after you pay in full.
How much longer
are you going to embarrass us?
Don't you get it?
We're asking for more time,
not for your kidney.
If this continues,
then I'll have to sell my kidney someday.
The wedding's around the corner
and you guys are giving me a headache.
The guy who called me an asshole
was right.
I was a bigger asshole to file a PIL,
so I could find more information
for you guys.
- But you are making my life hell--
- Wait a second!
The PIL against the state government
was filed by you?
Of course. Who else has the guts to do it?
Goodness! You showed your guts and
your brother-in-law got thrashed for it.
Whose brother-in-law?
That guy wasn't wrong.
Let me make it clearer for you.
You don't just look like an asshole,
but you think like one too.
What are you saying?
I am calling you an asshole.
What happened?
I came to get my cap.
Until we don't get a green signal
from the Social Welfare Department,
taking any action in this matter
won't be right.
This case is connected to girls.
If it misfires,
we'll be the only ones humiliated.
Sir, when will we get the green signal
from the Social Welfare Department?
Will we ever get a go-ahead or not?
They've had the report for two months,
but no action has been taken.
The case is connected to girls.
If this doesn't misfire,
we'll be exposing a huge racket.
Sir, I think we should take the risk.
Respect the stars on your uniform.
I've seen several people
losing these stars
for taking risks.
And you're doing a good job.
Common men are wearing helmets
while riding their bikes on the streets.
I am confident that
soon you'll educate them
about wearing a seatbelt as well.
OFFICE, INSPECTOR GENERAL OF POLICE,
MUNAWWARPUR, BIHAR
RESIDENCE, SENIOR SUPERINTENDENT
OF POLICE, MUNAWWARPUR
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Are you sure you'll only have tea?
Nothing to eat?
No, I am fine.
You asked to meet, so I was a little...
The police tried to arrest Sonu yesterday.
Did he get arrested?
Bansi Sahu didn't let the police enter.
And I'm confident that
it wouldn't have made any difference
even if the police had barged in.
So what will we do now?
Honestly speaking, Vaishali.
We cannot take any action
after reading this report.
Especially when we don't have
the official report.
And we cannot use your brother-in-law
to our advantage.
If they prove in court
that it was just a mere coincidence,
then that will be the end of it.
And as for Bansi Sahu...
Even if he's done something wrong,
it won't be easy to expose him.
You've started reporting him,
which means he is on alert.
Secondly, if the government
had this report for a couple of months
and they haven't taken any action,
you can imagine Bansi Sahu's connections.
Madam, you've left no options.
There's only one person
who can find some options.
Who?
You.
We'll have to put pressure
on the Social Welfare Department,
Mr. Bhaskar.
Only then can we expect some action.
It's a dangerous department.
They don't allow anyone inside.
Everyone's a pro in their field.
We cannot trick them.
So?
Even cricketer Sachin Tendulkar
was a pro in his game,
but sometimes even he used to get out.
Yes or no?
How did Sachin get involved in all this?
There must be some trick up our sleeve
that they aren't expecting.
One wrong ball and out.
We just have to try.
And we need to put pressure
on Minister Rajni Singh as well.
You see, the fear of losing power
is far worse than the fear of death.
And that's what we have to target.
Her husband is Brijmohan.
But there's nothing he can do.
Have you ever done theater
in school or college?
Yes. Several times.
I've played Ram, Raavan.
Girls were crazy about me.
They were my fans.
Juniors and seniors alike.
You got to perform again.
Will you?
Madam.
Madam, just direct me to a stage
and watch in awe.
Raju, if you can't fix it,
then go make some tea.
JAN ADHIKAR PARTY
His pictures used to be in the newspaper.
Now the newspaper is on his picture.
You know what, do some good work.
The minister is furious with you.
Understood?
Mister.
You put a newspaper patch
on Vinayak Yadav's picture.
Isn't he one of your main leaders?
He was, but not anymore.
Who are you?
I want to speak with Mr. Brij.
What should I do?
What do you want?
I just want to speak with him.
It's private.
What's so private?
It's a private matter,
so I'll speak to him in private.
This is not done.
Tell me first.
I'll hear you out, then decide.
If I am convinced, then I'll inform him.
That's a pretty long process.
- Do you understand private?
- Yes.
This is important.
I understand, but it seems like you don't.
Go out.
If I go out, Mr. Brij will have to go in.
Try to understand the complexity
of the situation.
Don't waste time and inform him.
That I want to speak with him.
And also tell him
that the person waiting outside
wants to speak about Mr. Bansi.
Bansi Sahu from Munawwarpur.
I'm sure you've heard his name.
Sit.
Never keep the mobile in your left pocket.
It causes heart problems.
Where did you read it?
WhatsApp.
I thought so.
Anything wrong?
No, sir. It's all good.
What can go wrong when you're around?
- You know the media...
- Yes.
- Greetings, sir.
- That's all right.
Sir, I made a huge mistake.
I came to meet you pretty late.
What's your name?
Bhaskar.
Vaishali Singh, the reporter.
Together, we run a news channel
called Koshish News.
Currently, we are reporting
about the girls' shelter home.
What can I do?
Vaishali Singh has some
pretty hard evidence against you
in connection with the shelter home case.
I mean, madam's name is coming up too.
I don't know any girls' shelter home.
See...
I know that you're a decent man.
She's unnecessarily involving you
in this matter.
Some Mithilesh Sinha from CWC
is supplying her with all the information.
Please wait outside.
See you, sir.
- Goodbye.
- Yes.
What was Mithilesh saying?
He said that the girls in the shelter home
were being abused and tortured.
Some woman called Baby Rani
has also been named.
Also Nafisa.
He claims that the girls are drugged,
stripped and made to sleep naked.
Some Baccha Babu
is also involved in all this.
What I don't understand is that
you're unaware of all this.
You don't seem like a person
who would do such a thing.
Why is Vaishali Singh
making a fool out of me?
Do you understand?
That motherfucker Mithilesh also said that
sometimes you go over there for pleasure.
Understood?
He'll become an approver
and get you all in trouble.
I don't want to see you in trouble,
that's why I am telling you all this
because I am a follower of yours.
Why are you being such a well-wisher?
No! I am not your well-wisher, sir.
Follower.
I've just been unlucky these days.
Mom is on her deathbed,
so I thought you could help me out.
You're rich people.
I would be really thankful.
Here.
- I don't want money--
- Keep it.
Take it.
And don't tell anyone
that you came to meet me.
No, sir.
But if you have any more information,
then come tell me.
Okay?
Definitely, sir. I promise.
On any other day,
I would've taken a selfie with you.
Yes.
See you later, sir.
Hello, this is Vaishali Singh,
bringing you
our special program, Bhakshak.
The lawyer who was attacked
is still in the hospital,
but his condition is much better.
But the system is not.
The police have registered an FIR
under SSP Jasmeet Gaur's pressure.
But the police failed to arrest Sonu.
Fun fact is Sonu works
for the same girls' shelter home,
which we've been reporting on our channel
for the past couple of days.
The police claim that the owner
of the girls' shelter home, Bansi Sahu,
came forward to stop the arrest.
Bansi Sahu misbehaved with the police
and did not let them set foot
inside the girls' shelter home.
What's so special
about the girls' shelter home,
which Bansi Sahu is trying to hide?
What connections do the state government
have with the girls' shelter home
that they aren't taking
any action in this matter?
But for now, we'll keep talking
on this matter without any hesitation
until the government doesn't take
any firm steps in this matter.
This is Vaishali Singh with Cameraman
Bhaskar Sinha for Koshish News, Patna.
So if I click here,
my YouTube page will open.
Yes.
But it's got only 60 views.
It will increase gradually.
- Will it?
- Yes.
You're back again.
How are you, Guptaji? Is everything okay?
I'm still alive.
I saw your scooter parked downstairs
and I thought I'd try my luck.
Will I get paid?
Give me two days. I'll pay you.
I promise.
Madam, you're working very hard.
You're very inspiring.
The world is filled with stupid reporters.
This is why I want to give you
another piece of news free of charge.
Tell me.
Sitamarhi Social Welfare Department's
officer, Satyajit Dubey,
was murdered four days ago.
Some group that runs
the scholarship scam killed him.
He was shot three times.
It's an open-and-shut case.
Now you see how you want to use this news.
Because if you change
the perspective of the news,
it always presents a new direction.
See you.
Mr. Bhaskar, you said I'm an asshole.
I don't know whether
anyone told you this or not,
but let me be clear.
That you look, think like an asshole,
but also your genes are of an asshole too.
Goodbye.
Your dad's being abused
and you think it's funny?
Don't tell your mom
what happens in the office.
Don't pay him for more couple of days.
But his news is correct.
Pay in cash for the newspaper tender.
If you keep records,
then people are going to ask questions.
Have you grown old?
The money received
from the shelter home is legal.
Spend that on other things.
Show small expenses.
Otherwise, I'll appoint someone else.
What the fuck are you saying?
Spit that out first!
Get lost!
He's made a mess of the office.
Good evening, Mr. Singh.
What a two-faced man you are!
Screwing the guy that's supporting you!
Why do you sound agitated?
I am not agitated.
That Mithilesh Sinha's shit-scared.
He wants to become an approver.
He spilled all the beans before Vaishali
on what we do with the girls.
Now, when this reporter
strips you naked publicly,
then don't come running to me!
Hello?
Motherfucker.
Why are you hitting me?
- Why are you hitting me?
- Fucker.
Why are you hitting me?
Sir, what happened?
- Brother...
- He's become an approver.
- Him?
- He's told Vaishali everything.
- That's a lie!
- Someone's lying.
- Sir...
Sir...
- Someone's lying.
- Sir.
- Sir...
- Someone's lying.
Sir, your hands will wear out.
Use this stick.
- This will hurt badly.
- Not with the shoe!
Not with the shoe!
Bastard...
Kick my ass!
I'll break your ass,
you won't be able to shit in the morning.
Why you...
Do you want to kill me?
How dare he?
I swear, someone's provoking you.
Someone's lying to you.
You hit me with your shoe.
That wasn't right.
How dare you betray us?
This is what you do?
I'll break your neck.
Are you ready, madam?
Ajit, start recording.
What are you doing?
That's a plain paper.
I know.
I'm going to write
Bansi Sahu's destiny on it.
Hello, this is Vaishali Singh.
Bringing you our special program,
Bhakshak,
based on the Munawwarpur shelter home.
There are several questions in connection
with the Munawwarpur shelter home,
which makes us restless.
The truth is,
honest people have no say in this.
Four days ago, an officer from Sitamarhi
Social Welfare Department was shot dead.
The government claims that a scholarship
scamming group is behind this incident.
But no arrests have been made
in the past four days.
And how can you expect
any arrests to be made?
Because that will expose them.
The public will know the truth.
But on Koshish News,
we don't work like the police.
We do a proper investigation
and bring the truth to our audience.
Through our investigation, we found out
that the deceased officer,
Satyajit Dubey, was an honest man.
He knew the truth about the shelter home
and was putting pressure
on the government.
That's not all.
During our investigation,
we learned the bitter truth about
the Munawwarpur shelter home.
We have a complete analogy
of what goes in there
and how the people are involved.
Stay tuned with us.
Tomorrow evening,
on our special program, Bhakshak,
we will expose all those names,
ranging from top ministers of the state
to well-known personalities.
This is Vaishali Singh with Cameraman
Bhaskar Sinha for Koshish News, Patna.
I can clearly see my resignation letter.
I wonder what you got me into.
It wasn't easy getting
this minister's post
and now you've ruined that as well!
Will you shut up or keep screaming?
Let me think!
Your post is safe.
I am still here!
All this will cool down.
Madam, the chief minister is on call.
Are you serious?
He's on the line.
Hello?
Good evening, sir!
Yes.
What?
I'll do it, sir.
Good night, sir.
What happened?
Will you tell me?
Tell me what happened!
Why are you screaming?
He's asked me to file an FIR immediately!
It's pretty cold.
You know what? Do we have
to go to Munawwarpur in this cold?
Let's go tomorrow morning after breakfast.
We have to be on the scene, Mr. Bhaskar.
What if something happens overnight?
Wait a second.
- Who is it?
- Ms. Jasmeet's calling. Wait a second.
Vaishali, congratulations.
The FIR has been filed.
FIR's done, madam?
Now it's your turn, madam.
Once I get the official orders,
I'll get the girls out of there.
I don't know what will happen after that.
I don't understand, madam.
What do you mean?
The state government filed the FIR
in the woman's police station.
This is POCSO's case now, Vaishali,
which is not under me.
The women's police officer and Child
Welfare Association will take action.
There will be a raid tomorrow.
The girls will get out of there.
Then they will be sent for medical tests.
Later, they will be handed over
to the Child Welfare Association.
The Child Welfare Association
will record their statement.
And if anything is proven,
then action will be taken.
Which Child Welfare Association
are you talking about, madam?
The one whose head is Mithilesh Sinha?
He is a rapist himself!
What report will he make?
Look, Ms. Jasmeet.
These people need to be arrested.
If they don't get arrested,
they will continue doing...
Now you tell me.
How do we stop all this, Ms. Jasmeet?
That's how the system is, Vaishali.
It bestows power on you with one hand
and snatches it from you
with the other hand.
We don't have a report
or evidence against anyone.
And the court only wants evidence.
They have nothing to do with reality.
It is sad but true.
Don't get your hopes high.
The case is not too strong.
But madam, what if I get you evidence?
If you can get evidence,
then Bansi Sahu will be handcuffed
without anyone's permission.
What happened?
Are we preparing for the party?
We'll be partying in Munawwarpur jail.
Scared of going to jail.
Stop, everyone.
This is
a government-recognized organization.
I won't be facing a trial alone.
Do you get it?
Listen, Mr. Bansi...
I have two little daughters.
I am a dad.
I am the dad here.
Let me go.
I've not held you captive.
The same goes for everyone.
Those who want to leave can do so now.
Don't complain later
that Bansi is selfish.
Thank you.
I am not a deserter.
I will sit here.
Let the police come.
Shall I make a cup of tea?
With biscuits.
I had already told you, madam.
My name shouldn't come up,
nor will I come forward.
Why won't you come forward?
They are nasty people.
I don't want to be anywhere
near these people.
And what about those girls?
I've no association with them.
With the girls, who helped you flee?
If you hadn't fled,
then your life would've been
like those girls.
Do you understand?
Don't you understand how important it is
for them to be arrested?
If they aren't arrested, Sudha,
some other girls will fall prey to them.
Some other Sudha
will be appointed a cook there
and she might not be as lucky as you are.
She might not be able to escape!
Then what?
Those demons will devour her.
What do you think?
Didn't I have an opportunity
to forget everything
and live a life of comfort and peace?
I did!
I don't care
what goes on in anyone's life.
I don't care if someone's living or dead!
Was anyone asking me questions?
Was I answerable to someone
about what was going on
in the shelter home? I wasn't.
I'm only answerable to myself, Sudha.
If I start thinking like you,
then I'll never be able to sleep.
I won't be able to face my own conscience.
Look at me.
Am I fighting for my own rights?
I'm fighting for the rights
of little girls. Do you get me?
For those orphaned girls.
No one will ask them whether they're okay.
But you don't care.
I didn't either.
But sometimes, Sudha,
you should do something without a reason.
Especially when we can save
someone's life.
You can change the lives
of those girls, Sudha.
But fine.
Just like the three monkeys of Gandhi,
you can keep your eyes,
ears and mouth covered.
Live for yourself.
Die for yourself.
It's like a dog chasing its own tail.
Let's go back to Patna.
Mr. Bhaskar.
The Munawwarpur girls' shelter home
belongs to Bansi Sahu.
The girls living there are being abused.
Bansi Sahu himself abuses them
and makes others do so too.
The warden, Baby Rani,
doses the girls with sedatives.
And then different people
rape the girls when they are asleep.
Baby Rani tells the girls to sleep naked
and lies down naked next to them.
The staff, Sonu,
Baccha Babu, Mithilesh Sinha,
the doctor, and several other men
make the girls dance to vulgar songs
and show them porn films too.
The girls staying there said
that a few girls got pregnant
and were killed.
GIRLS' SHELTER HOME, MUNAWWARPUR
MUNAWWARPUR POLICE
Where was...
My little sun hiding?
How did it rise today?
Why do we ignore
Things happening around us?
Carelessly, in our own selfish world?
Somewhere around us
There are lives
Living in complete darkness
We are responsible for their state
Now, it's our duty
To bring smiles on their faces
We too are...
We too are responsible to some extent
You too
And we too are
Responsible to some extent
We either become
The voice of the crowd
Or remain tight-lipped
And fear of raising voice
We either become
The voice of the crowd
Or remain tight-lipped
And fear to raise voice
It's our responsibility
To speak the truth
We will speak
Fearlessly
We are...
We too are...
Responsible to some extent...
Our government has always
propagated women's empowerment
and has always worked in this direction.
People are claiming that
the report arrived two months ago,
but the government was tight-lipped.
No action was taken.
People make all sorts of claims.
Why would I stay tight-lipped
when I ordered the investigation?
I took immediate action
as soon as I got the report.
The girls will first
be sent for a medical test
and then they will be handed
over to us within 24 hours.
Then we'll record their statement.
If the allegations turn out to be true,
then the law will take strict action.
- Understood?
- Yes.
As the chief minister of the state,
I assure you
that our Social Welfare Department
has been working efficiently
and will continue doing so
under the leadership of Rajni Singh.
- Ma'am!
- That's all!
Listen, this is the miracle of the system.
It takes time,
but all goes well in the end.
There's a minor difference
Between right and wrong
It's the power that brings in attitude
You have lost all your dignity
Like a candle blown out
By a strong gust of wind
Look into the mirror for a while
Is humanity alive in you?
With wily smile
We shake off our responsibilities
Are we going to endure
The atrocities forever?
We too are...
We too are responsible
To some extent
Are you ready?
How does it matter?
Today, it happened in Munawwarpur.
Tomorrow, it will be some other place.
Some will be angry
and some will also feel bad.
Many will express their sympathy
on Twitter and Facebook with a hashtag.
Some will be political
and others will realize
when their kin is mistreated.
Whatever happens,
it doesn't make a difference
because this Facebook world
has made our emotions zero.
Do you know what zero means?
This news might be published
in the newspaper.
Or maybe some ad might take up this space.
Media will show you
only what gets them TRP.
A well-dressed anchor
will show you the recap
and concluding part of the story,
but the truth...
Can't say.
There are several things in our lives
that are much more important
than this news.
Of course, they are.
You see, we don't have time.
Rather than hearing
these girls' rape stories,
we would rather cover our ears.
You're right.
Cover your ears.
Why would you want to hear?
It will evoke your sympathy.
Don't let it wake up.
Stay where you are, like a zero.
Do you know what zero means?
You don't?
Then Google it.
Rather, listen to spicy, entertaining
and give high TRPs to the news channels.
Listen to that.
The girls who were raped
in Munawwarpur were orphans.
They were so young
that maybe they didn't understand
what was happening to them.
You and I are lucky.
We can discuss
every little thing with our mom.
We can tell them.
But look at their luck.
Many of them have never
even seen their mom.
But how does that matter?
Today, it's one thing.
Tomorrow, it will be something else.
Don't think too much about it.
It will provoke your sympathy.
Don't let it wake up. Let it sleep.
But before I go,
I'm leaving a question for you.
Think about it if you like.
Otherwise, it doesn't matter.
Have you forgotten to feel sad for others?
Do you still consider yourself a human
or are you a predator?
This is Vaishali Singh with Cameraman
Bhaskar Sinha for Koshish News, Patna.