Here you go.
Thank you.
- Welcome, ma'am. Can I help you?
- I'd like some salt, please.
Just a moment, okay?
- Sir?
- Yes?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
One, two,
and I'll add another piece of soap
for you for free.
- Thank you!
- You're welcome.
- Bye then.
- Have a good day.
What can I get for you?
Some coffee and sugar, please.
Coffee and sugar.
Just a moment.
How many kilos?
Aren't you going to buy some?
To, get me another one!
Yes, sir!
Sir.
- I need soy sauce.
- Sure.
Welcome.
Hi, welcome to my shop.
BAKTI WIRATAMA HOSPITAL
Ni, I've got enough money for the surgery.
His kidneys will heal soon.
Oh, thank God.
Thank you, dear.
For Ardi,
I will do anything.
Ardi, everything will go smoothly.
You'll recover soon, okay?
Nurse, anesthesia.
Oh, you're awake.
Just a moment. I'll get the doctor.
Ardi.
Let me give you a checkup, okay?
Di, have you seen my wallet?
No, Mom.
Ardi?
Come on, put on your sandals. Come on.
You said we were going to go.
- Yes, come on, come on, come on.
- Hooray!
Come on.
Two weeks after surgery,
he's looking great, ma'am.
Thank God.
But there's something I want to ask about.
Ever since the surgery,
Ardi has been complaining about his eyes.
He says he keeps seeing shadows.
Shadows?
If you'd like,
I can write you a referral
and you can take him to an eye specialist.
Yes, please.
- Thank you so much.
- No problem.
What is it, dear?
My shoulders feel heavy.
You should rest.
Marni, let me do it.
- Have you gone to the doctor?
- Yes, he said there was no problem.
It may be because
Ardi keeps rubbing his eyes.
Di? Ardi?
Come on, get up, son.
Ardi, what is it?
- Ardi?
- Ardi!
There's...
- There's...
- What is it?
On top of you, there's a...
creepy woman!
Things like this can happen.
His third eye was opened
after the surgery.
He can see those who are invisible.
What he saw last night
followed you from the market.
I got rid of it.
Then what should we do?
It will be hard on Ardi
if he keeps on seeing things.
Listen.
I can't close his third eye,
but I can narrow down his view.
- Narrow down?
- Yes.
So he will only see those
who are willing to show themselves.
If they don't want to,
he won't be able to.
If that's the case,
I can help.
A piece of advice, though.
You should try to keep him away
from the market.
Why?
As a trading place,
there is bound to be fraud,
lies, cheating,
broken promises, and false oaths.
The worst place to be is the market.
At the market,
there is a world that no one wants to see.
Not to mention trades
allied with supernatural beings.
Polytheism.
There are deals with the devil and...
black magic.
What's the lesson today?
Mathematics.
- Mom.
- Ardi.
Hey, Arif!
My body needs more energy.
Mom!
Arif has already eaten three.
Arif.
Mbok, please fry some more!
Gosh.
You're saying you need more energy.
For what? Playing soccer?
Sheesh. He just wants to practice gamelan
for the school performance.
Just practice at home.
Dad got you a gamelan set, right?
What?
I want to help my friend
deal with apparitions.
I'm serious, you know.
Here, I got it from my friend.
Do you think what is written here
is the same
as what you saw?
My friend said it's the same thing.
Your friend is a know-it-all.
Let me lock your mouth.
What?
Scaredy cat, scaredy cat!
That's enough.
Come on, kids, eat properly.
Scaredy cat.
Di, this is the last day
to pay for college, right?
Oh, right, Mom.
And...
my pocket money?
Stop by the market and ask your father.
Mbok and I are going to your aunt's house.
Your brother and sister have school.
I know, but...
Just make it quick.
Don't look around.
- How much is it?
- How much?
- Sorry, just a second.
- It's okay.
Excuse me, sir.
Back off, back off.
I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
I don't need your help!
You little shit.
I'm so sorry, sir.
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
He just hasn't moved on.
He lost his daughter two weeks ago.
- I see.
- Yes, yes.
Thank you. Excuse me.
Oh, Ardi?
Have you seen my father?
He's upstairs.
- Oh, right. Thank you.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, of course.
- Just a second.
- Okay.
Cipto, Cipto. Enough with this.
Don't be greedy!
God will take care of your wealth!
I know that! I know!
Just don't get involved.
It's none of your business.
You're so stubborn.
Whatever then.
Uncle.
Sardi!
Dad.
What happened, Dad?
Nothing.
How long is Uncle Sardi going to
hold a grudge against us?
Will he live a peaceful life
if he keeps doing this?
This is not your fault, Dad.
Your shop is always busy.
Your life is complete.
Meanwhile, Uncle Sardi
has lost his entire family.
He barely has customers.
He's living frugally.
It makes sense that he's jealous, Dad.
Enough. He's your mother's older brother.
What brings you here?
I need money for my tuition, Dad.
Today is the last day to pay.
Just a second.
Okay, Dad.
How much is it?
I want to buy some sugar.
I'll see you around then.
Yes, take care!
Bye.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
A little higher, please.
You knew you were going to the market,
and yet you didn't eat much.
You lost your energy
because they sucked it out of you.
- Thank you.
- You're such a know-it-all.
I do know it all.
What did you see there?
A lot, right?
Did you see the real store owners?
What do you mean?
All places have real owners.
You don't believe it?
Have you ever heard of
the Queen of the South?
The ruler of the coast in southern Java?
If you go there wearing green clothes,
the waves will snatch you away.
Ardi?
Do you think the Queen is good or evil?
Ardi!
- He bit my hand!
- That's enough.
It hurts, Arif!
Arif, Syifa, go to sleep!
It's late!
Ardi, they say that
if your brother has a sixth sense,
then his siblings might have it too.
Who knows? Maybe Syifa can also see...
Yeesh, Arif!
Enough, enough.
I know that
having a sixth sense is not good.
It's just no good.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Now go to bed.
Hey!
Bring it on!
I'm not scared!
Dear?
Are you sick?
Just tired.
Let me give you a massage.
No need.
All right then.
I'll be in Syifa's room.
She's too scared to sleep alone.
With the seven rituals
at the seven points,
and with the sacrifice of body and soul...
Who are you?!
...one illness,
one grudge,
with their power from the ocean...
What are you doing to me?!
...I call you, soul-takers!
Suanggi!
Come!
Suanggi! Come!
Let me go!
You are mighty.
You are the predator.
Make this man and his family
all dead!
Tortured one by one!
Dear, have breakfast first.
Didn't you eat last night?
Eat first, Dad.
Take your medicine after.
Your body is hot.
Have a drink, Dad.
Dear?
- Dad?
- Dear?
- Dear!
- Dad!
- Dad?
- Dear?
Dad?
Dad! Dad! Dad!
- Dear!
- Dad.
Dad...
Dad. Dad?
Dad?
- Dad!
- Dear!
- Help him!
- Dad!
Wake up, Dad.
- Wake up, Dad.
- Mbok!
Where is she?
Mbok!
Dad. Dad?
So far, there seem to be
no internal injuries.
All vitals are in good condition.
But to be sure,
we need further observations.
Sir, we'll keep you here
for two more days, all right?
No need.
Dear...
I just want to go home.
So, they still don't know
what your illness is?
If the doctor doesn't know,
just go and see a psychic.
I don't need one.
I'm just afraid that it's black magic.
Yes, your shop is the most popular.
Someone will definitely be jealous.
Listen.
I don't believe in witchcraft.
Excuse me, everyone.
Let's just chat outside and let him rest.
- Yes.
- Of course.
Excuse us, sir.
Hope you get well soon.
EVIL OF THE UNSEEN
CHAPTER V: BLACK MAGIC
"There are various types of black magic."
"There is also black magic that is sent
using invisible creatures
to injure and kill someone."
Ardi, pick me up after sunset.
Yes, Mom.
- Sister?
- Brother.
How is Cipto?
He's still weak.
- Are you looking after the shop?
- Yes.
Okay. Here's some herbal medicine
for your husband.
Drink it once a day.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Ardi, it's for your dad.
- Take it home.
- Yes, Mom.
I'll see you again later.
Mas Arif, I can't make it
until the afternoon.
I told your mother earlier.
I have to go now, okay?
Yes, thank you, Mbok.
Still 39 degrees.
Let's take him to the doctor, Mom.
We'll go tomorrow.
For your father's checkup too.
Okay, Mom.
Ardi, Syifa.
Please sleep here with me.
Okay, I'm right here.
Okay?
I love you, Ardi.
I love you so much too, all right?
I love you, Syifa.
Get well soon.
I'll fry you all the eggs you want.
Ardi, Syifa.
Be strong and brave.
All right, that's enough.
Go to sleep, all right?
Mom?
Dad!
- Dear!
- Dad!
- What is it?
- Dear?
Dad?
Mom...
What's that, Mom?
Dear?
Dad? Dad?
Wake Syifa up!
We're going to the hospital!
- Okay!
- Dear!
Dear? Dear!
Syifa, wake up. Syifa!
Dad is having a seizure.
- Wake up! Dad is having a seizure!
- What?
Dear!
- Mom?
- Dear!
Dad?
Mom, what's wrong with Dad?
- Dear!
- Dad!
It's 41 Kenanga Street, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am. Yes. Yes.
Thank you.
Dad?
Dad...
- It hurts!
- Arif? Arif!
- What's wrong?
- It hurts, Ardi, it hurts!
Here, let me take a look.
Ah, it hurts!
Ah, Ardi, it hurts!
Ah, it hurts, Ardi! Ardi!
It hurts! It hurts!
Ah, it hurts!
Why? What's happened to you?
Arif? Arif! Arif!
Arif! Arif! Arif!
Arif? What's happened?
Arif! Arif! What's happened to you?
Arif!
Arif! Arif! Arif!
Arif, wake up...
Mom! Mom!
- Syifa!
- Mom!
- He's burning up, Mom!
- Wake up, Arif!
- Ardi?
- Mom!
Mom! Syifa!
Arif!
Mom! Mom!
Arif...
- Leave.
- What is it?
- Leave. I said leave!
- What is going on?
- What's wrong, Ardi?
- Leave!
- What?
- This is all your fault!
- What do you mean?
- Go!
Let go!
- Sister...
- Go!
- My deepest condolences.
- Let go!
Go!
- Go now! Leave!
- Enough, That's enough.
Chronic brain dysfunction?
Yes.
He seems conscious
and his vital functions are good,
but his body
shows no signs of self-awareness.
Dad.
You have to be sure you will heal, okay?
Mom, you need to eat.
Or else you'll get sick.
Let me die so I can be with Arif.
Mom.
You still have me and Ardi.
Do you still remember Mr. Rustam?
Do you
still have his phone number or address?
What is it, Ardi?
I'm afraid...
We are being attacked by black magic.
Your father is surrounded by bad forces.
Arif's death was also because of that.
But the black magic used...
I'm not familiar with it.
It does not seem to come from Java.
Then,
what are we supposed to do?
I can't remove the black magic.
I need to find out
what kind of witchcraft this is.
Only then can I help.
But...
can we be protected,
so we don't get hit?
For now,
I can only shield you.
Ma'am.
This amulet will hopefully
provide protection.
But if you suspect someone is using
black magic on your family,
don't ever carelessly confront them.
You might be killed on the spot.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
All right.
Dad.
I...
I'm going to run the shop, okay?
Sir, can I help you?
Oh, no need, no need.
It's okay.
- It's delicious, right?
- Yes, it is.
Ma'am, please stop by.
Sorry, Ardi. Yesterday was quiet too.
That's right.
Ever since your father got sick,
there have been no customers here.
Sir.
You should tell him about it.
All right, just a second.
But you should tell him, okay?
What is going on?
Well, Ardi,
yesterday, there were
two employees who left,
and me and my friends
also want to resign.
Because we have another job offer.
Oh, I see.
Well, that's that then.
Take your last salary, okay?
- All right.
- Yes.
- Ma'am, what can I get you?
- Nothing, thank you.
Yes, nothing.
I need some rice.
Right, of course.
How many kilos of rice do you need?
- Just one kilogram.
- Oh, okay.
All right.
I got you extra.
Here you go.
Where's your father?!
Mr. Wicak?
- What are you doing here?
- Sir!
- Your father killed my daughter!
- Sir?!
You, your father,
and your family must die!
Leave! Leave!
Mom?
Mom, what is it?
I was just...
I have a headache.
Okay, you should lie down.
Let me clean up.
Mom!
Mom? Mom!
Ardi?
What happened?
This is like Arif's illness.
Call Mr. Rustam, will you?
It seems like this is from the East.
If you see anything like this again...
do not touch it.
Do not open it.
You could be cursed.
That's why you are still safe now.
Ardi.
Ardi!
- Uncle!
- Ardi?
What kind of curse
are you going to send this time?
Haven't you had enough?
You got Dad, and now Mom!
What happened to her?
Don't pretend to care.
Who's next? Me?
Or Syifa?
Ardi!
I have never put a curse on your family!
Nonsense!
I'm the one protecting your family!
Your father is the one using black magic!
Your father started it all!
I got laid off, Sardi.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Sardi.
Please help me.
If there is an empty stall here,
I also want to start a shop.
Please teach me.
Here's your coffee and sugar.
I'm sure there's an empty stall.
I'll definitely help you too.
Don't you worry.
Cipto!
Throw that away! Throw it!
What was that?
They kept sending him stuff.
All sorts of things from different people.
- Soon after, he started losing customers.
- Welcome, ma'am.
He ended up not having any.
At that time, you were also sick.
What should we do?
If this continues, we will go bankrupt.
Ardi also needs surgery.
Be patient, Marni.
Be patient.
At first,
your father didn't believe in witchcraft.
But he thought it was all he could do.
Are you Mbah Di?
Yes, I am.
How can I help you?
After his visit to the shaman,
your father's shop
became the most popular.
His shaman had better powers
than the shamans that other people used.
He snatched all the customers
from his rivals.
He could also return
all the stuff people sent.
I told him not to be greedy.
But he didn't want to hear it.
Your father was consumed
by revenge and greed.
Until one day...
Hang in there, Marni. Be strong.
Nails?
I've never seen anything
like this before, sir.
I have cleaned your wife's stomach.
This one was sent by a person named Wicak.
This isn't the first time
he's sent something.
But he has crossed the line.
He hurt your wife.
What now?
Mbah.
Make him sick.
Like my wife.
Dad, here's your drink.
The eggs will be ready soon.
All right then.
Dad.
Sweetheart?
- Dad!
- What's wrong?
My stomach hurts, Dad.
Sweetheart?
Daughter?
Sweetheart...
Oh my!
The counterattack
was supposed to be for Wicak.
It was supposed to make him sick.
But they missed.
It hit Wicak's daughter and she died.
Not long after that,
your father got sick, right?
Whatever shaman Wicak is using,
they're definitely very strong.
To the point that
your father couldn't return the curses.
Even Arif...
Dad would never use black magic.
Mr. Rustam, the psychic,
said that he doesn't do magic.
That's because
your father has a protector.
So that people don't know that
he's using witchcraft.
I understand, Ardi. I do.
Because I used to use it too.
I used to dabble in black magic too.
Until I lost my family because of it.
Ardi.
I work at the market.
I can also see things like you.
So I know everything that happens here.
You're lying.
Dad doesn't even want to see a psychic.
Uncle, you don't need to make up stories
to cover up your crimes.
Ardi.
If you don't believe it,
see for yourself.
Go check your father's office upstairs!
Hello.
Good morning.
Can I talk to Mbah Di?
Syifa.
Yes?
I have to go now.
I might be home late
because it is far away.
Where are you going?
Ramangunrejo Village.
You take care of Mom, okay?
Wait for me!
- Excuse me, sir.
- Yes?
Is Mbah Di's house around here?
Oh, Mbah Di?
Yes, it is. Let me take you there.
Thank you.
This is her house.
That's Retno,
Mbah Di's daughter.
Excuse me, Miss Retno.
There's someone looking for Mbah Di.
Who is it, sir?
I'm Ardi.
Oh, hello.
Well, I should excuse myself.
- All right.
- Yes.
- Thank you, sir.
Take care.
I'm sorry, but what brings you here?
I'm Ardi.
Mr. Sucipto's son.
What do you want? Why are you here?
Because she helped your father,
my mother is also sick!
She can't speak.
She can't move.
She can't do anything.
Just like my father.
After Wicak's daughter died,
she said
she could hear the sound
of an inland tribe.
She also said
that there was a huge black figure coming.
And then her condition
became like this.
A huge black figure?
Yes.
That's the black magic attack.
That is why my mother
can no longer protect your father.
Wicak uses a shaman
whose power surpasses my mother's.
They come from the East,
and they use a type of black magic
which is called Segoro Pitu.
That is high-level witchcraft.
The ritual requires
the sacrifice of the soul,
based on hurt and revenge
from the sender.
They have to perform long rituals
with an agreement ceremony
which is done
seven times
at seven different coastal points
on Javanese soil.
It's done to summon an evil spirit
from across the Java Sea.
Its ability to cross oceans
proves how strong it is.
The evil spirit's name is Suanggi.
Suanggi?
Uncle!
Ardi?
What is it?
Uncle.
Have you ever heard of Segoro Pitu?
Uncle, it's Mom!
- It's Mom!
- Come on! Hurry, Ardi!
Come on, come on, come on!
Syifa.
Syifa?
Mom?
Mom, are you okay?
Still have a fever?
Thank God.
Make me some hot tea.
Just a moment, Mom.
Syifa!
Mom!
What is it, Mom?
Mom! What...
Mom!
Come on, hurry up!
Mom.
Mom!
- Marni?
- Mom? Mom!
Mom!
Marni!
Mom...
Syifa. Syifa...
- Marni...
- Mom!
- Mom.
- Marni.
Mom!
Oh my God, Marni.
Marni!
May Allah forgive her,
have mercy on her,
provide salvation,
and forgive her mistakes.
Our Lord, give us good in this world,
and good in the Hereafter,
and defend us
from the torment of the Fire.
Praise be to Allah,
the Lord of the Universe.
Ustadz, thank you.
BORN: 10 DEC 1943
DIED: 18 MAY 1983
With this way,
I ask for Your guidance,
God Almighty.
With this way,
I ask for Your guidance,
God Almighty.
Protect me from
the bad things in front of me.
Guide us to fight against
this black magic.
Ardi.
Forgive your father, okay?
Everything your father did
was for you and your family.
- Where are you going?
- Wicak.
Ardi, wait.
Ardi.
Mr. Rustam said it would be dangerous
if we carelessly confronted someone
who cursed our family.
That is true.
Wicak might be very powerful.
He is protected by his shaman.
I'm confused.
What am I supposed to do, Uncle?
What? Now we just keep quiet?
And wait
until we become the next victims?
Isn't that what Dad is doing now?
Just waiting for death?
Mr. Rustam isn't here either.
What should we do?
Hello.
I'm sorry I couldn't help your mother.
Come in, sir.
From the results of my meditation,
there are clues.
There is something we can do
to stop this curse.
We need to perform ruwat.
- Ruwat?
- Yes.
Purification using water from
the seven beach points
where Wicak performed his rituals.
Someone must go to the seven beach points
to get some water there.
Yes.
Then take the water home
to purify your father.
The purification must be done
on the same day as his weton.
Your father's birthday.
And before 8:00 p.m.
We still have five days left.
All right.
Later, I will tell you
the procedures and readings.
Please do.
Ardi.
If you're willing,
I can open your third eye completely.
We need someone
with an unlimited sixth sense
to do this.
Because later there,
you will face seven figures
which were assigned by Wicak's shaman
to guard those places.
You will still be able to see them
even if they don't want to
show themselves to you.
Rustam.
I'll go with him.
No, you stay here.
I need your help
to prepare the purification ritual.
Right.
If that's the case, then I'll go.
Syifa.
I want to help you.
Do you want your third eye
to be fully opened?
You have talent.
It just hasn't been opened naturally.
I can open it
if you are willing.
Yes, I am willing.
This boy named Ardi Pangestu bin Sucipto
and this girl named
Syifa Aulia binti Sucipto
intend to open their crown chakra better.
Their eyes will see wider,
their ears will also hear,
and their hearts will also speak.
Indeed, what has been given to them
is a gift.
Open your eyes.
Now, you should go.
DAY 1
You start from the east, then go west,
starting from Watu Ulo Beach.
But at which point on the beach, sir?
You'll know when you get there.
Your sixth sense will give you clues.
- Right here.
- Yes.
With this way,
I ask for Your protection.
Where is it, Ardi?
There, at Watu Ulo.
There it is, Syifa.
Do you see it?
I see it.
Okay, come on.
Ardi.
Looks like we have to
put out the candles first.
All right. I'll get some water then.
- What are you doing?
- Ardi.
I'm not afraid!
Syifa, you go first.
Ardi!
Come on.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're going to see a lot of things, okay?
Syifa. Syifa. Syifa!
It's okay!
Ardi! Ardi!
Ardi, hurry up, hurry up! Ardi!
...who loves them and fights for them.
Ardi! Right here!
Ardi!
- Ardi!
- Ignore it, come on!
...who loves them and fights for them.
Ardi!
What is it?
Come on, come on, come on!
Give him a chance to come back to You.
DAY 2
Come on.
No!
- Ardi.
- Syifa!
No!
Syifa. Syifa. Syifa!
Accept his regret.
DAY 3
Ardi! Ardi!
Come on, let's go. Let's go!
DAY 4
Where is it?
There.
Syifa, I'm getting the water.
Okay.
Syifa. Syifa!
Ardi!
Come on, come on, come on!
Syifa. Syifa.
This water is a gift from our Queen.
Go home immediately.
Thank you.
Rustam.
Is Ardi here?
What was that?
Rustam?
Stay there.
- Take care of Sucipto.
- Okay.
Rustam!
With this way, I ask for Your protection.
I play this song to protect us all.
Rustam?
Hello?
Oh, God, forgive me.
Rustam!
Oh God...
Uncle!
Uncle...
- Uncle...
- Uncle.
Oh no.
Uncle. Uncle...
Mr. Rustam.
Mr. Rustam!
Syifa.
I'm going to Dad's bedroom.
Uncle...
The waters of the seven seas will heal.
- Syifa, help me!
- Uncle!
The waters of the seven seas will heal.
Syifa, keep going, keep going.
Syifa, take care of Dad.
I'll find a flashlight.
Ardi!
Ardi! Ardi, are you okay?
Go back inside.
Go, continue the ritual.
Continue the ritual, Syifa!
Suanggi!
Your business is with me!
The waters of the seven seas will heal.
Syifa.
Syifa...
Syifa!
Syifa.
Syifa...
Ardi...
Finish the ritual.
Okay.
The waters of the seven seas will heal.
Ardi?
Dad.
The waters of the seven seas...
Ardi...
Dad! Dad!
Let go of him!
Ardi...
Help me.
Help me, Ardi.
Help.
The waters of the seven seas will heal.
Dad? Dad!
Dad. Dad?
Dad, wake up. Dad?
Dad!
Dad. Dad.
- Dad?
- Dad, Syifa.
- Dad.
- Dad?
- Dad, wake up.
- Syifa.
Ardi.
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me.
Mbah?
Mbah!
The candle is out, Mbah.
Mbah, can't Suanggi complete the mission?
What are you doing, Mbah?
Making a talisman to protect us.
What for?
You idiot!
Those who send black magic
will be attacked
if the creature they sent loses!
Now get those oranges and bananas.
Yes, Mbah.
Here you go.
Mbah!
So
after I got purified,
you started to get better?
Yes.
That night, Suanggi left Java.
So that being's power is no longer here.
Mr. Wicak's witchcraft is indeed over.
But...
what about the magic at your shop?
I'm sorry.
I promise
I won't use it again.
Your task is complete.
Time to move.
Come with me to the new house, okay?