DANCING VILLAGE
To the ruler of the forest,
the ruler of this place.
I offer these dancers for your selection.
To the ruler of the forest,
the ruler of this place.
I offer these dancers for your selection.
To the ruler of the forest,
the ruler of this place.
I offer these dancers for your selection.
Save this village from the impending doom.
Inggri!
Bring this object out of this village.
Quick!
Inggri!
Run, child!
Come on!
Run.
Don't ever look back.
- But...
- It's okay.
It's okay, child. Hurry. Go.
Child.
Don't take that, child.
Do not get involved.
Return it.
Return it!
Don't take it, child!
25 YEARS LATER
EAST JAVA, 1980
Are you okay, Mil?
I’m fine.
Were you able to sleep, Mil?
- I was.
- Me too.
Let's go, Mil.
Let's have breakfast.
Is this really the place?
Yeah, I think.
Oh, dear.
Mil, here's some cake.
My grandmother said if we eat this cake,
we will be saved from bad luck.
Thanks, but I'm not hungry yet.
Let me just keep it for now.
Where's your friend?
Hang on.
Jito!
Wait, Arya?
My friend!
You're sticky.
You think you're better than me.
- Hang on, Mil.
- How are you?
If I'm not well, I wouldn't be here.
This is my friend, Yuda.
- Jito.
- Yuda.
What are you doing here?
I'd like to ask for help.
Don't go there, child.
Don't.
Don't go there, child!
What are you doing here?
Mil?
What happened?
I don't know.
Come on.
This is the village I'm looking for.
The one with the gate.
Do you know the place, Jito?
About this gate,
every village here has a gate like this.
The gate looks like this.
How come you don't know? Look again!
What's going on here?
You said he knows.
You really don't know?
Sorry, Jito.
We need to go there.
There's something we need to do
for Mila's mother,
my aunt, who is currently sick.
Try to remember.
This is important.
To?
This a drawing of a dancer, right?
I think so.
A village with dancers.
It exists!
There's this village I know of.
Well, the village is often called
the Dancing Village
because a lot of dancers come from there.
Is that the village?
I told you this friend of mine
can help us.
Can you take us there?
Oh, dear.
It's far away.
The village
is in the middle of the forest.
What should we do?
Wait. What's this?
- You don't need to...
- So you don't want it?
Only if you insist.
Six thousand.
This is only half of it, right?
Yes, this is only half of it.
I'll give you more when we return.
What do we do now, To?
Are you sure you want to go there?
- We are.
- Hold on.
I'm going to change my clothes first.
Oh, dear!
Stop, you'll hurt me.
All good, Mil?
- Just go straight ahead from here?
- That's right.
Okay, then.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Let's go, Mil. The sooner we finish,
the sooner we can go home.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
What is it?
Is this really the way?
Yes, this path leads to Dancing Village.
Why didn't you tell us
they put an offering here?
Sorry.
I didn't know about this.
Are there any more offerings ahead?
Don't know.
Still far ahead?
I'm sorry. I don't know.
This is my first time coming here.
My whole life, this is my first time
entering a place like this.
Is there no other way?
I told you earlier.
The village
is in the middle of the forest.
I told you, right?
Right?
Mil?
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Just like in the drawing.
- Hey.
- Let's go.
Come on.
Come on, move gracefully.
Good.
Mil.
Ask her, quickly.
Be patient.
Excuse me.
May I ask you something?
I'd like to meet with the elder here,
where should we go?
Over there, at the end.
But our elder, Putri, just died.
We belong to Allah,
and to Him, we shall return...
What business do you have here?
Sorry, Miss.
If I have some questions,
to whom should I ask?
Buyut, but he's currently away.
Do you know when he'll be back?
I don't know.
Should we just go home for now?
Let's come back here
when Buyut has returned.
If you want to go home,
we have to do it now.
I'm afraid there will be no truck
passing by when it's dark.
What do you say, Mil?
Let's just wait here for a while.
Excuse me.
If you allow us,
may we...
stay here in this village
until Buyut returns?
We can stay anywhere.
At the guard post.
Is that okay?
- Thank you, Miss.
- Let me take you there.
Excuse me, may I know your name?
Sundari.
- Are you sure about this?
- Her name's Sundari.
Only this place is available.
Thank you, Miss.
It must be cold here at night.
Wear this, Mil. It's cold.
Thanks.
I don't think you can sleep here.
It's okay.
"It's okay."
Do you want the cake I brought, Mil?
You can have it.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Miss.
I'm sorry, Miss.
What is it?
I'm Yuda.
We're the ones who are going to sleep
in the guard post.
Sorry, Miss, but if you allow it,
is it okay for my cousin, Mila,
to stay in your house?
Stay?
I feel bad if she sleeps
in the post with us.
Please accept... I...
Sorry. You don't need to.
- It's okay.
- Seriously, you don't need to.
Okay, then.
I'll let...
your cousin stay in my house.
Thank you so much, Miss...
My name is Ratih.
- Ratih.
- Let me call Mila.
- Okay.
- Just a moment.
Thank you.
This is my house.
This one is my mother's room.
If you...
- Mila.
- If you need anything,
the kitchen's here.
- The kitchen's here.
- Okay, thank you.
Yes.
And...
Sorry, Miss.
But if it's possible, don't be too noisy.
My mother is...
She is ill.
Okay.
Just a moment.
A clean cloth for you.
If you want to rest,
you're welcome to come in.
I can just sleep here.
Please, you can use my room.
It's okay. Please.
Sorry for bothering you.
You're not. Please.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
You came here to meet me, didn't you?
Beautiful child,
I've been waiting for you for so long.
Miss.
Excuse me.
But if I may know...
what kind of illness
does your mother have?
She...
Mother.
Mother...
Sorry, Mother.
Drink first.
Drink again.
Drink, Mother.
This way, Mother.
Forgive me, Mother.
I'm sorry
that you had to see her like that.
My mother is in the same condition
as your mother.
She's also ill.
Same?
Exactly the same.
I hope you don't mind
that I brought a shaman here.
I hope he can see
what's going on with your mother.
Besides...
the doctor cannot explain
the reason for your mother’s condition.
Child...
Your mother brought an item
that she shouldn't have brought.
What item?
What is this?
That item came from a faraway village.
At the easternmost tip
of the island of Java.
Return the item.
If you do that,
your mother might get better.
My mother
has been in that condition
for over a week.
I don't know why she suddenly...
can't wake up.
She can't talk either.
My purpose here
is to return this to its owner.
He said that my mother
might get better afterwards.
Is this...
a gate?
Is that in this village?
It's called Tapak Tilas.
No one is allowed to go there.
Why?
I'll let Buyut explain to you about that.
Yes?
- Excuse me.
- Miss.
Mil. Were you able to sleep?
- Excuse me.
- Please.
I believe this is the right village.
I showed the drawings to Ratih.
Ratih? You showed them to her?
Ratih also said
that she thinks she has seen that gate.
But we're not allowed to go there.
We have to wait for Buyut.
Okay, then.
Let's just wait for Buyut. Okay?
Last night, I...
I saw...
What did you see, Mil?
Do you feel something is strange here?
Yud.
Do you want to bathe?
Let's bathe first. Come on.
Sorry, Miss.
Where can we bathe?
Let me take you.
But just a moment,
I'm going to tell my mother first.
Okay.
Take a cloth with you, Mil.
Ouch!
These are my friends.
I'm Jito.
I'm Ratih.
Arya.
Bitten by mosquitoes?
Not only mosquitoes.
There were also wasps and flying termites.
Take that.
That's why bring a jacket.
You can bathe down there.
Okay.
Those are the stairs going down.
Be careful.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
The place for females is over there.
Come on. Come down here.
- I didn't hear you.
- I'll kick you.
- Do all the villagers bathe here?
- They do.
- Hello.
Yes. Only the females.
It's far, isn't it?
I'm used to it.
Excuse us.
Let's go.
Is this the place?
It is. This is the bathing place.
The twin pool.
I heard there's another one like this.
But I don't know where it is.
This pool was used by the dancers
before they performed.
But it's only a rumor.
Is it okay for me to bathe here?
It's okay. But rinse yourself first.
Here, please.
Okay.
You use the one over there, okay?
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Ratih?
Miss.
Come here.
The water's so refreshing.
Don't be shy.
What's the song about?
The song...
tells a story about people.
People...
who often break their promises.
You... are not that kind of person,
are you child?
Return my bangle.
Return it.
Miss!
What happened?
Snakes.
- What happened?
- Let's go back.
What should we do, Yud?
I don't know.
Let's go to Buyut's house first.
Maybe he's home already.
So we don't need to stay another night.
Is this the right way?
It is the way. It's...
A graveyard!
- Oh, my God.
- Wait.
Oh, dear.
I got it wrong.
Come on, let's go back.
We didn't pass through here earlier.
Why are they covered by black cloths?
A graveyard like this is usually
when they die of unnatural causes.
Watch your words!
You always talk back.
- This is a graveyard.
- Who says this is a guard post?
Is this really Buyut's house?
It is.
The villagers say this is his house.
Excuse me.
Sir?
Nobody's home.
- What is this?
- Robbers!
Gotcha!
Who are you looking for?
Hey! We're here
because we have some questions.
Is this really Buyut's house?
What business do you have with him?
Hang on!
Has Buyut come home yet?
He hasn't!
Who are you to him?
You ask too many questions.
I'm Prabu.
What business do you have with him?
Where is he?
He...
I don't know.
When will he come home?
I'll hit you!
What do we do now?
Well...
Let's just wait.
Okay, then.
Sir.
I want to tell you something.
About Buyut.
It is said that...
he can turn into a black dog.
Sir.
When there's danger,
his eyes turn red and light up.
And he runs fast. This is true.
You crazy boy!
It's impossible!
How can a human turn into a dog?
- But this is true!
- You're just making up stories!
Oh, dear.
Earlier today...
when I was taking a bath,
I saw snakes.
Lots of them.
But they suddenly disappeared.
Snakes?
You saw snakes?
We met a crazy boy earlier today.
He told us a crazy story.
And your friend here believed him.
He said it was scary.
There were graves covered by black cloths.
A human that can turn to a dog.
This place is in the middle of the forest.
Don't you think there is something wrong
with this village?
So, what do you think, Mil?
Should we just go home?
Aren't you going to return the item?
Shouldn't you wait for Buyut
to come back first?
I'm so sorry.
I accidentally dropped them.
It's okay.
Can you hear it?
Maybe... there's a dance performance
going on out there?
But where?
In...
the neighboring village?
The neighboring village?
There's...
a place where dancers practice.
Do you...
want...
to go there?
Ratih.
Excuse me.
Ratih?
Mila?
They're not here.
Jito.
Shit!
Oh, God.
Close the door.
Yud, it's been a while.
Where are they?
Why haven't they come home yet?
I can't find them.
Where are they?
Mila!
Mil!
Excuse us, Ma'am.
Is anyone inside?
No.
Mila.
Thank you.
It's empty.
Nyai.
This is Mila.
You finally came, child.
Your scent...
is enticing.
Where is...
my bangle?
If...
I return this...
will my mother be cured?
That shaman is kind
for leading you here.
That item came from a faraway village.
At the easternmost tip...
of the island of Java.
Return the item to that place.
If you do that,
your mother might be cured.
Just stay here, child.
You've done your job, child.
Forgive me...
but what about my mother?
Go home.
And meet your mother.
Mila!
Yud.
We've been searching for her all day.
Let's go back to the village.
Maybe they've come back.
I'm hungry.
No.
I have a bad feeling.
Where else can we look?
A food stall?
Let's ask them.
Why is there a food stall there?
Excuse me, Sir.
I'm looking for my cousin.
A girl this tall.
Have you seen her?
- She has long hair.
- Let's go back.
She went with another girl.
Let's go back now.
Let's go back.
Thank you.
Child.
You're not from around here, are you?
I hope you can find your cousin.
Bring this.
Thank you.
It just so happens that I'm hungry.
It's rude to reject someone's gift.
Hurry. It's going to rain.
Ratih!
Ratih! Wait for me!
Ratih, who was that?
Her name is Badarawuhi.
She promised me that if I helped her,
my mother would be safe.
Ratih...
Help me!
Mother...
Mother!
Poor woman,
your mother.
Who are you?
Badarawuhi.
Right now,
your mother is suffering, child.
You can save her.
As long as you...
help me.
Mila! Mila!
Mila.
What happened?
- Miss...
- Let's go back.
That's all.
I only did what she told me to.
But you knew she's not human.
Ratih...
Ratih!
Mother!
I did what she told me to!
Mother...
Mother, what should I do?
Oh, God! Mila!
Mila!
Where have you been?
- Oh, my God.
- I want to go home!
- Mil...
- I want to see my mother!
Mil, there is lightning! It's dangerous!
- Let's go back in!
- Run!
It's dangerous!
- Where do you want to go?
- I have to go home.
Hey, Mil.
You want to go home in this weather?
- I have to see my mother's condition!
- Mila, it's dangerous!
- But it's dangerous!
Yuda is right.
You won't find any vehicle in this storm.
But we don’t have time.
I have to make sure
that what I did was right.
What are you talking about, Mil?
What did you do?
I've returned the item.
But why does it feel wrong?
You mean...
you were gone all day
just to return the item?
All day?
I was only gone for a little while.
We looked for you all day, Mil.
In the forest too.
Why didn't you ask me to come with you?
It's dangerous, you know.
I was worried about my mother.
I know, but it's dangerous.
I'm scared.
I was worried about my mother.
What is that smell?
What is that?
What were you thinking?
There was a food stall
in the middle of the forest.
People with black nails.
Why did you accept the food?
What did I eat then?
A monkey!
What's going on?
Mil?
Mila?
Mila, my beautiful daughter.
Wake up.
Mother?
What's wrong?
You had a nightmare?
No. I'm fine.
Let's eat.
I've made your favorite food,
Lontong Balap.
I'll eat it later.
I'm still tired.
Eat now.
Later. Stay here, Mother.
Don't go anywhere.
Stay here while I rest.
My beautiful child.
Mil.
Mila.
My beautiful child.
Mil?
Mila...
Go home, child.
You don't need to save me.
You don't know what you're about to face.
It's very dangerous.
Don't give in
to any of Badarawuhi's persuasion.
Don't!
Go home, child.
- Go home.
- Mother?
I can't stay long. She has seen me.
Mil? Mil?
Mother.
Wait.
- Wait. Don't!
- Mother!
- Wait.
Mother!
Beautiful child.
Your mothers are now in Angkara Murka.
The villagers here
know what they have to do.
Perform the ritual, child.
Perform the ritual...
before they all...
get hurt.
Mother. Mother.
- Ratih!
- Mother!
Mother!
No!
- Don't!
Mother... Mother, what's going on?
Mother...
- Ratih!
Ratih!
Mother! Enough!
Stop it, Mother!
Mother... Mother...
Mother!
Buyut! My mother! Help her!
Why did you bring this bangle here?
I'm sorry.
What is actually going on?
Before she died,
your grandmother had told me
to look for your mother.
I came to your mother's house.
But it was too late.
Badarawuhi got to her first.
Pardon me.
Grandmother?
Your mother is Inggri.
She's Putri's only child.
You mean...
Putri, the village elder?
Your grandmother died
from bearing the heavy burden
of this village's tradition.
She wanted to protect your mother
and the entire village.
Protect them from what?
Jiyanti's aura
attracts supernatural beings.
I don't want her to be chosen
as the dancer.
DANCING VILLAGE
If someone needs to die,
let me be the one,
and don't let my twin know.
What's going on here, Mother?
Why are my friends here?
Tomorrow...
your friends will dance for this village.
Are you sure you want to do this?
What if Badarawuhi knows
that Santika is not the chosen dancer?
Twins have the same placentas.
If not now, there will be
no other opportunities.
Do you want...
this village to continue
to be the slave of that devil?
Your job...
is to take Inggri away from this village.
But, Mbah, you...
will never meet Inggri.
Forever.
On the night of the ritual,
the fates of the twins were switched.
Jiyanti...
who was supposed to be the chosen dancer
was replaced by Santika.
We had to do it
to deceive Badarawuhi
and to take the bangle
out of this village.
Take this thing out of this village.
Hurry!
Inggri!
This whole secret,
no one knew about it
except the two of us.
The sacrifice Santika had made
caused a great pain
especially to Jiyanti.
But thanks to that,
the village was able to be free
from Badarawuhi's clutch.
It's not your responsibility.
Return it.
Don't take it.
Return it!
DANCING VILLAGE
Badarawuhi could not choose a dancer
for 25 years.
And all that time, Putri endured the pain
as a result of her decision.
This bangle should not have been
brought back here.
It was wrong for me to come here.
Forgive me...
This is all my fault.
But what about my mother now?
While I'm inside,
no one is allowed to come in.
Okay.
That is a rare black chicken
used in rituals,
which means it's serious.
Don't.
In the east, don't open a door so easily.
You never know what's behind it.
Oh, my God.
How did all the livestock die?
All of the cows are dead!
What's going on here?
All of my crops are ruined!
What happened?
Jito!
Oh, God.
Come on. Let's go home.
We have to go home now!
In my grandparents' house,
this is used to avoid misfortunes.
You are the misfortune.
- Don't be a know-it-all.
- I'm serious.
Here.
I'm sorry.
Don't get involved.
Mil.
Mila.
Why hasn't she gotten ready yet?
Mil.
Let's go home.
What else are you going to do, Mil?
I want to make sure
they perform the ritual.
You don't need to.
We better go home now.
See your mother's condition back home.
Come on.
Maybe the ritual can help my mother.
I don't want this journey to go to waste.
Drink this.
How does it taste?
Sweet.
She is the last one.
There's no other girl.
You want to taste the coffee?
Mil.
Drink it, child.
How does it taste?
Sweet.
This is bitter.
Don't talk nonsense.
Let's go.
You've been chosen...
as one of the dancers of this village.
What are you talking about?
She only chooses seven candidates
to become Dawuhs.
If the coffee is sweet, it's a sign
that she has to perform the ritual.
This is the cloth for the ritual.
Why can't we be there for the ritual?
Sorry, but they say...
that's the way it’s done.
No one from this village
can go for the ritual.
Only the elders.
What if something happens to you there?
We don’t know anything.
My job here is to protect you, Mil.
We will stay here
until Mila comes back.
Mil, but promise us
that you will come back.
What are you two saying?
Who can guarantee that Mila
will be safe there?
I won't accept it.
I can't.
You can't join something
without knowing the consequences.
If your mother knew, she would forbid you!
So, what should I do then?
This is the only way.
We will perform a ritual
that hasn't been done for a long time...
to save this village.
One dancer
will do her duty as the chosen dancer
to protect this village
in the years to come.
Close your doors and windows.
Keep on hitting the bamboo
to repel uninvited guests
born from the darkness.
Don't stop hitting the bamboo
to protect this village.
The village that is surrounded
by supernatural beings.
Don't come out of your houses,
whatever happens.
Because tonight,
the supernatural will come out
and eat anything.
Mil.
Don't do this. Please.
Mila.
Keep hitting the bamboos
until the ritual is finished.
Don't stop.
Don't ever stop.
This will be painful.
But this is your only way to come back.
After this, you will dance all day.
But I...
can't dance.
You can.
Kneel, please.
Don't stop playing the music
until the last dancer falls.
Inhale the shawl.
To the ruler of the forest,
the ruler of this place.
I offer these dancers for your selection.
Save this village from the impending doom.
One by one,
soul to end the anger.
Child, what did you see over there?
It's almost dark.
Mila still hasn't come back.
- I have a bad feeling.
- Don't!
Remember what Buyut said.
Jito.
Why hasn't anyone been chosen?
It's been too long.
It's the first time I have seen
something like this.
Child.
Here...
you are loved.
Adored.
Like a flower
that smells very good.
Don't you want to stay here, child?
What about my mother?
What's wrong, child?
Scared?
Stay here, child.
Accompany me.
Won't you?
Accompany me, child.
No...
No!
What did you see, child?
Bada...
Badarawuhi.
Why is she dancing again?
Cover them with a white cloth.
We have to try to stop this.
They're still unconscious.
They haven't come back.
Dancers...
- Dancers...
We can't be here. Come on,
take them to the village immediately.
- Dancers...
- Come.
- Put it there.
What's happening?
Be careful.
- Go on, go home, hurry.
- Yes.
- Go home.
- What's going on here?
- Protect your family.
Mil?
- Mila?
- Calm down.
What happened to Mila?
- What's happening to her?
- Get some salt.
Throw it to every side of this room.
Mil! Hang on, what's going on?
- Wake up, Mil.
- What's going on here?
Mil, wake up. Mil.
Oh, God. Ratih.
Ratih...
Mila...
- Yud!
- What's happening to her?
Badarawuhi hasn't chosen
between Mila and Ratih.
One thing is for sure,
currently, both of them
are in Angkara Murka.
What should we do?
Mila, wake up!
Help my cousin.
Ratih?
Mother?
Stay here. Let's play together.
Let's play together!
Mil, wake up! Mil, wake up! Mil!
Yuda!
Are you all right?
- Close the door!
- What happened, Yud?
Close the door!
Ratih!
Stay here, child.
Accompany...
her.
Ratih...
Ratih!
Don't you want...
to be...
like her?
Ratih...
with her mother...
Jiyanti.
Someone wants to meet you.
- Mila!
- Mother!
Mila!
Mother!
Mother... Mother!
Mil...
Mother!
- Mila!
- Mother!
Mother!
Mil... Mila!
Mother?
Mila.
My most beautiful child.
Mother?
Go home, Mila.
Let's leave, Mother.
I can't.
Come home with me, Mother.
I can't, Mil.
Go home, Mila.
I can't, Mother.
I cannot go home without you.
You can, Mil.
You can.
I don't want you to be a part of this.
Go home, Mila.
You are strong.
You have to live your life well.
Remember...
never ever...
Don't ever do what she wants you to do.
Remember that, Mil.
Mother... Mother...
Mother...
Mother!
Mother.
Don't you want...
to accompany your mother here?
Like... that girl?
Mother!
Mother...
Can you bear to see your mother like this?
Take pity on her.
Mil...
- Mila. Mil.
- Mila...
What's happening?
Her body is getting cold.
Help her. Mila.
Wait here.
- Mil!
- Mila!
Mila!
What is that?
Mother!
Don't!
Mil?
Mila.
Mil...
Mother...
Mil!
Child...
You are the only dancer who came back
from Angkara Murka.
I was able to come back
because of my mother.
Excuse me, we have to leave.
Mother!
What should we do after this?
I don't know yet.
But one thing is for sure,
there shouldn't be any more victims.