TUESDAY
NOVEMBER 25TH, 1986
Welcome to the short semester!
I hope you don't have to repeat courses.
Our currency is depreciating fast,
tuition fees will be expensive as hell.
But enough talk about money,
fun stuff coming your way.
Stay tuned to hear
your horoscope reading later by Miss Lin.
Now it's time for "Dudu! From Me to You."
Happy birthday to you
We wish you a happy one
May you live prosper and be healthy
And be happy and live long
No, Mawar! Stop!
Vey…
Can you hand me the pad from my bag?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Perfect.
You look gorgeous.
We picked the right dress.
It fits you nicely.
Wear this, for the extra oomph.
You're looking prettier than ever,
let's go out and meet some boys!
I need to look pretty
to meet my parents, too.
You're going now?
It'll be too late.
Who turned this into a messy celebration?
Is Melati going?
She's busy.
She can't leave her dorm.
Not even for her sister's birthday.
Babe, I'm coming in, okay?
Hey, you can't!
Why not?
See?
She's decent.
So, Mawar…
The birthday feast is tomorrow night?
Of course! Promise.
Deal!
All right, then. I'm going home.
Don't be too late.
I'm catching a ride with you. Okay?
- I'm going ahead.
- Bye!
Let's go home.
Mom, Dad…
Sorry for coming in so late.
Do you remember…
it's my birthday today?
Don't you miss me?
I miss you so bad.
Melati misses you too, Dad, Mom.
Dad…
do you remember?
Mom used to bake us a cake
for our birthdays.
They were so good.
I've tried everywhere and still
can't find one as good as Mom's.
Well…
I shouldn't be feeling sad.
Besides Mom's cake…
what else should I wish for?
Maybe a boyfriend?
Am I allowed one now?
I turned 20 today.
Do I have your blessing?
Yes?
Thank God.
I pray
for a boyfriend who loves me.
Someone who cares deeply…
and who will always be there for me.
Just like you two had each other.
Amen.
I have to leave now, Dad, Mom.
You shouldn't have, Mpok Atik.
Listen, this is a reminder I'll be
locking the gate at 10:00 p.m. sharp!
Well noted. Don't worry.
Thanks, Mpok.
Has Mawar come home yet?
Where is she?
At her parents' grave.
This late, babe?
She visits on her birthday,
she must miss her parents more.
Poor girl.
Her parents are gone,
her sister is far away,
and she's single.
Hook her up then with one of your boys.
Just someone less annoying than you.
Let me take her to a club.
Are you still clubbing?
You said you'd stopped.
Are you guys talking about me?
Alex wants to take you clubbing.
What's going on?
What is that smile on your face?
Nothing.
Did somebody give you a ride home?
A boy perhaps?
No.
I swear!
Mawar is wearing perfume.
What? No, Tika.
I can smell it from here.
No.
Mawar!
Mawar, we're not done. Spill, Mawar!
Tell us! We've embarrassed her.
Hello, who is this?
Who is this?
Mawar!
You're still up?
That was a prank call, just ignore it.
Did the prankster call again last night?
Maybe it was your mysterious boyfriend?
He must've hung up
when it wasn't you who answered.
A late night phone call, I see.
Mawar has a boyfriend?
When's your turn, Kartika?
Why me now?
Answer the question, Tika.
Tupac is my only man.
Look, your nose is bleeding.
Oh no, Mawar.
You promised you'd tell me anything.
What are you talking about?
We're not dating yet.
We just met.
But…
we clicked right away.
Like we have known each other.
What are you feeling now?
Well…
Happy.
Feels like I'm no longer alone.
So he's going to be
your very first boyfriend.
Well done, Mawar. It's your first love!
Stop it.
- Well done, Mawar!
- You're making me blush.
Mawar?
He's cheating.
What do you mean?
Hey.
What's wrong with your friend?
On her period?
Who was that?
That was Miss Lin, the campus' psychic.
She has that show on our radio.
Kartika knows her, too.
I told you about her. You don't remember?
You must've forgotten.
The food is here, but Mawar isn't.
Where is she, anyway?
I'm starving.
Let's not wait for her.
Maybe she's on a dinner date
with her boyfriend. Right?
By the way, who is her boyfriend?
You both are closer to her.
Nosy, much?
I'm curious, that's why I asked.
Hey! Use the plate.
Thanks, Mpok.
Dig in.
Here you go.
Miss! Let me help you.
No need.
This is for my guest.
Please remind your guest of the time.
I'm locking the gate soon.
See, it's hot!
Really! They didn't even drink the coffee!
That took effort, too!
See if they come back.
Good morning, Mpok Atik.
Hey! Shoes, shoes. Shoes!
All right, no problem. Easy peasy.
I'll just take them off.
Don't pout.
I want to see your pretty face.
Smile for me, all right? Beautiful.
Mpok.
Can I come up for a sec?
I swear I won't go in Vey's room.
Okay?
Do you want me to walk you out?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Want to go with us?
Drop by the radio station.
Tika's broadcasting.
We promised her.
Hello, Biru's friends.
Lunchtime is almost over.
But before we go back to our classes,
let's do some
"Dudu, From Me to You"!
I think someone's on the line right now.
Hello. Name and location?
Hello, your name and location, please?
Any song requests?
Or maybe you want to greet
someone on the air?
Well, Biru's friends,
I think we have a shy caller here, so…
From Restu…
to Mawar.
Mawar?
Mawar from Anthropology, Class of '94?
- What do you want to say to Mawar--
- Keep…
our promise.
Well, Biru's friends, that was a message
from Restu to Mawar.
He said, "Keep our promise."
Yes, Restu, that was smooth.
Have you noticed
Mawar is acting strange lately?
She bailed on us multiple times.
She never joins us at the house.
- I think--
- Did you hear my broadcast?
Tika…
This might have something
to do with Mawar.
Is there anybody
on our campus named Restu?
He called in and sent a message for Mawar.
I think that's her boyfriend.
Restu?
From which faculty?
He didn't say.
Have you seen Mawar?
She hasn't been here for two days.
I haven't seen her around.
Do you know Restu?
Restu?
Yeah, do we have any "Restu"
on our campus?
It's not like I know everybody
on our campus.
But I'll ask around, okay?
Babe.
Did you…
Did you ever see
Mawar with a guy in her room?
What do you mean?
Nothing. Forget I asked, babe.
I have to go.
Go to bed, don't worry about her.
Quoting Harman and Chomsky from 1988.
This type of situation created
dissatisfaction among the citizens
that was reflected
in the new wave of journalism.
Such as public journalism and
peace journalism as a response to…
Mawar?
Quoting Harman and Chomsky from 1988.
The situation created dissatisfaction
among the citizens…
Restu, promise not to ever leave me.
You're all I have in this world.
I promise…
I will follow you wherever you go.
Mawar?
Who were you talking to?
The gate is locked.
Your boyfriend?
Have you been inviting him in?
Even to your room?
Who is he?
Is his name Restu?
Restu, promise not to ever leave me.
You're all I have in this world.
I promise…
I will follow you wherever you go.
I have asked around.
There are three Restus on our campus.
First one, a literature major.
He has a girlfriend.
The second one is Restu Wulandari.
A girl.
The last one…
dropped out.
Two years ago.
Wait a second.
Hey, babe.
Thinking about Mawar?
The other day,
I saw an eye peeking out
from Mawar's window.
When was this?
You didn't say anything.
When I came to pick you up last time.
Can you describe the eye?
Well…
It was too quick.
- But Lina said--
- Lina? Miss Lin?
Yeah, not important, when Mawar--
What did she say?
It's not important, babe.
What's with you?
- Babe?
- Are you really a psychic?
Hey, stop it. Let's go home.
What did you say about Mawar?
Can we talk somewhere else?
You stay there.
Alex.
He said he saw something
in your friend's room.
So I did a cleansing ritual on him.
That's all.
Was what he saw supernatural?
Because my friend
has been acting strange lately.
Mawar started to change
since she has a boyfriend.
It started after she visited
her parents' grave.
Was there anything unusual…
when she went there?
She went there too late…
despite our warning.
She was on her period.
That night…
did she bring something home?
What do you mean?
I see…
a wooden box.
You can start by looking for the box.
If it exists…
there might be spirits
attaching themselves to her,
or someone put a spell on her.
Only then could we be certain.
Mpok.
You're home early.
Isn't Mawar home?
I think she is out.
Can I borrow the spare key to her room?
I need to get something.
Please, Mpok? She said it's okay.
Why are you in my room?
I'm worried about your boyfriend.
Stay out of it.
You don't know him.
You never introduced him.
Do you really know him though?
Where he's from, what his background is?
- Does Melati know?
- Don't drag her into this.
We don't want you
to get involved with the wrong guy.
His name is Restu.
He's a good person.
Mawar, your ear!
Leave me alone!
Now on to international news.
In the evening of Saturday,
September 7th, 1996,
famous rapper Tupac Shakur was gunned down
in his vehicle in Las Vegas, Nevada, USA.
Tupac is in critical condition
and under doctors' intensive care.
In the meantime,
local authorities are still investigating…
I don't get it.
Something is wrong with her boyfriend.
He's a bad influence on her.
I talked about Mawar with Lina.
And she said something is odd.
Did you find another Restu?
- Because I'm positive Mawar--
- Vey!
I don't want to talk about
Mawar right now.
I'm grieving.
Who is it?
Vey!
What's the matter?
- What's wrong?
- It's…
What?
A spirit…
is attached to your friend.
What kind of spirit?
You really want to see?
I still don't understand.
So according to Miss Lin,
scattering moringa leaves will let us see?
What the hell is going on?
What has Mawar's boyfriend done?
Put a spell on her?
I don't understand.
Neither do we, Don.
We're doing this to be sure.
Just in case Lina is right.
That something is attached to Mawar now.
Or followed her home.
Something, what?
Spirits, Mpok.
What are you talking about?
Ghosts.
Hey, watch what you say.
I also felt something strange last night.
Me too.
We have to save Mawar
from whatever makes her this way.
Oh, no. My laundry upstairs!
Laundry. My laundry!
- Mpok.
- Mpok!
- God forgive me!
Mpok, what happened?
What's wrong? Mpok?
There's… there's…
What is it, Mpok?
There!
God forgive me. God forgive me.
Slowly, slowly. Sit here.
Mawar.
Wake up!
Your boyfriend is no good!
Look at Mpok Atik!
What if we're all next?
Dona's right, Mawar.
Let us help you, okay?
We're very concerned about you, Mawar.
We want you to be okay.
- We're afraid your boyfriend--
- Restu.
He's a good guy.
So can we meet him?
What for?
Because we care about you.
This one has a boyfriend…
who cheats on her.
This one has an idol…
who is dead.
Got killed.
And this one…
doesn't even have anybody.
So she pokes her nose into
other people's business!
I have Restu.
If you want to see him…
he's coming tonight.
Mawar.
Isn't he coming?
He will.
Where did Mawar go?
I'll go outside. You, her room.
Where do we go, miss?
Vey.
Come on in…
let me introduce you to Restu.
This is…
Restu.
What's wrong?
Vey, what happened?
What are you doing here?
Don't you want to meet Restu?
God forgive me.
Mawar is outside.
You're still thinking about her?
Didn't you see what's outside? Fuck.
But she's in danger.
Vey!
Let's go!
Mawar?
Mawar!
Mawar.
Mawar! Hey!
Hold her.
- Mawar?
- Mawar…
Restu…
Mawar. Please snap out of it.
- Mawar…
- He's waiting for me outside, Vey.
Mawar, snap out of it.
Mawar, please. Restu is not human.
Wake up, Mawar.
Mawar… Mawar…
Restu…
Vey, Restu is waiting for me.
Mawar, snap out of it.
Restu, come and take me with you!
- Mawar!
- Mawar.
Mawar!
- Vey!
- Mawar!
Dona, get a rope!
Hurry!
Her name is Melati.
Tell her to come
as soon as she can. Tonight.
Where are you going?
What are you doing here?
Lin…
Babe, I can explain.
I don't give a damn.
I just need her help.
What is it?
It's actually worse.
She's in love with the demon.
If you're feeling bad…
now you can make it right.
Wait.
Hey… Babe!
Vey.
Help me.
Vey…
Those moringa leaves,
the string you showed me, and a shroud.
Vey.
They're ready.
Lin.
Put her on the shroud.
Mawar!
Lock the door, Mpok!
Kartika, get the moringa leaves!
Mawar.
Mawar?
Tik, Mawar is gone, Tik.
Tik, Mawar's gone.
I'll look in her room.
I'll look outside.
Mpok, the key.
Vey?
What's going on?
What happened to Mawar?
Mawar…
Forgive me, Mel.
So…
my sister…
is in love…
with a demon?
Mawar started acting strange
after visiting your parents' grave.
Your family…
there's a connection with this demon.
What do you mean?
Your parents' house.
Restu is going there.
Taking Mawar with him.
You're useful after all.
Vey, sure you don't want me
to go with you?
It's okay, Dona.
Stay here with Mpok Atik.
Keep each other safe.
We're going.
Babe.
Not now.
Let's go.
Hey! Oi!
What should I do?
Wait here.
If we don't come out, come inside.
Mawar?
Let's split up.
Mawar!
Mawar?
What's behind that door?
Mawar was here on her birthday.
Is this…
your father's room?
I don't know.
I didn't even know
about this room until now.
As I suspected.
This was a ritual…
for good fortune…
and prosperity.
A ritual that involved a corpse like this…
The spirit of the corpse
will attach himself to the family members…
for a thousand years.
And the person who performed the ritual…
must be buried in the same spot
where he dug the corpse out from.
That's impossible.
It can't be.
My father was a good man.
He would never have anything to do
with the demon.
Now what?
Where is Mawar, then?
We have to return the corpse to his grave.
Are your parents buried in the same grave?
My father…
asked to be buried on top of my mother.
Take us to your parents' grave.
What are you going to do
with my parents' grave?
It was Restu's grave first!
Your father dug this corpse out
from that grave.
Vey, the string!
Tie it on top!
Babe?
Lex, tie this string around the shroud
on top of his head.
Babe.
Lin!
Why do I have to carry this?
A little help here?
Tika?
Lina?
Mawar?
Sis, be careful! Wait!
Mawar!
Vey!
We lost Vey and Melati.
Alex is gone, too.
Did that asshole go back to the car?
Vey!
Damn it.
Why am I stuck with this freaking corpse?
Vey!
Lina!
Babe!
Mawar!
Sis!
Where else should we look for her?
Your parents' grave.
Vey…
They are all the same…
Lin, the headstones are all the same
with the same names.
Kar…
don't look left.
Walk straight ahead.
Follow them.
Seriously?
Maybe it's our fault.
Mawar.
Please forgive us.
Give us a chance to see you one more time.
Before you go with Restu.
Please, Mawar.
Please, for the last time,
we want to see you.
Hey, punk, what the hell did you eat
when you were alive?
You're heavy as fuck.
God damn it, what now?
Stay away, stay away, stay away…
- Lex!
- Shit!
You guys suck!
I should've waited in the car!
We suddenly lost everybody, too!
Vey and Melati?
How should I know, bitch?
Tika! Lina!
Vey!
Where have you been?
Look. The headstones…
Go to your parents' grave.
Over there!
Mawar!
Take off the string!
- The strings!
- Okay.
Cover it with the boards.
- Hurry up, Lex!
- I'm trying!
Hold her!
Restu!
Lex, let's bury him!
Sis, I need you!
Mawar, we all love you!
Sis!
How dare you, bitch!
Remember what we promised Father!
Always take care of each other.
We miss you, Mawar.
Please hear us, Mawar.
We need you in our lives.
Please don't leave me.
You're all I have.
Listeners, it's time
for international news.
Famous rapper Tupac Shakur
was pronounced dead last night
after a week of intensive treatment
in the hospital.
At the time of this broadcast,
authorities are still looking
for a suspect
responsible for his shooting
in Las Vegas, Nevada, USA.
Hello, Biru's friends.
We have Miss Lin this afternoon.
For your monthly horoscope reading.
All you Virgos must be waiting for this.
To every Virgo out there…
This month might be hard for you.
But don't worry.
Your friends are there for you.
They will face your problems with you.
You will find new happiness…
and make new memories
that you've been longing for.
But my Virgo friends, please beware.
There's a chance of you…
having to make a difficult choice.
Vey.
I want to thank you.
I'm really grateful to have friends
who care and love me this much.
Who won't let me fall in love
with the wrong person.
Thank you.
But love as they say, is blind.
Maybe in your eyes, Restu is wrong for me.
But what if for me,
giving this love feels right?
My birthday wish this year has come true.
To find someone
who can love me for who I am.
I wish…
you could see what I see.
Mawar.
It's okay, sweetie.
His name is Restu.
He's going to save our family.