OF THE CASES OF POSSESSION
IN THE CATHOLIC CHURCH,
90% ARE RELATED TO MEDICAL CONDITIONS
OR MENTAL ILLNESSES
ONLY 10% OF THEM NEED AN EXORCISM.
THIS IS ONE OF THOSE CASES.
BASED ON A REAL STORY
OF EXORCISM IN INDONESIA
Help!
Thomas…
Thomas!
Di! Di!
Di!
Hush now.
Di. Di!
Di. Di.
Di. Di…
Ma!
Help…
Help!
I'm scared.
I'm here, Di. I'm here.
- Thomas…
- Di. Di.
- I'm scared, Thomas.
- I know.
Please pray for me, Thomas.
- I'll pray for you, okay?
- Mm.
Dear Lord,
please help my sister.
We believe in Your wounds.
We need Your miracle.
Dear Lord, please have mercy on us.
Di?
Di…
Di!
"JESUS CALLED HIS TWELVE DISCIPLES
AND GAVE THEM AUTHORITY
TO CAST OUT UNCLEAN SPIRITS
AND TO WIPE AWAY
EVERY DISEASE AND WEAKNESS."
MATTHEW 10:1
REST IN PEACE
DIANDRA VALENCIA, DIANA DOROTHY
- Excuse me, sir.
Yes?
Please take it.
- Thank you, Father.
You're welcome.
- Good morning.
- Father.
Ah.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong, Thomas?
You know why I'm here.
- Oh.
- I wish to resign, Father.
Thomas.
Have you considered this carefully?
How about giving it some more thought?
I've made up my mind.
The service will start shortly.
We'll talk more about this later.
- Father, please!
- Okay, all right.
I can only stay
until the end of the semester.
I'M IN A MEETING.
WHERE SHOULD I PICK YOU UP?
Maya?
- Are you okay?
- It's Kayla.
She said she was coming to church,
but the service is over
and she's not here.
She's not picking up her phone.
Where is she?
Maybe with her friend.
Teenagers, you know?
- You're right.
- Don't worry.
Would you please talk to her?
Okay.
I'll try to,
even though she hates me.
You're ignoring
your food and your phone.
Poor thing. Please, be strong.
That's just how girls are.
They act like they don't need you.
- Whatever.
- Your mom is calling.
- Hey. Hey.
- Mm?
Just relax, okay?
I don't give up easily.
I'll try talking to Kayla.
Daughter to future stepdad.
I appreciate it.
Let me try once more.
She might pick up.
I hope so.
Just pick up.
It could be important, Kay.
They're probably just wondering
why I missed the service.
Oh.
I get it.
You don't want to meet
your mom's boyfriend.
Let's just drop it.
- Did she pick up?
- No.
She didn't.
For you.
- Can't you just talk to her?
- No use.
She won't listen to me.
I've told her that he is unfaithful.
He's got girls everywhere.
But she didn't believe me.
Yeah, I get it.
That's how my dad was too.
Luckily, they got divorced.
There's an upside, though.
The money is all mine.
Those homewreckers won't get any.
I miss Papa.
If he were alive,
Mama would've listened to him.
Only him.
I have an idea!
My dad has passed away.
How can I ask for his help?
We summon his spirit.
- You're a freak.
- True.
It's okay if you don't want to.
We can find another way
that's more appropriate.
Maybe…
we could secretly stalk Denis
until we get proof that he's cheating.
KAYLA, DENIS PROPOSED TO ME.
PLEASE COME HOME SOON.
Then, we'll show your mom the evidence
so she'll believe us.
Perhaps…
if you still want to use
a mystical approach,
graveyard soil will do.
You know how to do it?
Which one? Stalking or…?
Summoning my father.
Yes, I do.
Come on, relax.
Trust me.
You want to save your mom
from that jerk, right?
Ready, Kayla?
Are you sure it's safe?
It should be.
What if it's another spirit that comes?
This is your dad's grave.
Of course it'll be him.
Unless we get the wrong grave.
- Ouch! That hurts!
- Please be serious!
Why are you so tense? Come on.
- Cilla.
- Yes?
Are you sure?
Definitely.
Are you scared?
No.
I'm not scared at all.
Actually, I'm scared.
But we're here anyway.
Should we come back tomorrow at noon?
We can't.
Too many people.
They'd kick us out.
Some aunties might record us.
That happened to me once.
- People are…
- Cilla.
That's my dad's grave.
Be careful.
- This one?
- Yes.
Come on.
Let's say the chant together.
Jelangkung, jelangse.
We have a small party.
Come uninvited.
Leave on your own.
Seriously, Kayla?
Your dad won't understand if you mumble.
Even his spirit will be confused.
Try it again.
Okay.
Jelangkung, jelangse.
We have a small party.
Come uninvited.
Leave on your own.
- Kay!
- Cilla!
Quick, Kayla. What do you want?
Which one is Kayla?
Papa.
Pa,
please keep Mama away from that awful guy.
Hey, what are you doing here?
My friend misses her dad.
We're heading home. The reunion is over.
We're heading home now, sir. Bye.
Now what, Cilla?
We just wait and see.
Relax. Your dad was a kind man.
He will definitely help you.
Let's go home, or we'll get in trouble.
Just got home, Kayla?
DENIS, YOU JERK! YOU'D BETTER DIE!
Who is she?
So, my friend was lying?
Back then, you said Kayla was lying.
I'm starting to think
maybe there is another woman.
Let's just break up!
Forget about the wedding!
Thank you, Papa.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Father.
Good morning, Father.
Father.
I'm sure
that Diandra would be happy in heaven
to see you smile.
Cilla, it worked!
Hey, are you sick?
No.
What's wrong with your neck?
I'm not sure.
It's felt heavy since last night.
I'll take you to the infirmary.
Don't worry about it.
Good morning, class.
Good morning, Father.
Before we begin,
who'd like to lead the prayer?
- Yohannes?
- Yes, Father.
Please come forward.
Hi, Kay. You're home.
Have something to eat.
Maybe she's tired.
Papa.
Why is Mama still with that guy?
Please keep them apart.
I don't want anything to happen to Mama.
Kayla?
You're all sinners.
- You're all sinners.
- Kayla?
- What happened, Kay?
- You're all sinners.
- Kayla? Kayla, stop!
What's wrong, Kay?
Please, wake up, Kay.
Kayla?
You're all sinners.
- Kayla! Wake up!
- You're all sinners.
Stop it!
Are you okay, Kayla?
I'm fine, Ma.
Die.
Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die.
Good morning, class.
Good morning, Father.
It is with great sadness
I have to share this bad news.
One of your friends,
Priscilla, passed away last night.
Her remains will be buried tonight.
Please pray for her.
Kayla.
Kayla. He's calling for you.
Kayla, please come with me.
We know this must be hard.
You might still be in shock.
But we need to know,
did Cilla ever talk to you
or act strangely?
I have no idea, Father.
She just said that her shoulder hurt.
What happened to Cilla?
She's not really dead, is she?
Cilla!
If you know anything,
you need to tell the school board
so we can investigate.
Kayla?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong, Kayla?
Hey.
Kay.
What's wrong with you?
Kayla?
Kay!
Kayla!
Kayla, what's wrong?
- Kayla!
- You're a hypocrite!
You think your God can save this child?
Hey.
Kay? Kay?
Kay? Kayla!
Sister, please help.
How's Kayla doing?
Still unconscious, Father.
How did they end up like that?
I have no idea.
But… from the words she said
and the language she used,
this could be really serious.
I heard her talking in Latin.
Hmm.
Judging by your explanation,
Kayla's condition is not a medical
or mental issue.
This is the dominion of darkness.
It's demonic.
There's a priest
who can help us with this problem.
- Stop it! It hurts!
- Albert!
Fight it, Bert!
Fight it!
How could a child let his mother
die alone in the nursing home?
Michael, this is Mama.
Why did you leave me alone?
You're not my mother!
In the name of the Father, the Son,
and the Holy Spirit.
I command you to leave!
You have no power over Albert's body!
You have control over this body, Lord.
There is no power greater
than the power of Your blood.
In the name of Christ,
I command you to leave!
Michael, please don't hurt your mama.
Hold him down!
I, a servant of the Lord,
am given authority by the Holy Trinity
to cast you out, unclean spirit!
I command you to leave Albert!
Reveal your name!
Reveal your name, demon!
Kadastor!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you, Kadastor,
to leave this child!
Leave and yield under the feet of Christ!
Father.
Forgive me.
I can't continue this task anymore.
I'm too consumed with guilt.
The demons can see it
and it's hard for me.
Michael, they are playing with your mind.
Don't let them win.
As long as you admit your sins,
Satan can't attack you.
Forgive me, Father.
Maybe I'm not the right person.
Every time I hear my mom's voice,
I'm overwhelmed with guilt.
I can't take it anymore.
Forgive me, Father.
Please, forgive me.
Can I see this child
to verify if it's demonic possession?
When can you
and Michael come?
Michael can't help anymore.
Please.
As you know,
these days the Vatican forbids priests
from performing exorcisms alone.
You need an assistant.
Yes, but…
you know that not just anyone
can do this job.
They mustn't just be brave and faithful.
They have to have come to terms
with their past.
Actually, I'm looking for a successor,
not just an assistant.
If I remember correctly,
a background in psychology
is also important for exorcism, right?
Yes.
What if a priest
who hasn't made peace with his past
finds answers after learning from you?
"THE POOR ARE THE TREASURE
OF THE CHURCH"
I'm not the right person for this.
Cadaster, you know I want to resign.
This task pulls me back to church duties.
How can you be sure
you're not the right one?
You haven't even tried.
Okay.
I will help you with your resignation.
But please,
help Father Rendra with this case.
My apologies, Father.
I can't.
I do want to quit, but not this way.
I might end up hurting Father Rendra
or Kayla.
You should know my faith is fragile.
Excuse me, I have to teach.
Diandra.
Cilla.
They were both Kayla's best friends.
Now she's on her own.
Kayla is just like you.
Left alone by your loved ones.
At least do this for Kayla.
She needs your help.
I'm late.
Sssh!
Kayla, be quiet.
What?
Get Father Thomas, now!
Kayla!
- Kayla! Father Thomas!
- Father!
- Father Thomas! Kayla!
Kayla!
What's wrong with you?
Kayla, wake up!
You're a hypocrite.
A hypocrite! A hypocrite!
Kayla! Wake up!
Kayla. Kayla!
Father…
Come on. Help… help me
get her to the infirmary.
EXAM TIME: 90 MINUTES
COMPLETED OR NOT, MUST BE COLLECTED
Why do sinners like me live longer
than good people like Cilla,
Papa, and Diandra?
Why couldn't I have just died instead?
Kayla.
Cilla's death was also my fault.
I shouldn't have shared my problems.
I deserve this, Father. I'm full of sin.
Kayla, stop.
Enough.
Humans tend to blame themselves
for the death of their loved ones.
But death is…
inevitable.
All we can do is move on.
That's the only way.
There's something…
I need to tell you something.
It might be related to Cilla's death
and my situation.
All because
- we played…
- Kayla.
Feeling better now?
The principal wants to see you.
Please understand Kayla's situation.
She's still grieving.
Her friend just passed away.
With your permission,
I can contact a psychologist I know.
Maybe it could help Kayla.
I think she needs more help
than just counseling at school.
As long as she's willing,
I'm fine with it.
But I think Kayla just needs
to rest for now.
- But it's for her own good…
- Ma'am.
Thomas, I'm scared.
Help me, Thomas.
It's so dark here.
Stay with me, Thomas.
Stay with me.
Stay with me!
Father!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
I'm not trying to scare you.
But this is a dangerous task.
It's okay if you're not ready.
Honestly,
it's not fear that's stopping me.
Everything I feared in life has happened.
So what made you hesitate?
Father Roby said you refused at first.
I'm not sure I can help others…
when I need help myself.
Thomas.
Do you know why
the previous priest who helped me
decided to quit?
When we fight against demons,
they can see our emotions
and our past sins.
They use those against us
to intimidate us.
Are you ready?
Not to mention how strong
the physical attacks are.
They're rebellious angels.
They're not made of flesh like us.
If you're not up for it,
then don't do it.
Speaking from what I've seen,
you'll give up and lose faith.
It's dangerous
for both you and the victim.
It's a matter of life and death.
To do the exorcism…
what do I need to learn, Father?
Only 10%
of these cases actually need exorcism.
We need to be able to tell the difference.
Kiss the cross.
You need to study this book
about various types of demons
and their names.
This is Kadastor.
The devil can see our sins.
So, we must make a confession
before performing an exorcism.
…because I am angry with God.
…because I didn't pray
for my late mother and sister.
And most important of all is faith.
We need to understand
that this is God's power
against the dominion of darkness.
So as servants of God,
we need to be humble.
Bear in mind that if we do succeed,
it's not our victory.
It's God's triumph.
Kayla.
How are you feeling, Kay?
Is there anything you want to share
about you and Cilla?
I'm really sorry, Kay.
Our communication's been off lately.
You know, when I had you,
I was still very young.
I'm still trying
to be a good mother, Kayla.
I went to the cemetery with Cilla.
Maybe since then
the terror started
and Cilla's dead.
It's all my fault, Ma.
You guys went to the cemetery?
What for?
I missed Papa.
Mama! Mama! It's me, Kayla!
What happened?
It's me, Kayla.
FATHER THOMAS
Hello, Father.
Good afternoon, Ms. Maya.
This is Father Rendra.
Since Kayla is a girl,
I have Sister Indah with me.
Yes. Thanks for coming, Father.
Please come on in.
Go on.
No need to take them off.
Please excuse us.
Excuse me.
This way, Father.
Father Thomas told me about the situation.
How's Kayla?
Any other bizarre incidents?
Yes, Father.
Kayla told me that ever since she
and Cilla went to the cemetery,
they've been experiencing terrors.
Well, occultism is one of the gateways
to dominions of darkness.
Kayla.
Meet Father Rendra.
He will pray for you today.
Ah…
Please wait outside.
During the whole process,
please recite the Apostles' Creed.
Can you do that?
Kayla, how are you feeling?
I'm fine, Father.
In the name of Jesus.
Dear God, have mercy on us.
Christ, have mercy on us.
In the name of the Holy Trinity,
have mercy on us.
In the name
of the Holy Trinity, have mercy on us.
I cast you out,
unclean spirit,
along with every Satanic power
of the enemy,
every specter from hell,
and all your fallen companions.
In the name of our Lord Jesus Christ,
begone and stay far
from this creature of God.
For it is He who flung you
from the heights of heaven
into the depths of hell.
He who comforts you.
He who once stilled the sea
and the wind and the storm.
I bind
all enemies of Christ.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command
all enemies of Christ
with no power over our lives to be gone!
I'm fine, Father.
Why won't you believe me?
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I sever all ties,
all bonds, and all connections,
between Kayla and any demonic sources.
What's this? I said I'm fine now.
You're just stressing me out!
Perhaps the demon has gone.
I adjure you, ancient serpent,
by the Judge of the living and the dead,
by your Creator,
by the Creator of the whole universe,
by Him who has the power
to consign you to hell,
to begone from this servant of God, Kayla…
…who seeks refuge
in the fold of the Church,
and to depart forthwith in fear,
along with your savage minions!
Kayla, stop!
Kayla, let go!
Sister!
Sister. Sister!
Kayla, wake up!
Wake up, Kayla!
Father!
Father, can I come in?
No! Continue praying!
Thomas!
Help me! Hurry up!
Kayla.
Get that thing away from me!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
leave, unclean spirit!
Dear Lord, please help us!
Help me, Thomas.
Thomas!
Thomas, get a hold of yourself!
Get a hold of yourself!
- Kayla!
- She's not Kayla!
Hold her!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
reveal your name!
Reveal your name!
You damn priest!
You're all sinners.
You belong in hell!
In the name of Jesus Christ, the Lord
of heaven and earth, reveal your name!
Dagal!
In the name of Jesus Christ
I command you, Dagal,
leave and yield
under the feet of Christ!
Leave!
It's okay now.
All praises and glory to You, my Lord.
Thank you. Amen.
Mommy's here, Kayla.
Forgive me.
I couldn't help much.
Don't worry about it.
You did your best
and didn't give up till the end,
no matter how hard it was.
Thank you.
GETTING TIRED OF STUDYING ALL THE TIME,
SO WE FINALLY TOOK A PHOTO
I'M SO HAPPY! MAMA GAVE ME
A SPECIAL PRESENT TODAY.
DENIS, YOU JERK! YOU'D BETTER DIE!
MAMA TRUSTS THE PLAYBOY
MORE THAN HER OWN DAUGHTER!
GOD, PLEASE KEEP MAMA AWAY
FROM THAT JERK!
THANKS, PAPA, FOR HELPING ME AND MOM!
AND FOR GETTING RID OF THAT JERK!
DIE! DIE! DIE!
YOU SHOULD SEE THIS
You still wish to resign?
Truth be told,
it's hard for the church to let you go.
Especially now
that Father Rendra has asked me
if he can take you under his wing.
Forgive me, Father.
I hope he can get a better partner.
He doesn't just need a partner.
He needs a successor.
He has been sick for a long time now,
and I believe
that you have what it takes.
I'm worried
because when he retires
and can no longer perform exorcisms,
who will be able to take over?
Very well.
I'll proceed with your resignation,
as I promised you.
Thank you, Father.
How impressive.
- Try it out.
- Okay.
Hey.
If your father were alive
he would've been proud.
- I'll try it out.
- Mm.
Here.
I'm proud too.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm!
- Does it suit me?
- It suits you.
It does.
We have something for you.
Thank you.
Just a thank you?
- What else do you want?
- Ice cream.
- I want a lot of them.
- You eat too much.
You eat ice cream every day.
Please pray for me.
Kayla?
Kayla.
What are you doing?
I wish I could sleep
with you more.
What's wrong, Ma?
Kayla!
Kayla? Kayla!
- This is your plan? You want to kill me?
- Mama!
- Denis! Denis!
You okay, Kay?
Stop it! She's my daughter!
Maya.
Listen to me.
Please.
Take a good look.
She's not Kayla.
I'm sure she's still possessed!
Now you see his true nature.
- I told you he was a jerk, Mama!
- Kayla!
Watch your mouth.
Wait, why am I the bad guy here?
As if you're the victim, Kayla.
Wow.
You think I don't know?
Your mom found your jelangkung.
You used jelangkung…
to split us up.
Right?
Do you trust him or me?
Denis, please.
I want us to talk nicely, not like this!
Really, Maya?
Talk?
You wanted to be a good mom, right?
Prove it.
Leave him!
- What…?
- Take this!
- Denis!
- What the hell?
You are both crazy.
Are you okay, Kay?
It's okay.
Good evening.
Father Rendra.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
How are you and Kayla?
Since you prayed for her,
things have been getting worse between us.
I feel so restless lately.
I feel like I made things hard
for my daughter.
Why do you think so?
I have a dark past, Father.
I got pregnant
when I was still in high school.
My parents kicked me out.
My life was a mess.
Until I finally met
and married my husband.
He led me to Jesus Christ, Father.
Kayla doesn't know, even now,
that he wasn't her birth father.
Ever since he passed away,
we've been losing our way.
Well, everyone has a past.
It doesn't matter.
The present does.
Where we live in a godly way
and take responsibility for our sins.
Remember,
God will never give us
more than what we can bear.
And I believe
that I'm here as His servant,
giving strength to you and Kayla
to overcome this.
- Father.
- Yes?
I don't know where to start,
but I found jelangkung in Kayla's room.
And I feel like she's not
fully healed yet, Father.
I still feel threatened, Father.
Father, are you okay?
I'm okay.
THE BIBLE
"Then it goes and takes with it seven
other spirits more wicked than itself,
and they go in and live there."
"And the final condition of that person
is worse than the first."
"That is how it will be
with this wicked generation."
Thomas? Hello?
- Hello?
- Thomas! Hello! Hello!
- Father?
- Thomas?
Kayla.
Father.
Why are you here?
Kay.
Kayla!
I'm sorry, Father.
I'm sorry, Ma.
Kay?
Kayla?
What happened?
- I'm sorry, Father.
- Kay?
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry, Father.
Kay? Kayla!
Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die.
I thought you two
had managed to get rid of the demon.
I'm sorry, Father.
I didn't realize it sooner.
We thought it was
just a result of occultism.
But it's more than that.
It's a case of Legion.
There wasn't just one of them.
What are you saying?
Kayla played jelangkung
to summon the spirit of her late father.
But Lucifer's disciple came instead.
Dagal is Lucifer's disciple from hell.
I'm afraid there are other disciples
who have also possessed Kayla.
And the last one standing
is the strongest one.
Ms. Maya's life
could be in danger.
Both of their lives could be.
Right.
Father.
Let me help Kayla.
You'd better leave now.
I'll ask the bishop for permission later.
Their lives are what's most important now.
Thomas.
May God be with you.
And you, Father.
Kayla.
Kay?
- Die. Die.
- It's Mama.
- Die. Die. Die.
- Kayla?
- Die.
- Kayla? Please wake up.
Die. Die.
It's Mama.
Kayla.
Wake up, Kayla. This is your mama.
A sinner like you
deserves to die.
Kayla!
Kayla! Please wake up!
Open the door!
Open it!
Mama?
Mama.
It's time to meet your husband.
Kay!
Help!
Kayla!
Kayla, wait!
I won't stop
until all your people
turn against Him!
Kayla!
See you in hell.
Kayla?
Kayla!
- Kayla!
Oh my God!
- In the name of the Father…
- It's no use to pray.
Even His power can't stop me!
Our Father who art in heaven…
Hasn't He failed to save
your mother and sister?
Thy kingdom come!
Thy will be done on earth
as it is in heaven!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I cast you out, demon!
Thomas…
Thomas, I don't want to die here.
I cast you out, unclean spirit!
The dominion of darkness…
It hurts…
In the name of Jesus…
Don't kill him!
- Surrender!
- Don't kill him!
- Help!
Help!
Father!
Release Kayla!
She's innocent.
I'm the sinner.
Take my body.
Kill yourself. And I'll go.
Keep your promise.
I'm sure that Diandra
would be happy in heaven to see you smile.
God is with me.
God is with me!
I'm proud too.
We have something for you.
Kayla?
Please, forgive me.
No, Ma.
It's for your sake, Kayla.
Don't leave me, Ma!
God has promised to always be by my side.
By the power of Jesus Christ
I condemn you, demon!
Meet your demise!
I cast you out, unclean spirit,
along with every Satanic power
of the enemy,
every specter from hell,
and all your fallen companions.
In the name of our Lord Jesus Christ,
begone from this creature of God!
Begone, you godless being!
Begone, you, the condemned!
Begone with all your trickeries!
For God has commanded humans
to be His temple!
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit,
reveal yourself, demon!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
reveal your name!
Zababel!
Zababel, the condemned demon,
in the name of Jesus Christ,
begone from Kayla's body!
Kayla? Kayla! Kayla!
Kayla.
Thank you, Lord.
GET WELL SOON, FATHER RENDRA
FROM MAYA AND KAYLA
Aren't you leaving?
You're not fully recovered.
If you wish to leave, then go.
I won't stop you.
I've found my purpose, Father.
God is with me here.
Actually, you've always known.
God never makes mistakes
in choosing His servants.
Help me from now on.
You've got a lot to learn.
Yes, Father.
PRISONER
I'm really sorry, sir.
I…
Please forgive me.
I didn't mean to run away.
I was just scared.
I forgive you.
THEN JESUS SPOKE AGAIN, SAYING:
"I AM THE LIGHT OF THE WORLD."
"THE ONE WHO FOLLOWS ME
WILL NEVER WALK IN DARKNESS,
BUT WILL HAVE THE LIGHT OF LIFE."
JOHN 8:12
FATHER RENDRA
Thomas, sorry to bother you.
Someone needs help tonight.
We need to do the exorcism now.
Please come quickly.