Please fogive me, Lord.
Ni Loro Pati…
Hey, Tari. Hey.
You're not ready?
You'll miss the queue number.
Come on.
Brother.
Do we have any other choice?
I don't think we should take Mother
to the shaman.
What choice do we have?
We've talked about this last night.
You agreed, and so did I.
Please, Tari.
Ever since you were a kid,
you never do what I say.
Come. Hurry up.
Mother…
Wake up, Mother.
Miss, you need to fill out this form also.
- Excuse me, sir?
- You need to fill this out.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Why do we need to put our birth dates?
It's Mother who needs treatment.
Don't make a big deal. Just write it down.
You want Mother to get well soon, right?
THE COMPANION'S INFORMATION
Brother.
I'm not really sure about this.
- Brother!
- Huh?
Were you listening to me?
What are you up to?
So preoccupied with your cellphone.
It's that…
My boss has been asking,
when will I be back for work?
…the bedroom, and this is the living room.
It’s to speed up the healing process…
Get well soon.
- A token of our appreciation.
- Thank you so much.
- I'll be on my way.
- Take care.
Here you go.
Sit down.
The swelling is getting worse.
Yes, sir.
The doctor has treated me
for two years now.
I'm still not cured.
No need to worry, ma'am.
Let's start, shall we?
Ni Loro Pati.
- Brother…
- Tari…
Come on.
It's done.
Thank you so much, sir. I'm healed.
Ma'am.
- Is it done, sir?
- Done.
You may see her.
Mother, how are you feeling?
I feel cured.
- You can walk on your own.
- Indeed.
- Let me put on some clothes.
- Please.
- Sir.
- Yes?
This is to neutralize the negative energy
and to protect from bad things.
Thank you so much, sir.
He can't make it tomorrow night.
Mbah Narto is going out of town.
His usual appointment.
I'm very sorry, sir.
Yes… Yes…
- Treatment done, sir?
- Done.
How are you feeling, ma'am?
I feel healthy.
May you be healthy always.
- What should I do with these?
- Regarding these…
Put them in front of the house
and inside her room.
- Okay.
- Got it?
I see.
Please accept.
Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yes.
- Excuse me.
- Take care.
- We'll get down here.
- Alright.
Stop here.
- Just a moment, Mother.
- Thank you.
Don't bother.
I'm completely healthy.
Mother.
- Come on.
- Sir.
- Thank you.
- Brother.
- Yes?
There's a package.
- From who?
- I don't know.
Mother…
PAY YOUR DEBTS
OR YOUR FINGERS WILL BE CHOPPED OFF
This hammer is so small.
What's wrong?
Right?
What do you think?
- This is the genuine thing.
- It's genuine?
- This is…
- Nugie.
Go and get
- the Balinese one.
- Okay.
Here you go.
It's not good enough.
Oh, I see.
It's alright.
It doesn't really suit you.
When it comes
to owning a dagger,
it's about taste.
It's about what you feel.
Ah, here's one.
Nugie, explain to Mister Agung.
If I may, Mister Agung?
This is a Nogotopo dagger.
It's almost 300 years old.
Its illustration,
Singkirgeni.
Its power is… Um…
It is believed
if our house catches fire, we just
brandish this dagger outside the house,
and our house will be safe.
Please, take a close look, sir.
You see?
Please…
This is…
- This is really good, sir.
- See.
It's just…
If you don't mind me saying,
I already have this kind of dagger
in my collection.
You mean with that kind of column?
- Yes.
- I see.
If you get something else,
something new, something unique,
inform me right away, Nugie.
- Bring them to my house.
- Will do. Will do.
If you don't mind, I have to go.
I have another appointment.
- I'll be on my way. Thank you.
- Pleasure's all mine.
Thanks to you too.
- Take care.
- Yes. Excuse me.
Nugie, Nugie…
You keep coming late every day.
And your advance has been piling up,
taken from your salary.
Yes, sir.
What's wrong?
- It's just, sir…
- Well, what is it?
I have needs, sir, for the house.
- There are so many urgent needs.
- Alright, alright.
Starting tomorrow,
you have to show up
on time for work. Punctual!
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
Otherwise, I must find a replacement.
Please don't, sir.
Here. This month's remaining salary.
Enjoy, sir.
Let's go.
- Sir.
- Hey!
You bastard.
- That's him!
- Hey!
Hey!
Stop!
You!
Will you stop?
Stop or else!
Stop.
Just stop, will you?
You're gonna die!
Die!
- Get in!
- Get in.
- Damn you.
- Have mercy.
You and your numerous excuses.
- No.
- Come.
Come on!
- Sir.
- Here you are.
Here he is, boss.
I actually hate violence.
I wholeheartedly help people in need.
But you people take me for granted.
I understand.
You borrowed my money
for your mother's treatment.
- I know that.
- Yes… Yes…
You have my respect.
Thank you.
But a debt is still a debt.
You have to pay it back.
- Please, sir…
- You have two days to pay.
I will come to your place
to collect the money.
Or do you prefer to be beaten like this?
No. No, sir.
You keep avoiding me.
When I called you, you ghosted me.
What kind of manner is that?
- You guys handle him.
- Sir…
Sir, please. I've had enough.
That's your lesson.
Come here!
- Sir, do you want to…
- Go.
That's cucumber tree,
musk oil, and agar wood.
All of the best quality.
Just as you requested.
Thank you so much.
If it wasn't for you,
we wouldn't have
an offering this good.
Yes, yes…
By the way…
Your daughter, Laksmi, where is she?
I haven't seen her.
It's like this.
- She doesn't live here anymore.
- I see.
Thing is,
Laksmi is still angry at me
because I asked her to get involved.
- Please… Have some tea.
- Thank you.
I hope
she will be relieved soon
because I'm in the process
of finding a successor.
I ask for your forgiveness.
I apologize.
I will still do my assignment.
I ask your forgiveness.
Peace be unto you.
And unto you peace.
Tari!
Where is it?
- I threw it away.
- How could you?
Gosh!
Brother.
I don't want our house to have
those unholy things, brother.
That’s considered shirk.
You see how Mother is now.
She's getting better.
That's not what I meant.
I don't want our family…
You're just being a smart ass, Tari.
- What happened to your face?
- Nothing happened.
Here.
The rest of my salary.
Thank you.
Yeah.
A debt is still a debt.
You have to pay it back.
You have two days to pay.
I will come to your place
to collect my money.
Have mercy.
You know what the consequences are.
He can't make it tomorrow.
Mbah Narto is going out of town.
His usual appointment.
Tari.
Mother?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Nugie, come on.
Leave this house, now!
Hey!
Wow.
This dagger…
- It's so special. Extraordinary.
- Great.
- Nugie.
- Yes?
All of my life,
this is the first time
I see a dagger this ancient
and still in good condition.
I see, sir.
Look closely at its form.
- See the illustration.
- Yes?
It must have originated
from a certain period.
- King Airlangga's period.
- Oh.
Magnificent.
I guess it's worth a fortune?
My current estimation…
A hundred million rupiahs.
A hundred million?
Nugie, be honest. Where did you get it?
Yesterday, I was
cleaning my house, taking things out,
moving things here and there.
Then I found a chest
with this dagger inside.
My grandfather's heirloom.
And you found it like this?
Without any sheath whatsoever?
No, sir. Just like this.
Yes.
I need to closely examine it.
See what lies inside.
Sir!
Sir?
- Sir?
- Let's be clear.
I don't want this thing here.
Take it away.
But you said you're interested in it.
You don't know what I saw.
Take this dagger away.
- Go away!
- But sir…
Go, and don't you ever come back.
I don't want to have anything
to do with you again.
IF YOU OPEN IT, CLOSE IT AFTERWARD
Thief!
Die!
- Die!
- Hey!
Die!
Wake up!
Wake up, sir.
What is wrong with you?
Nothing is wrong, sir. Excuse me.
It's closed. Mbah Narto
isn't seeing anyone.
CLOSED
Is it okay?
Yeah, I don't know.
Sir…
We couldn't find it anywhere.
You sure you haven't forgotten
where you kept the dagger?
That chest is always here.
I'm doomed.
The full moon is coming.
If the dagger isn't returned…
Sir!
Waskito.
Yes, sir.
Have you…
Have you called Roso?
I've tried. He still can't be reached.
Oh, no.
Then…
Get Laksmi. Tell her
to come home. Alright?
I want to see her before it's too late.
Yes, sir.
- Excuse me!
- Nugie.
- Please have some kindness, sir.
- We're taking everything.
- That one…
- Ah, there he is.
- He finally showed up.
- That's the only memento of my late father
Please don't take it.
Brother, do something.
Then pay up.
- Please, sir.
- Move away.
- Please stop.
- Can't we talk about this?
Pay.
I will report it to the police
if you don't stop taking our things.
Call them. Call the police.
- Please don't take our belongings.
- Don't take them…
- Have mercy on us.
- Ma'am, please be quiet.
Quiet!
I have rights here.
Nugie has an outstanding debt.
Forty million rupiahs.
- He hasn't paid it back.
- Sir…
- Mother.
- Nugie…
- Here, here.
- What debt is this?
Tell me.
Yes, Mother. I will tell you later.
Sir, can we…
You promised to pay.
- I know, sir.
- I've been waiting for you in the office.
- Where's the money?
- I'm about to pay it back.
- I will pay it back today.
- If you don't,
you can guess what will happen.
- Yes, sir…
- Be true to your word.
Look, sir.
A dagger?
You think our boss Broto is a shaman?
- Sir…
- Do you want to fool around?
Because if you do,
I will chop off your hand.
Please be patient.
This dagger worth’s a lot.
If you sell it,
it will be enough to cover my debt.
Our boss is expecting cash.
Not a rusty dagger like this.
Sir!
Sir, don't do it.
Brother, don't.
Mother.
I ask for your forgiveness.
Brother. Brother.
Why didn't you tell me you owe
that loan shark that much money?
Initially, it was
ten million rupiahs, Tari.
- But with interest…
- Didn't you know they're loan sharks?
Exactly.
That's how it became 40 million,
with interest.
Tell me how?
How can we get that much money
to pay them back?
I didn't know either.
I lost my wits.
I eventually broke into Mbah Narto's house
to steal money.
"Steal"? You stole?
- Stealing is a sin.
- I didn't know what else to do.
- Don't you know the cardinal sins?
- I didn't know what else to do, Tari.
Today is the due date.
When I opened that chest,
I didn't find money.
I found that sacred dagger instead.
Don't you realize Mother is ill?
If she finds out,
she will be very disappointed in you.
She can't be burdened with things.
- You must return that dagger.
- Are you insane?
I'm insane? You are insane.
You know it's a sacred dagger.
You have to return it.
If I go to prison,
who will look after Mother?
- Who will look after you?
- I don't want to know.
- Who will look after Mother--
- Return the dagger. You saw what happened.
- Think about--
- Nugie.
Do what your sister said.
Return that dagger.
Hi.
Miss, welcome.
Your father is waiting for you.
Please, miss.
Be by his side.
Father.
Daughter.
Thank you.
You've come home to see your father.
My life… is about to end.
I apologize.
Even until these last seconds,
I've been a burden to you, child.
I'm very sorry.
YOU HAVEN'T PAID YOUR DEBT
DEADLINE IS TONIGHT
PAY UP, OR I WILL BURN YOUR HOUSE
I'M WAITING. DON'T PLAY AROUND WITH ME
Where else should I go?
Brother.
Yes?
You're not getting ready?
You're doing it, right?
You'll return the dagger today.
You want me to go with you?
In case something happens,
I can explain to them.
No need, Tari.
This is my responsibility.
In the name of Allah, the most gracious,
the most merciful.
Afterwards we'll figure out
how to repay your debt.
Okay.
If you don't mind me saying,
I already have this kind of dagger.
If you have something else,
something new and unique…
Inform me right away, Nugie.
Bring them to my house.
This is so beautiful.
Really beautiful.
Can't believe my luck.
I've been searching so long
for a dagger like this.
How about I pay you for this dagger
50 million rupiahs?
Yes. It's yours, sir. We have a deal.
Your bank account. I will transfer now.
If I may…
If it's possible, I'd prefer cash, sir.
You're kidding, right?
If it's cash you want,
I will prepare it for you.
You wait here.
So beautiful. I can't believe my luck.
Money… Money, money.
Let the money flow.
Sir?
Sir! Sir!
Tonight it's a full moon.
Time to bathe the dagger.
I have no strength anymore.
I will find an alternative cure.
Be strong. Wait for me.
Please look after them.
I'm going to get an alternative cure.
Yes, sir. Please take care.
Mbah Narto must find a way
to cure your mother, whom he loved dearly.
For days, 30 days, to be exact,
Mbah Narto went meditating.
Yet, his wish was shattered.
Fate came and played tricks on him.
Your father is here, Laksmi.
Laksmi. Laksmi…
You have asked for the cure.
And I, Ni Loro Pati, have fulfilled.
I beg for forgiveness.
Laksmi…
Awake, child.
Quick…
Give me your daughter's blood.
As proof of your service to me.
I will.
I will do it.
I know it's not easy, sister.
He has been searching
for someone who shares
the same birth date as you,
so the dagger's ownership can be replaced.
Alright.
If my father passes away
before the dagger is inherited
by someone else,
I will die.
- Sir!
- Father!
- Help him!
- Sir!
Father!
Father! Father!
Sir.
Mr. Rekso.
Is there a way
for me to get away from this plight?
There is one thing you can do.
But only after you find that dagger.
Listen.
You have to do the usual ritual.
And it will ask for an offering.
What do you mean by this?
I told you to bring money to me.
- Money. Money. Money.
- Yes.
So why did you bring this damned dagger?
Sir…
- No!
- Hold him.
It's a priceless dagger.
Someone wanted to pay 50 million rupiahs.
Gosh.
Yes, sir.
You're not lying?
No.
If you lie to me…
Yes, sir.
Seventy-five?
We'll meet tomorrow then.
Yes.
Ouch. Tari. Tari.
- Tari.
- Mother.
You are so pale.
I seek forgiveness from Allah.
- My body…
- Mother.
You have a high fever.
Oh, my feet. My God.
Hold on. Let me…
Allah…
My Goodness… Mother.
Why are they swelling again?
- It hurts.
- Okay, okay.
I feel pain everywhere.
- Let's go to the doctor.
- It hurts.
- No.
- Okay, to the doctor.
No, don't. Ouch.
Just a minute. I'll fetch some water.
It hurts a lot.
So painful.
It hurts.
Please.
Not so fast.
- What's the matter, sir?
- I will definitely give
this release letter to you…
on one condition.
What?
You will not receive a single cent
from the sale of this dagger.
What do you say?
I agree. Just sort it out.
- It's a deal then?
- Deal.
That's settled, then.
Here you go.
If you need anything,
call me. I will help you.
I surely hope in the future,
I wouldn't need to ask for your help.
I was just offering.
Such an expensive dagger.
Yes, Tari?
Mother is sick again?
How come?
I'm coming home.
Sir?
Sir!
Sir…
- Peace be unto you.
- And unto you peace.
How is Mother?
She…
My God…
What happened to your face?
Nothing.
Brother. Why are you black and blue?
I bet it's because of Mbah Narto.
- No, it's not.
- Brother, I'm talking to you.
Please tell me. I'm so confused.
What is wrong with you?
You have returned the dagger, haven't you?
You've been gone all day. Why?
Brother… You have really
returned it, right?
Tari.
I'm so tired.
I have… I have returned the dagger.
Tari, don't.
Tari, don't. Tari.
You haven't returned it after all.
I have, Tari.
You don't learn, do you?
You don't remember
that terrifying incident?
It's God's way of warning you.
Don't let it get worse.
You better go. I can't think
if you keep on blabbering.
If you won't get rid of that dagger,
then I will.
Tari. Tari.
Tari. Tari, don't.
What shall I do now?
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Nugie…
The voice doesn't exist.
There's no voice.
Don't listen, idiot.
Think about it.
That voice…
I'm not hearing the voice.
Shut up, idiot.
Shut up!
Stop it!
Stop it.
Have mercy.
Worship me,
and you will get the world.
No…
Wake up. She's your sister!
This is Tari!
Tari…
Tari.
Mother.
Mother…
I'm sorry, Mother.
I'm sorry.
REGISTRY FORM
THE COMPANION'S INFORMATION
Sir.
Damn it!
It was you who stole it.
- Ungrateful bastard.
- Sir…
What? What are you saying?
- Mercy.
- Too late.
Mbah Narto died because of you.
- You thief!
- What is it, Uncle?
What's going on?
Miss, this man…
He's the one who stole Sir Narto's dagger.
Who are you?
My name is Nugie.
- Nugie?
- Yes…
Are you Mrs. Sumeni's son?
That is correct.
My name is Laksmi, Narto's daughter.
Miss Laksmi.
I apologize for doing that stupid thing.
I swear
I had no intention to steal that dagger.
- You think it's easy for you to apologize…
- Uncle.
- Nugie.
- Yes…
Please get up.
Thank you for returning
the dagger to our family.
I bet you've faced
many strange happenings.
Miss…
Ever since I had that dagger,
many people have met their demise.
I eventually hurt my sister.
And
my mother is getting sick again.
Nugie…
Let's consider your business
with the dagger is done.
Thank you, miss.
However…
I'm more concerned about your mother.
Listen…
Your mother was ill
and then cured by this dagger.
And then,
her family, which is you,
stole the dagger.
So we need to do a cleanse
to dispel the bad luck from your family.
Miss, I will do anything
to atone for my sins.
Then, we need to do
the ritual to bathe the dagger.
The main act to cure your mother.
But the ritual requires blood.
The blood from Mrs. Sumeni.
Alright, miss.
Then, you only have tonight to do it.
And no one else should see it.
Alright, miss.
Tonight.
Miss, please reconsider it.
This is not the way to do it.
Every ritual should be done properly,
with full sincerity.
Uncle…
This is the only way.
No more discussion.
Do I need to remind you
that my father raised you
since you were a child?
If you don't want to help me,
it's alright.
I can do it on my own.
But don't you dare to get in my way.
Now,
you may cut her arm.
Please.
Why?
You have doubts?
Nugie… Remember.
This is the only way to save your mother.
Please…
Forgive me, Mother.
Mother?
Brother?
Brother…
Mother.
Ni Loro Pati.
I want to ask something.
To redeem my soul,
I'm giving this offering
for your power.
May Ni Loro Pati
grant my request.
Mother.
Who's inside?
Sir?
Sir, help me. I'm locked inside.
Get out.
Come.
Slowly.
Careful.
Where is your brother?
He's going to do the dagger
bathing ritual with Laksmi,
Narto's daughter, in this house.
What ritual, sir?
Laksmi tricked Nugie.
The ritual is not to cure your mother.
It is actually
a ritual to pass the dagger's ownership.
Nugie, will be the dagger's new host.
He shares the same birth date
with Sir Narto,
Pahing Saturday.
That's why
the dagger has been following him
ever since he stole it.
Mother!
Brother! Brother!
You, mortals…
do not interfere.
Ma'am.
Brother. Nugie.
Nugie!
Brother. Brother.
Brother!
Brother.
Wake up, brother! Brother!
Brother!
Brother. It's me, brother. Wake up.
Brother.
I seek forgiveness from Allah.
Wake up!
Brother?
Brother. Brother.
I seek forgiveness from Allah.
Brother.
IN THE NAME OF ALLAH,
THE ENTIRELY MERCIFUL,
THE ESPECIALLY MERCIFUL.
TO ALLAH BELONGS
WHATEVER IS IN THE HEAVENS
AND WHATEVER IS ON THE EARTH.
THERE IS NO POWER
AND NO STRENGTH EXCEPT WITH ALLAH.
Allah is the Greatest.
O MY SERVANTS WHO HAVE TRANSGRESSED
AGAINST THEMSELVES BY SINNING
DO NOT DESPAIR OF THE MERCY OF ALLAH
INDEED, ALLAH FORGIVES ALL
INDEED, IT IS HE WHO IS
THE FORGIVING THE MERCIFUL
SURAH AZ-ZUMAR - VERSE 53