Thank you
for riding with us.
Paul, open this door.
I know what you're
doing in there!
Paul!
Why are you doing this?
Paul, come out here
and talk to me.
You're shit!
So I don't know
anything about wine,
but the guy at the store
said this was very good.
You asked?
I did. I didn't
know what to get.
Cheers.
To us.
Ooh, wine store guy nailed it.
Yeah?
Is that good? I like it.
I love you.
You make me feel
really safe [echoes].
I would never do
anything to hurt you.
I know.
I think Danny's
warming up to you, too.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
But it'll be even better
now you guys are here.
I think so, too.
Paul?
Paul!
Hey Cook,
you got a minute?
All right, ladies and
gents, little announcement.
We have 50-50 raffle
tickets on sale
for Frank's daughter's
soccer team.
Little Kickers.
We love some Little Kickers
'cause they kick a little ass.
So your degenerate gambling can
actually go to a good cause.
All right?
- Thanks.
Oh, you're welcome.
All right now, so another
day in Paradise awaits us.
Before you hit the streets,
I'd like to introduce
our newest team member.
This is Detective Angela Dutton.
Get acquainted, say hello,
welcome her like family,
which means we insult
her to her face
and talk about her
mama behind her back.
Angela comes from Atlanta,
and she was accidentally
dropped off in the Bronx,
which I'm amazed
you're not murdered,
and she's gonna be with
us for the long haul.
And the best person to
bring her up to speed
is our very own
Detective Deo Russo.
Russo, meet your new partner.
All right, everybody,
be safe out there.
Wal... Walden! Lieutenant?
Lieutenant, can I...
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Just a
second. Keep up, man.
What happened to your face?
What, you can't shave?
Yeah, I
got a skin thing.
I was gonna put in for
a medical exemption.
A medical exemption 'cause
you allergic to a razor?
Man.
Russo, I don't wanna hear that.
Seriously, you
blindside me like this?
What is this,
karmic retribution?
Did I do something to
you or your loved ones
in another life?
Because last I checked,
me and your significant
other get along great.
We both find you to be
equally intolerable.
Listen, man, I was
fine with you goin' solo
when you worked on cold cases,
but now on homicide,
I want you with a partner.
Then put me back on cold case.
Deo, it's been five years.
I know how long it's been.
Probably down to the minute.
Look, I got a good
thing goin' here.
I get up alone.
I go to work alone.
I eat alone. I'm like
Macaulay Culkin, man.
I go home alone, I sleep alone.
I don't have to care
about another human being.
It is a sad, sad,
beautiful thing.
I don't want a partner.
Well, you got a partner.
Her name is Angela.
Go out there and
show her around.
- She's taking a selfie.
- Oh, come--
So she's taking a selfie.
Man, she needs someone like you,
and you need someone like her.
I need someone?
I need her like I need an enema.
What's she gonna do,
teach me about pop culture?
You're so full of
shit you don't even know
when you need an enema.
Come on, you don't socialize.
You need more human contact.
And if you won't do it in your
private life, hey, thank me.
Now you can do it at work.
Is this a precinct
or a dating app?
'Cause I can't tell
the difference.
Look, why don't you just
take the evidence box,
take it across the bridge,
and give it to the DA.
- Is this...
- Yeah, I mean, what?
This the guy? We got him?
It's moving forward. Well,
at least that's good news.
Yes, maybe you'll have
a little more good news,
if you, you know, take your
partner across the bridge,
a little scenic
something and, you know,
maybe a nice bagel at Luigi's.
You know, bond
with your partner.
Yay.
What?
Is this because I put the
embarrassing photo of you
up in the precinct and
got everyone to play
"Where's Walden?" for a month?
You're cute, and no.
It's just 'cause I hate you.
Get the fuck outta my office.
Tell Bob I said hi.
I ain't tellin' Bob shit!
See, these people don't
realize I know where they live.
Does anybody got some snacks?
It's my first day on the job
and I cannot wait to get in
the car with my new partner.
He seems, okay.
Experienced, maybe
a little bit grumpy,
but you know, I mean, I guess
what are you gonna do?
Guess it's you and me?
Yeah. Angela.
Deo. Let's go.
Okay.
Your chariot awaits.
And, where are we going?
We need to drive to Manhattan,
take this box to the DA.
Can you drive?
Of course.
Nice catch.
Thanks.
Off to a great start, partner.
Know the way?
No. No, I do not.
Get outta here
and turn left.
And don't kill me.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Least not today.
Ooh, I'm so excited!
All right, makin' a left.
Okay, this is really weird.
Are we just supposed
to drive in silence?
I mean, I thought this
is when we were supposed
to be getting to
know each other.
You know like, bonding,
like gettin' tight.
No, this is the
part where we drive
the evidence box to the DA.
And why am I driving?
Equity.
Why do you think?
To get used to the city.
Okay. Hey, first
breakfast on me, partner.
Oh, money bags
over there, huh?
Is that from all your
click clack followers?
Okay, that's not
what it's called.
Whatever.
I have 1,297 followers,
thank you very much.
Can you monetize that?
Let's just say
there's room for growth.
But I really just like doing
those challenges, you know?
Like the lip syncing
and the dancing,
you know the--
- Hey, what do you say
we maybe, like, table this
conversation, you know,
give it a rest until after I
get a cup of coffee in my hand.
What do ya think?
Okay. Shavasana.
Gesundheit.
No, no, no, no.
That means rest in yoga.
So you just...
Okay, so we're gonna stop
at Luigi's and get a coffee
and whatever else
you want to eat,
on you of course, moneybags.
Luigi's?
Best bagels in the city.
Well, I'm, uh...
I can't have gluten.
Well, have a tomato.
No, it's fine.
I'll get a kombucha.
What?
So they're this
really healthy drink
that has live bacteria
and probiotics in it.
You're paying
for bacteria?
Because you know your
intestinal tract
is full of bacteria but it's
like really healthy bacteria.
It helps with the--
- I don't wanna know anymore.
I'm sorry, I asked.
Okay.
So, they tell me you
usually drive solo.
Sorry if I'm
messing up your chi.
No, no, no, I'm serious.
I mean like, okay,
so I practice yoga,
but I only like to
practice by myself
because everybody else's energy
just really throws off my chi.
People really like honking
in this city, don't they?
Deo, huh?
Like the "Banana Boat" song?
Do not even do it.
What does it mean?
Godlike.
No way.
- Yeah.
- No way.
Yeah, I know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't, you don't. No.
Angela, it means angel.
Gods and angels
protecting and serving.
I mean, I cannot
make this shit up.
That is amazing!
Yeah, well, I'm
definitely no god.
Well, I am
definitely an angel.
Okay, so this is
Williamsburg Bridge.
What is that bridge over there?
The Queensboro Bridge.
Queens. So does
that go to, like, Queens?
What do you think?
I don't know.
Well, Queens is a borough.
It's the Queensboro Bridge.
The Queensboro Bridge
connects Queens to Manhattan.
Sassy.
Let's see, Queens.
Yeah.
We got, now is
Manhattan a borough?
- Yes.
- Okay. What about the Bronx?
It's a borough.
Uh, Harlem.
- Not a borough.
Got it. I think
that's all I got.
Staten Island.
Look at you.
- Oh my God.
- You're learning quickly.
Look at me. I'm like a native.
Good job, hayseed.
I'm like I'm from New York.
- Don't do that. Anywhere.
- Don't do what? New York?
Is that offensive?
You're gonna love me.
At some point, you will love me.
Maybe not today.
So are we gonna go
near Times Square?
No, it's a shit hole.
Oh! I thought they
like got rid of all the porn
and now it's all
nice and fabulous.
Yeah, it's nice
and tourist central,
which is a shit hole.
They were better off when
they had all the porn.
Oh.
Okay, the ADA is
out front waiting for us.
Okay, here we are.
It's up here on your right.
You're just gonna find
a place to pull over.
There he is.
Derek!
Thanks so much, man.
Thanks for meeting me out here.
Good to see you.
- Good to see you, too.
- Glad we got the guy.
- Glad we do, too.
With this we'll be
able to nail him.
You get him.
Let's go.
All right? Okay.
We're gonna step over, come on.
Here we go, boy.
Here we go.
Love you, buddy.
Be right back!
Hey, thank you.
Hey, Bill. How you doin'?
- Good, Willy. How you doing?
- I'm good, good. You?
I'm stayin' outta trouble.
Good, good. You do that, man.
I will. You, too.
Pickles are on sale.
Pickles. Are they kosher?
- They're always kosher, man.
- Oh, okay.
'Cause I don't
look at the label.
I hear ya.
Hey. Took ya long enough.
I had to find you something
with bacteria in it.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Oh, this is good.
Oh!
You do not know
what you're missing.
What?
Oh. Yeah, I got a gluten
allergy, I'm afraid.
I do not care.
Oh.
Mm, sweet baby Jesus.
"You know what, Angela,
you seem like a
really cool person."
I'd never say that.
That is so kind of
you to say. Thank you.
Well, you know what, I was
born in Marietta, Georgia.
I'm a Libra, so I get
along with everybody,
and I know what you're thinking.
That you're ruining my bagel.
Extroverts do not
make good detectives,
but I have you fooled, darlin',
because I am an outlier.
My dad was in the Air Force.
I wanted to follow
in his footsteps
because he's really my hero,
but I didn't wanna go to war.
So I joined the force,
and I got promoted about a year
and a half ago to detective.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You know, that almost
sounded sincere.
Married 10 years, no kids,
and I'm just gonna lay
everything out on the table.
- Please don't.
- Put all the cards out there.
Prefer you didn't.
He got his tubes tied
without telling me.
You're gonna do it anyway.
And we weren't great
going into COVID,
and then after everything
opened back up,
that included his
secretary's legs.
- Wow.
- So I divorced
his fucking cheating ass.
His loss, not mine,
because I am a catch.
I've got an ass like a
25-year-old, I'm great in bed,
and I am so over that
fucking high school drama.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
That why you moved to
a city 800 miles away
that apparently hates cops?
You know what,
that city is my past.
My family's gone.
My brother lives here now.
This city...
This city is my future.
Well...
Your future smells like piss.
Okay, Detective,
what about you?
What's with this lone
wolf mysterious thing
you got goin' on?
All right.
I don't like people.
So I shouldn't
take it personally?
Look around, bubblegum Barbie.
Community is dead.
Journalism is dead.
Narcissism's at
an all-time high.
Flip on the news, if that's
what you wanna call it.
They tell the flocks
what they wanna hear
the way they want
'em to hear it.
As long as it
confirms their bias,
they go along like
good little sheep.
Nobody can think for
themselves anymore.
The politicians and the media
are doing everything they can
to divide the people.
Hypocrisy and entitlement
are like fuckin' epidemics.
So I've learned to keep my
expectations for humanity low.
People are generally disappointing.
Maybe.
But there are some
really good ones as well.
Life is a team sport.
We are all in this together.
You're gonna have to learn
to trust somebody
eventually, Oscar.
Oscar?
The Grouch.
Isn't that your home,
like, right over there?
- That's cute.
- It's a nice little trashcan.
Yeah.
73.
Central to 12 Squad.
I swear, always
when I'm eating.
This guy.
12 Squad Central.
Request a report.
Possible stabbing
4th and Syracuse.
Bus is rolling.
- Uh-uh. I drive.
- Of course you do.
12 Squad Central.
Show us responding.
Copy that, 12 Squad.
And you leave all
your shit on the seat
for me?
- Oh, just get in the car.
You are so inconsiderate.
- Shut the fuck up.
This car
needs a tune-up.
Hey guys, we're on our way
to a stabbing right now,
and this one is
driving like a maniac.
Are you fuckin'
kidding me right now?
But I kinda like it.
Do not film me.
Why? Are you camera shy?
- We're working.
- I know.
You're doing your
little click clack videos.
It's not called that.
Come on, you gotta
be fuckin' kidding me.
Welcome to New York.
Yeah, seriously.
Although, it does remind me
of rush hour in Atlanta.
Atlanta?
- Yeah.
- You're gonna sit here
and try to compare
New York City to Atlanta.
I'm just saying the
traffic is shit there, too.
Everything's shit there.
What? What
you got against Atlanta?
Atlanta sucks.
Sir? Sir?
What's happening?
Are you okay?
He needs help. He needs help.
I don't know what's going on.
Sir, are you okay?
Can you breathe?
- He needs help.
- Are you okay?
I'm gonna...
All right, sir, I'm
gonna get you help.
Call 911.
Yes, hi, I'm at the corner
of 94th and Denmore.
We need an ambulance right away.
An old man is passed
out on the ground.
No one
listens to me!
Look, oh
man. All right, look.
We don't wanna have to--
- Stay the fuck back!
- Don't make us do that.
Put the weapon down!
Get on the ground now!
Get on the ground.
Relax.
- Get on the ground.
- On the ground!
You piece of shit!
We don't wanna hurt you, bro.
Hang back.
10-84.
Back up,
back up, back up.
Let's go. Let's go.
- On the ground!
All right, we got it.
Back up, back up.
Man, we don't wanna
shoot you, all right?
Killed a fuckin'
dumbass today!
Don't make me
fuckin' have to shoot you.
I'm fucking done. Stand back!
You fuckin' got no idea
what I can do.
Shut up!
- Hey.
- Hey. What's up?
Looks like you
got your hands full.
Mm.
Can I ask you a favor?
If you want to,
go ahead and do it.
12 Squad behind you.
What's up?
- Jesus Christ.
I don't even fuckin' know.
This guy, this motherfucker,
he's just been doin',
yeah that shit.
He's been doing that shit.
- Is that a meat cleaver?
You mind if I try?
You know what, be my guest.
Ah!
I'm Detective Deo Russo.
I'm gonna holster my
firearm here, okay?
Just gonna have a talk.
What's your name?
Go fuck your mother
and your sister!
- Hope that's not a family name.
- Fuck off!
Look, listen, man.
Looks like you're just havin'
one of those days, pal.
Hey, just me and you.
You don't really wanna
hurt yourself, do you?
You don't fuckin' know shit!
You don't know what I want.
Know me!
I know that a tough
guy like you,
if you wanna do some damage,
you could do some
real damage, yeah?
Yeah, I might! Okay, okay.
Yeah? Now listen,
listen to me.
We don't wanna hurt you
and we don't wanna see you
hurt yourself anymore
than you already have.
No woman, no cry.
No guns, no problems.
No one listens to me!
Now, if you just
lower that meat cleaver,
you and I can have
a little chitchat.
Fuck you, you fucker.
Don't fuckin' think
I won't do it.
All I wanna do is
get you to the hospital
and get you cleaned up.
That looks like that hurts.
Okay, your arm is
not a piece of pizza.
We can do this all day.
But I think you
got things to do.
I got shit to do.
You had a bad enough day, man.
Yeah, well,
you don't know shit.
Ya know, I know I've
been there. How about that?
Fuck off!
Okay.
Don't tell me what to do.
Where'd you get the taser?
Really feeling yourself, huh?
Yeah, I am.
What's your problem?
You're my problem.
I said hang back.
For no good reason.
Plenty of good reasons.
Bullshit. Name one.
How about the only
one that matters?
I'm your partner
and I asked you to.
But you showed me
when it comes to you,
the only thing I can
trust is your damn ego.
Oh, bullshit.
You didn't ask me, you told me,
like you were my fuckin'
superior or something.
Here we go.
You think I don't
know what this is about.
You have been
butthurt ever since
you got placed with a woman.
You don't know
shit about fuck.
Oh, tell me I'm wrong.
Tell me this isn't some
stereotypical bullshit.
But for the record,
I don't have a problem
with stereotypes.
Most of them are true and
a lot of them are funny,
and if you ask me,
this world could use
some of that truth
and humor that we lost
somewhere along the way.
Nobody fuckin' asked you!
Generally speaking,
I think men do some
shit better than women,
and generally speaking,
I think women do some
shit better than men,
neither of which has anything
to do with right the fuck now.
So whatever wokey pokey,
misogynistic, virtue signaling,
victimy horseshit
narrative you got rollin'
through that hayseed brain
of yours, Detective Dutton,
it is so fuckin' wrong,
it's not even funny.
Why don't you two get a room!
Shut the fuck up!
Get up.
Clear the way.
Be careful.
Fucking move.
Let's go.
Hey Sarge. Thank you.
Thanks, Detective. Good job.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
Stay back.
Hey. Are we good?
Clearly you're
good at what you do
or you wouldn't be here.
Hell, you're probably
better than me.
I'm just an average
detective at best
just trying to make it
through the damn day.
So I highly doubt
Walden would put you
with the likes of me
if you were anything
but fan-fuckin'-tastic
at what you do.
Then what's up?
It's your first shift.
So sue me if I
didn't want anything
to happen to you on day one.
I'm not your responsibility.
The hell you aren't.
Around 8 a.m. this morning,
you became mine, I became yours
whether we like it or
not, that's the code.
Negative.
Meet me at the hospital.
Keys are in the car.
I'll ride with the
electric slide.
Hey.
Would you have asked me to
hang back if I wasn't a woman?
Probably not.
Let me ask you.
Is that so bad?
Negative.
Hey, I'm gonna ride.
You got it.
Just follow the
ambulance. Yeah.
Just breathe, buddy.
We're five minutes out.
Hey, take it easy, pal.
Avery here's gonna take
good care of ya, okay?
I'm just trying.
I like it.
Can I get anything outta
him? What do you think?
He's got all kind
of shit in his system.
It'll be a while before you
get any useful information.
No harm in trying.
You ready to tell me
your real name, pal?
What do you think?
Oh, Bullet.
Bullet?
Don't you think Blade would
be more appropriate for you?
What did you take?
Everything.
Okay, Willy, take a nice
deep breath for me, please.
Good. Okay, one more.
Very good. We're almost there.
Don't worry, buddy.
What do you think,
that stabbing yourself,
a little bit of an
error in judgment?
All right, I want you
to think about this.
When we get to the hospital,
you can talk to me,
you can talk to the DA.
I promise you I'm
a lot nicer, okay?
Help.
Just breathe,
guy. I am helping you.
She's helping you, she's
giving you the good stuff.
Jesus.
Easy, easy, easy.
And we're off.
I got a perp, self-inflicted
wound, stabbing.
His name's Bullet. I don't
know his real name yet.
Oh yes, we have
him in the system.
My first New York tase.
Comin' through!
My dog.
Please, it's tied up
outside the store.
Hey.
Denmore Street.
Listen pops, I'd love to help.
I'm right in the
middle of a tour.
Please. He's all I have.
You have to help me.
Please get him.
He's all alone.
- What's your name?
- It's Willy.
We'll
take care of him.
Please.
Did you see his dog?
Nope. No dog.
Oh my God,
will you stop whining?
Listen, what's
your dog's name?
Tango. Tango.
Thank you.
- Tango.
Angela, you got the keys?
Why? What are you doing?
I'm gonna go get his dog.
Okay, Dr. Doolittle,
just in case you forgot,
we still have an arrest
we have to complete.
Thought you were an angel.
Where's your sense of heroism?
Okay, I love dogs just
as much as the next person,
but dog heroism is
the ASPCA's job.
And what about you Mr.
I don't like people?
Dogs aren't people.
They're loyal.
Besides, I thought we
were all in this together,
or was that just part of your
after school special speech?
Look, post a video
of a dog rescue,
I bet you double your followers
on your little click clack.
Again, it's not called that.
Again, I do not care.
Please process it for me.
Here's the keys to the cuffs.
If he shits or pisses
in the back of the car,
you're cleaning it up.
Funny, I told Walden
the same thing about you.
You're
such a comedian.
Gods and angels protecting
and serving, right?
You are definitely not a god.
And you're
definitely no angel.
Beg to differ.
- Hey, Logan.
- Hey.
- Let's have a chat.
- Yeah.
Come on in.
It's a nice place you got.
Yeah. Fuckin'
Valenti send you?
Huh?
Let's have a seat.
Yep.
Yeah, get
comfortable all right.
Thanks.
Jack.
Just gonna sit
down and relax a bit.
Dad, what the fuck?
Sit your fuckin'
ass down. Go ahead.
Sit down.
- That's my son, man.
- Sit.
Sit down.
Leave my son alone.
Go ahead, sit down.
He's good, he's good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, he's good.
Right? Come on.
Daddy's a fuckin' troublemaker.
Pal, you're okay.
He's good.
So look, I don't
wanna waste time.
I don't wanna look around
this shit hole. Where is it?
Where's what?
Hands behind your back.
Where is it?
It's not here [chuckles],
I'm--
Where is it, then?
How about you let me
talk to your boss, Jack.
If the boss wanted to talk
to you, he'd be here right now.
- I got you.
- It's not here.
- Where is it?
- It's gone.
Throw my fuckin' kid around
my fuckin' house?
All right, Logan. Logan.
Logan, here's what
we're gonna do.
I'm just gonna ask you questions
and you're gonna either nod
or shake your head, okay?
So, okay?
You say it's not here.
Did you move it somewhere?
No.
Logan, did you sell
it to someone else?
Because they paid more?
Yeah.
Logan.
All right,
buddy boy, come on up.
Relax.
I'm just, I don't understand
what you thought
was gonna happen.
What did you think
was gonna happen?
Did you think the boss would,
what did you think he would say?
What do you think the boss--
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay...
We're having a conversation.
Hey, make it
easy for us, okay?
You did what you did,
so now you gotta accept
the consequences.
Yeah?
Okay, so let's
talk rationally.
What do you think he would
say to you, congratulations?
"Logan, you're a champ.
You're a good capitalist.
You know how to work the market.
Well done, you made a profit."
I mean fuck.
So strange. Take this shit off.
Shh. It's okay.
I needed money.
I owed people money.
- That's it?
- Jack, you know me.
You've known me a long time.
I'm not gonna fuck you over.
You guys are at the top
of my priority list, man.
We go back. I'm good for it.
I'm gonna get the
money back to you.
Just let me and my kid go,
and I'll go out and
I'll get the money.
So, okay.
I got no product,
I got no money,
but I have your fuckin' word?
My word, bro.
I'm fuckin' good for this.
Just tape him up.
Man, I swear to you.
It's not like before, I'm
not gonna fuckin' do it.
Jesus.
Shh. Shh.
My hands are tied,
like yours.
That was
good. That's funny.
I know. It's true.
His hands are tied.
My hands are tied, too.
Fuck, you stupid asshole.
Somebody has to pay 'cause
that's the way this shit works.
I didn't fuckin' invent
the fuckin' order,
but that's the way it works,
and that's the bad news.
But here's the good news.
I'm gonna give you options
'cause we've known each
other a while, you're right.
Okay, Option A, you die.
Your son, he lives, fuckin'
jerk off every day he wants to,
and skateboard, do
whatever the fuck he does
the rest of his life.
To be a fuck-up like
you or not, maybe not.
Most likely.
Option B, your son
pays your debt for you.
- No. No!
- No, but listen.
No, but listen.
- No. Just fuckin' kill me.
- I get it.
Shh, shh, shh, but listen.
Think of it this way. Listen.
You go to therapy, you cry,
and you go back to
your own fuckin' life.
Do whatever the fuck it
is you wanna do. Clean.
- No. No.
- No, but listen.
We put him in there so you
didn't have to look at him,
or he doesn't have
to look at you
while you're makin'
this choice, all right?
I did that for you. Okay?
So just relax, and I need you
to pull your fuckin' pants up,
your big boy pants,
put your thinking cap on,
and I need you to
think hard, okay?
Listen, I promise if
you choose the kid,
I'm gonna make it as quick
as possible. I promise.
Okay? So go ahead.
You're gonna think about it,
and I'm gonna give you...
- Please, man.
- ...30 seconds.
Shh.
Just you say the word
and it'll be quick, okay?
Logan, Logan.
Logan.
- What?
- Look at me.
Logan.
You want your kid growing up
in this fuckin' world anyway?
15.
You want me
to kill my fuckin' kid.
- Shh.
- Seven,
Six,
Don't make me to
kill my fuckin'...
- Five.
- Shh.
- Four.
Three.
Okay.
What the--
Give up your own fuckin' kid.
Let's fuckin' go.
You must be Tango.
You're not gonna bite
my hand off, are ya?
All right, so I want
that on whole wheat,
but I want only one
of the slices toasted.
Oh, look at you.
You're a handsome
fella. You're all wet.
Oh, let me get you some
water. I'll be right back.
I'll have the,
the Muenster.
The mayonnaise on the
side that's not toasted
'cause it like sinks in.
Hey, man, I got
my dog outside.
You don't happen to have a bowl
of water or a cup of water?
- No.
- Anything back there?
Anything else?
You could put
bacon on it, too.
- Bacon on it too?
- Yep. Lettuce, tomato's good.
Lettuce, tomato's always good.
- Thank you. I appreciate it.
- There you go.
Let me get on a spinach wrap,
chipotle mayo on there
with the smoked Gouda.
Want some water? You thirsty?
Central requesting units,
in the vicinity of Denmore
and Cornerstone.
Central 12 Squad,
you're not gonna believe this,
but I'm in the area.
I could be there in three.
Well, it's your lucky day.
Report of shots fired
at 420 East Cornerstone.
Unit 312.
All right, dispatch,
show me on scene.
Central, send additional units.
Copy that, 12 Squad.
Hey, what do you think, pal?
Wanna go on a little
adventure? Come on.
Wanna hop in there? Good boy.
Tango, I'll be right back.
That's a good boy.
Hey!
Got here as fast as I could.
What's with this weather?
It'll pass.
You process our collar?
Yeah, all taken care of.
Killed a father and a son.
Looks like a double
homicide, but I don't know.
Well, I checked on his dad.
He's gonna be in a couple
weeks, but he'll be okay.
Oh.
Huh, buddy? Huh?
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Meet me for lunch
at our place in 10.
Why?
Because I wanna know how
the honeymooners are doing
and because I said so.
Did he just hang up?
I should poison him.
Boss is makin' us
eat with her. Let's go.
Okay.
Open this door.
Paul? Paul?
Open this door! Paul?
Feels like we're a
family now, ya know?
Yeah. We've never had that.
No?
No, I mean, his dad left
when he was so little, ya know?
He's never really known a dad.
No pressure.
Okay. Okay.
Paul, I know what you're
fucking doing in there!
Paul, open this fucking door.
Danny, get your backpack,
baby. We gotta go to school.
I got us a new apartment.
We're gonna be leaving
at the end of the month.
Why?
Are you fucking kidding? Why?
You know why.
You're using again?
Good, I'm glad you're
not even gonna deny it.
Maybe now you can get some help.
I'm fine, Sandy. I'm fine.
Don't lie to me.
Don't do that.
I love you.
Don't do this, Sandy.
I'm not doing
anything. You did this.
I told you from
the very beginning
that I would never ever
put myself or my kid
in this position ever again,
and you promised me
that I would never
have to worry about that.
- I've been--
- I don't even know
why we're talking about it.
It's not a discussion.
I put a deposit down.
We're leaving.
No.
I'm sorry, what?
You're not leaving.
I decided, no.
I am leaving.
I've put a deposit
down on an apartment.
- We are leaving.
- Nobody
is fucking leaving me!
Yo, yo
I don't care if you
from the streets
That shit don't matter
I make 'em see scatter
all over the wall
Like fuckin' brain matter
When it comes to wine
Me quick to knock
you out the box
Fuck around my knuckles--
Yeah, Walden
likes this place.
I have no idea
why, but this is...
She loves to shit herself.
Nice.
- What...
- Heard that.
You can't take
him anywhere, huh?
- I try not to.
- Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Hey,
how is everyone?
Good. How are you?
Would
you like some menus?
Go right ahead.
One
cheeseburger, one philly.
Okay.
- I'll have the usual.
- Usual. And?
I'll just do a burger
and a salad, please.
Gluten-free, please.
Absolutely. Be right back.
Thanks. Don't gimme that look.
You gotta make sure
your water's gluten-free.
- You know what?
- You should have told her.
You and your sass
today? I cannot.
Oh boy.
Hoping that you had
some bonding time.
Oh yeah.
We're just, you
know, peas in a pod.
Just really enjoying today.
Know what's funny?
Now there's two
of us against him
and he's just gonna, ooh-wee.
I cannot.
- Pray for him.
You know, I do every day.
Oh, and today being the
first day, startin' off strong.
I am. Well, thank you so
much for treatin', Boss.
I really appreciate it.
- Oh, not a problem.
It's a business expense.
- Ah, there it is.
- Oh, okay. Fair enough.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Be right back.
So, I spoke with the DA.
He's confident that the
prosecution is going our way.
One second.
Can I order another one
of these to go, please?
- Absolutely.
- Thank you. On her.
Yeah. Thanks.
So you were saying?
I spoke with the DA.
I just wanna make sure you're,
you know, sure on the motive.
Twice convicted on possession
with intent to distribute?
Yeah, I feel strong.
Hm-mmm.
It was a fentanyl issue.
I don't know what
causes more deaths,
the war on drugs or--
- Or the drug itself?
I'm sorry, today wasn't
exactly what I expected
to be for you to bond.
Oh no, we're gettin'
married next Tuesday.
- Uh.
- Oh.
Oh, I already
picked out my dress.
Oh, well you got
a flower girl.
- I'm so excited.
Here is
your second burger.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
Can I have another box, too?
- Absolutely.
- Thank you.
- I guess he's hungry. Oh!
- Thanks for lunch.
In the 11 years that
we've done this together,
it's only happened what, twice?
Thank you.
- Come on, man.
There's been plenty of dinners
that I have bought
for everybody.
Lunch, dinner, drinks. Okay.
I mean, would
you like mine, too?
- Oh, thank you.
- Oh!
I'll just take that.
Thank you so much.
- Well, I am so glad--
- You're so generous.
Thank you.
Well, I'm glad I could
help at my expense,
but at least you guys
are getting along.
You owe me a chicken, man.
I guess we're leaving now.
Yeah.
And you know what?
Thank you for lunch.
Well, I think he likes you.
I am terrified to see
the people he doesn't like.
Well, just give him some
time and he'll grow on you.
Yeah, like
a fuckin' cold sore.
I'll see ya later.
That asshole has
a dog?
Give him some
slack for a second,
I wanna see something.
- Okay.
- Stay.
Will you roll?
Can you roll?
Oh my God.
He's just
like [grunts].
You got cheese on you.
Stay. Relax.
I think he just nodded.
Sit. Sit.
He's a good boy.
Relax. Yeah.
You're so smart. You're
smarter than my partner.
You know what,
I resent that remark.
- Uh-huh.
- But you did
just call me partner.
- It was a slip of the tongue.
- Oh, was it?
- Freudian slip.
- I see.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes you are,
you're a pretty boy.
I think you're in love.
He's so handsome.
Come on, buddy.
I know, buddy.
You droppin' off?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So, you're gonna have
to fill out a AHS form,
a surrender consent,
proof of vaccinations,
dietary restrictions, and...
His owner's in the hospital.
He'll be out in
like three weeks.
Dog's name is Tango,
but that's all I got for ya.
Well, he just left.
- Gimme a second.
- Mm-hmm.
Why'd they even come in here?
It's okay, buddy.
Cruella here promises
not to do it again.
Isn't that right, de Vil?
'Mkay. You know what?
If I can give the
dog a second chance,
you can give humans
a second chance.
I don't think that's
a fair exchange.
Oh my God, you
are so stubborn.
Just take the deal.
If I take the deal,
will you shut up?
No. No, I will not shut up.
But I will change the subject,
or I could just keep asking
you personal questions
and annoy the shit outta you.
Fine!
Repeat after me.
I will give humans
a second chance.
So dumb. So dumb.
- Just say it.
- So dumb.
I will give humans
a second chance.
I will give humans a
second chance. There.
See? So godlike of you.
See, now that's why
I don't do this shit.
So, how does it feel?
You're gonna give humans
a second chance,
- Feels idiotic.
and you're gonna stop
being such a pussy about it.
Excuse me, I am not
being a pussy about it.
You're kinda being a pussy.
You got a mouth on you.
That's what she said.
That's good.
- Ah, thank you.
- Actually good.
- I got you to smile.
- I didn't see that comin'.
- Ah, well.
- That's what she said.
It's true.
Oh man.
Till it hit her
right in the eye.
Oh!
- She saw that.
- What do they call that?
She saw that.
What do they... well,
she may not have,
depending on the angle.
What do they call that?
It's not a cream pie, is it?
Nope. I don't know.
- I don't know.
- Is it?
No.
- No, it's not.
I think a cream
pie is when they,
you fuck 'em in the rear, then
you pull out, and then you...
No?
Oh, I thought a cream pie
was when you come inside
and then suck it out.
Then why would you
think it was the--
I don't know. It's what
came out of my mouth.
See, look at you.
You're melting a little.
See, there you go.
- Good.
Ah, you don't hate me.
You love me.
- Don't push it.
You know how I
feel about that.
I feel huge.
You still love me like this?
Yeah.
Well, now, maybe [indistinct].
Shut up.
But I love you, baby.
I love you, too.
Hey, real quick, I'm gonna
make this run, all right?
I'm not going back to
jail, I promise you that.
I promise you that, honey.
How
are you gonna promise me that?
I'm not going back
to jail, just...
Are you the law?
Fuck
the law, all right?
What good did the
law ever do for us?
- Nothin'.
- Okay then.
Okay then.
If the law ain't never did
shit for us, fuck the law.
Michael Crawford, 340.
Michael Crawford,
please call 340.
Excuse me.
Team to ICU, please. 17.
Michael Crawford, 340.
Willy. Remember me?
Hey.
What about this guy?
Hey, baby. Hey.
Oh.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
- Here's my number.
I'll watch him
until you recover.
Come on.
So you have to recover.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Okay, Mr. Willy,
it's time for your...
What is this?
Animals are prohibited
in the hospital.
It's all good.
We were just leavin'.
- Okay.
- Take care.
- Go on boy. Go on, Tango.
- Come on, buddy.
Yeah.
Again, thank you so much.
Oh my...
I'm not going back to jail.
Run a New
York plate. JEC8522.
It's all good, it's
all good, it's all good.
It's all good. I got this
handled, all right? Okay?
- Okay.
Okay, Central, show
12 Squad at a car stop
on 12th and West 29th.
They're coming.
There you go. Chill, chill.
Just relax.
How you doin'?
All right, Officer,
how you doin'?
License and
registration, please.
Know why I pulled you over?
No. Why?
Stop sign back there.
You didn't see that?
Oh shit. For real?
Nah, I didn't see it.
Congratulations.
How far along are you?
Very.
I saw you two earlier.
For real?
It's a little dangerous
to be driving like this.
Just being
curious, what was I wearing?
A wise guy, huh?
Nah.
What do you think?
Your license in there, pal?
Man, I put all
kinds of shit in here.
Gun!
Hey,
stop it!
No, let him go!
Lemme see your hands!
Let me see your hands.
Fuck off me, man.
Get outta the car,
slowly. Let's go.
Turn around, put your
hands on the hood.
Let's go, asshole.
Two pounds of sweet
tarts in the trunk.
Oh [chuckles], the DA's
gonna love this one.
Look Frank, I got
a dog in the car.
Do you mind if...
Go ahead, Deo.
We'll process it.
Thanks for picking up
my bag of shit, Frank.
- No problem.
- Appreciate you.
Hey! You drive.
Wait.
Thanks.
Aww.
Oh, thank you.
I just got kissed.
You know, I could probably
drop you guys first
so everybody doesn't know
that we're the new
parents of a dog.
He's been in here for a while.
Maybe we should take him to the
park first, give him a walk.
Sounds good.
What a day.
What a fuckin' day.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay, come on.
Come here.
Okay, go ahead.
You think we should get him?
I think you should get him.
- Right.
- Yeah.
I failed, Sissy.
Paul?
I'm so sorry.
Slow down. What's goin' on?
She said she was gonna leave.
This is your idea, isn't it?
Get away from me.
You're not my dad!
We're leaving today.
Oh, you're leaving today.
You think you're leaving, huh?
I give you clothes to wear,
I give you food to eat.
And this is how you repay
me, you little shit?
Huh? You're leavin' me?
Nobody's, nobody's,
nobody's leavin'.
You understand?
Leavin' me?
No. Nobody leaves me!
You're shit.
Nobody, nobody's leaving me!
Paul, what the
fuck is happening?
Paul?
Fuck.
It's my brother.
Okay, get in. I'll drive.
Where we goin'?
I'm trying
to find it now.
I know it's in Queens.
What the fuck did you do?
What the fuck did you
fucking do?
Can you tell
me what's goin' on?
It's my brother.
Apparently his girlfriend
wants to leave him.
Look, he's not well.
He began using to
cope with the PTSD
when he got back from
two tours in Iraq.
He was clean for a long
time, so I thought.
I'm pretty sure
he is using again,
and when he does,
it's really bad.
Paul?
I love you.
All right,
we're almost there.
Turn right. Turn right here.
And it says about 800
feet on the right side.
Yeah, yeah, this
complex. Unit 404.
Door's open.
You let me go in first.
Paulie?
Oh.
Boss, we ain't
do nothin' wrong.
You didn't
do nothin' right.
What did you expect us to do?
Jackie, Jackie, Jackie.
What are the rules, Jackie?
No women, and above
all, no fuckin' kids.
I sent you there to intimidate
and persuade Logan to
givin' up the goods.
I didn't tell you
to fuckin' kill him.
How am I supposed to get
paid back if he's dead?
He sold the goods.
He sold 'em. He made
a fuckin' profit.
The fuck was I supposed
to do, let him rip us off?
What you were supposed to
do is maybe break his fingers.
How about chop off a thumb?
But you gotta go to the
extreme? Kill his fuckin' kid?
The shit was gone.
What the fuck were we gonna do?
The biggest problem we
have is you two douchebags
got caught on the
security cameras.
So now the security
company has your footage,
which means the
cops have it also.
And my bet is that you
are both not willing
to do 25 to life for
killin' that kid.
Which means to me
that you're gonna sing
like the little canaries
that youse both are.
No, no, Boss, we
would never do that.
That's right, you will never.
Clean up this
fuckin' mess, all right?
The sight of blood,
kinda makes me feel
a little hungry.
Do a nice job,
maybe go out and have a
couple of steaks, huh?
Did he just say
what I think he said?
He said hurry up and
clean up this mess.
When he see the
blood, he get hungry.
He gonna take us for steak.
Fuck you, Paul.
Is there someone
I should call?
Why do men always feel like
they have to fix everything?
It's our nature.
Your parents still alive?
Mm, look at that.
We're both orphans.
How'd they die?
Okay, you know what you could
do? You could talk to me.
You could talk to
me about anything
other than what the fuck
I'm feeling right now.
How about that?
You know what?
We're gonna play a game.
I'm not much of a games guy.
I wasn't asking.
I'm gonna ask you questions
and you're gonna
answer them honestly.
And if you don't, you
have to take a shot, okay?
My dad died when I was 19.
How?
Stabbed. Prison, all right?
He was a criminal.
Hmm, so you went
the other way. Nice.
What about your mother?
Good woman.
Passed three years ago.
- How?
- Life.
Hmm.
It eventually kills you.
My dad died in
combat, Afghanistan.
My mother drank herself
to death after that.
And Paul, well, he just
went a little crazy.
And you know when
everything around you
just starts to fall apart,
it feels like, the
only thing you can do
is just grab the
wheel and hold on.
Why'd you get divorced?
You should crash here tonight.
Just answer the question.
I was a jerk.
Why?
I caught her
with someone else.
Like red-handed?
What did that look like?
Ooh. So why'd she cheat?
I was inadequate.
Bullshit. Why'd she cheat?
- We grew apart.
- Why?
Because I wasn't around.
Why?
Threw myself into
my work, or escaped,
whatever you wanna call it.
I was never present, and when
I was, I was mostly drunk.
There.
Why?
We had a daughter.
Ava.
Ava Marie. She was only
supposed to live one year.
She made it 18 months.
Congenital heart disease.
I guess after that,
it just got hard to find
peace amidst the chaos.
Sorry.
Me too.
What a day.
What a fuckin' day.
You should take the bedroom.
I'll take the couch.
You don't have to do that.
Yes I do.
Thanks, partner.
I'll get you some towels
and, ya know, whatever.
Who's that? Who's that?
Who's that?
- Hey, Tango!
Tango, my good boy. Come here.
Hey.
I cannot thank you enough.
No, no, get that outta here.
Come on, no. Absolutely not.
But I'll give you this back.
This 75-pound ball of joy.
Okay. Thank you.
I just, ah, I just
have one request.
Let me walk him
from time to time?
He's been, ah, he's been good
for me the last few weeks.
Anytime you want.
You know, when I was laying
there and nearly dying,
the only thing I thought about
was what would happen to Tango.
So, I had to survive.
I couldn't leave
without knowing.
When you came back with
him, I knew he'd be okay.
Everybody needs to
live for somebody
or something outside
of themselves.
Thank you.
That's my ride.
All right, this isn't goodbye.
This is just a see
ya later, yeah?
Appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, say goodbye, Tango.
Say goodbye. Let's
go this way, baby.
Come on. Come on.
Why are you filmin' me?
Come on, no one
wants to see this.
Hey, you're the
one that told me dogs
bring followers, and cops.
Even cops with 40-year-old
asses.
Remember those contract
killers from a few weeks back
that killed the father and son?
Yeah.
We found 'em, chopped
into tiny little bits
in a garbage dump.
All right.
So that's where we're headed.
Wait.
Coffee and a bagel first.
You got it, partner.
Thanks for stopping.
Today's her birthday.