Sweet girl, you're not gonna let us down.
You were never here for us before.
I'm so glad
you could start now.
And you can all see...
The reason is right in front of us.
Your I-Ching horoscope.
Your wedding is February 14th?
You should have been married in April.
Your ovaries are very healthy.
Very powerful flow.
You'll be pregnant on your first try.
Stable.
Obedient.
A lap dog of a man!
I'm what?
I have a bat mitzvah I must attend.
Please hold up.
You're right.
Success has to be recognised.
I-Ching horoscope.
You said your business was successful?
Your palm.
Your love line and career line
are tangled.
Finding your soul mate
will help your business.
And this person will be
one of the next five dates you go on.
Shame on you both.
You've gone too far.
Wishing you prosperity!
You know...
Life is like a dance.
Find your balance.
Follow the rhythm.
Dance however you want.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
Not him, huh?
No.
But they're going to be
very happy together.
So, who did you choose?
My child, I didn't say whose wedding.
I believe you have one date left.
Your sister has amazing taste
in hors d'oeuvres.
I can't say.
I wish you guys
one hundred years of happiness.