Is this the place?
Yes.
You go.
I think there are many of them here.
Has any of them appeared?
Yeah.
But they're gone.
Why do you think they left?
My grandpa said,
ghosts are also afraid of humans.
No wonder we never find any back home.
It's not that we can't find them,
it's because you can't see them yet.
That's why I'm asking you to teach me.
Hey, come here.
There.
I can feel a strong aura
coming out of there.
-See anything?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Din.
Stay close to me.
And be careful.
-Where.
-I don't see anything.
It's behind the door.
That's not how you do it!
Grandpa said that human eyes
are sharp when they see ghosts.
If you look at them like that,
they'll run.
Then tell me how to do it.
You must be seeing something!
Hurry up and teach me!
Din, be careful! Din.
Hurry!
Is it that scary?
It's okay.
Please. Come on.
Okay, but don't blame me
if things go south.
All right.
Keep your eyes straight ahead.
Don't move, stay focused.
Do you see something moving to your left?
I see it, over there.
Now, look to your left, slowly.
I don't see anything.
Are you lying to me?
I think they know
that we're trying to see them.
That's why they keep disappearing.
Let's… Let's just go home.
I can't figure out how to see them.
Din! We should get out of here!
Why?
Din! Dinda!
Dinda, run!
Run!
Don't look back!
Rayhan!
Another nightmare?
No, I'm just tired.
Even after getting enough rest, you still
talk in your sleep the last week.
Don't think about it.
Just go back to sleep.
-Babe.
-Yeah?
Have you called Mom back yet?
-I have.
-And?
At first, she told me
Hera is having another baby.
Really? Fifth kid?
It's hard to find a clinic that offers
birth control in Australia she said.
Unbelievable.
After that, Mom asked…
"When are you going to have a baby?
When are you going to get pregnant?"
Tell her
that we are trying until the last drop.
-We empty it all out.
-What on earth are you saying?
What is that even?
Han, my back, please.
-Bye, Sher.
-Wait.
-You forgot something.
-What?
-Good luck for today.
-Rayhan.
It's too early to make us envious.
-Somebody is going to be jealous.
-Who is it?
You know, the one with the white dress.
Who is it?
The pretty girl in a white dress?
Yes, there is someone.
She's very pretty, but…
her feet doesn't touch the ground.
You're unbelievable.
-Get to work.
-Be careful on your way.
-Bye.
Kiss bye!
Drive safely!
You always do that.
-Right on time. Here's your coffee.
-Thank you.
What's wrong? Sher!
Make sure to check every single detail.
All details and data are prepared.
It's right here.
-So, all good?
-Yes.
-Good.
-Sorry, I've to take this.
Hello, what's up, honey?
Trying until the last drop finally works.
Finally.
Honey, we'll finally be a family.
See? Keep your eyes on the road.
Don't you worry.
-What is it?
-I thought someone was crossing.
No, I didn't see anyone.
Is that so?
Han, I'm making some juice.
Do you want some?
Han.
Huh?
Do you want some?
Of what?
I'm making some juice.
Would you like some, too?
No for me, thanks.
Han.
Stay with me.
Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
You shouldn't make your own juice. Let me.
-Look at you.
-Let's go.
-You're being too much.
-Not at all.
Can you imagine?
We're about to have a third family member.
-What are you looking at?
-Nothing.
Another dream?
No.
Just thirsty. Do you want some water?
I'll be back.
What are you doing?
This thing.
The bed lamp went out,
then suddenly the room lights too.
Isn't it weird?
See?
Do we still have any light bulbs left?
Wait. I'm coming with you.
Sure.
Sher, can you turn the lights off?
Isn't it off already?
Hey. Here.
-Hang on.
-Does it hurt?
Let me help you.
Are you okay? Where does it hurt?
-Here?
-My back.
Ouch.
What's wrong with the lights?
Why are we stopping?
Didn't I tell you?
I have a meeting. I'm quite in a hurry.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-Sorry, I forgot.
-Are you being honest?
-Of course.
All right.
Babe. You forgot something.
What?
Go get it.
Take care, you.
Bye!
Aunty Siti?
I'm glad you still remember me.
I've been looking for someone
to connect me with her.
Her?
Your mother.
I hope she can forgive all my debts.
Okay. I'll let her know.
You don't have to worry.
I'm sure she's forgiven you.
Wait.
Have you ever been here before?
This is my first time.
Hang on a second!
Yes?
Package delivery.
Did you just knock?
What do you mean?
Excuse me.
Here's your package.
I'll take a picture.
Excuse me.
Did you buy this?
You're so sweet.
Gosh.
Is this why you came home early?
To buy this?
Don't worry about it.
I just can't wait
to take them strolling around.
Now I'll make some dinner.
What do you want for dinner, husband?
I'd love just anything.
But let me take a quick bath.
Okay.
I'll put you over here.
Han?
It's not funny!
Han!
What's wrong, Honey?
-Han!
-What is it?
Han! The stroller is moving by itself!
The stroller is over there.
-It can't be…
-Hang on. I'll be right there.
Han…
What's wrong?
The stroller was moving on its own
all the way there.
And something grabbed my leg.
-From the stroller?
-Yes! Go take a look!
There's nothing there.
Look, I'll bring it upstairs, okay?
Don't worry.
I'll go with you.
-Goodness.
-Something grabbed my leg, Han.
-Are you sure?
-Very sure!
It's right there, I think.
I'm sure there is something in your house.
What? You mean ghosts?
"Spirits."
You think so?
Actually,
I know someone who can help.
My uncle. My mother's relative.
Is he a shaman?
No.
I guess…
he has some kind of ability.
Like a psychic.
He can communicate with the unseen.
Honey.
I've thought about it.
I don't think we need any psychic.
Why not?
It's a waste of money?
So, just ignore it?
Not exactly.
If you believe they exist,
just befriend them.
Befriend them?
You do it!
But you can't make me.
As far as I know,
the more we give them attention,
the more they will bother us.
So let's just ignore it.
It's just flickering lights anyway.
"Just"?
What about the stroller?
You fell off the stairs?
And you said to ignore it?
Han!
I thought you were still downstairs.
Han, my back, please.
Okay, wait a sec.
Hello.
Honey, sorry…
Mom called.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
It's hot!
So?
Do you need my uncle's help?
Yes.
I'm serious.
Things have gone too far.
What about Rayhan? Is he okay with it?
Whatever.
I'd be long gone by the time he'd say yes.
Okay.
I'll call him after lunch.
Yes. I think I'm here.
Okay.
See you at home.
Who are you looking for?
Mr. Kasman?
Just call me Kasman.
I'm Tyas' colleague.
And I need your help, Mr…
I mean, Kasman.
Do you have time?
Well…
Come have a seat.
Please come in.
Sorry for the mess.
Please.
So…
Hey!
Be quiet.
Hey! Be quiet!
Stop seeking attention!
I'm sorry. That's how those kids are.
When they see attractive guests like you,
they tend to get showy.
So, what can I help you with?
Uncle.
Well, okay.
Tomorrow…
plant moringa leaves around here.
Over here.
Moringa leaves are good
for warding off ghosts.
-Move aside.
-Sorry, Uncle.
Let's start.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
That?
That's…
-Is he your husband?
-Yes. My husband.
I see.
Your husband.
He looks familiar.
Maybe it's just my vision.
What's upstairs?
Just our bedroom.
I see. I can look at it, right?
Excuse me!
Can a broomstick cast out ghosts?
I read on the Internet
that broomsticks can cast off spirits.
One.
Two.
Well, hello.
Hey.
Hey!
It's enough.
The owners of the house are good people.
You understand?
Go away.
Be gone.
Who is it, honey?
Just a friend from work.
Don't worry. I've protected your house.
Okay.
No one can bother you anymore.
For God's sake!
Come on.
Fight me.
Do you think I'm scared?
Dammit.
Go on, fight me!
Okay.
Han.
I heard something.
Wake up.
Something fell off the stairs.
I was right!
It moved on its own.
They were just messing around.
The house is protected,
but why is it still happening?
What did you say?
-Nothing.
-No, you said protected.
-What is?
-It's nothing.
Sher.
Sher, who said it's protected?
Who said it's protected?
I asked for psychic help.
I told you not to do that.
Why are you involved with such a person?
What's wrong about asking for help?
We clearly have an issue with this house.
And with you.
Me? What's my problem?
I called Mom and
I asked her about your childhood.
Whether you used to have nightmares.
She said no.
That means,
you started having nightmares and
sleep-talking after we got married.
And that's an issue for me.
Because you never talked to me about
your nightmares that kept you up at night.
Sleep-talking?
That's what you're having problems with?
Well, that is a problem!
Don't turn a blind eye to it!
Who said I did that?
Well, if you think this is a problem,
what is so wrong about asking for help?
I feel very disturbed, Han!
Do you enjoy seeing me
come home scared every night?
Of course not, Sher.
Then don't just ignore it!
Come here for a minute.
There is something…
I haven't told you.
-Don't scare me more.
-No.
You should know…
ever since I was a kid,
I had a sixth sense.
Like psychic abilities.
I had lost my ability, but recently…
it came back.
You also need to understand
that my not telling you about this
is because…
I wish for a normal life for us.
Like other people.
I don't want you to be scared.
Honey, I'm so sorry
if it feels like
I undermined your experience.
But I didn't mean anything like that.
Based on my experience,
the only way to deal
with these kind of stuff
is to just ignore it.
The more we let them know
that we're bothered,
the more they will bother us.
Are you saying…
you could see them all this time?
You know who's been bothering us?
Unfortunately, no.
-Han.
-I've been trying to, but to no avail.
-Don't lie to me, Han.
-I'm not.
Hey.
The only one I saw…
was my late maid
who still owes my mother some money.
I'm sure she's not
the one that bothered us.
Then, who is it?
I don't know.
But don't be scared.
I'll find out.
Okay?
-Sher.
-Hey. Where are you going?
-Uncle Kasman passed away.
-What? When?
He had an accident last night.
They brought him to the hospital but…
he didn't make it.
You want to come?
Hang on.
Han.
Hey, this is Sheren.
And her husband.
-I'm sorry for your loss.
-Thank you.
-Follow me.
-So,
what happened at the hospital?
-Was he still conscious?
-No.
But after spending two hours in the ICU,
he regained consciousness for a while.
He said something
but I can't make anything out of it.
He said something?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Han!
-What is it?
-Nothing. Let's go.
-Really?
-Yes.
You really don't know
who you saw at Uncle Kasman's house?
Because it seemed like you were focused
on a single spot.
It was a blur.
I don't know what I saw.
Are you sure?
Your expression was different.
You looked surprised.
Like seeing someone
you haven't seen in a long time.
I'm afraid you've had
problems in the past.
Or maybe you owe someone.
Or maybe you have unfinished business
with someone who passed away.
Sher, you're overthinking it.
I don't have enemies.
I don't know who's trying to hurt us.
I'm trying to find out.
Okay?
And you, don't bring together
things that unrelated.
It would make things more complicated.
What are you saying?
What about Tyas' uncle?
You're saying it's unrelated?
He died while returning from our house.
After helping me get rid of
the spirit in this house.
And I can't connect
those two things together
though it's so obvious?
That's because you tried to connect them
that he died.
What did I say?
Befriend them if you believe they exist.
If you don't want to do that, ignore them.
You didn't do that either.
What did you do?
You called a psychic
in a very unnatural way.
You resisted and fought them.
Now this is the consequence.
Uncle Kasman died.
So it was my fault
for seeking help for both of us?
Suit yourself.
Honey.
Where are you going?
To Dad's house. I'm staying there.
What are you going to say to him?
That you're scared of ghosts?
He will laugh at you.
He doesn't believe in this stuff.
I'd rather be laughed at than be haunted.
If this evil is trying to bother you,
it will keep bothering you everywhere.
So what should I do?
I'm not safe at home,
and I can't stay at my father's house.
What am I supposed to do?
What are we supposed to do?
Tell me!
Should we hire another psychic?
But what if they also end up dead
like Tyas' uncle?
Enough. Hey.
Deep breaths.
I promise you, just a bit more.
I'll find out who's been bothering us.
Okay?
It's okay.
I love you.
Brother Rayhan.
Who is it?
Brother Rayhan!
Dinda?
Han?
Han!
Han.
Sher!
Rayhan!
Sher! Sheren!
Sheren! Honey!
Honey, what happened? Hey.
How did this happen?
Honey.
Hey, sweetheart.
Are you okay? Honey?
Honey, we're going to be okay.
It looks like your wife suffered
a pretty hard impact
on the back of her head.
That's what caused her
to lose consciousness.
What about her pregnancy?
Given that the incident
your wife experienced was quite severe,
I cannot confirm the condition
of her pregnancy yet.
We need to do an intensive examination
to see the condition of the baby.
Hey.
Hey, baby.
Babe?
You're okay, baby?
Hey.
Where are we?
We're at the hospital.
Our baby…
Let's… Let's hope for the best, okay?
Honey?
Sher.
Han?
I was worried sick.
You finally woke up.
How did this happen to you?
Tyas…
Why are you here?
I got here when Rayhan was about to leave.
Where is he going?
He said to a relative's house.
I'll cut up some fruits for you.
So you'll feel better.
Where is it?
Do you see any?
Be patient.
I think there's no more left here.
What do you see?
You found one?
Okay.
I'm not scared of that.
Then what makes you scared?
Run!
Run away!
-I'm running away!
-Where are you going? Come here!
Seriously!
Rayhan.
It's been a while
since you were here, Han.
How are you?
Auntie, I'm sorry if it's a bit rude, but…
I'm here because
I have something to ask you.
What…
What actually happened to Dinda?
Why can't we let her
rest in peace in her own place?
That's what I'm trying to say.
I don't think she rests in peace.
Auntie.
I need to know
what really happened to her.
Auntie…
Why am I like this?
It's hot.
Hello, housekeeping?
Could you come here right away? Thank you.
Sher,
you and Rayhan are okay, right?
What do you mean?
I think Rayhan is keeping a secret.
A secret?
I think this has something to do
with something he saw
at Uncle Kasman's house.
What? That's…
Miss, I'm sorry, I dropped a cup.
Can you clean that up? Thank you.
Tell me more.
I don't understand Rayhan.
He knew that ghosts
still had human qualities.
The more you think about them,
the more they would feel important.
He said the same thing.
I'm so scared, Tyas.
Sher.
You don't have to be scared.
You have me.
How are you so brave?
Do you have abilities as well?
-Did you learn from Uncle Kasman?
-No!
All I know is that
ghosts only bother cowardly people.
Besides, if ghosts see me,
they're the ones who will be scared.
Miss?
What are you doing?
Miss? What is wrong with you?
Help!
Security!
Sher!
Help!
Sher.
Let go off me!
Let go!
Don't touch my friend!
Sher, run!
Irma!
Irma! Are you possessed?
Irma! Come to your senses!
Irma, snap out of it!
-Irma!
-Irma. Oh, no.
Honey?
What happened?
Hey.
How could you?
How could you leave me?
-I'm sorry. What happened?
-You said you would protect me!
I'm so sorry. But what happened to you?
Look at her! Look at Tyas!
She almost died because
you asked her to stay with me!
I almost died, too.
Honey, I had to leave to find out
about who's been bothering us.
Who's that woman?
Your ex?
You saw her?
It's a long story.
But, you still need to be treated.
Let's go.
Let's go, baby.
I don't want to stay here.
You still need to rest.
I said no.
I don't know what else to do, but…
I still have business to take care of.
I'm your wife.
Your business is my business.
I know who's messing with us.
Who is it?
Auntie Hesti's daughter.
Her name is Dinda.
You've never met her.
When we were little,
we were very close.
Because we had the same interests.
Hunting otherworldly beings.
Do you see it?
I can feel them, but…
I can't see them.
You need to practice.
Then teach me.
Since she was little,
Dinda really wanted to see them
and meet them.
One day she did.
But what she encountered
was a kind of demon.
Dinda!
Run!
Don't look back!
The devil kept chasing me.
I felt like I was entering another world,
and then I met Dad.
So, you entered the world of the dead?
If I were to get lost again
in the world of the dead,
would you accompany me?
I sure will.
What if we make a pact?
One that binds our blood together.
How scary.
Then you did the blood pact?
Let's see.
After we graduated elementary school,
Dinda moved out of town.
We met again in high school, but…
so many things changed.
She was no longer…
the Dinda that I knew.
Rayhan! Let's go out this Saturday.
-Where?
-Let's see ghosts like the old days.
Din, I don't do that stuff anymore.
I don't even know if I can see them.
Your girlfriend won't let you?
What girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Right.
I'm your girlfriend.
Don't be silly. We're related!
Oh, relax.
Stop!
Sorry to keep you waiting. Helmet, please.
I'm taking Nita home today.
What about me?
Don't worry, I'll go home by myself.
It's okay, I'll take you.
No. Emir can take me.
Thanks, Nit.
-Can you take me home?
-Sure.
Which way is your house?
That way.
What?
Be more sensitive.
I wanted to take Nita home.
I can't hear you.
Pull over. I can't hear you.
Gosh.
What did you say? I only heard gibberish.
You shouldn't have done that.
People are looking at us differently.
So what if they do?
It's uncomfortable.
It's your fault not telling me
you and Nita are dating.
We're not dating!
Then why are you mad?
It's still weird.
Nita was totally fine!
She was just pretending.
She wouldn't hurt your feelings!
Nonsense.
Dinda!
Nita!
Hey.
Why didn't you come?
To where?
Nita and Emir's funeral.
Oh, I can't.
Their family must be devastated.
Such a great loss.
I don't have the heart.
I was supposed
to take Nita home yesterday.
If I die,
you would stay with me
in that realm, right?
Din, our friends just passed away.
And that's what you're thinking about?
Rayhan!
I just found out from Auntie Hesti,
that Dinda went to a spiritual teacher
to learn black magic.
And not only just
to be able to see spirits.
She went that far?
If Dinda has supernatural powers,
she must be in alliance with the devil.
Okay. So, where is she now?
She's dead, Sher.
Dead?
From what?
Auntie, I have to know
what happened to Dinda.
How did she die?
Why did you come home?
Isn't the semester break next year?
Why didn't you tell me
Rayhan is getting married?
It's beca…
Din!
Dinda, stop!
Listen to me!
You have feelings for Rayhan, right?
He's your cousin, Dinda!
What will the whole family say?
This is a family event, Mom.
I'm still family, why can't I come?
I don't want you to cause a scene!
You will mess everything up!
What?
You can't answer that?
You know that I'm right.
I always obey my family.
I always do what you say!
Who wanted me to study abroad? You!
Why would I want to study so far away?
-Is that how awful you think I am?
-Enough!
Din!
This is what I meant!
You can't control your emotions!
Din.
Can you just for once listen to me?
I'm sorry, Dinda.
This is not for me.
And not for you.
This is for the whole family.
You only think about the family!
You never think about what's best for me!
Rayhan and I are cousins!
So what if I come to his wedding?
Is that how badly you think of me?
I always obey you!
Whatever you ask, I do!
Even when you sent me far away,
I complied!
This is crazy!
Now you're not letting me
to a family event?
Mom!
Don't lock the door, Mom!
Mom! Open it!
Mom!
You're so mean!
You're evil!
All this time,
I've succumbed to your wishes.
From now on, stop controlling me.
-Din.
-Get out of the way!
Din, enough. Din!
PROMISE
This way, sir.
What's the status?
A woman is suspected
of committing suicide.
Repeat after me.
I promise…
…that if one of us strays…
…into the world of the dead
or if one of us dies first…
the living must guard
and accompany the dead
to protect them from the devils.
…so that he or she
is not disturbed by the devils.
Okay.
Write it on top of mine.
Honey?
Okay.
So, what can we do now?
The soul of a departed person
won't be able to rest
if there are unpaid debts.
Does she owe you something? Or do you?
How are you going to pay it?
I have to meet her in her world.
Careful.
Han.
Is this your wife?
Yes.
Please forgive Dinda.
That kid is full of drama,
to the point of hurting people like this.
Han, let your wife rest. Get inside.
Nurse.
Be careful.
Don't be reckless, Han.
I have no other choice, Auntie.
If I ignore this,
things can get more dangerous.
I almost lost my wife and child.
So, what are you going to do?
I have to fulfill my promise
to meet Dinda.
Where are you going to meet her?
The place where she died.
Are you sure?
Han.
Rayhan.
Auntie?
You're awake.
Please.
You fell asleep while we were talking.
Where is Rayhan?
He left to sort things out.
I told him not to, but he insisted.
He left you with me here.
You're okay, right?
Sher!
Rayhan.
It's pointless. They can't see us.
Thank you for coming to see me.
Nurse. Do you know
the factory Mrs. Hesti talked about?
I'm sorry for disturbing your family.
But trust me, I have no ill intent.
I want to hasten our destiny
so we can meet again. That's all.
Rayhan.
What's wrong? Are you scared?
Please don't. You should be happy
that we can fulfill our promise.
Okay.
Din.
-Dinda?
-Yes.
I'm so happy to see you again.
-I've kept my promise, right?
-Yes.
So… now you can rest in peace.
What do you mean?
Right?
Now can we be respectful
of each other's lives?
I won't make you sad anymore.
So, please…
Please stop messing around with my life.
Sher.
Rayhan.
I won't disturb anyone anymore. What for?
You're here with me now.
And we'll stay here, together, forever.
Stop this nonsense.
I'm being serious.
I took my own life so that I can see you.
Do you think I sacrificed my life
just to see you one last time?
I died for you, Rayhan.
Okay.
Faster.
Rayhan!
Dinda!
No need to think about us being cousins.
-We're safe here.
-No!
I… I can't do this!
I need to go back to Sheren.
You don't realize, do you?
Do you want to see the reality
you are living in?
Han!
Han, hey.
Han.
Hey.
Rayhan, calm down.
Calm down.
Hey.
Relax.
This is not happening.
Rayhan, calm down. Hey.
You don't have to be scared.
I'm right here.
-There must be a way for me to return!
-No!
All doors are closed for you.
You can't get out.
Rayhan!
Sheren!
How's his blood pressure?
Good.
Rayhan!
-Rayhan.
-No!
Enough!
You've ruined my life!
Don't talk to me unless
you're helping me to return!
Then why are you here?
Why?
I thought you loved me.
Don't you ever think
that I don't love you.
I wouldn't be here if I didn't.
Just to keep my promise.
I love you too.
That's why I committed suicide.
You shouldn't have!
You should've let me live my life.
But I'm suffering alone here.
You're suffering
because you don't actually love me.
-What? I do love you!
-No.
Dinda.
You love the idea of us together.
You don't love me.
The person who loves me
wouldn't hurt my wife.
She wouldn't hurt my baby.
And my family.
If you really loved me,
you should've let me live my own life.
All right.
I'll help you get back to her.
Nurse!
Ma'am, let's wait outside.
Set the defibrillator to 200 joule.
Rayhan!
Dinda!
Is it working?
We did our best, but your husband…
Han…
I know you can hear me.
I know you made a promise to Dinda…
but your life is here, Han.
Please remember your promise.
To be a good husband
and father to our kids.
Come home, Han.
Please come home.
I know you can do it.
Dinda!
Listen to my voice.
Come back.
Han.
Dinda!
Wake up, Dinda!
It's me, Rayhan!
Dinda, I know you're there.
Fight back, Din!
I know you can, Dinda!
Dinda!
Dinda, wake up!
Wake up, Dinda.
Dinda!
Din…
Hey, Din.
Dinda.
Thank you, Rayhan.
You helped me once again.
Be good here, Dinda.
Han.
Hey.
Rayhan, I'm here.
Don't leave me, Han.
THIS IS A PART OF MY LIFE STORY…
SENTOT SAHID