Some people say that
believing in supernatural creatures
is the manifestation of fear
experienced by the
social community involved.
The belief in
supernatural creatures' existence
has long been rooted in our culture.
In the villages,
we see the belief
is getting even stronger.
Two years ago,
a team made a documentary film
about the existence
of supernatural creatures.
Existentialism is a view that puts humans…
ANTHROPOLOGIST OF
PEOPLE RELIGION AND CULTURE
…in the center point of a relationship.
To exist, humans must realize
that there are no other creatures
that exists aside from themselves.
All of us here are physically visible.
But that doesn't mean that the invisible
or the supernatural doesn't exist.
When we believe they exist,
then they do exist.
The point is you can't say
something is wrong
just because it can't
currently be proven.
One of the sources was Risa Saraswati,
a famous indigo in Indonesia.
Risa, we'll start the interview now.
- Okay.
- I will sit there.
Direct your eyes towards me.
- Mic. Get ready.
- Ready.
My name is Risa Saraswati.
I'm a writer. I'm a band member.
I'm a content creator.
I'm a government employee.
And I can see ghosts.
Aside from Peter, there are William,
Hans, Hendrick, Janshen and Marianne.
I was afraid of them at first.
But in time, I eventually started
to communicate with them
and wrote stories about them.
Many think I'm lying.
But for me, their names
and their stories are very real.
They don't care whether you believe
about them or not.
They only want to be heard,
not to be believed.
There is one entity that really scared me.
I accidentally called upon it
in a Jurnal Risa podcast
on our YouTube channel.
What's its name?
No.
Never call that name,
or else it'll get angry.
It is best to not remember
and say its name ever again.
Almost all of my family members
have the ability to talk to ghosts.
That's why we made Jurnal Risa.
11:20 AM
JURNAL RISA'S TEAM ARRIVED
The journal is our process
to communicate with ghosts
and introduce what we can see.
This will be our ghost hunting place.
Great.
It's suitable.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
- Risa, sound check.
- Okay.
One, two, one. Good?
- Okay. Come on.
- Okay.
Peace be upon you. Welcome to Jurnal Risa.
Today we're going to do a search
just outside Bandung,
in the Subang area.
I won't say the exact location,
but I'm not here alone.
I'm with Jurnal Risa's team.
Here's Dimasta.
Here's Nicko.
Indy.
And there's Kakang.
There's Riri who came all the way
from Jakarta. And also Fahrul.
And there are two masters,
Angga and Jeffry,
who will do the cleansing
during the hunt to protect us.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Great. Ready?
- Ready.
Risa, here are our
brave test participants.
Hi!
BRAVE TEST PARTICIPANTS ARRIVED
- Hello.
- This is Ardi.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Risa.
- This is Felly.
- Hello.
- Prisa.
- Prinsa.
My bad.
Thank God everyone's here.
Now, before we start the hunt,
let's pray first.
- Angga will lead the prayer.
- Okay.
Okay, before we start,
let's pray first,
so everything goes smoothly.
- Amen.
- Let's start our prayers.
Amen.
As usual, before we start…
- Come on, Ko.
- Iko.
Let's go.
For Jurnal Risa,
our nation, and our country.
Come on. Okay.
Great.
- Hello.
Is this the first time
you have joined Jurnal Risa's team?
- Yeah.
If I may know, why did you join?
For me, it's really interesting.
And I'm also a big fan of Risa.
I'm curious what it will be like
to meet them.
What about you, Prisna?
Why did I join this?
By the way, before I answer you,
my name is Prinsa.
- Not Prisna.
- Right. Sorry.
People always mistake my name.
But everyone remembers the names
of the ghosts that Risa has met.
There's even a ghost whose name
can't be mentioned, but everyone knows it.
So maybe, by joining this,
I can be more popular
than the supernatural.
It's only a rat.
It's drizzling. Let's move.
- Let's move. It's drizzling.
- Move over there.
09:00 PM
THE SEARCHING
Okay, now's the right time
to do the search.
It's nightfall, a suitable time.
But there are too many people here.
So we're going to split into three teams.
Have you started to feel dizzy?
- What?
- Starting to feel dizzy.
I feel that.
Especially because
this structure is very old.
Don't embrace him.
What do you feel here?
You are brave.
See?
Did you hear that?
No.
Seriously. Just now… Did you hear it?
- No.
- This sound.
Why are you taking us here?
I think there's an entity
that's pulling me to come here.
Not too deep.
Hang on.
What are you feeling, Indy?
- I want to cry.
- Come here, Ko.
I want to cry. Oh, God.
You see that?
Why are there so many women here?
I can't stand it.
How curious are you?
Pretty curious.
Because I've never seen them.
- You want to see them?
- Yes.
Maybe…
Oh, dear.
As…
Up there.
This is not right.
Let's cast it out.
We can't talk to it anyway.
Miss.
- Sorry.
- Let me move to the side. I'm scared.
Not here. Please. There are a lot of them.
We only just started.
They're watching us. Really.
Over there, okay?
Okay.
I'm scared.
Okay, Fel. We're going to leave you here
to test your courage.
We've put two cameras,
up there and down there.
There are cameras over there
and over there.
You can see a camera here.
There's also a camera there.
These two cameras
will record all your activities.
So you can communicate what you hear,
what you see and what you feel.
If something happens,
if you can't bear it, just clap like this.
- Okay.
- And we'll come get you.
- Ready?
God willing.
- We'll leave you, okay?
- Okay.
Can you see that?
It's dark.
I'll try exploring this place.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Let's play, guys.
Okay, guys.
Excuse me.
So, this is the structure that…
Wow!
Hi, guys.
I'm doing the courage test here.
I…
Now…
Own a doll
Prins?
Can't imagine…
Prinsa, stop singing.
How nice…
And cute…
Hello?
Peter?
She's calling for Peter and friends.
- It's moving.
- Hans?
- Is her phone on low battery?
- Hendrick?
Asih?
Why aren't they coming?
Or…
Should I call
the one whose name must not be spoken?
Maybe it'll come.
Samex?
Samex.
Maybe I should call on it faster. Okay.
Check on her.
Come here.
Prinsa.
She's possessed.
Come on.
Seek God's forgiveness.
Prinsa, seek forgiveness from God.
- Stand up.
- Come on, seek God's forgiveness.
What's going on?
- She's possessed.
- What's going on?
She's possessed.
Oh, God.
Not here.
I think that's enough for now.
- Let's go back.
- Okay.
Okay then. Let's wrap this up.
Let's pack everything up. Come on.
Come on.
Maybe I should call on it faster. Okay.
Samex.
Was Samex the one trending on Twitter?
Don't say its name.
Never.
I think Prinsa said
that name deliberately.
When this was viral back then,
people felt that the entity came to them.
But is it possible it came to Prinsa?
Check on it, Kang.
Play it.
It's…
Should I call
the one whose name must not be spoken?
BRAVE TEST PARTICIPANT
EXPERIENCED SUPERNATURAL
Let me try.
Samex.
The documentary team agreed
to follow Prinsa's daily activities
to know her development.
- Can I have a kilo of this?
- Okay.
You're the girl from that viral video,
aren't you?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Someone from Jurnal Risa's team
had gone to Prinsa's house.
She needs to be checked on.
I'm afraid something has latched onto her.
What do you mean by "something"?
Uwa Satirah.
One of our distant relatives.
She got that name
when she started to haunt our family.
PRINSA MANDAGIE'S HOUSE.
The people from her village
gave that name.
According to my father,
if someone
doesn't cast her out in five days,
the soul from the body
she inhabits will be gone.
I hope it's not Uwa
who has latched onto Prinsa.
Oh, God!
Hi!
Guys, guess who's here?
Angga and Indy are here.
Say hi.
Angga and Indy are in Jurnal Risa's team.
You remember that I had joined
the search the other day, don't you?
Come in.
So much fun!
Jurnal Risa comes over to the house now?
Bayu.
Angga, Indy, this is Bayu, my cousin.
He also handles all of my activities.
- Sa…
- Bayu.
Jurnal Risa is good for me. Okay?
Please.
I'm Angga.
Bayu.
- Indy.
- Bayu.
What's going on?
If I may ask,
after the courage test,
did you experience anything strange?
No. Everything's normal.
Right?
Okay, Prinsa.
After the courage test,
the video went viral.
But Jurnal Risa's team
feels that something has latched onto you.
And we came here
to do a cleansing ritual on you.
Allow us to do it, please.
Okay.
Where is she going?
Wait, Riri?
Riri?
Brother?
Indy?
Indy!
Help!
Uwa.
Uwa?
Sit down.
Sa?
Prinsa?
I think that was Uwa.
Uwa likes to come
in the form of people that we know.
I thought it was Riri.
But…
The documentary team was allowed
to put cameras inside Prinsa's house.
Like this?
Yes.
How's it? Check the battery.
What's that?
What are you doing?
Prinsa?
What's going on?
What happened?
There was…
Guys, today I've been invited
to a content creator's podcast.
I've never been invited to
something like this.
This is the first time I've been invited
to someone's podcast.
During my five years doing YouTube videos,
people have never been
this interested in me.
I don't know if I'm too ordinary or what.
One thing is for sure, I'm very nervous.
- Let's go.
- We're leaving.
- Okay.
- Do you see it?
- It's over there. Over there.
You sit there, the guest sits here.
The second one…
Mi. This is Prisna.
- Let her sit there.
- Thanks.
When it's done, please take it off…
Sit here.
Thanks.
Let's start.
Hi, guys. Back with me, Mimi,
in When Someone In Love With podcast.
Prinsa got angry during the podcast.
Bayu called.
She got angry?
Sa.
We need to do the cleansing again.
Why do I need to be cleansed again?
I'm still Prinsa!
- We're only afraid that it's…
- Samex?
You mean Samex?
Sa…
Di…
Let her go. Stay here.
Prinsa?
Prinsa!
- Prinsa's not here.
- Not here?
And she's not outside.
- Sa?
Sa?
- Prinsa?
- I'll check one more time.
- Sa?
Prinsa?
She's not here.
Sa?
- Can't find her?
- No.
Prinsa?
It's from the surveillance camera.
Hello.
Hello. I'm Fras from
Dreamland studio management.
Is this Bayu,
Prinsa Mandagie's contact person?
She is scheduled
to do a photoshoot this morning?
Right, that's me.
Is it today, at 9:00 a.m.?
But, I'm so sorry,
I think we have to cancel it.
- Because…
- Listen.
Something happened last night.
You better come to the studio right now.
It's about Prinsa.
We'll be waiting.
Come here asap.
Thanks.
Bay?
Here.
Prinsa?
Pri…
- Her clothes.
- Oh, God! Prinsa!
Hang on. Don't come here. Wait!
Prinsa. Oh, God.
Oh, dear.
Sit here.
Sa…
Where am I?
Bayu, what happened to me?
Why am I here?
Here it is.
Am I the only one who has seen this video?
We, the documentary team,
didn't have the heart
to show this video to Bayu.
This is from last night.
What do you think?
Is she possessed by
Grandma Satirah or Samex?
Uwa Satirah was
a distant relative of our family.
She was our late grandma's best friend.
Angga and I were kids back then.
She lived a life far away from religion.
Our late grandma
once gave her a prayer clothing.
She rejected it.
Not long after that…
she passed away.
Since then,
her spirit started to haunt our family.
Our father and our grandpa
tried to tie her
with the help of someone from her village.
Since then…
her name was changed to Samex.
Prinsa mentioned her name
during the shooting.
Son, be safe!
Just like most people,
Prinsa must have been
curious about that entity.
But she didn't know
what the consequences of her actions.
You're already home? That's Mom.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Let's not discuss this anymore.
Why are you recording like that?
The documentary team asked me to do this,
just in case.
What happened this afternoon?
I think something wrong is happening.
Hey. What's wrong with your hand?
Why do you keep on scratching it?
Forget it. Let's just sleep.
Okay.
Ri, son.
Wait.
- Ari? Where is he?
- He was just there.
Ri?
- Ari?
Let me check on him.
Ri?
Ari is sleeping in his room.
Wait.
Let's check on him. Ari?
Ari?
How is he here? Wasn't he in our room?
Nevermind.
It's better if he sleeps in our room.
He has a fever.
Come on.
Hey.
Ari's condition is better.
His fever has gone down.
The doctor said he's fine.
Okay? Don't be sad.
Calm down.
I'm going to be with him.
Okay.
We need to meet Dad.
We have to talk to him.
Okay.
Calm down.
Let us take care of this.
You just focus on Ari.
She accidentally mentioned
Uwa's name on YouTube.
How could she be so careless?
You all know the consequences.
Sa. Prinsa.
- Go say your prayers.
- Yeah, later.
Later.
So that you get some peace
and you're not disturbed anymore.
Okay?
I will say my prayers too after this.
Thank you for giving me this.
But I will not wear it.
You can go to heaven by yourself.
I'll stay in a huge rice field.
They kept on doing
the cleansing ritual on Prinsa
and the process was
monitored and recorded.
This is day three.
And I'm really exhausted.
Going through the
cleansing ritual repeatedly.
I kept on going through situations
where I wasn't aware of
what was happening.
So, I'm going to take precautions tonight.
- Indy.
- Yes?
Aren't you scared
having to live this every day?
Sometimes, yes, I'm scared.
But we have the others here.
So, we're safe.
I only have Bayu.
Earlier…
I was only by myself.
I have a question.
Do you have a best friend?
Nicko is my big brother
and my best friend.
Everyone in the Jurnal Risa team
are also my friends.
What about you?
Earlier, I had one.
A long time ago.
We were best friends.
There were four of us.
Two of them went to the city
with their parents.
There were two left.
But they're not together anymore now.
One killed herself.
One died and never once said her prayers.
Why are you calling her Aunty,
and not Samex?
Di.
Where's Prinsa?
It's not Prinsa.
Uwa is here. Be careful.
Prinsa?
100 bodies, 200 bodies, 300 bodies…
Slowly, Bay.
Prinsa.
Prinsa, wake up.
- Bay.
- Yes?
Who is it?
Have her sit over here.
Aceng…
Why are you disturbing Prinsa?
What do you want?
I'm not disturbing her.
I was called upon.
Come on, hurry and go home.
Go home.
Hold her, Bay.
No way.
I don't want to be tied again.
In the name of God.
"There's no god worthy of worship except
Him, the Ever-Living, All-Sustaining."
It's hot!
Wake up, Sa.
Bay.
I can't!
Be careful, Bay.
Watch out, Ko.
Oh, God.
Don't stand there.
Hold her!
Uwa.
Stop it, Uwa, possess me instead.
No!
Move.
Is she awake?
Move her to a chair.
Prinsa.
I don't think it's Uwa.
I think it's something supernatural
in the form of Uwa.
Hurry.
Go back to the village where it came from.
Only they can bind her.
They're the ones who helped
bind Uwa back then.
They're also the ones
who gave her the name Samex.
It's getting dangerous for Prinsa.
According to Dad,
the only way to solve this
is by taking Prinsa
to Uwa's home village.
Anything can happen there.
But they have to be able to face it.
Or else,
Prinsa…
may never come back, ever.
Where are you taking me?
If you think
I'll be scared to be taken back
to the place where I was born…
You're wrong.
Come on, Sa.
Slowly.
Is that…
empty?
Who are they?
They're from the city.
What are they doing here?
What's wrong with him?
What's the matter?
Leave. Get out of here.
Just go home, all of you!
Go back!
Go home! All of you!
Brother, what's going on here?
Sir, ma'am.
We're here to meet the village head.
Are you his guest?
Yes.
Come with me.
Excuse me, sir.
For the earth, for water,
100 bodies,
200 bodies.
For the earth, for water,
100 bodies,
200 bodies.
What is this blood and mat for?
The mat is…
for the ritual.
So no one will die anymore.
People died?
It's been a few days.
There have been lots of signs
that don't make sense.
Something strange is going to happen.
Can we meet the village head now?
Come on.
Come on, Bay.
Nobody from the village
dares to stay here.
They're all afraid.
This is Satirah's house.
We have arrived.
Be careful.
We're here.
All of you, don't go in for now.
I'm going to clean it first.
Come on, Arja.
She has come back.
- Excuse me.
- Please come in.
I am the eldest here.
Are you all Aceng's grandkids?
Yes.
It's the fifth night, isn't it?
Get me a chair.
Put it here.
Let her sit.
Excuse me.
What are you doing to my cousin?
Bay, remember what Risa said.
Just listen to him.
- It's Prinsa.
- It's for her own good.
- Do what he says. They know.
- Yes.
Come on.
Please help.
100 bodies, 200 bodies, 300 bodies.
100 bodies, 200 bodies…
300 bodies.
You've finally revealed yourself.
Satirah.
Aki.
- Satirah.
- Aki.
Father said it's not Uwa Satirah.
Who is this, then?
It's not only Satirah who is called
Samex in this village.
Supernatural creatures,
from people who died in unnatural ways.
- Ito.
- Yes, Aki.
Not everyone can come in.
Let's just stay here, Bay.
Stay here.
Calm down and stay here.
Trust them. They know better.
Okay?
This is Uwa Satirah.
This is Enok, our grandma.
This is Mak Eya, Grandma's big sister.
And this is Uwa Imas.
I'm going to ask again.
What are you doing here?
Did you think I'd be scared to be brought
to my own village?
During the ritual,
the supernatural gate will open.
When Samex comes out
of this woman's body,
she might not be the only one
who is going to get out.
Lots of supernatural entities
are looking for humans
as their dwelling place.
This village has been
cursed for four years.
And it has impacted
a lot of the villagers.
And they died in unnatural ways.
Agricultural failure.
Prolonged drought.
Some of them
who consistently haunt the villagers…
are called Samex.
That's what happened to Prinsa.
Brother, what should we do?
Let's just stay here
while waiting for their preparation.
Okay.
Let Prinsa and Bayu
rest for tonight's ritual.
Okay.
Bridge…
Ryan, let's go.
Bayu, Ryan and I are heading out.
We're going to see
the ritual preparations.
- Okay?
- Sure.
Offering.
Bridge.
- Sa…
- River.
Hot.
Let me help you.
Bridge.
- Sa…
- Offering.
Earth.
Bridge.
Don't disturb my cousin.
Bayu, this is me, Prinsa.
I'm exhausted.
I want to go home.
- Sa…
- I want to go home.
Prinsa.
I promise you, after you get better,
we're going to go home.
What do you want?
I'm going to fulfill
whatever you ask for.
I want to taste the placenta
of a newborn baby.
I'll split it slowly.
Its heart…
Or its organs.
Sa.
I'll always remember how good it tastes.
Sa…
Turn on the lights.
Where is she?
Where's Prinsa?
Prinsa?
Try looking for her over there.
Sa?
She's not here.
Prinsa!
- What?
- There's something…
Prinsa's not here. Let's look over there.
Shit.
Prinsa.
Sa?
Prinsa?
Where are we?
Rik, let's go back.
Bayu.
It's locked.
It's Prinsa's voice.
Sa?
Prinsa?
Bay?
Bayu?
Bay? Bayu?
Bay?
Bayu?
Bay? Bayu?
Bay.
We're back at this house.
Don't go into that room.
Let's try to go out the front door.
The door's open!
Pull it!
I can't!
Bay, pull it!
The door opened!
Ki! Aki!
She took my child!
My child is missing!
Help, Ki! My child has been kidnapped!
Calm down. Help them.
Help us.
- Bayu?
- Bayu!
Help!
Indy!
No, keep recording.
- Calm down.
- Prinsa!
Be careful. Sit down.
Are you okay?
Bayu…
What happened to Bayu?
Prinsa's missing.
- Help us!
- Prinsa's missing.
Where did she go missing?
I don't know.
- Wait here.
- I recorded Samex.
- Samex?
- Yes.
- Calm down.
- It was Samex.
Samex.
It hurts!
Hurry.
Before she gets to the rice field.
Let's look for her along the way.
Maybe she's there.
Come with me.
Prinsa!
Sa!
- Prinsa!
I heard something.
There she is. Prinsa!
Sa…
Prinsa.
Prinsa…
Tie her hands!
Quickly!
We have her.
Quickly, let's go.
THE RITUAL FOR PRINSA BEGINS.
Stand her up.
Okay, Mak.
Prinsa!
Stop it, Prinsa!
Mak!
Tie her with the mat.
Wrap her, tie her with the mat. Guys!
Hurry up!
Wrap her.
Wrap her with the mat.
Go inside.
Don't go out.
Go there.
He said, whatever happens,
we need to stay inside.
Bay, I'm leaving, okay?
This ritual
can't tie the supernatural just like that.
Just moving it from the girl's body
to another body…
isn't what we hoped for.
Just in case,
we've prepared a dead animal.
But it's the entity that will decide.
If it's the human who will die
or the animal.
We ask for permission and forgiveness.
To our ancestor
who rules the sea.
The ancestors from the north, the west,
the east and the south.
The exalted and the wise ones.
The dark shapeshifter
that rules the earth.
Now we shall start the ritual.
Let's start.
Get out!
Why?
You're inside
someone else's body, it's a sin!
Why?
You're inside
someone else's body, it's a sin!
Your mouth stinks!
You're the one who stinks!
Now, go home!
Go back to your world!
The world of calm.
No way!
What do you want?
I want you to see.
A very beautiful place.
Full of fire!
Get out!
You have a dark heart.
I have a dark heart.
Get out!
No way!
Brother, what should we do?
Be patient.
Let's just wait and see.
Keep recording!
Bring her here.
Hurry, bring her here.
Make her stand here.
Come on. Make her stand.
Stop.
Now, tie her hands.
Tie her hands.
A long time ago, you were born here.
But now it's not your place anymore.
Go.
Go back to where you belong.
Arja,
slaughter it.
Take its blood.
Taste that blood.
Taste it!
This…
This is not right.
If it's getting worse,
we need to go to them.
Where am I?
- Bayu!
- It usually doesn't last long.
Help! I want to go home.
I want to go home.
Ito!
Hurry.
Tie her with the mat.
Quick, spirit, get out!
I have been there.
It's scorching!
So beautiful!
When I get there,
I'll come get you!
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
Sister?
- Get in.
- Get back in!
- But…
I want to eat.
Do you have a newborn baby?
May I eat it?
Oh, God…
Ki, Neti has been chosen.
Come here, Ki. Look.
Ki, Neti has been chosen, Ki.
Neti!
Get her up.
Be careful. Take her hands first.
The elders of the universe have chosen.
Move Neti from there quickly.
Move her!
Move her dead body here.
This body is not yours,
your place is in the grave.
It went out. The light went out.
Not only the light.
The fire too.
All the torches also went out.
Why is it so quiet here?
Something's off.
Yan, turn the camera light on now.
And hold the camera.
Okay.
Mic!
Indy, hold Iko.
- Ga, what's going on?
- We must stay close.
Ga, can you explain this?
Aki said, during the ritual,
a gate will open.
The gate must be opened now.
Brother, Prinsa is missing.
Don't let her be alone.
- Don't let her be alone.
- Bay, calm down!
Bayu!
I will not let her be alone.
We'll find her. Let's split.
- Angga, Indy and Bayu, you go with Ryan.
- Okay.
- Nicko and I, we're together.
Let's split. Angga, you go there.
We will go there.
- We will go there.
- Okay.
Keep holding my hand.
Go first.
Prinsa?
Check over there.
Sa?
Prinsa?
You wait over here.
Sa?
She's not here.
Prinsa.
- Let's look over there.
- Let's go.
Sa?
Let's continue our search.
Where else should we look?
I don't know.
Dan?
I thought…
Let's continue our search.
That sounds like the villagers.
Let's just ask them.
No.
No, they're not human.
Let's just let them pass.
Turn off the light.
Let's hide.
Nick.
What?
Don't look.
Let's move.
Prinsa?
- Bay, it's Prinsa.
- Prinsa!
- Sa!
- Sa?
Prinsa?
- Prinsa?
- Sa?
Sa?
Dy. No.
Angga!
- There, Bay.
- Where?
Shit! Prinsa!
Prinsa!
Listen.
Listen to that.
The coffin Prinsa was in is here.
Let's try saving Prinsa.
Lake, forest, sea!
The words of the north
needs to be obeyed.
Lake, forest, sea!
It comes. It has come.
It's bitter.
It has come!
What should we do?
Bitter, here.
- Brother.
Let's leave.
They're not chasing us anymore.
But let's walk slowly.
Ryan, come on.
Sister. Bay.
Sa!
Prinsa!
Her eyes are normal. She's conscious.
Thank God.
Where am I?
We need to get out now.
Brother, why are they here?
Angga, what's going on here?
Why are they like this?
Are we back to our realm?
Right?
Return Prinsa to the coffin.
Come on, Sa.
No.
You don't belong here!
Go.
Go back to where you belong.
You don't belong here!
Sister!
Are you okay?
You don't belong here!
Samex! Samex is out!
Brother, he's cured.
Our village is free from Samex.
Take Prinsa back.
Is it finished?
It's done.
Hurry, take Prinsa back.
Nicko.
They succeeded in
casting the spirit out of Prinsa's body.
Prinsa and the team
were allowed to go home.
But the ritual went on.
We were not allowed to cover it.
I don't know if the village succeeded
in cutting its ties with the supernatural.
I felt guilty for saying
its name carelessly
and making people
curious about its existence.
The incident was the most terrifying
and the saddest,
which was hard for us to share.
And after the incident,
I decided not to make content
for a few weeks.
Whichever name
of the supernatural creature
that you see and hear in this movie,
don't ever call out its name,
or even think about it for a long time.
Because they can really come
and take over your life.
It can come when you're not ready.
All that happened in that village
was out of our control.
It's hard for us to believe it,
but we know there's always
a lesson learned
for everything that happens.
Don't ever call its name again.
Hi, my name is Prinsa.
PRINSA MANDAGIE
RESOURCE PERSON
I want to apologize to Risa, Angga, Indy
and all of Jurnal Risa's team.
And I also want to say
thank you very much
for helping me and Bayu
throughout the incident.
I've learnt my lesson that
there's no point in me existing
without being myself.
This is a big lesson for me.
Peace be upon you.
Welcome to Jurnal Risa.
Maybe it feels weird
when Jurnal Risa came to the cemetery.
We are now going back to our hometown.
So, this is
our Grandma's hometown.
I will not reveal the place.
Jurnal Risa,
the searching at my house,
part two, there was
a moment
when I was possessed
in the squat position.
She asked for their praying.
So, we looked for her grave.
Don't come. Here is enough.
I don't have anything with you.
Answer it, Andi.
- What do you think?
- I saw a pocong here.
As tall as a tree.
That tall?
Panicking. Just going around
with nowhere to go.
You're thirsty.
There's no food and drink here.
Don't do that, Fahrul.
Hey. Fahrul, get up.
He usually says something?
- Risa?
- Yes?
Help!
- There's another one.
- My goodness.