[FAINT TRAFFIC SOUNDS]
[TRAIN RATTLING]
[BROODING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
MAN:
The game of kings - chess -
transcends culture,
religion, race, politics
and economics.
Doesn't matter what
your circumstances are,
you can enjoy
a good old-fashioned battle
over a chessboard anytime.
This here's
not an ordinary game, you see.
Could say
it's a high-stakes game.
The highest stakes of all.
This is Abe.
Abe is my boss.
I drive for him.
Sounds simple enough.
But it ain't.
You see, Abe is a gangster.
Old-school.
It's all about loyalty
and honour with Abe.
But the thing is,
Abe suffers from DID -
dissociative identity disorder.
Or, in layman's terms,
multiple personalities.
Now, this is Frankie.
Frankie is his own
sort of fuckin' crazy.
Not crazy like Abe crazy,
just...sociopath crazy.
You see,
Frankie used to work for Abe
until he decided
to do his own thing.
Abe and Frankie have been
at each other ever since.
The media call it a gang war.
Abe calls it a problem.
And Frankie?
Frankie calls it business.
[TENSE INDUSTRIAL ROCK MUSIC]
[SIREN WAILS]
MAN: Abe has been good to me.
Like a father figure.
A mentor.
And a mate, faults and all.
To be truly honest, the last
24 hours feels like a dream,
and not a good one.
More like a fuckin' nightmare.
[MUTED CONVERSATION]
None of this feels real.
But here I am.
DETECTIVE: ..electronically
recorded record of interview.
And, Ben, can you state
your full and correct name?
Ben Michael Carter.
DETECTIVE: OK. Do you go by
any other names or nicknames?
- Benny.
DETECTIVE: Benny.
And you understand
why you're here?
OK, Ben, so we are here
because of an incident
that occurred
at the Lucky Saints Bar.
Can you tell me what happened
before police became involved?
From which part?
BEN: Let's rewind.
[TAPE REWINDING]
[PENSIVE PIANO MUSIC]
The day started
like every other day.
Wake up, you sleepyhead!
Wake up!
- Wake up, wake up, wake up!
- [ABE GROANS]
- You gotta get out of bed.
- Mia!
Leave your father alone and
go and get ready for school.
- Wake up, wake up!
- [GRUFFLY] Mia...
..you just...
..woke up Tickle Frankenstein!
- No!
- [ABE ROARS PLAYFULLY]
Tickle Frankenstein!
Mia, go and get ready
for school.
And, Abe, stop stirring her up.
Go get dressed.
You stir her up and then
I have to chill her out
and get her ready for school.
It's not my fault she woke up
Tickle Frankenstein.
[HUFFS] Tickle Frankenstein...
- Hey, Your Honour, come here.
- [CHUCKLES]
Hey, Your Honour,
I'm pleading the Fifth.
Mmm. You always do.
- Mm-mm.
- Come on.
Mm-mm. Uh-uh.
- I've got to get ready.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
There's things to do.
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
Yep.
[LOW OMINOUS MUSIC]
[INDIE POP SONG
PLAYS ON STEREO]
Morning, Princess.
Smells awesome.
Hey, don't forget
we've got dinner
on Friday night
with Michelle and Ryan.
Friday? Mmm...
I'm just playing with you.
I love hanging out
with your sister and Brian.
I can see that.
And it's Ryan, not Brian.
Yeah, yeah, I know it's Ryan.
I'm just joking around.
Friday?
Friday. Locked it in.
Can I go to Stephanie's
on the weekend to the movies?
Abe?
Fine by me.
Alright, well,
I'll call Stephanie's mum
- and sort something out.
- Yay!
But you have to do
your homework first.
- That's the deal, OK?
MIA: Yes, yes. I promise.
ABE: Coffee, honey?
SOFIA: No, thanks.
I'm being good and cutting down
on my caffeine.
OK, you be good and all that,
but you are missing out
on the Abe special brew.
Special brew?
It's instant coffee.
Hey, it's how you make it,
my angel.
Milk first, and stir.
Your facetiousness
will not sway me
from my mission
to make a world-class coffee.
- [INTERCOM BEEPS]
- You're so full of it.
It's instant!
You know we have a
thousand-dollar machine there?
- You should try it.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Benny.
He'll be down in five.
I'm making him a coffee.
At least he will appreciate it.
Poor Benny.
He has to like it -
he works for you.
Mm-hm, yeah, very funny.
He will tell me the truth.
You'll see.
- And he'll love it.
- Sure he will. Yep.
You know, honey,
some days just...
..feel special,
and today feels that way.
You're not getting all
philosophical on me, are you?
Nah, nah, I just...
I've just got
that tingly feeling, like...
..that feeling
of a change in the air.
Feels like a good day.
You be good at school.
Learn heaps.
See you later tonight.
What are we doing for dinner?
I'll grab something
on the way home.
Something special.
Something healthy.
[CUTLERY CLINKS]
[PENSIVE PIANO MUSIC]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Hey.
Love you, Princess.
Love you too, Daddy.
[INDIE POP SONG
CONTINUES PLAYING]
[BROODING ATMOSPHERIC MUSIC]
DETECTIVE: So,
what have you seen that, um...
..you would consider
to be illegal activity?
[PHONES RINGING IN DISTANCE]
You know, he... [SCOFFS]
..he was good at hiding...
..everything from me.
You know,
he-he made sure that...
..I saw nothing,
I heard nothing.
That was...
..that was Abe.
I was just his driver.
He just made sure that was it.
BEN:
Now, that was a fuckin' lie.
I knew everything about Abe.
The only thing I didn't know
was his state of mind
that morning.
[TRAFFIC BLARES IN DISTANCE]
Nah, nah, finish your smoke.
Thanks, boss.
My pleasure, young Benjamin.
You want one?
Not here.
- Sofe'll kill me.
- Mm.
BEN: Sofe.
Sofe left a few years ago.
Clearly off his meds.
[INDISTINCT
POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Well?
- The coffee.
- Oh! Mm.
Pretty bloody good!
Fuck yeah. I said that.
It's good, right?
Yeah! That's good!
Yeah, that's what
I said to Sofe.
- It's really good.
- I said it's good
and you would
tell me the truth, yeah?
100.
Yeah, that's good. Mmm.
For instant coffee.
Fuck you, instant coffee!
What?
Never mind. Instant coffee...
Get in the car.
[BEN CHUCKLES]
[INDISTINCT
POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Fuck!
- Instant fuckin' coffee...
- [CAR ENGINE STARTS]
- Fuck...
- [BEN LAUGHS]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO
CHATTER CONTINUES]
BEN: Every day
was the same routine.
And today felt no different.
Cops were like clockwork.
It was always
a bit of cat-and-mouse
with the boys in blue.
POLICE RADIO:
..formal operation in progress
in North Sector 26...
[CHUCKLES]
Morning, cocksuckers.
DETECTIVE: Keep on 'em, Wannie.
Keep on 'em.
These guys are so obvious
it's a fuckin' joke.
Glovebox.
BEN: New burner.
[OPENS GLOVEBOX]
Burners were how Abe talks
to his different personalities.
A bit of a charade, but it's
how he manages his illness.
So, what's on today, boss?
What are we doin'?
- It's a big day, Benny boy.
- Oh, yeah?
- A big day.
- Alright.
Just lose those clowns.
Yep, once we hit the traffic.
DETECTIVE: Keep on 'em.
[TYRES SCREECH, ENGINE REVS]
DETECTIVE: Go!
[ENGINE REVS]
DETECTIVE: They're runnin'.
Go, go, go!
[TYRES SQUEAL]
DETECTIVE: Fuckin' hell! Urgh!
[CHUCKLES]
Now, that, young Benny Boy,
was a piece of art!
And that is why you
are my driver.
Thanks, boss.
They may want to take a few
demerit points off your licence
but well worth it.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Fuck 'em.
[TYRES SCREECH]
So, what's the plan?
The plan is already happening.
See, in this business, it's all
about doing and reacting
to what's happening around you.
A reflex.
Everything's changing, Benny.
This Frankie situation...
I've got to adapt.
It's like a game of chess.
Someone does that move
and takes a rook,
so you do this move
and take a knight.
The trick is
not to expose your queen...
..or fuck the king.
And tonight Frankie will know
who the real king is.
It's about getting
that shit done.
[STATIC ON RADIO CRACKLES]
['AHH' BY REALBOY
PLAYS ON RADIO]
♪ Being a child of abandonment
just like you
♪ Forced to live
in such a sick green world
♪ It's been months now
and you're all hooked on it
♪ It's been years now
and you're just as hopeless
♪ But you should have known
this by now... ♪
I was just his driver.
He just made sure that was it.
DETECTIVE: Come on, Benny.
I think you can do better
than that, mate.
We did stop
at a building on Fison.
DETECTIVE: Who lives there
at this meeting place, Benny?
No, no idea.
DETECTIVE: No idea?
- No idea.
I'd never been there before.
BEN: Well, that was bullshit.
We'd been there
plenty of times before.
It was just another part
of the process.
[GRUNTS]
BEN: And this is Kane -
Abe's most dangerous
personality.
The fighter and the fixer.
The killer.
This was his darkness.
The closest personality to him.
The part of himself
he could always rely on.
See, some of us are thrown
into this world by chance.
But Kane...
..Kane was created
for this world.
A tailor-made savage.
BEN: Fison Ave?
ABE: Just a tick.
[LINE RINGING]
I gotta deal with
this finance fucker.
[SERENE CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS]
BEN: Meet Richard. Another one
of his personalities.
The part that does
all the finances.
Washes the cash,
turns it legal.
Every successful crime boss
needs a Richard.
[LINE RINGING]
Can you believe this guy?
Ignoring me
for over a week now.
Thinks he's above me.
[LINE RINGING]
Guy's either got big balls
or he's a fuckin' idiot.
Or he's both.
[CHUCKLES]
[PHONE RINGS]
[PHONE STOPS]
BEN: The problem is,
Richard wasn't answering Abe.
Richard had gone rogue.
And it was like he'd created
his own separate life.
To Abe, these personalities
were as real
as the person
sittin' next to you.
[DISCONNECT TONE]
I fuckin' bankroll this maggot
and he thinks he can
walk away and cut me out,
just flush me
like a fuckin' turd!
You want me to chat to him?
BEN: As if that'd ever happen.
Nah, it's well beyond that,
Benny.
Well beyond chatting.
[LINE RINGING]
STAN: [ON PHONE] Boss.
- Stano.
Meet us for a catch-up.
No problem.
- Yeah, you got the address?
- Fison Ave.
How long?
- 15.
- Alright, see you there.
- Righto.
Some days, Benny, you just
gotta show these pricks
who's holding the aces.
No more fuckin' around
with these clowns.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[HEAVY MUSIC
PLAYS ON HEADPHONES]
BEN: You see, Abe saw the world
as one big hostile place.
Hostility attracts hostility.
[TYRES SCREECH]
What the fuck?!
- [MUSIC CONTINUES]
BEN: Kane was Abe's way
of dealing with
that hostile world.
[ENGINE REVS, TYRES SCREECH]
That's where Abe was different.
He manifested them
to suit his needs.
In Abe's mind,
Kane was the lone wolf.
The natural born killer.
Disconnected from society.
Did his job,
no questions asked.
100% reliable.
No conscience,
no moral compass, no guilt.
He just did what was needed.
The perfect soldier.
The funny thing is
that 10 degrees of separation
was a lot closer
than I ever thought.
None of us really knew
how far he'd detached himself
from the real world.
I guess it's easy
to see it all in hindsight, eh?
To be honest, at this point,
I had no idea how dangerous
he really was.
MAN: I fuckin' told
that cunt, bro,
if he doesn't fuckin'
pay me by Saturday,
I'm gonna fuckin' stab him.
Yeah, fuck him. Gotta do
what you gotta do, bro.
Fuck you lookin' at, dog?
[MEN GROAN]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
- [KANE GRUNTS]
- [TENSE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- [TAPE REWINDING]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
Those things
are gonna kill you.
Everything'll kill ya nowadays,
mate.
I like my poison.
BEN: Abe lived a fantasy life
through Kane's world
of violence.
[ENTRANCE ALERT CHIMES]
It was all just
a beautiful violent illusion
playing out in his mind.
[STATIC, INDISTINCT CHATTER
ON POLICE RADIO]
[HEAVY MUSIC
PLAYS ON HEADPHONES]
Abe would say,
in this business,
if I can't negotiate it,
and Richie can't buy it,
then there's only one way
to fix it.
[KANE GRUNTS]
BEN: You have to be a monster.
A true fuckin' monster.
See, Kane might have been
a figment of Abe's personality,
but the address was real,
and so were the people
who lived there.
[SECURITY PAD BEEPS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
- Hey, handsome.
- Hey, Tracey.
Always looking good.
TRACEY: [IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
OK.
[TRACEY SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
[BOTH CONVERSE IN RUSSIAN]
[KEY RATTLES IN LOCK]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[PHONE RINGS]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
BEN: I think Kane was becoming
harder for him to control.
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
BEN: Maybe even he
had his own demons.
[SINISTER MUSICAL STING]
Knock twice,
slip it under the door.
No problem, boss.
DETECTIVE:
What was in the envelope?
No idea, mate.
Just, uh...
could've been anything.
Could've been a letter or cash.
And why would you say cash?
From what I've seen
in the papers, it...
..you know...
..it could've been cash.
BEN: I knew exactly
what was in that envelope,
and it wasn't cash.
[ARGUING IN RUSSIAN]
[SECURITY PAD BEEPS]
[DOOR SLIDES OPEN]
BEN: Stan had no idea. He was
just part of the charade.
Like a good little soldier,
he played his part.
[HEATED ARGUING IN DISTANCE]
Even the most hardened hearts
feel guilt.
Can be a heavy burden.
Eventually breaks you down,
those inner thoughts.
And inner demons.
They come creeping back
to haunt you.
Always there.
[TV SWITCHES ON]
Police are no closer to solving
these gangland
execution-style murders
that have been going on between
the south-side crime gangs
and the north-side syndicate.
There is a real concern
from police
that this growing turf war
could see an increase
in these murders...
[TV SWITCHES OFF]
BEN: We all have choices.
Sometimes those choices
are more personal than others.
[ENGINE REVS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Plan?
Give us a second.
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Don't answer it.
Don't listen to him.
Take the call.
Shut up.
Don't.
Just let it ring out.
GHOST 2: What does it matter?
We're all dead anyway.
Yeah?
You got what you need.
Job needs to be done
in the next 24 hours.
[DISCONNECT TONE]
There you go.
Looks like the job's on.
GHOST 1: He still has a choice.
I think he's made his choice.
He had a choice with all of us.
We all made choices
to be where we are.
Yeah, and you chose
to skim off Abe.
[SCOFFS] And you
were such a saint!
GHOST 2:
Hey, it was just business.
Oh, business.
You hear that? Business.
It was business that put
a bullet in your fuckin' head.
We all got a bullet
in the head.
[MAN 1 GRUNTS]
[MAN 2 SHOUTS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC BUILDS]
BEN: I wished
I'd seen it coming.
[WISTFUL INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[POP BALLAD PLAYS]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
Hey. How was your run?
Powered, baby! Whew! Powered.
BEN: Richard was
a special sort of monster.
He'd decided he was
the dominant personality
and nothing and no-one
would stand in his way.
- Ah...
- [SIGHS WEARILY]
[PHONE RINGS]
BEN: Abe would never
allow that to happen.
- [PHONE RINGS]
- [SIGHS]
Fuck...off!
You are not gonna ruin tonight.
PAM: Who's ruining tonight?
Don't worry about it, baby.
Just some idiots trying to
muscle in on the Menzies deal.
But no-one... [EXHALES]
..is gonna ruin tonight.
It's good.
It's my best one yet.
It's good. OK.
And how's good down here?
- My back hurts.
- Oh, back hurts?
- Mm.
- Yeah?
- Stop hurting Mummy, Daisy.
- That's her foot.
RICHARD: That's her foot?
Give me a little kick.
- You been kicking Mummy?
- Yes.
Alright, I'm gonna take
a quick shower.
OK.
[POP BALLAD CONTINUES PLAYING]
Baby, get any more shampoo?
You've run out.
I'll get some more tomorrow.
Fuckin' hell.
Fuckin' stud.
Ah, babe, looks amazing.
My wallet. Do you know
where my wallet is?
On the side table
in the bedroom.
- Mmm.
- [SCOFFS]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Alright, baby, I'm gonna head
out early, beat the traffic
'cause tonight, you know,
it's a pretty big one.
You need to rest.
Thanks, babe.
OK. So can we not get into
a whole thing over a meal?
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah?
I love you.
Love you.
OK.
Well, don't wait up, 'cause you
know what Mackenzie's like.
Tomorrow, you and I,
we celebrate, just us.
- OK?
- Of course.
Of course.
OK.
[PENSIVE PIANO MUSIC]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[SLAMS CHAIR]
[CAR ENGINE HUMMING SOFTLY]
[OMINOUS PULSING MUSIC]
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
[TYRES SCREECH]
[TENSE ATMOSPHERIC MUSIC]
BEN: The wheels were in motion.
We were all
on a collision course.
Call it fate,
if you believe in fate.
As Abe put it,
the plan was in motion,
like a psychotic fucking opera
playing out.
No-one could've stopped it now,
not even Abe.
AUTOMATED PHONE VOICE:
Who would you like to call?
Call Lollipop.
[PHONE BEEPS]
AUTOMATED PHONE VOICE:
Calling Lollipop mobile.
[LINE RINGING]
WOMAN: [ON PHONE] Hi, babe.
[CHUCKLES] Hey, gorgeous.
You, uh, you ready
for tonight, yeah?
I've been thinking about it
all day. [GIGGLES]
My body is just tingling
thinking about it.
OK, OK, OK...
OK, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Give me 45, I've just got to
take care of a few things,
sort out a few papers at
the office and I will be there.
[BREATHILY] Oh,
I want your body now.
Oh, my God, I can't wait. OK.
AUTOMATED PHONE VOICE:
Who would you like to call?
- Please call Kelly.
- [PHONE BEEPS]
AUTOMATED PHONE VOICE:
Calling Kelly mobile.
KELLY: [VOICEMAIL]
Hi. Kelly here.
- Please leave a message.
- [BEEP!]
Babe, can you please
call me back?
Bastard. You fucking bastard!
So, tell me, tell me, tell me,
what are you wearing?
WOMAN: [ON PHONE] Nothing.
[LAUGHS]
Nothing, OK.
Describe nothing for me.
Well, picture me
stepping out of the shower...
Yeah.
..dripping wet.
You're like this.
Alright, alright.
You know what? Um...
Let's slipstream this.
- Yeah?
- I can do this in 20.
I want your body now.
I know, I know, I know. OK.
Um, you know what?
I think about you, I can
smell you. Ah, God, gorgeous.
- Shit!
- What? What's up?
- [LINE RINGING]
- It's Pam calling me.
OK.
Listen, don't-don't answer it.
I feel sort of guilty,
you know?
Don't...don't feel guilty.
- Oh, she's hung up, thank God.
- You know what?
She's just calling you
because she's bored.
Do you think
she suspects anything?
No. Not in a million years.
She has no idea
what's going on.
Just...
I... [STAMMERS]
I don't want you to worry
about anything, OK?
I will deal with her
and, look, I've got to
put one more thing in place
and we will not have to worry
about her fuckin' bullshit
ever again.
- Just...
- I know. [SIGHS]
It just hurts
not being together.
- And-and...
- Hurry up.
..20 minutes.
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
AUTOMATED PHONE VOICE:
Who would you like to call?
Please call Kelly.
[PHONE BEEPS]
AUTOMATED PHONE VOICE:
Calling Kelly mobile.
[LINE RINGING]
KELLY: [ON PHONE]
She's ringing me again.
Should I take the call
and just call you back?
Take the call,
find out what she wants,
- don't say anything...
- [LINE RINGING]
I've actually got another call
coming through. Deal with it.
- Get back to me.
- OK, babe.
Yeah, Richard speaking.
[LINE RINGING]
KELLY: [ON PHONE]
Hi, babe. What's up?
Fuck, I don't even know
where to begin.
I'm-I'm in the car
and I'm following Richard.
- You're following Richard?
- Yes.
My mind is going, like,
a million miles an hour
right now.
OK, slow down.
Take a deep breath
and tell me what's going on.
I think Richard's
having an affair.
- With who?
- I don't know!
With this girl that he names
'Lollipop' or something.
Lollipop?
I saw this message
on his phone tonight.
- Message on his phone?
- I saw it with my own eyes.
I doubt he's having an affair.
How could he do this to me?
Like...how could he
do this to us?
Wait a second, he's turning.
- Just one second.
- Where?
Yeah, he's turning
into this carpark.
- Can he see you?
- I'll have to call you back.
OK?
[TICKET MACHINE WHIRRS]
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
[LINE RINGING]
KELLY: [ON PHONE] Hi.
- Hey. How'd it go?
She knows
you're having an affair.
No way. She's got no idea.
She's following you.
You...you're at a carpark.
Richard...
Hello?
[CONCERNED] Babe.
[MOTORCYCLE ALARM BLIPS]
[GRASPS GUN]
[SINISTER MUSIC BUILDS]
[GUN COCKS]
How much?
[SCOFFS, SHOUTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[CAR ALARM BLARES IN DISTANCE]
[CAR ALARM CONTINUES]
[CAR ALARM INTENSIFIES]
Fuck.
Fuck! Fuck!
[ENGINE REVS, TYRES SCREECH]
[BEN INHALES, EXHALES]
Can I get a cigarette?
Sorry, mate, I don't smoke.
[DETECTIVE GROANS]
Knock yourself out, mate.
DETECTIVE 1: Don't you know
smoking can kill ya, Benny?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Ironic, eh?
Thank you.
DETECTIVE 2:
You're right, mate.
Then, what? Then you've
headed to the Lucky Saints Bar?
- Is that right?
- Correct. Yep.
BEN: Like every day,
as if they didn't know that.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY]
Benny.
- Boss man.
- Winks.
How we going for time?
Frankie should be here
in about 30.
Mm.
Today's a good day.
BEN: [CHUCKLES WRYLY]
A good day.
[THUNDER RUMBLES, RAIN PATTERS]
DETECTIVE 1:
Time's ticking, mate.
He, uh...
He asked me to go in
when we arrive,
which never happens.
I thought it was kinda nice,
instead of sittin' in
the fuckin' car all the time.
BEN: Another lie.
So we went in.
Uh...Abe and Frankie
had a meeting set up.
And, uh...
I dunno, we-we had a drink
and just got ready.
- [DANCE MUSIC PLAYS]
- [PHONE BUZZES]
Why shoot yourself
in the foot, mate?
Frankie's here.
[GUN COCKING]
Today's a good day.
Let's make history today.
Let him in.
[TENSE ATMOSPHERIC MUSIC]
[SIREN WAILS]
SOFIA: [ON PHONE] Sofia here.
Hello?
I know you're there.
[SIGHS]
DETECTIVE 1: Ready?
For the meeting, you know.
Just got ready.
It wasn't long
before they arrived, so...
So who's...who's 'they', Benny?
Come on. Can't read your mind.
- Who's 'they'?
- Frankie...Frankie and Tony T.
DETECTIVE 1:
Who's Frankie and Tony T?
Come on.
DETECTIVE 1: OK, mate...
- Fuckin' hell.
You know Frankie, mate.
Everyone knows Frankie.
DETECTIVE 1: Do we? Alright.
You would know him
better than I would.
BEN: These guys knew exactly
who Frankie and Tony T were.
And how was everybody's moods
when all these people
came together?
- What was the atmosphere like?
- [EXHALES]
Everyone was pretty...relaxed,
considering, I guess.
BEN:
Now that was a fuckin' lie.
[SLOW-PACED SURF ROCK MUSIC]
That's right,
South-side in the house!
Knock, knock!
Who's fuckin' there?
Ha-ha-ha.
What up, you fat fuck, Stan?
Oh, look.
It's the fuckwit island boys.
- Ha-ha.
- Hey?
- Go on, get over it. Ooooh!
- Fuckin' hell, hey?
Abe's waitin'.
Hey, next time take me to
dinner first please, mate.
Tell ya mum to hold on the
casserole. I'll be home late.
Always be a fat fuck, Stanley.
ABE: Frankie, Frankie. Welcome.
What up, Abe?
Benny. Long time.
- Huh.
- Long time.
Come on.
Shalom, shalom, brother.
Shalom.
[SNIFFS] Yeah, you smell good.
Don't he, bruz?
He smells real fuckin' good.
Oh, nice place. Yeah.
Love what we done with it.
[LAUGHS]
Mi casa, su casa.
It means
'my house is your house'.
- Oh, but I don't speak Greek.
- He don't speak Greek.
Yeah, take a seat.
Benny, get us
a couple of bourbons.
Tony, you're welcome
to have a drink.
- Get Tony a drink.
- Nah, don't fuckin' bother.
- I don't fuckin' drink.
- He don't drink.
My father always told me never
trust a man who doesn't drink.
Fuck your father. [SCOFFS]
You think we give a fuck
what your father thinks?
Get Tony a cranberry juice.
[CHUCKLES]
- Shit, son.
- Get fucked.
Salud.
L'chaim...
- [GLASSES CLINK]
- ..old man.
- [MUSIC PLAYS FAINTLY]
- [ROWDY VOICES IN DISTANCE]
[GLASS SMASHING]
[MUSIC, VOICES CONTINUE]
What, you play chess
or somethin'?
Yeah. You?
[SCOFFS]
I ain't just good-lookin', man.
I love a game.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I'm like Bobby Fisher, man.
Two moves ahead. You feel me?
Grandmaster!
[FRANKIE CHUCKLES]
- Shall we?
FRANKIE: Fuck yeah, homie.
- Now...
- This fool.
- ..as my guest...
- Uh-huh.
..you can start.
FRANKIE:
What are we playing for?
Huh? You got crypto?
What you got, huh?
I don't want this
fuckin' shithole. [LAUGHS]
How about the winner lives...
..the loser dies?
Fuck you, old man.
We young and hungry. We ain't
dumb, playing a stupid game.
That's fuckin...
[SCOFFS] ..punk.
[CHUCKLES]
Fuck, you for real, old man?
Fuck you, fuckin' cunt.
Nah, we outta here.
Fuck this shit, man.
- Hey, what the...!
- Sit the fuck down, princess.
- Sit the fuck down.
- What the fuck's this shit?
- Alright. Alright, man.
- Don't fuckin' move, cunt.
Fuck.
You fuckin' for real?
You gonna do us like that?
- Fuck is this?
- A fuckin' game?
For our life?
You're fuckin' crazier
than I thought.
[MENACING MUSIC]
DETECTIVE 1: Seriously?
The winner...of the chess game
lives?
I'm being 100% honest with you.
That was the deal.
Chess.
As in king, queen, checkmate?
BEN: Yes. Yep.
It was like...
..Deer Hunter,
Russian roulette,
just with a fuckin' chess set.
What was Frank's reaction
to that?
What do you think?
And you must think
I'm just some dumb punk. Huh?
Yeah.
That's right,
I didn't just show up here
without no backup, bitch.
An insurance policy?
Yeah, a fuckin' insurance
policy. Did I stutter?
ABE: That's clever, Frankie.
- Fuck you, I'm clever.
Tell me about
your insurance policy.
I'll tell you about it.
That fuckin' white sliced bread
of yours, that yummy mummy?
Mmm! She ain't bad, son.
And that little daughter
of yours?
Yeah, one phone call.
Them first.
You want to play this game?
I said,
do you want to play this game?
- Clever.
- Yeah.
Your fuckin' family.
BEN: You could feel
something bad was comin'.
What, cat got your tongue,
cunt?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Not so fuckin' smart now,
are ya?
My family's first?
Yeah.
Your fuckin' white bread
yummy mummy.
And that little daughter
of yours. Mia, right?
One phone call, fool.
[ABE INHALES]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
Yeah.
Your family first.
And then all you fuckin' dogs.
[SPITS]
I ain't playing.
Go ahead.
FRANKIE: Go ahead what?
- Make the fuckin' call.
I ain't fuckin' playing, dog.
Make the fuckin' call, man.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
- [LINE RINGING]
- [THUNDER CRASHES]
Put it on speaker.
[SETS DOWN PHONE]
MAN: [ON SPEAKERPHONE]
Boss, are we red or green?
Yeah...I reckon green.
We good to go?
Don't hang up.
Yeah, everything's rosy.
- Are we good to go?
- Fuckin' green's good to go!
Yeah, we're good to go.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[MEN BREATHING SHAKILY]
MAN: [ON SPEAKERPHONE]
Boss, it's weird.
What? What's weird?
The joint. It's...
The joint's fuckin' what?
It's fuckin' empty.
What the fuck you mean
it's fuckin' empty?
As in there's no furniture,
no people, no nothing.
What do you mean,
there's no-one there?
It's like nobody
fuckin' lives here.
It's just a box.
Yeah, like a shoebox.
What's in the box?
[LOUD WHOOSHING OVER PHONE]
- [PHONE BEEPS RAPIDLY]
- Fuck.
Oi!
Fuck you.
Boom.
Come on, man.
A fuckin' game? You're fuckin'
kidding me, right?
I said, you're fucking
BEN: I wish he was.
I'm intrigued, Benny.
What happened next?
ABE: You threatened
my family, cunt.
My family.
That's what you said.
I was playing, man.
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Well, Frank, I guess that
didn't go as planned,
but shit happens.
But I am a man of my word.
Like I said...
..the winner lives...
..and the loser dies.
Fuck you, man.
Give me a fuckin' drink.
- [BOTTLES CLINK]
- Give me a fuckin' drink.
Fuck, man.
I said, get me a fuckin' drink!
Fuck!
[LIQUID POURING]
Thanks, Benny.
FRANKIE: Just fuckin'
leave the bottle.
I said
fuckin' leave the bottle.
BEN: OK.
FRANKIE: Alright?
[POURS DRINK]
[SETS DOWN GLASS]
[EXHALES]
Winner lives, loser dies.
- You got this, man.
- Fuck off.
[TENSE EDGY MUSIC]
[POURS DRINKS]
[SETS DOWN BOTTLE]
OK.
[THUMBS CIGARETTE PACKET]
[TAPS CIGARETTE]
Frankie.
Fuck.
You're good, Frankie.
You are good.
Aren't ya?
Hmm?
OK.
BEN: This was the moment
I knew 100%
he was off his meds.
Fuck.
KANE: You're going to lose.
You always lose.
[FRENETIC WHISPERING]
VOICE 1: Don't fuck the king.
VOICE 2: You always lose.
ABE: You can't lose.
You've never lost.
Checkmate.
Fuck yeah!
South-side!
Ah-ha, bitch!
Fuck yeah!
In your motherfuckin' face.
Frankie won the game.
Frankie won the game?
Yeah, he fuckin' won,
fair and square.
It was a helluva game.
Helluva game.
BEN: It was also
the tipping point,
pushing Abe over the edge.
Suck on that!
KANE: Come on.
You've lost everything.
ABE: I've never lost.
KANE: There's nothing left.
- Fuck yeah!
KANE: Kill them all.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa...!
- [GUNSHOT]
BEN: Ah, fuck me.
What happened?
Abe shot Tony.
Abe shot Tony T?
Ah...
He just...
..pulled the gun on him and...
..shot him in the head.
FRANKIE: Agh! Agh! I won, Abe!
You said you were a fuckin'
man of your word, ya dog!
Poor old Tony.
Eye for an eye
for an eye, cunt!
Frankie,
today's a good day to die.
You see, we are all monsters.
Parasites. Pariahs.
Leeches on society.
We prey on the innocent,
the weak, the vulnerable.
You, me, Tony,
Stan here, Benny boy, Winks,
even fuckin' Joe
behind the bar.
We are all monsters.
Stan...
..how many people
have you fucked up?
How many fuckin' people?!
I don't know, boss. A few!
ABE: Frankie, how many people
had Tony fucked up?
Dunno?
And you, Frankie.
How many lives
have you fucked up directly
or indirectly?
Huh?
How many?
FRANKIE: I dunno.
You don't know.
Well, I'd say a lot. Agreed?
Probably not from
your hand personally
because you're sort of
a gutless fuckin' snake, right?
Benny.
We're all monsters.
But the thing is, I'm the
biggest monster of them all.
And you know why?
Because I know who
and what I am
and what I need to become.
A fuckin' monster!
FRANKIE: God!
[FRANKIE HOLLERS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BODY THUMPS]
[FRANKIE SHOUTS]
[FRANKIE HOLLERS, PANTS]
Fuck you!
Agh! Agh!
[SHUDDERS]
BEN: It was like the switch
in his head had flicked.
[FRANKIE GROANS]
Agh! Urgh!
BEN: And just like that,
Abe was gone.
And what was left -
his psychopath, his monster.
[FRANKIE YELLS]
Today's a good day to die,
Frank.
[MUFFLED GROANING]
Shh.
[SHELL CASING CLINKS ON FLOOR]
BEN: I'd never met
any of Abe's personalities,
but I knew exactly
who this was.
Kane.
We're all monsters, Benny boy.
The difference is...
[POURS DRINK]
..I know what a monster I am.
[SETS DOWN BOTTLE]
Do you, Benny?
Hey?
Do ya, kid?
I'm confused.
What...what's goin' on?
BEN: That was
a fuckin' understatement.
Today...
..is a good day to die.
[SETS DOWN GLASS]
Stan here, he's a good soldier.
He's also a monster.
Like every other fuckin' dog
in this joint!
Don't fuck the king.
You, Benny boy...
..may be the only one in
this room who's not a monster.
You drive me around,
you tolerate our bullshit...
..but are you a monster
like us?
See, there comes a turning
point in everyone's lives...
..where you choose right
or wrong.
You choose good over evil
or evil over good.
I know which way I choose.
You grab that gun.
Grab the gun.
Grab the fuckin' gun!
I'll show you something.
He, um...
He made me
point the gun at him.
DETECTIVE 1: Did you?
I did.
He didn't give me a choice.
DETECTIVE 1:
Everyone's got a choice, Benny.
He didn't give me
a fuckin' choice.
DETECTIVE 1:
What happened next?
Today is a good day to die,
Benny.
Now, cock that gun.
Cock that gun
and point it at me.
Point it at me.
Right fuckin' now!
Good boy.
Now, you can die a martyr
or a monster.
The choice is yours.
Now, I will count to three.
And if you're the man
that I think you are...
..decision will be made
for both of us.
BEN: Come on.
- OK?
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
One...
..two...
[BODY THUDS]
[SOFT MENACING MUSIC]
[ROARS]
[SOMBRE GUITAR MUSIC]
[SOBS SOFTLY]
DETECTIVE 1: Come on, Benny,
there's blood and guts,
brain matter everywhere...
I killed him, mate.
I shot him.
I fuckin' killed him.
'Cause he didn't
give me a chance, did he?
It wasn't him.
It was someone else!
And he wasn't there!
And I shot him.
Something.
Not Abe! Not my mate!
Right?
He didn't give me...
[SNIFFLES, EXHALES HEAVILY]
BEN: I mean,
was any of it real?
It was all real to him.
Those personalities were
as real to him as you and I.
He couldn't
control them anymore.
Took him to places
so fuckin' dark.
Fucking arsehole.
[SHELL CASINGS CLINK ON GROUND]
Oh, my God.
BEN: Sometimes I guess you just
can't come back from that.
[TAPE REWINDING]
[GUNSHOTS]
Maybe sometimes
you just don't want to.
The real scary thing was...
..somewhere in all that
fucked-up mind, that insanity,
he knew exactly
what he was doing.
[ROARS]
BEN: He created it all.
It was all in his twisted mind.
We lived in his nightmare.
And we all went along
for the ride.
Something happened to Abe.
He went somewhere.
His fuckin' brain
just flicked off and...
..and he came back
as a different person.
He was out of his mind.
He starts fuckin' ranting
and raving
about how everyone's evil,
there's all this shit
wrong with society
and he's evil
and Frankie's evil
and we're all fuckin' evil.
[CONTINUES INAUDIBLY]
[SOMBRE GUITAR MUSIC]
BEN: The one thing
he was right about...
..is that we are all monsters.
But I was just his driver.
[TENSE INDUSTRIAL ROCK MUSIC]
[FRENETIC WHISPERING]
Captions produced by
Access Media Pty Ltd