The director is glaring, so let's move on.
This one is about
high school entrance exams.
From our listener, "Sleeping Lamb."
"DJ Naoto, good evening."
Good evening.
"I hate studying for entrance exams."
"I feel like dying."
Uh-oh. That's not good.
"It's not that I hate studying, it's…"
Masamune, do you know this one?
Hm? Not a clue.
Happy Turn's so good!
Hey, Senba, let me see that.
Hey, you've got powder on your fingers!
How tragic that you do not know happiness.
-I don't care about your happiness.
-Sorry, I know it doesn't matter…
If they can admit that it doesn't matter,
why'd they bother sending it to the radio?
Happy Turn!
Why did you fart under the blanket?!
-It stinks like the end of the world!
-You're rotten!
-My brain is rotten.
-It smells like pickles.
Oh, geez…
What is that?
The steel factory…
"There's nothing I want to do
and I don't care about the future."
"So why do I have to try so hard?"
"It feels like it's always dark
no matter how far I go."
At that moment, we knew.
Even without anyone explaining it to us.
For some reason, we knew.
That this place
was different from where we were before.
"If I do that, I think I can become
a better version of myself."
"If I get into high school…"
Masamune, are you going?
Hurry up, Masamune!
"I'll read one book a week
and even help my parents sometimes."
"So please let me pass the exams."
"Please, god!"
The sky is shattered!
Hey, that's…!
There's smoke
coming from the steel factory.
Is that really smoke?
The smoke is biting onto them…
The cracks…
are closing.
MABOROSHI
Ready, go!
Masamune Kikuiri, age 14.
He's out. He's unconscious.
Masamune, hey, hey, hey!
He made such a weird sound.
Masamune, how was it?
I saw it.
Masamune Kikuiri has long hair.
Stop it!
Sasakura, stop getting horny
just like that.
I can't help it,
Masamune looks like a girl from behind.
You're the one who's chubby and has boobs.
Oh, erotic!
I don't really mind
people saying I look like a girl.
It doesn't mean that I like boys.
I like girls,
but it's not like there's a girl I like.
But still…
Masamune, take a look.
It's Mutsumi Sagami.
I'm sorry!
Oh, they're just amazing.
The backs of their knees…
are so erotic.
That's a little too niche.
Many thanks for the compliment.
Stop talking like an old geezer.
She's an old bag too.
Masamune Kikuiri hates Mutsumi Sagami.
Those who haven't turned in
their Self-Monitoring Form,
make sure to finish it before the weekend.
Kikuiri, I'm talking about you.
But it's so boring.
Writing the same thing
over and over to avoid change.
Just write something and get it over with.
They don't read it anyway.
That's not true.
They got mad at me for
changing my dreams for the future.
What did you write?
"Mutsumi Sagami's boy toy!"
Of course.
What do you see in her? She's so plain.
I just love how she seems
quick to give in to pushy men.
Here's a push! And again!
That hurts!
-Another push!
-I said that hurts!
For some reason, whenever we hung out
we went out of our way to do things
that were difficult or painful.
-Want to go again?
-What?
Give me a break.
Again…
Masamune, hurry up.
I'm home.
Masamune, food's almost ready.
Hey. Welcome home.
Uncle, you came over?
Here's some ginger pork.
It doesn't have ginger in it though.
It's just garlic pork.
It looks the same.
It's close enough to the real thing.
Yeah, you got that right.
Tokimune, if you're coming over
you have to let me know in advance.
I only made two cups of rice.
It's alright,
I'm good as long as I have this.
I want to know everything!
"Want to know everything"?
That's right!
Grandpa, you left the water running
in the garden again.
Hmm.
Oh, geez!
All you men in this family…
SELF-MONITORING FORM
Masamune Kikuiri is…
Aren't you supposed to abstain
from alcohol and cigarettes?
That's unacceptable for
someone who works under gods.
The steel factory is
running on its own now.
All we do now is pretend to work.
We have a morning assembly
and then we do some checkups.
Maybe check where the smoke is going.
That's about it.
Were you drawing just now?
Want to draw illustrations
for the factory's monthly report?
No thanks. I'd feel awkward
if you go out of your way like that.
Come on, a child shouldn't worry about--
But I'm not a child.
Though I'll never be an adult.
That's the second time today…
It's getting more frequent.
That's horrible! Poor Sonobe!
-What happened?
-They were gone this morning.
Huh?
It was one of the boys, wasn't it?
-Hell no.
-Hey!
Don't put your butt on Hara's desk!
-What?
-That's horrible.
-Cheer up, Sonobe.
-I'll infuse my fart into it.
-You're the worst!
Sorry, you go ahead.
I knew it…
Pervert.
Give those back.
They're mine.
MUTSUMI SAGAMI
Thank goodness!
These are too big to walk in.
YUKO SONOBE
Sonobe?
Sonobe started it.
Sonobe stole my indoor shoes first.
And since my mine were gone,
I put on hers.
Huh? I don't understand.
So you guys take each other's shoes
back and forth?
It's like that passing-out game
that you guys play.
It's all out of boredom, isn't it?
Do you want me to
show you something that will…
blow away the boredom?
In this town,
there are signs of it everywhere.
Signs that
those without lives are breathing.
AUTO SNACK MIFUSE
Hey, wait up!
We can't go anywhere.
It all started…
on that night with that explosion.
The survey results are now available.
The tunnel is now impassable
due to the landslide.
And we cannot leave by sea
due to the ocean current.
Regarding this matter,
we'd like to hear from Mamoru Sagami,
an employee at Mifuse Steel Factory
who is from Mifuse Shrine's
hereditary Shinto priesthood.
Mr. Mayor, th-thank you…
Huh? Isn't that Mutsumi Sagami's dad?
What?
Mr. Akimune, I'm going up there now.
Yes, please do.
Mr. Sagami, please hurry.
Umm…
S-Since the age of
the Industrial Revolution,
we, the people of Mifuse,
h-have lived relying on the blessings of
the metals we obtained from Mt. Kanzari.
However, please consider this.
Mifuse Shrine
worships the mountain itself.
In other words, this town has been
chiseling at the god all this time.
That's right, I believe we are now…
being presented with divine punishment!
-I don't understand.
-We're getting a present?
Who is this?
Don't you know?
Sagami's only son
is famous for being eccentric.
How blissful ignorance truly is!
What you see there now
is no longer the same steel factory!
In the wake of the explosion,
it has changed!
It has changed into a machine of the gods,
a Sacred Machine!
And this Sacred Machine
has trapped us in Mifuse!
This is crazy!
What will we do if the grownups catch us?
Hey, do you hear a voice?
It wasn’t long after the speech by
Sagami’s dad that we would come to know…
We weren't just trapped in this place.
We had also been separated from
the seasons by this Sacred Machine.
DANGER
Masamune Kikuiri.
In a never-ending winter at 14 years old.
THE 5TH BLAST FURNACE
I was guided by the hand
of the person I hate, Mutsumi Sagami.
Hey, stop…
Guided to a girl in captivity.
Hey, wait a second!
Ugh, it stinks.
It’s a shocking stench, isn’t it?
But you weren't as surprised
as I thought you'd be.
I was too stunned to react.
So what's with that girl?
She kinda looks like you.
Stop it. That’s gross.
Then what is she?
What does she look like?
A monkey? A gorilla? Or a chimpanzee?
If I had to pick, I guess a wolf.
Is that good?
Yeah.
Anyway, they say
we can't let that girl outside.
So they put me in charge
of taking care of her.
Oh, did your dad put you up to this?
But with how big she is,
it's hard to get her to take a bath.
I wanted the help of a boy,
but that also comes with its own problems.
So I brought you here
because you're like a girl.
Huh?
You even liked it
when Sasakura felt up your chest.
I didn't like it!
Screw you!
It really doesn't suit you
when you talk all tough like that.
I'm going home!
Come by on Mondays, Wednesdays,
and Fridays, Masamune.
We're on a first-name basis?
You can call me Mutsumi too.
Huh?
Do you know what characters
are used to write my name?
"Mu" meaning "six"
and "tsumi" meaning "sins."
Don't make up dumb lies.
It was something like
"harmonious" and "reality."
Hmm, so you are interested in me.
A wolf.
The girl is not the wolf, I am.
The wolf girl who’s full of lies.
Masamune, come get your grandpa.
The disaster prevention meeting
starts at 8 o'clock!
Masamune?!
Yeah! Just wait a second!
Get in.
Masamune Kikuiri has a driver's license.
I can’t believe the only adult right
I have is being able to drive a car.
You can't do anything
in the countryside without a car.
But it's not like
we can do anything with it now.
My name is Soji Kikuiri.
I'm 74 years old.
I have no wife. I have no hobbies.
I do have back pain.
You can stay seated.
Umm… Hitoshi Tachibana.
-I'm 80… No, was it 90?
-Has he lost it?
No, that's how he's always been.
Listen.
When the world returns
to its original form
and you've changed from
your previous selves, there may be issues.
This is why we check to see if you have
changed from your previous selves.
If you do find that you've changed
even the slightest, we must correct it.
Masamune, do you listen to the radio?
No, it's always the same show,
and the guy that writes in is annoying.
You know how the DJ doesn’t reply
and puts on a song instead?
I kept listening to it over and over,
wondering what it meant.
And I found myself
wanting to become a DJ too.
I thought you preferred jobs
where you could be in the background.
Yeah.
I guess if none of this had happened,
I wouldn't have ever wanted to do it.
We're not allowed to change,
so on my Self-Monitoring Form,
I say I'll take over the family business.
That's the wife of Mr. Yamazaki.
She was so happy
she had finally gotten pregnant.
But all this happened
before the baby was born.
While the baby's still in her womb.
I'm sure she'll see her baby
when we all get out of here.
Yeah.
"Philosophical Secret Technique,
Energeia"? That's so bad.
Uncle even came to pick you up.
How long are you going to skip work?
You know, Energeia is a behavior
unique to humans.
It's when you disregard
how much time an action takes
and the action and purpose are
aligned to simply live in the moment.
You can't just keep running away.
I've always run away.
Back in the day,
I ran from university and dropped out.
I also ran away from your mom,
but she followed me to Mifuse.
Then we had you.
You make it sound bad.
I don't regret that.
It's been easy being with your mom
and you're an interesting guy, Masamune.
But…
it's impossible now.
I can't run away anymore.
Remember what that Sagami guy said?
If the anger of
the Sacred Machine subsides,
the world might go back to normal.
For the first time in a while…
my dad went to work the night shift.
And he never came home after that.
FAMILY: MOTHER, GRANDFATHER
SAFETY FIRST
Man, such a bummer.
It's literally hell
working under that guy.
He even said he knows
about the gods of Mifuse the most.
He used to be just some weird loser.
Hey, you're being summoned, Kikuiri.
Hey, over there!
THE 5TH BLAST FURNACE
5TH FURNACE
You want to eat this?
Eat!
So you can speak, huh?
Spea… Speak?
Hey, who are you?
Hm?
You look like Mutsumi Sagami.
Are you guys twins?
Mitsumi?
The girl who always comes
to look after you.
Girl! Tsumi!
Mitsumi!
Do you want a name too?
THE 5TH BLAST FURNACE
Like Itsumi?
Mitsu?
Mitsumi!
No, not that.
Itsumi!
I'm Masamune.
Masamine! Girl!
I'm a boy!
A boy!
Girl!
Hey, Itsumi!
Can I call her that?
A train?
Hey, Mitsumi!
Is this your playground?
Careful!
Hey! Where are you?
Hello?
We're on patrol.
Where did you go?
Wow, you've gotten so big again!
Look how she's grown!
Just look at her, almost complete.
A complete woman!
What? Is Mutsumi not here?
You can't come any closer.
It’ll be a problem
if you fall in love with me.
I guess Mutsumi has been
taking good care of you.
Mr. Sagami, can't we look for another way
instead of keeping her locked up here?
What?!
The Sacred Machine went through a lot
to call her here.
The girl destined to be
a woman of the gods!
As long as we have this girl,
we might one day be forgiven
by the Sacred Machine!
-And yet!
-What would my late brother think?
Mr. Akimune lost his ability
to make the correct decisions.
Such a waste,
even after I made him my right-hand man.
Mr. Sagami--
In this world…
you should do as I say.
Don't disappoint me, Tokimune.
What was that about?
Oh. Isn't this egg coffee? How nostalgic.
I had this often when I was a student.
Tastes great!
Did you and my mom
go to the same university?
Yeah, when Misato came to visit my dorm,
she met my brother.
I had unknowingly become Cupid.
Uncle, you working in
the 5th Blast Furnace…
Hm?
Are you going after my mom?
Is there anyone
who can take this to Sagami's house?
I'll go.
Oh, thanks Sonobe.
Should I go with you?
I don't have anything to do today.
No thanks.
Huh?
Did you know that unpopular girls
tend to hang out with the cute girls?
Hoping they can get some scraps.
He keeps barking and barking.
I brought my old books.
Spooky, spooky ghosts!
Ghosts…
SLEEPY SLEEPY GHOST
Are you cold?
You're so weird.
Here.
Oh, this is hand-knit.
Mitsumi gave to me!
No wonder I thought it looked weird.
I thought you hated Mutsumi Sagami.
You don't really talk when she's around.
Hey…
Don't you ever want to get out of here?
Though I guess even if you left…
you couldn't get much farther.
Sonobe?
Why are you here?
She wasn't home. She skipped class.
Huh?
That's Mutsumi's house.
Huh? Why?
The Sagami house is at Mifuse Shrine.
Mutsumi is a stepchild.
What?
Her mother died a little before
the world changed.
She's living by herself now.
Sonobe, you--
The Sagami family wanted an heir.
But that old man has no interest in women.
So the Sagami family chose my mom,
who already came with a child.
But in this world,
there's no longer a need for an heir.
So I was kicked out.
That's horrible, Mutsumi…
"Mutsumi"?
Huh?
You called her by her first name…
So you two really are a thing?
What do you mean?
Aw…
What did I even do wrong?
If you have a car, give her a ride.
It's your fault after all.
CEDAR INCENSE
Hey.
Y-You and the steel factory woman
are related, right?
We aren't related.
Liar.
It's not that I hate her.
It's just that whenever I'm with her…
I feel so anxious.
What?! A test of courage?
That's right,
I heard they haunt that place.
The Kanzari Tunnel.
The ghosts of the workers
who were killed by the smoke monsters.
Huh?
But if we go to the tunnel,
the adults will be angry.
We just won't get caught.
It sounds fun,
but hanging out with boys at night?
Everyone's going to tease us.
Whatever. I don't care if you come.
Huh?!
-Come on, man.
-I didn't mean it!
-The devil in me just took over.
-That's no excuse!
You are the real devil!
-Nitta, help me out with your powers.
-I… I think I'll go.
No way, Sonobe! Why?!
I thought you didn't like
this kind of thing.
If Sonobe's going, I will too.
Seriously?!
Now there's two girls.
Yay!
What? Yasumi?
Are you serious?
-It's perfectly creepy.
-I haven't been to the station in forever.
The tunnel is a dead end now
from the landslide.
Let's write something on the wall
once we get pretty far in.
Write something? That's too vague.
Something that proves we were there.
Alright, the first pair!
What?
Who's next?
It's wet here.
Should we do it here?
I can keep going.
But even if we keep going…
Okay, I'll write first.
Done.
YUKO / MASAMUNE
Who's Yuko?
Me.
You can't just write that.
Do you hate me?
Well, why do you--
I think I like you…
Why though?
I think I like you. You even let me sit
in the passenger seat the other night.
Wait, I don't think that's how
liking someone works.
So you do like Mutsumi…
Guys?
Um, Sasakura said that
he heard a weird sound.
Y-Yeah! We were worried
so we came to find you.
Huh?
Hey, what's this?
No, it's…
-A couple's umbrella?
-It's not!
Huh? You don't have to hide it.
Idiot! Stop it!
Why?
-Sonobe!
-Wait, Sonobe!
Sonobe!
The sky!
It's just like that day!
-Mutsumi.
-Huh?
We've played our games
to escape the boredom, right?
Games to make ourselves think
that we don't want to run away.
Right now, I…
I'm so embarrassed, I want to run away.
My feelings for someone…
have become a spectacle.
Huh?
Hey, that’s…
The smoke…
It looks like a wolf!
Get down, Sonobe!
Hey!
Sonobe!
-No way.
-This is crazy!
-What should we do?
-I don’t know.
What…
Sonobe…
What's the meaning of this?
Everyone, please don't panic
and calm down.
How can we be calm?!
They're saying she was eaten
by a wolf made of smoke.
Somebody explain!
Are you going to say
we're being punished--
Chomp!
Was she really eaten?
By a wolf with its mouth open like this?
I'm not sure.
It… kinda looked like
she disappeared as soon as she got hit.
That's it!
I'm sure you've all seen this before.
The smoke from the steel factory flies
right into the cracks throughout the sky.
That is the smoke wolf
created by the Sacred Machine.
The Sacred Wolf!
The Sacred… Wolf.
The Sacred Machine
tries to close all cracks in this world.
If you want to stay alive,
don't let your emotions overpower you.
There must have been something
that caused a crack in her soul.
Relax!
We all share a common destiny.
We all experience
the same pain in the same world.
That is why we must not even dream
of escaping this world.
Where's Masamune?
A large amount of smoke has appeared.
Please return to your homes immediately
and make sure your doors are shut.
Until we are able to confirm safety,
please avoid traveling outside…
What are you doing, Masamune?
Uncle…
Hurry up and come home.
All of your friends went home.
I don't want to!
Why do we have to stay locked up at home?
We're already locked up in Mifuse.
Calm down, Masamune.
No.
I don't want to be here.
I want to go to a city
with a big bookstore and a theater!
And I want to study a lot
and see a bunch of things.
I want to be an illustrator.
It's okay.
What's okay about this?!
I can't trust you, Uncle!
You knew all about Itsumi!
Itsumi?
Why? Dad knew about her too, right?
You guys locked Itsumi in that place
and you were both okay with it?!
Why won't you answer me?
Why won't you say anything?!
That child…
She shouldn't be here.
That's enough. Let's go.
I'll protect you on my brother's behalf.
You and…
everyone.
I didn't ask you to do that.
SHE SAID SHE LIKED ME
Masamune Kikuiri
was told by a girl that she liked him
for the first time.
SONOBE DISAPPEARED
IT WAS MY FAULT
IT’S ALL BECAUSE
I LIKE MUTSUMI SAGAMI
Did I wake you up? Sorry.
You smell, but somehow I feel at ease.
Do you understand?
The feeling of love?
Love?
I don't understand.
Sonobe said being in the passenger seat
made her fall in love.
I know it's not like that.
I know that much.
But, I'm also strange.
My feeling of love is so similar to hate.
It hurts and it just doesn't feel right.
Huh?
Why am I…
Masamine…
I'm sorry.
I…
Masamine.
Itsumi.
My heart wasn't pounding.
It just felt warm and nostalgic.
Love really is so warm.
But Sonobe didn't know.
She doesn't know either.
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
I guess you're male after all!
Wait…
What's "Itsumi"?! Her name?!
That's right!
I gave her that name
because she has one less sin than you!
Itsumi, come here.
I'll get you out of here.
Out of here?
I'll show you so many things!
Why are you crying?
What are you doing there?!
Masamune!
Itsumi, run!
Mutsumi, I'm sorry.
-Come with me!
-Wait there! Hey!
You dare bare your fangs at the gods?!
You are a sinner!
It’s a huge platform.
Why is there a train back at the furnace
when this platform is here?
That's because…
Itsumi…
What is this?
On the other side of the cracks…
is a different world.
Itsumi!
Itsumi, stop! It's dangerous!
Look!
Look! Look!
Masamune, where are you?!
Where is the woman of the gods?
-If I don't get her back, the world--
-No way!
You're…
Don't move, Masamune!
Why can't I move?!
Look!
They dare resist the gods?
I want to see too!
I want to see so many more things!
Look more! More!
Just maybe that girl can…
No… No!
You want to see more, right? Much more!
More! More!
More!
Itsumi, this is…
No…
Would you look at that?
Even that girl cannot leave
through the cracks.
She had me worried.
Oh, it's coming out!
Sacred Wolf!
Close the cracks of this world!
Uncle!
The place on the other side of the light.
-It's reality.
-Hey, shh!
H-Hey, Tokimune,
that's supposed to be a secret.
We can't hide it anymore.
We've been locked in Mifuse as punishment.
But someday,
we will be able to leave this place.
That was…
a lie we told you all
so you wouldn't lose hope.
It may have been a lie,
but it was a very small one.
To be precise, this world
is an anti-reality dimension
created by the Sacred Machine.
So it's not really a big difference--
It's a huge difference!
If this isn't reality then what are we?
Are we dead?
Are we made up?
Like, we're immaterial?
So Mifuse and all of us here are fake?
Sounds good to me.
Why did you keep quiet?!
-Explain everything!
-So we can't ever leave Mifuse?
Why does it matter
if this world is not reality?
As long as you don't get a crack
in your soul, it doesn’t matter at all!
Are we fake? Nay!
We are a fleeting illusion!
That is why our lives
can continue for eternity!
I don't need your eternity!
Huh?
I don't want to be stuck
in this town forever.
We can't ever grow up.
I can't take it!
Okay, I think we're done
listening to the boy's opinion.
The eternal existence of this world
is of utmost importance!
To accomplish this, that girl must be
returned to the Sacred Machine!
Not that again!
Let's stop this, Mr. Sagami.
Huh?
Even when we had her locked up,
the cracks continued to grow every year.
No matter how much
the Sacred Machine closes cracks,
the end of this world is near.
It will end?
-"End"?
-It's going to end?
-What does he mean?
-What happens when it ends?
-Wait a minute!
-Will we disappear?
-We're going to die?
-We aren't alive anyway.
Tokimune… What have you done…
We did what you said
because we had no idea
what this world was and we felt lost.
But, I ask everyone.
Do we need rules
that deceive an ending world?
That's a good point.
If it's going to end anyway,
there's no need to listen to Sagami.
-That's right!
-Let's just do what we want.
That doesn't make sense!
He's gone crazy! What?!
You're not making any sense!
Mr. Sagami.
You all don't care
what happens to this world?!
Is there nobody here
who can think straight?
Am I the only one making sense?
That's enough, old man.
Mutsumi.
Y-You…
This world may be an illusion,
but you need to get a grip on reality!
If the world is ending, let's eat!
I can't believe we followed that guy.
She sure has energy.
How was reality?
It looked like a ruin.
Because of the accident?
There must have been a lot of deaths.
If the steel factory is gone
then Mifuse must be done for.
Mifuse?
The truth is, everyone had already
realized what had happened.
Every time we hung out,
we always did things that hurt.
Because…
we never really felt pain.
As existence that cannot be erased.
Never feeling cold
while living in a winter.
While holding onto
all of these vague sensations,
we had come to realize early on…
We are all an illusion.
It's okay! You might as well go
and confess your feelings now.
But I…
It's not that easy.
I mean…
You said it'd be awkward
if you went to the same high school,
but you can no longer
go to the same high school.
You like him, right?
I do.
I do like him, but…
It hurts?
Love hurts?
It hurts, but how should I say…
It's a sweet pain.
Hara, I’m sorry, but that’s hilarious.
W-What's so funny?!
"Sweet"?
She means it hurts but it's also sweet.
It hurts but you like that,
don't you, Hara?
I'm going to shut you up forever!
Stop it!
Hey, the bus is coming!
You sure are close. Are you two a thing?
Huh?!
No, no. It's not me
that Hara has a crush on…
You sure have a lot of energy, Hara.
Of course!
If your name is called, come pick it up.
Aoyama!
Here.
-Ueda.
-Here.
There's no point in getting them back now.
-Let's burn it.
-Kikuiri.
Oh, here.
SELF-MONITORING FORM
You were able to
avoid turning them in after all.
I apologize.
Guess you were right this entire time.
Is there anything that is right…
in this world?
Senba?!
Hey, don't look!
You'll get a crack in your soul!
The gods must be testing us!
By creating this difficult situation,
the true heroes to lead the fools
of this land shall be revealed!
Nice! That's exactly right!
Yeah! Am I the hero? Amazing!
I’m trembling with excitement!
They sure are energetic.
Senba's dad's eyebrows
look exactly like Senba's.
Yeah.
Why do people have to go and disappear?
Senba had a dream…
A dream?
Damn it, I can't take it.
It's all a pile of shit.
That's enough. The wolf's going to come.
Are you sure it's okay?
Of course!
I'll look after her when you're at school.
It's so rare for Masamune
to ask for something.
Hey!
I'm so sorry, sir.
It's okay, she doesn't know any better.
Sweet… I like this!
Oh, that's good! Eat some more.
But it doesn't hurt.
Masamine!
-Look, look!
-Oh, my jacket.
It looks good on you.
I used the bath.
Okay.
Were there enough towels?
Yes.
What?
Look. It's done, Mutsumi.
My father and grandfather
will come riding on this.
It's kinda cute.
The evening paper came.
Originally, they said there might not be
fireworks at this year's Obon Festival.
They're running
the steel factory train too?
But I guess this will be the last time.
Right. It'll be the last time.
I'll make some coffee.
Don't!
You can see reality even indoors now…
The Sacred Wolf.
Why aren't you surprised?
The girl had a backpack on.
And there was a name tag.
Saki Kikuiri.
So Itsumi is our--
She's not my child.
But that woman was you!
That's the me in reality.
She's a completely different person
from the me in this world.
But when we were eating,
you acted like you were Itsumi’s mother…
If I were her mother,
I wouldn't have locked her up like that.
I wouldn't have let her suffer
for all of those years.
But that person
must have been a kind mother.
Even now…
she continues to wait
for her lost daughter.
But there's no way
for Itsumi to return to reality.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Really? That's unexpected.
I never realized.
I didn't plan on telling you.
But…
There's nothing left to be scared of.
I wanted to know how you felt, Nitta.
Why don't we date?
Really?
Really.
Does that mean you've liked me too?
Well, yeah, a little…
Hara, congratulations!
Kiss! Come on and kiss!
Love wins in the end!
Come on, you should have
gone home with Hara.
No.
I figured hanging out with
my pathetic friend would be more fun.
I think something is happening
between Masamune and Mutsumi, too.
I'm sure of it.
Yeah, definitely.
He's definitely touched her boobs.
MIFUSE
GAMES
AUTO SNACK MIFUSE
I turned on the heater.
We might be able to dry off.
That was my first time
seeing someone confess their feelings.
What?
I thought Hara was more confident.
She was shaking, kind of weak.
Hara is a girly girl.
On her Self-Monitoring Form,
she said she wanted to be
the wife of someone she loved.
What did you write?
A daycare worker.
You always lie about
things that don't matter.
It's better than mulling over
things that don't matter
and not writing anything at all, isn't it?
You could have at least written down
"art teacher" or something.
Since you're good at drawing.
How do you know I like to draw?
I don't know if you like it,
but I know you are good.
We’ve been in
the same class for years, you know?
I see…
Yeah, I’m sure of it now.
What is it?
I have feelings for you.
That's not fair.
You think because you have me in reality
that you can do the same with me here?
You've known, right?
That from the beginning, I've liked you.
You knew from the very start!
-That's why you used my feelings--
-I knew.
Mutsumi.
But I…
I don't like you.
Hey!
-Wait up!
-I'm not waiting!
You're such an idiot, Masamune!
Hey, I--
We are not the same people
that are in reality!
We aren't even alive!
None of this matters!
I-I'm sorry.
See?
I don't smell, right?
Because I'm an illusion.
It's the snow.
The smell is absorbed and disappears.
I don't smell because I'm not alive.
But I…
I can hear your heartbeat, it's fast.
That has nothing to do with being alive.
Then…
that means you do love me.
I don't.
Liar.
You're an idiot.
Being with Itsumi,
I feel like I finally have the answer
to why I've been feeling so hazy.
She tries to see everything
with her eyes wide open.
She is moved deeply
by everything she feels.
I realized that's what it means to live.
I learned that from Itsumi.
But,
you taught me what comes after.
Huh?
I get annoyed just looking at you.
I get interested in everything you say.
You get on my nerves
and then you excite me.
It's not just Itsumi.
I'm also really alive, even here.
When I'm with you, I feel it so strongly.
Your heartbeat is fast too, Masamune.
If we do this,
it'll beat even faster.
It's turning into rain.
It… It's summer…
I'm sorry.
I don't want to stop.
My chest might explode.
My heart…
feels so tight.
It hurts…
It hurts!
-Hurry up!
-Let's go!
The smoke…
It stopped.
So many cracks.
Nitta! Run!
It's not only in the sky?
What happened?
Itsumi!
Itsumi, why are you out here?
Left out!
I'm left out!
What are you saying Itsumi?
Calm down!
Emergency announcement.
The Sacred Wolf has stopped.
Please evacuate immediately.
Prepare for the evacuation!
If you are in the Momose Area
or the Ashina Area, please evacuate to…
After learning the truth,
many people wished to disappear.
The Sacred Machine worked incessantly
to close the cracks in our hearts.
It continued to produce the Sacred Wolf.
So we think
the blast furnace was overloaded.
Incorrect.
It's obviously because
you let the woman of the gods leave!
That's right!
You understand now, you fools?
What?!
There you go again, spouting nonsense.
Without the Sacred Wolf,
it won't be long until
reality floods in through the cracks.
Unfortunately, our world
has come to an end.
-Mr. Sagami!
What's his problem?
Masamune, can you come here?
We found this.
A notebook your dad left behind.
He kept writing in it
even after the event.
Dad's diary?
A landslide occurred at Mt. Kanzari.
The cracks are severe.
It’s the first time
since the day of the explosion.
Since I worked the night shift that day,
I must have died in reality.
We found a small girl
on the freight train.
She had a unique odor.
This girl rode in
on the train from reality.
If the machine that carves
the god mountain is a sacred machine,
then so must be
the machine that carries it.
So if she rides on the train,
Itsumi can go home?
I don't know.
The laws of physics are
different in reality and in this world.
We had no idea what effect it might have
for a girl from reality
to exist in an immaterial illusion.
Return that girl to reality?
Yes, for example, if she gets older
and begins to lose control of her feelings
it's possible it could affect this world.
Itsumi's feelings
have an effect on this world?
Yes, that's what your father told me.
But Sagami…
I was thinking the same thing,
Mr. Akimune!
The girl chosen by the gods
must not lose control of her feelings.
How impure that would be!
So then, we should lock her
in the Sacred Machine.
It's to protect this world!
A philosopher once said,
"Hope is a dream
seen by those who are awake."
Saki Kikuiri.
It's ironic.
It was because of this world
that I was able to meet her.
She was born after I died
and brought hope to my family.
My granddaughter.
So he knew.
In a hopeless world
that continues at her expense,
Masamune is drawing yet again today.
No matter how good he gets at drawing,
he will never be an adult.
It will never lead him to his future.
But…
Stop it!
…he's getting better and better.
Even in this abnormal world,
people can change as much as they want.
That's what I think
when I look at Masamune.
Yeah…
That's right.
I…
I've gotten good.
Even if I get good at drawing,
it doesn't mean I can leave this place.
Even if none of this matters…
I've gotten better
after drawing every day.
I'm really happy.
That I got better and got praised for it.
It doesn't matter
that it won't lead to a future.
It's been fun and exciting.
I've been alive here.
Despite this,
we stole that child's chance to change.
I want to change, just like Masamune.
But it just wasn't possible for me.
Masamune.
I want you to forgive your father.
There's no forgiving or not forgiving.
I'm just happy to be praised by him.
Uncle, I want to take her back.
I want to take back Itsumi to reality.
Masamune.
Phew! Masamune, take care of Grandpa!
Alright, now for us…
What is it?
You see…
There's something I want to tell you.
Is that okay?
No, I don't want to hear it.
If everything is going to end,
I want it to end while being a good mom.
I see it's Obon there.
The Obon Festival was always fun.
There were tons of fireworks
and food stalls.
Yakisoba, candied apples…
I don't think
this world was created as a punishment.
Grandpa?
I'm here with you.
The gods of Mifuse
must have known this land would end
with the explosion of the factory.
So they must have wanted to preserve
the best days we ever had.
When everyone praised the town.
The happiest of times.
I ask for your understanding.
Just like in reality,
we can operate the factory.
Then we can
create the Sacred Wolf ourselves.
-You said the world was ending anyway!
-There's no point in struggling.
You're right!
It may be pointless
even if we make the Sacred Wolf appear.
Even so,
if we had one more year or half a year…
No, if this world can continue
even for just one more day…
we won't give up!
-That's what I'm talking about!
-Good job, Kikuiri! You've got guts!
Are you serious?!
You said you'd wait until Itsumi escaped!
-Sorry, but I am serious.
-Huh?
Just as you want to save that girl,
there's someone I want to save.
I don't plan on letting Misato end
as a good mom.
What the hell is his problem?
The cracks in the tunnel should be
connected to the outside of Mifuse.
If we can get her there
on the train from reality…
Who's going to be driving it?
Well…
We just have to give it a shot!
Before that lovesick geezer
revives the Sacred Wolf!
Lovesick?
Itsumi!
I said stop it!
Itsumi's not going!
Wait, she doesn't want to
go back to reality?
Of course she doesn't.
I bet she doesn't even remember
what it was like.
Hey, if she doesn't want to go
wouldn't it be better to not force her?
Hey, this world is coming to an end.
Man, she's just like an animal.
We have a chance to save Itsumi.
But it might speed up
the end of this world, you know?
That's too ominous!
It's not impossible.
Stop it.
Just when things are going well…
Mutsumi.
What do you…
Hey, Mutsumi!
Hey!
Don't get cocky just because we kissed.
Itsumi saw us.
Huh?
It makes sense
why the cracks suddenly grew.
They had me looking after Itsumi
because the woman of the gods
must not fall in love with a boy.
But Itsumi fell in love with you.
Hey, Masamune! It's Itsumi!
Will it be okay using raw fuel
for the first time after 10 years?
Don't worry, it'll work.
I forgot how this feels.
Mr. Kikuiri.
Sagami is doing something weird
at the 5th Blast Furnace.
Leave him be.
Are you sure?
Sagami is amazing.
From the very beginning,
he just wanted to have fun in this world.
That's right.
We all could have changed our future with
a single thought, anywhere at any time.
We were just too late to realize.
Let's do it.
We are undeserving to utter your name
Great god of Izanagi
-Where's Itsumi?
-She's not here.
In Tsukushi near Himuka-no-Tachibana…
There's a staircase ahead.
She might be up there.
She's beautiful.
We've come for you, Itsumi!
It was really a hassle.
She didn't want to take off
that dirty jacket.
But she is the one
who chose to remain here.
Why are you trying to interfere when she
is willingly becoming a woman of the gods?
You know nothing! Itsumi is--
Itsumi stays here!
She's quite beautiful.
Your mother must have been
beautiful as well.
However…
like you, she has those eyes
that seem to mock me.
Not that it matters now.
I've never heard Mom
say anything bad about you.
Th-That doesn't matter either.
Why the hell was my dad
friends with this guy?
"Friends"?
D-Did Mr. Akimune
really say that about me?
It doesn't matter now, right?
That does matter!
Let's go!
No!
Answer me!
Hurry up and chase them!
No! I won't go!
Itsumi doesn't want to!
I don't want to!
Itsumi, calm down.
Why is the train here?
Wait, it's dangerous!
Grandpa?!
Man, that's so reckless!
She's just assertive.
No, she's a crazy driver.
Alright, let's take this
all the way to the tunnel.
I-I'm sorry!
What happened?
Kikuiri!
Get Itsumi in here!
Masamune! Don't trust Hara!
They took Itsumi…
You drive so aggressively!
Shut up, I'm sorry!
Itsumi!
Love hurts, but the meaning is different.
Love is the feeling of
wanting to be with a person
today and tomorrow,
and even when you become an old grandma!
Kikuiri and the others are here!
-Go faster!
-Hey wait!
-Go faster! More, more!
-Itsumi!
I'm sorry about her.
Nitta, call out to the criminal.
Okay!
Hara, please reconsider!
No!
Itsumi, Itsumi!
What's that?
Is that festival music?
Reality is just on the other side.
I'm starting to get pumped!
Get away, you pervert!
Get back, pervert!
Not you, Nitta!
Shut up, you…
Wh-What do I do?
Nitta! No, no, no!
Don't die!
Gotcha!
Turns out you still have a heart!
You tricked me.
If you do not return the woman of the gods
there will be divine punishment!
It's Sagami!
The more you resist,
the more your spirit will be cursed
leading to your ultimate destruction!
Ah, the gods are angry!
We're out of time!
She's going to disappear along with us.
We can't let that happen.
She's our daughter!
She isn't though.
Huh?
Don't rush it.
Damn it! Push the car!
Mutsumi!
I see… That's right.
We can laugh and we can cry.
Even in this world,
we could have been as free as we wanted.
But, it's different for us in reality.
Please! I want this!
Mama!
Look at this!
I want this!
Don't touch it, it's for sale.
I won't move until you buy me it.
Okay, then go ahead.
We're going to go now. Let's go, Masamune.
Are you sure?
It's okay.
She'll give up and come after us.
Saki?
Excuse me, did you see
a girl that was just there?
She's five and she…
Here's your change.
They can go anywhere they want…
but they're stuck with feelings
that can't go anywhere.
It's not that I want to free just Itsumi!
I also want to free us in reality.
"Us"?
If you fully enter reality,
you'll disappear.
It's no use Mr. Kikuiri!
-It's all over!
-It's not over!
It's not over. It can't be over!
The Sacred Wolf!
Stop!
Our prayers have been answered!
Alright, get in!
The Sacred Wolf is back.
We have to return Itsumi
before the tunnel closes.
Back to reality.
-A commemorative train will be arriving.
-Um, excuse me.
Could you take our picture?
Sure.
That's right! The train from reality!
If we get her on that train…
How?
It's on the other side.
I'll figure it out.
We're in the crack!
At this rate, we'll disappear!
I know!
But the only way to
get her on that train was to dive in.
From our listener, "Sleeping Lamb."
-What?
-"DJ Naoto, good evening."
Senba liked this program.
"I hate studying for entrance exams."
"I feel like dying."
Really? If that's the case, then die!
Die!
Hey, don't say that!
You don't even know what it means to die.
Don't make light of it!
We don't know what it means either!
And I don't want to know!
"I don't like feeling I've nowhere to go."
If you look, you'll find somewhere.
"It feels like it's always dark
no matter how far I go."
There are shining lights if you look!
"A new environment might help me find
what I want to become."
"Then, I think I can become
a better version of myself."
"If I get into high school,
I'll dye my hair and go on a diet."
You can change even if you don't!
"I'll get a part-time job."
"I'll read one book a week
and even help my parents sometimes."
"So please let me pass the exams."
"Please, god!"
What happened?
I thought a car flew onto the tracks.
What? We're on the overpass,
is that even possible?
No, I don't want to.
Please Itsumi, we have to--
I'm not going!
Itsumi isn't going. Staying here.
I'm staying with Masamune and Mutsumi.
Itsumi…
When we first met…
Back then…
I thought I shouldn't get too close.
Hey!
If I got close…
I knew…
I'd start to love.
So you can say "Mutsumi" now?
I'll be with you, Itsumi.
Let's go together.
Let's go. You get on first.
Wait, if you go together, you'll…
Mutsumi!
I'm coming too.
No, wait!
Masamune…
No! I don't want things to end like this!
Meeting the both of you…
has been so much fun.
Masamune!
Come down here!
Obon Festival fireworks.
I guess you can't see
the Sacred Wolf from this side.
And soon, I'll also be…
Get off. Mutsumi needs to get off.
A peppermint pipe?
I know what that is.
I used to like these.
The Obon Festival is fun.
You wear a yukata and you dance.
And there are so many shops.
But in my world, it's always winter.
Obon will never come.
Huh?
Hey, Itsumi.
It's not only Obon
that's waiting at the end of the tunnel.
There will be lots of different things.
Fun things, difficult things, sad things…
Things that are strong,
intense, and moving.
You can make friends.
You can even have dreams.
You might even get frustrated.
But if you get depressed
and you feel like it's all over,
you can always find a new dream.
I'm so jealous.
These are all things I will never have.
That's why I want you
to give me just one thing.
Look.
I'm taking Masamune's heart.
Huh?
The future is yours,
but Masamune's heart is mine.
Even if I disappear in reality,
I'll be the one Masamune thinks of
at the moment this world ends.
No!
And I'll also be thinking of
Masamune in that final moment.
No, no!
Masamune loves me
and I also love Masamune.
I'm left behind!
That's right.
But…
there are people waiting for you.
People who will think of you all the time.
I hate you.
That's why I won't go with you.
I hate you!
Yeah…
We're almost at the tunnel!
The Sacred Wolf is swarming!
Hey, that's…
Mutsumi!
Masamune Kikuiri knew.
Ow…
What were you thinking?! You're bleeding!
Masamune! This is amazing!
It really hurts!
It's because you're here, Masamune.
I can feel it in the cells in my body
that I am alive.
I don't care if this world ends today.
It doesn't matter
how much time we have left.
Right now, I am alive.
Mutsumi.
Itsumi.
Did we make it?
CLOSED
Alright, she made it!
Ow!
It hurts?
Don't copy Itsumi.
We are alive.
Go on your way, Itsumi.
Go and see the things we can't.
Go and smell every new smell.
You two, stop being so lovey-dovey!
As for us,
we don't know how long we have here.
MASAMUNE KIKUIRI WILL LIVE
ALONGSIDE MUTSUMI SAGAMI
Do you hear that?
What is it?
I can hear a voice.
It's a voice like… a newborn baby.
It hurts.
It hurts…
It hurts!
Hello? Yeah. I arrived at Mifuse.
I was asleep since there was nobody else.
Yes, I know.
You're always worrying.
I told you it'll be okay.
The taxi is here. Tell mom I said hi.
Bye.
RESERVED
Please take me to the steel factory.
It's been a while
since I took someone to the factory.
A while ago there were a number of people
who liked looking at ruins.
But now, it's almost all demolished.
Here's a candy for you.
Oh, thank you.
It is creepy to just leave it though.
A long time ago, there were
talks of people being spirited away.
Just rumors though.
Ah, I see.
MIFUSE STEEL FACTORY RUINS
THANK YOU
WE WON'T FORGET
GOODBYE MIFUSE STEEL FACTORY
This is where it happened.
My first…
heartbreak.