What is the meaning of happiness?
What is the meaning of life?
What is the point of a love lost?
What is fate if you can't change destiny?
The darkness that lingers on.
A bloodline lost.
Now I'm left all alone,
a witness in the darkness.
The evil that embraces… Will it ever end?
TWO DAYS AGO…
Tonight…
it's a fight to the death for you.
You don't have a choice.
You have to prove you are the best
and that there's no one better.
Know this, you will not be
remembered if you lose.
Greetings! It's time.
- Armand! Armand!
- Come on!
What are you waiting for?
- Armand! Armand!
- See? He can't even hear you.
Who cares?
What do you care? Why don't you go
sit over there and leave us alone?
They're fighters, I'm a lover.
I have to look after the two of you.
You're being a bit too much right now.
Well… don't be too proud.
All right, go home and get some rest.
Go take care of that girl over there.
All right, then.
So, you're the one who knocked out
the other guy, huh?
But this doesn't mean anything.
Why didn't you end the fight quickly?
That's just not my style.
I prefer a good brawl.
I want my battle scars.
I'm not into clinching.
Now, it would be different if I…
If you were to hug me, huh?
Well, the view from here isn't so bad.
Maybe you can say, "I love you too."
But I think how I feel
is more important than what I say.
I still love you, you know.
You have to be so sickly sweet, don't you?
I swear I'm about to throw up.
You don't like it when guys act all sweet?
Let's just go home. It stinks here.
It stinks! Let's go. It stinks.
What was that all about? Sore loser.
- Did he need something?
- Come on, let's get going.
What does he want?
He's lucky they sent you instead of me.
- What else do you want, Nyi?
- Did you forget?
Are you senile?
Old man.
- The time has come for me to take Roxana.
- You have no right to come here…
and touch what's mine.
The moment you retired…
the covenant between our worlds
was broken.
I must destroy you and your progeny.
Oh God!
- Why do you keep sighing?
- I'm bored.
I've asked you repeatedly,
where are we going?
You keep saying,
"I'll tell you in a minute."
I'll tell you in a minute.
But you ought to stop sighing.
It's not doing your plump figure
any favors.
Damn you!
Just follow my lead, Mir.
I know how we can get some gold.
How?
Well, first,
we have to find us a dead body.
- A corpse?
- A corpse.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I am.
Have you lost your mind?
You know what,
I've always done what you asked.
It's time for you to return the favor.
Do you want anything?
- No, thanks.
- How about you?
Let's go.
We rarely get the chance to go out
just the two of us.
What brought that up?
Those two rascals
are always tagging along.
You know what,
those two rascals are like our bodyguards.
Okay.
How about we go on a dinner date?
Dinner in KL.
Dinner? In KL?
Why? Is there a ring in the picture?
Why so special all of a sudden?
And a ring? That's such a western thing.
We don't have to do as they do.
You're right.
Today isn't special?
Not just screaming,
how does it go, "Adrian!"
- Hey!
- What?
Don't make fun of that scene, okay?
Hold on, I have to go to the bathroom.
Is that all?
- I need a bag, please.
- No problem.
Is that really your name?
What do you think?
I think your name is Russell.
I think you think my name is Russel.
That's too deep for me.
I've got that loving feeling, hey!
See that girl in the distance,
I wonder if this is enough.
Yes, I'd like to make a reservation.
- Yus!
- Yes?
- What's that ugly thing?
- What? Where?
Hurry, Zayton!
Where are you going?
He always has to play the hero.
Why not take the car? Come on, let's go!
Is this really where we're supposed to go?
According to this app,
this is where Armand is.
Who in their right minds
would come to such a place?
Never mind. Let's just go in.
You just wait there, okay?
I'll feed you later.
Don't be scared!
I just want to play with you.
Wow! You have such beautiful eyes!
Where's my toy?
Did you take my toy?
You stole it, didn't you? You're a thief.
Where is it? Where is my toy?
Be careful, Zayton, be careful.
It's so dark.
- Be quiet!
- It's too dark.
Listen!
Rose is somewhere over there.
I'm going to sneak in.
The two of you stay here.
Armand! Idiot!
Where's my toy?
Where's my toy? Where is it?
Who's that?
Why don't you come on in?
I forgot to put the phone on silent!
- Don't be mad!
- Yus! Zayton! Hurry up and untie me!
Get inside, Zayton. Hurry!
What is this place?
What is that godawful smell?
- Oh, my God! There's a dead body!
- Hurry! Hurry!
What kind of road is this?
- Turn left! Left!
- Now you tell me!
I said left!
- Do you know how to drive?
- Hey!
- Are you even paying attention?
- That burns!
Where are we?
I don't think I've been here before.
If you're that horny,
go find yourself a hooker!
Hookers?
Where's the thrill in that?
I thought we were getting closer.
- Nothing! Still nothing!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Where do I go? Turn right!
- Turn right!
Armand! That's Armand right there.
Oh, my… He beat that guy to a pulp.
Rose, get in the car!
Get in the car!
Where are we going?
Let's go!
Scoot over.
I can't see out the rear window!
Hurry, Yus.
What the…
What are we going to do?
We have to call the police.
- Let's go.
- Rose. Rose.
I just beat him up.
Rose, Rose, Rose. Hear me out.
We need to lay low. Forget the police.
All right. Okay.
We'll go to my house, okay?
We'll go to my house
- Okay. You killed someone.
- I just killed someone.
I killed him!
- Zayton, get in.
- Let's go.
Yus, get in. I'll drive.
Get in. Zayton?
It was an accident.
I didn't mean to hit him.
A YEAR AGO
You can't protect Roxana forever,
Haji Ramli.
Don't you dare say my name!
I am Tuan Haji Ramli, son of Haji Putih,
General of Sulur Prahanga.
Humans are weak.
If not for that machete in your hand,
you would've died a gruesome death.
It's okay.
Tonight, there will be bloodshed.
Fate will determine…
who will come out on top.
Don't you dare come back here again!
Where on earth
are we going to find a corpse?
We've looked everywhere!
My pants are wet
and I need a shower. It's a mess!
Patience, Mir. Are you hungry?
- Of course.
- Come on, I'll buy you breakfast.
- All right, let's go.
- Where to?
You're buying, so it's your call.
Anywhere will do.
Somewhere with plenty of eye candy.
Nice.
Oh, no, my pants!
- Oh god!
- You-- Well, hurry up!
You're such a lousy driver.
Waiter!
Coffee, black. And French toast, please.
Same for me, with extra eggs. Soft-boiled.
Waiter?
- What's going on?
- That ruckus? They found a dead body.
A corpse? I see…
- A corpse!
This is our chance!
Let's grab the body
before a crowd appears.
- I'll get the car.
- All right, I'll take care of the rest.
What happened?
Who did this to you?
I told you, choose your friends carefully!
Jeffrey! I'll take you to the hospital.
What? I'm too late?
- I'm sorry, my friend.
- Coming through!
Oh, my God! Kassim! Oh, my God! Kassim!
Kassim! What happened?
Who did this to you?
This isn't Kassim.
This is his identical twin, Jeffrey.
What? Kassim has a twin?
Enough of that, let's put him in the car.
Guys, please.
Can you help us get him in the car?
My friend here can't lift.
Let's do this together, all right?
Grab him right here, will you?
Yes, right here.
Right here. Okay. Ready? One, two, lift!
Very good. Over here. All right.
Here you go, have some.
Eat.
Let's eat.
Are you okay, Rose?
Why did you have to go
and remind me? I'm fine.
- I was just wondering.
- Babe, that's what we're supposed to do.
The dead guy must be mad at us.
- You drove right over him!
- Your grandpa can hear us!
I've lost my appetite.
Zayton, are you okay?
Let me through, please!
Let me through.
This punk with his feet
sticking out the window…
Slow down!
Hold your horses!
Relax, bro! What are you so mad about?
You know what
we're supposed to be doing today, right?
Oh, man, I totally forgot!
Mind if I take a raincheck?
- Now is not a good time.
- That's unacceptable.
If you want my business,
don't waste my time.
That's enough. Let's get going.
Where's Armand?
Cut it out!
- Armand? Armand?
- Roxana! Armand wants to go work out!
- Come on, man! Quit yelling.
- Are you mad, bro?
Come on, let's go.
For a measly pot of gold,
you're willing to go pretty far.
Why are you still complaining?
When it's your plan,
I always just go along with it.
When it's my plan,
something's always the matter.
Well, you know what?
For my entire life, I have never
had to go looking for a dead body!
Is that the witch doctor?
No wonder you're so eager.
That's not a witch doctor,
that's a model.
Cut it out, man.
She's been waiting for a while.
You want her to put a curse on you?
You're getting a little thin on top.
You should ask her for a potion for that.
Hey, Nap!
Don't make fun of my hair.
It's a sensitive subject.
At least I can reach the top shelf,
unlike you.
You want to flirt with the witch doctor,
don't you?
Says who? And so what?
You think you stand a chance?
Just you wait.
That's enough of that, it's about to rain.
You turn me on
Hey, Nap.
What are we going to do?
This guy is way too heavy.
Why are we doing this right now
in this godforsaken heat?
Why can't we do it at night,
when it's nice and cool?
- But no, we have to do this now!
- Come on, bro. Stop complaining.
Guys, look! A Beretta!
- What on earth? What's wrong with you?
- Here, take it.
- Are you trying to start a war?
- Why did you hand it to me?
- Why did you drop it?
- You want me to hold it?
Calm down! It's just a gun.
Better to have it and not need it.
Those guys are crazy.
Like…
I am going to explode! You see this?
It's about to explode in your face!
A gangster wannabe
who can't do it on his own.
He had to drag us along.
He had to bring Armand.
Why did you kill him?
Are you crazy?
Oh, my God!
- Why would you do something like that?
- It's not funny!
- You guys are boring.
You guys are boring.
What do you plan to do with this body?
Where's the gold you promised?
What? This isn't gold.
What the hell!
I'm sorry.
This is for filling up my tummy,
not my coffers.
Take this to Pak Walok.
Tell him it's from me.
You'll get what you want.
I see. All right, then.
I think it's time for us to go.
Hey, Nap. What's the hurry?
Are you trying to get between us?
Why don't you just stay for a bit?
Don't you want to wait for him to awaken?
I'll make you some food.
Deal?
Hello? Armand?
Where are you?
Hold on, babe.
Hurry! What's that over there?
Hey, how do I look?
I think my hair is all messed up.
Must be from last night.
You should come with me
when I go get it repaired.
Pak Walok.
I've done what you asked.
Now fulfill your promise.
Good.
Hey?
Stop messing around.
Hey!
Oh, shit!
Just kidding.
Little brother!
Great, we have a wannabe comedian here.
Give it to him.
Hey!
- You think this is Compton?
- Come on, Sosa, let's just go.
No, there's something's wrong
with that guy.
Hey, we've finished the deal.
No need to act all macho. Let's just go!
- Great! Just great! Sosa, come here!
- Who's that lady over there?
How long have you been sitting there?
I've been waiting for a while.
You just now combed your hair, right?
Now, why don't you do mine?
Me?
Why are you being so affectionate
right now? You're embarrassing me.
You were trying to scare me, weren't you?
Okay, and now?
You want your hair up or down?
Either is fine.
Run!
Four maidens sit by the river
Trying to trap the crab on the rock
Keep singing!
I think I got him!
But wait, isn't that the guy
I drove over last night?
- He's still alive?
- Let's get out of here!
What are you saying?
Grandpa!
You impudent demon!
I couldn't find you earlier.
Where were you?
I was upstairs.
Roxana,
find Ustaz Asri in here and call him.
Call the number below as well.
Don't forget the rope.
You've crossed the line, Nyi.
So young.
Nowadays, even the young can be an ustaz.
Oh, no, this is bad.
How do you know?
No one who's been possessed,
has ever called me "sexy."
There is no god worthy of worship
except Him, Ever-Living, All-Sustaining.
Neither drowsiness
nor sleep overtakes Him.
To Him belongs whatever is in
the heavens and whatever is on the earth.
Who could possibly intercede
without His permission?
He fully knows what is ahead
and what is behind,
but no one can grasp His knowledge,
except what He wills them to know.
His seat encompasses
the heavens and the earth.
The preservation of neither tires Him.
For He is Most High, the Greatest.
Roxana, where's the water bottle?
- Zayton has been possessed.
- She's been possessed?
Mand, floor it! Mand, floor it!
In the name of Allah.
Oh, Devil! I remind you of your oath!
Oh, Devil! I remind you of--
[chanting]
Blood debts are paid in blood!
Descendant of murderers!
What else could go wrong today?
Faster, Mand.
Mand, what is that? What is it?
- It's that lady again!
- Watch out!
Now you're just asking for it!
So you're going to play rough, huh?
I need to change my strategy.
Peace be upon you. What is your name?
God, I saw my life flash before my eyes.
Thank God this car is built like a tank.
Did you see what I saw?
I think I broke my bones.
It's that old lady
I was telling you about earlier.
What are we going to do?
- Come on, let's go.
- What about the car?
Great, now we have to walk.
What?
Now it's going to explode?
It's an old Saga, bro.
Makes you feel like an action hero,
doesn't it?
Just like Will Smith.
What happened?
I'll tell you later, okay?
- Ustaz?
- Yes?
- Is she okay?
- Who is she to you?
We're just friends, Ustaz.
- I see. So, that means she's single?
- Oh, my God.
- I'm just trying to help her.
- No way.
- I helped her.
- But you're a religious teacher.
- We have needs too.
- What about me? I don't have needs?
I think…
- I think I know who's behind this.
- Who?
- Who is it, Ustaz?
- I'm very sorry.
I have to go somewhere.
Make sure you use this properly.
- Peace be upon you.
- Likewise.
Likewise.
How can he hit on my girl just like that?
He took his hat and his shotgun,
but he forgot the bullets.
He's such a pain in the ass.
A pain?
And he raised me.
You don't care about your family.
- You don't appreciate your family.
- Guys, calm down.
We're all stressed out.
We'll find a solution.
Just one step at a time, okay?
Stay here and keep an eye on Zayton,
I'll go after Roxana.
Be careful.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'll see you later.
I didn't know
Pak Walok had such a beautiful house.
He must be filthy rich.
What do you want?
We need to see Pak Walok.
I'm also here to see Pak Walok.
Wait.
- I'll go first.
- What?
He's going to jump the queue
just like that?
- I ought to teach him a lesson.
- He's lucky he's an Ustaz.
Look, Mir, there's a live band.
Let's check it out.
What would you like to order, Ustaz?
Give me…
a cup of tea, please.
We don't serve tea here,
we only have coffee.
Give him a cup of coffee.
Be my guest, Ustaz.
Do you have something to do with
what's going on tonight?
Stop it.
Otherwise, there'll be trouble.
That's just the way it is.
There is always war.
Whether between humans
or with the supernatural.
Grandpa!
Oh, my God!
That looks like a bat!
- What's with you?
- Bathroom break.
Hey, Nap!
Don't just leave me here by myself!
That's a bit over the top.
He must think he's Ozzy Osbourne.
Something smells delicious.
Grandpa. Grandpa.
Grandpa's gone.
He's gone.
Grandpa!
Grandpa's gone.
What a stuck-up…
Are you tired?
Get some rest, okay?
- Hey, Nap, you know what I just saw?
- You know what I saw?
- What did you see?
- I have no idea.
Pak Walok,
this is the yellow, glutinous rice
you're supposed to turn into gold.
Nap, don't eat that.
We don't know what kind of meat that is.
You don't know what I saw earlier.
Eat! Eat!
We're done for, Nap!
- I don't want to get eaten!
- We're going to get raped, Mir!
Are you going to kill me, Roxana?
Babe…
Listen, babe…
Remember what you said to me once?
Roxana, you are the woman of my dreams
The time will surely come
When we will be together in love
Bring Roxana to me, Nyi.
Without a scratch on her.
Don't disobey him.
Pak Walok wants Roxana…
unharmed and intact.
Your friend is gone, Roxana!
Do you want to kill me, Roxana?
No!
What's the matter?
You don't approve?
An eye for an eye, blood for blood.
This is your parents' fault.
For killing us…
the practitioners of the dark arts.
Trying to be heroes,
trying to save the world.
You know what?
The dark arts are the future.
It doesn't matter how many of us you kill.
There will always be more of us.
And we will conquer the world.
Tantari.
What do you want?
I've killed General Atuk.
Don't try to stop me, murderer!
Where's the thing that you stole?
You're not fit to hold it.
Tantari.
It will be mine once I've killed you.
Let's settle this once and for all
and see who reigns supreme!
Kill Roxana.
Hey! Wake up! Wake up!
I don't want to be in a stew!
It's all your fault
that we've turned into goats!
I'm sorry, Mir,
I didn't know it would turn out this way!
SIX MONTHS LATER
Do you know why I'm here, Pak Walok?
I want you to answer my question.
And then, you have my permission…
to die.
Die?
Shut up!
You should have accepted
my wedding proposal.
Now, look! Look what happened!
General Atuk and Zayton are both dead.
Armand…
dead.
I can't believe
you went so far as to ruin my life.
Not even God will forgive you, Walok.
I told you.
You shouldn't have turned me down!
The Almighty has decreed it.
Djinn… and humans can't be together.
An offer from a cursed Djinn…
You turned us into goats!
I've been eating grass for months!
In the darkness,
we hope for a ray of truth.
In the dark abyss,
we ask for the gift of sight.
We sinners, we are naught but dust.
Without a soul, the body can't survive.