Some individuals are recognized
by their name,
while others are known for their work.
However, there are those
who establish their reputation
through their work.
Today, we will meet one such warrior,
who, three years ago,
made the move from Maharashtra
to Srinagar
to take on the role of SSP for SOG.
Senior Superintendent of Police,
Bajirao Singham.
please can you tell our viewers
how the SOG operates?
SOG was formed in 1994,
at the peak of militancy
in the region.
Back then, the SOG did not have
a designated base of its own.
Instead, they began operations
from the Air India cargo facility.
SOG's headquarters is still referred
to as Cargo.
Most ordinary people don't know
that 80% of the SOG commandos
are actually locals.
Whenever there is an attack,
the J&K SOG is the first responder
on the scene.
We have our own intel network
and bulletproof vehicles.
One of our primary missions now is
to prevent the radicalization
of children in the region.
You'd be surprised to know that
SOG even has reformed militants
working within its ranks,
who now serve the country.
One last question:
Why did you choose
to become a police officer?
Ma'am, that's because stars
look best in the sky
or when they adorn
the shoulders of brave men.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Shaurya?
He's doing fine too.
He really misses you.
You'll be here
for his birthday, right?
Yes, I'll be there.
If you don't show up, just remember
I work for the Cultural Ministry.
I could speak to the Home Minister
and get my husband transferred.
Please don't do that, ma'am!
I'm just a regular police officer.
Cut it out and come home soon.
- Bye.
Omar Hafiz, don't assume
the story ends here.
Do you have any idea where I am
and what I'm capable of?
Stone pelting is old-fashioned, sir.
This is the new Kashmir
of a new India.
We are all with you.
Omar Hafiz.
I never imagined fate
would be so kind to me.
I was looking for you,
and here you are.
Did you really think
it would be that easy
to get rid of Bajirao Singham?
How do you feel witnessing
the new India?
I bet you're regretting your decision
of running away from India.
But you should be happy
After dying like your sons did
you too will have the honor
of being laid to rest in this land.
You are right.
Your fate has been kind to you,
and that's why you're still alive.
However, I promise you one thing:
I will claim your last breath.
Because the deaths of you
and your friends
is the only goal of
Omar Hafiz's lineage.
You're on your own
in this battle now, Omar.
The youth of Kashmir is evolving,
and the youth of Pakistan
is becoming more aware.
Our children won't get swayed
by the likes of you anymore.
But you already know that very well.
That's why you left Pakistan
and fled to Sri Lanka,
where you started selling drugs.
Don't think that you've won
this battle by capturing me.
I am not alone.
There is someone...
planning your funeral.
He will definitely come.
I will bury him in that very coffin
Don't make the mistake
of underestimating him, Singham.
He's a firestorm.
He will turn your
and your country's ego to ashes.
Why is your storm bothering
to come after me?
Just tell me where he is.
As you know,
India now infiltrates and eliminates.
I'll be damned.
Omar Hafiz's arrest is a great
achievement, Singham.
But what's more important
is that you are safe.
I've been in this uniform
for 20 years, sir.
I don't fear death anymore.
Our intelligence has been trying
to track Omar's network.
There's a port in Sri Lanka
where they repair ships
in a private section.
It's owned by John Lucas, a Russian.
He has connections to Omar Hafiz.
We requested the Sri Lankan authorities
to interrogate him,
but you're aware of the current
situation there.
He has rapidly expanded
his drug network in just a few days.
He orders drugs from Afghanistan,
which arrive in Sri Lanka.
From there, they reach
the coastal areas of Tamil Nadu.
And from that point,
they're distributed throughout India.
The money Omar makes
from this is used against our country.
I'm sorry, sir, but this is a failure
of our intelligence network.
In every state, there are officers
who withhold intel from
other police just to claim credit.
Due to lack of evidence
and judicial restrictions,
the forces can't operate effectively.
That's why individuals like
Omar exploit the situation.
I know, Singham.
That's why sir has given us orders
to establish a new task force.
It will be a new bureau,
similar to the CBI, IB, and R&AW.
It will operate directly under us
And Singham, I'm appointing
you as the Chief of this bureau.
You'll have your own squad and budget.
There will be no judiciary for you.
Every state's police
will work with you
and you'll only report to me.
But why me, sir?
Well, it's because of you
that we have officers known
as Bihar's Singham,
Punjab's Singham, Tamil Nadu's,
Gujarat' Singham in our police force,
and they all see you as their hero.
That means there won't be
any egos getting
in the way of working together.
Sir and the name of this squad?
Shiva.
Just nine days to explore
the history of a country
that spans over 9,000 years?
It will be enough,
as this Ramleela play,
spanning nine days,
promises to be a very unique
and wholesome family experience.
This is a grand celebration...
of our culture's rich history.
I know many people in India believe
that the Ramayan is merely a story,
and not a part of our history.
In fact, some of those
individuals might be
in the audience right now,
like my son, Shaurya.
Hi, Shaurya.
But I assure you,
our distinctive Ramayan
will not be confined to Ayodhya.
You'll find its remnants
in places like Panchvati in Nashik
and even in Sri Lanka.
We will present evidence of everything
that took place in this journey.
From Hampi,
where Lord Ram and Lord Hanuman met,
to the footprints of Lord Hanuman
in Sri Lanka.
We'll reveal the secrets of miraculous
herbs found in the mountains there,
and a location where satellites
temporarily lose signal due
to a low gravitational field.
We promise you,
it is going to be an experience
you'll never forget.
Today, we will begin
with the Swayamvar (wedding)
of Lord Ram and Mother Sita.
Gautam.
This is Janakpur,
the Mithila Palace,
where the Swayamvar of Lord Ram
and Mother Sita took place.
Do you know where this is located?
It's in Nepal.
People travel from far
and wide to visit this palace.
Similarly, we will continue to present
you with evidence as we move forward.
All the best, Avni.
Where's Singham?
Are you really asking me that?
Thanks to you, ever since the
Shiva Squad was established,
he's been out on missions more often
and spending less time at home.
- Please, come.
- Okay.
Just go and ask him to make a list
- Swara, all set?
- Yes, ma'am.
Sixty seconds to go.
Ma'am, you have special guests -
officers from the Shiva Squad.
Hello, ma'am.
The show looks grand, ma'am!
All the best.
Your hard work is clearly evident.
Singham Sir was so excited
to be here.
I know what you're getting at.
I know my husband very well.
He couldn't make it,
so he sent you two
to cover for him instead.
No, no, ma'am, not at all.
Ma'am, sir has sent something for you.
The leader of a Holy Land.
The powerful,
The knowledgeable.
The roar of Courage.
The roar of Virtue.
A Leader.
A warrior.
he Almighty.
The world knows him as Ram.
What's the police doing here?
it's not the police.
That's my dad.
Have you two made a vow
to always embarrass me?
Mom, that day at the function,
you pinpointed me
in front of everyone!
And today, Dad,
you showed up
at Melvin's party unannounced!
Do you know
what my friends thought?
They literally felt like
the police had raided the place.
It was so embarrassing, Mom.
Amazing!
Now you find your parents embarrassing!
So what if he showed up there?
It's not like that, Mom.
I admit Dad's the GOAT.
GOAT?
Greatest of all time.
But guys,
I have a life of my own, right?
Of course, he has a life of his own.
That's why he's leaving his family
and his country to go to London!
Oh God, Mom!
Don't you think you're being
a bit overdramatic?
Ramayan, country...
Mom, you really need to stop enforcing
your outdated beliefs on me please.
Hey, Shaurya, behave yourself!
This is the problem
with his generation.
They think our traditions
and culture are all outdated.
I had such big dreams for you
when you were born!
I told your dad you would grow up
to be a police officer.
The next Bajirao Singham -
My talented, capable,
good son, Shaurya!
But no,
he wants to leave his family
and his country for London!
Dad, do you see
how overdramatic she is being?
I'm going.
Did you see that?
Hey...
I'm talking to him,
and he's just walking off.
Do you want my blood pressure pill?
You can have it.
You are not any better.
You don't take care
of yourself these days.
Why are you directing
your anger at me?
It's so embarrassing.
You saw how the whole party came
to a standstill.
Why are you so angry?
Honestly, if my dad were Singham,
I'd totally take advantage of that.
But what an amazing
personality he has!
Everyone became alert
the moment they saw him.
Oh hi, Uncle!
Hi!
How?
Dad? What?
Knock?
Sorry.
Actually, I shouldn't have
shown up the way I did,
both here and at your friend's party.
I know you're all grown up now
and need your own space.
But I hadn't seen you in so long,
and you're leaving
in a couple of days,
so I thought we could
spend some time together.
But for now I'm right here dad
and you're always busy...
in saving the country.
That's why I wanted to surprise you.
I thought you'd be happy, but...
Sorry.
It's okay, Dad.
So...
girlfriend?
Not exactly...
it's a situationship.
Situationship?
What's that?
It's pretty basic, Dad.
You know
what a relationship means, right?
- Yes.
- Good.
In a relationship,
two people are romantically involved
and committed.
- Yes.
- But in a situationship,
they aren't as committed.
Then why are they even together?
Because they want to be together.
So why aren't they committed?
Because of the situation, Dad!
And they want to not be committed
but to be romantically involved
with each other.
I'll be damned.
I have to say, Singham,
Avni has put on the Ramleela play
on such a grand scale!
It's an amazing concept.
It wasn't something anyone
could have managed alone.
Have you had a chance to attend it?
No, sir, I couldn't.
But I'll go in a day or two.
Please make sure to attend.
Avni blamed me for your absence.
I met Shaurya there.
He's really grown up.
Yes, sir.
He's going to London
and has a girlfriend too.
Oh, he's in a relationship?
Not quite, sir. It's a situationship.
What does that mean?
Well, a situationship means...
There's more commitment
in a relationship,
while in a situationship...
Forget it, sir.
We won't understand
how kids think these days.
No, no, Singham,
I've seen it on social media.
It's called ghosting.
- Ghosting?
- Yes.
It's when a boy and a girl are talking
to each other,
and one of them suddenly disappears.
- One of them disappears?
- Yes.
And I've heard of another term,
it's called benching.
- Benching?
- Yes!
Benching means there's a girl
and a boy who are in a relationship,
but there's another
girl waiting on the bench.
If the first girl leaves,
the second one steps in.
Singham look at me,
I'm still with the same
woman even after 30 years.
Our college days were great, sir.
We didn't have mobile phones...
Or cameras!
Just imagine otherwise, Singham...
By the way, your Shiva Squad made
headlines again.
Congratulations!
We didn't do it alone, sir.
The credit goes to you.
It's been two years since
we captured Omar, sir,
but it still feels like someone is
managing his operations.
From what Omar mentioned,
it seems he handed over his control
to someone else.
I know, Singham.
Our R&AW team there is also trying
to hunt him down.
Singham, did you gather
any information
from the smugglers you arrested
when you raided that place?
No, sir.
Our team is interrogating them,
but we haven't made
any breakthroughs yet.
Did you personally interrogate them?
No, sir.
But I will, today.
Hey... get them out.
Why have you brought us here,
ma'am?
You will find out soon enough.
- Jai Hind, sir.
Jai Hind.
Since how many days have you
been interrogating them?
It's been six days, sir.
They keep claiming they are
from Tamil Nadu
and know nothing.
They were caught with drugs
worth 6,000 crores,
yet they say they don't know anything.
Hand it over.
Are you new here?
Don't you know we don't use
our official guns for this?
Give it
So you don't know anything?
No.
Fine.
Go.
GO!
- No, sir
- Please, sir!
Please sir.
You will kill us.
Why aren't you talking then?
Who do you work for?
If we squeal on him,
he'll wipe out our families, sir.
He's a ghost, sir.
No one has seen him.
No one knows where he comes
from or where he goes.
But if anyone tries to enquire
about him ends up dead.
We take responsibility
for protecting you and your family.
You won't be able to save us, sir.
Neither our families nor us.
Your entire force won't be enough
He's a demon, sir.
He doesn't come alone;
he shows up with thousands.
Danger... Danger Lanka!
What are you doing?
Shut up!
Do you really think
our families are still alive?
No, he must have killed them
the moment we were arrested.
He is Death personified, sir.
He is Death!
Don't make the mistake
of underestimating him, Singham.
He's a firestorm.
He's known as Danger Lanka.
He is right.
No one has ever seen him.
But he has three main guys.
Sarath,
Ranga,
and Biju.
Where can I find these three?
They aren't from Tamil Nadu;
they're from Sri Lanka.
In Madurai,
near the Meenakshi Temple,
there's an astrologer named Iyenger.
All three of them believe
in him without question.
Since Devi Pooja is going to begin
they will go to meet him
They definitely will.
Who's the officer
in-charge of that area?
Shakti Shetty.
I'll be damned.
Hey Officer,
your fellow officers have already
gone down back there.
The only reason we are not hurting you is
because you are a woman, otherwise...
Shut up, you idiot.
The reason you came into
this world was a woman,
if you act smart
then the reason you will leave
this world will also be a woman.
Yes, sir.
I got those punks.
Good.
Bring all three of them here tomorrow.
Okay, sir.
And Shakti, just do as I said, okay?
I want them alive.
I've learned all of this
from you, sir.
That's why I said
that I want them alive.
Yes, sir.
Shakti Ma'am!
Look who's here!
Hello, ma'am!
Sneha! What are you doing here?!
I came to visit the temple.
I had no idea I'd run
into you all here.
You made quite the entrance,
just like a hero -
it was fantastic!
Both of them are your biggest fans.
Subbu keeps telling him
stories about you.
Thank you.
Ma'am, you should come over.
It's Kartik's birthday tomorrow.
We'd be thrilled to have you.
I'll definitely be there.
- Hi!
- Ravi, bring me a cup of coffee.
- Let's go
Subbu!
Hey, Shetty,
you have two options.
Let us go,
and you'll make so much money
that there won't be enough space
in this police station to hold it all.
And second option:
You might end up with
no police station at all.
You don't know him.
Are you trying to threaten me?
You are referring
to Danger Lanka, right?
Where is he?
Tell him, the real "danger"
is waiting for you.
Every officer that wears
a uniform thinks
they are Singham.
Come on,
he is our Guru.
I am not Singham,
I am Lady Singham.
What place is this?
Indeed, it's Ayodhya.
This is the birthplace of Lord Ram.
If he had chosen to only live
in this palace,
Today it would just be known
as a king's palace.
A tourist spot.
This became Lord Ram's birthplace
because he gave it up...
for 14 long years.
What made you want to eat
Pav Bhaji from Dadar today?
Reminds me of our date nights.
- How did the show go?
- It was great.
Tomorrow, all the drama will begin,
That's what we are preparing for.
Tomorrow in our Ramleela play,
Lord Ram will embark
on a 14-year exile.
Mother Sita will accompany him as well.
Such a beautiful love story, isn't it?
Beautiful?
Mom, don't you think
it's all dramatic?
Dramatic?
Your generation
doesn't even understand
the concept of true love.
What was that... situationship?
Dad...
But Mom, do you seriously think
Lord Ram went all the way
to Lanka just for Mother Sita?
3,000 kilometers away?
Of course, it's a fact.
Fact.
So, if you ever get kidnapped by
a character like Ravan...
Dad, would you go...
to save Mom?
Excuse me!
Just Google the name
Bajirao Singham,
and you'll know
what your Dad's capable of.
He'll go anywhere
For the one he loves...
and the one he hates.
Dialogue, Dad!
Nice.
Ravan.
Mom, I really think Ravan
is quite cool.
He makes me further believe
that Ramayan is a mythological story.
What are you looking at?
Get ready; you have a meeting
with Singham Sir
in Mumbai tomorrow.
Seriously, you tell me,
how could anyone possibly have
ten heads?
There are still plenty of people
who think like you.
Oh no, I'm going to be late!
- What happened sir?
- My son's birthday just started
- Take care, alright?
- Okay sir.
Ravan was a fearless warrior.
What's going on?
Check the main switch.
Those ten heads symbolize
his knowledge and wisdom.
Super powerful...
Super knowledgeable...
The invincible...
Ravan!
Call the control room
- Close all the windows fast.
- Yes sir.
Guns!
Pick up the phone ma'am.
Please, sir. Please don't kill me,
sir. Please, sir, please.
My husband saw you as his hero.
He always told our son,
"You should grow up
to be like Shakti ma'am."
Today is my son's birthday.
What do I say to my 4-year-old?
He keeps asking, "Where is Dad?
What's wrong with Dad?"
Where has my dad gone?
What should I tell him?
You tell him...
You tell my son,
"Son, your dad is never coming back
because I left him
there alone to die."
Just say that!
Why...?
It's alright, my dear;
this too will pass. Let's go.
I'm sorry, sir. I let you down.
No, Shakti.
It's not your fault.
I underestimated him,
thinking he was just
an ordinary criminal.
But he's much more than that.
Sir.
According to the intel,
all three of them were spotted
near Panaikulam, sir.
All the detainees we arrested came
from that same village.
Sir, I think we should send
our forces there.
Shakti, take your team
and track them down.
Sir, I...?
Sir you still trust me?
Sir, I don't deserve your trust.
You can never break my trust, Shakti.
You're not just that officer's hero;
you're my hero as well.
You are my pride.
Every officer of Singham
is his pride.
History bears witness
that Singham has never lost.
And Lady Singham
will never lose either.
Yes sir.
Go and get them.
Bring them back alive if you can;
if not, you have my permission.
A lion instills fear,
but a wounded lion causes destruction.
That's my line.
Everything I know,
I learned from you.
What is Dharma?
What defines a human's Karma?
Dharma is that noble force worthy of
our unwavering commitment,
while Karma is the guiding light
that leads us along its sacred path.
The highest Dharma is the one
that courageously navigates
the treacherous journey of truth.
And the true ideal is he
who stands undaunted
in the face of adversity.
How did the footage get deleted?
I don't know, ma'am.
I can't figure it out either.
There must be a backup
on the hard drive.
The hard drive is missing too, ma'am.
There must be some way
to retrieve the footage.
Unfortunately, no, ma'am.
We'll have to go to
Rameshwaram and reshoot it.
Ma'am, Gautam
and I can leave tomorrow.
No, you need to stay here
for the show flow.
I'll go.
I'll also come with you.
Is it really necessary for you to go?
I will have to go.
So who will go with you?
Mrigiya is coming with me
but now I think I'll take
this fool also.
No!
No, no, no, Mom!
I can't go with you.
I have my last football match on Sunday.
I can't miss that.
Please.
You don't have time
for your mother, do you?
Come on, get up and come inside
to help me pack.
- Mom...
- Get up!
What's wrong, sir?
Something doesn't feel right, Daya.
Rameshwaram is just four hours
from Madurai,
and you know what happened
in Madurai.
The monster who can kill
15 police officers
and burn down a police station...
can do anything.
We can't take him lightly.
Do one thing, go with Avni.
Yes, sir.
Prakash did you find the bag?
I can't find the big bag ma'am.
Ok I'll have a look you take this inside.
Avni,
Daya will be going along with you.
Daya? Why?
You're worried because of what happened
at Shakti's police station, right?
Aren't you overthinking this, Singham?
Avni, just do as I say.
Take Daya with you.
Fine.
Let's go, Daya.
Sure, ma'am.
I'll meet you at the airport
tomorrow morning.
Okay.
If there's any emergency
in Rameshwaram, call Satya.
Yes, sir.
A city in Maharashtra, Nashik.
When you hear its name,
you might immediately think of the Shirdi temple
or the Trimbakeshwar temple -
both significant religious sites.
But nearby lies another location
where a pivotal event unfolded,
adding a new chapter to Lord Ram's
tale of bravery and Indian history.
I'm referring to Panchvati.
Do you know what happened here?
This is where Mother Sita was abducted.
No matter how beautiful
a forest may be,
it remains a forest.
Danger lurked at every step;
misfortune awaited at every turn.
Hunger, thirst, rain,
and heat were merely
minor challenges,
but little did they know
that the real hardships were yet to come.
Yes, ma'am.
I've downloaded all the files.
Great!
I'll be back on tomorrow
afternoon's flight.
- By the way, how's it going there?
- Good, ma'am.
We're about to start the act
of Mother Sita's abduction.
I wish I was there.
All the best!
The shimmering grace
of a deer so bright,
Sparked Janaki's curiosity
with pure delight.
"My Lord, what is that,
so beautiful and enchanting?"
"Please bring it to me,
I immediately want it."
But the deer's cry was not
what she found;
It was Lord Ram's voice,
a plea that resound.
To guard Mother Sita,
Lakshman drew a protective line,
Then rushed to the forest
without wasting any time.
Yes, Mrigaya, where are you?
- We're waiting.
- I'm sorry, ma'am,
but my car broke down
behind the Kalaam House.
Could you please send Daya here?
Okay.
Ma'am, Kalaam House isn't
far from here.
- Bhaskar.
- Yes, sir.
You stay here with Avni Ma'am.
- We'll be back shortly.
- Sir.
- Bhaskar
- Yes, ma'am.
Could I get a hot cup of coffee?
Why not, ma'am?
I'll go grab it right away.
Avni Bajirao Singham.
You work for
the cultural ministry, right?
- Yes.
- Ramayan...
I mean you are doing
the Ramleela Project.
I saw you on the news.
Oh, okay.
How's Singham Sir?
You know him?
Who doesn't know him?
You must be very proud of him.
Of course, I am.
By the way, you are...?
You could say I'm also committed
to my duties, just like your husband.
But don't take this the wrong way, Avni;
Singham isn't that perfect either.
Like anyone, he has flaws too.
His biggest flaw
is thinking only his viewpoint is valid.
He's so proud of his honesty
and loyalty
that he often overlooks others' feelings.
And you know what, Avni?
Sometimes, the arrogance of such 'clean'
and morally correct people
can lead to trouble
for their families.
By the way,
where are Daya and Mrigaya?
Oh, did you think
Mrigaya works for you?
There's no one here, sir.
Sir, I believe we've been misled.
We've searched every corner
of Panaikulam,
but we haven't found
those three here.
You won't find them there;
it's a trap.
They've abducted Avni.
What?!
Daya, break down the door!
Well done, ma'am!
You've been shot.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
But...
Ma'am...
She is my mother.
Our Kalari Ashram is nearby.
Avni, are you alright?
I'm fine, but he's been shot.
Don't worry, he'll be fine.
Let's go.
Get him airlifted immediately.
And you stay with him.
Sir.
Sir, we got a message
from Satya Sir over the wireless.
Ma'am is with him.
Your wound will heal in two days.
Why don't you take better
care of yourself?
You keep getting scolded,
yet you still don't pay attention.
What can I do, Revti Amma?
My wounds crave your scolding more
than this salve for healing.
I see.
Since how long have you been
teaching Kalari?
Since I was a little girl.
This ashram belongs to my father.
That's why your son is brave,
just like you.
Despite being shot he's still smiling
Actually, I didn't give birth to Satya.
What do you mean?
Many years ago,
our ashram's healer,
Revti Amma,
was walking through a forest
when she heard
a child's cry from afar.
When she got closer,
she saw the child had turned blue.
Then she noticed a snake passing by.
She picked up the child,
and by a miracle,
he was completely fine.
Nothing happened to him.
She brought him back to this ashram.
Since then, countless miraculous
events have occurred with Satya
that you wouldn't believe them.
I truly believe he is under
the protection of Lord Shiva.
Are you alright?
Yes, ma'am.
By the way, who were those people?
I have no idea.
All I know is that whoever he is,
he's after Singham.
He put a lot of thought
into this plan.
My assistant Mrigaya works
for him too...
Singham was right about it
I just hope Daya is fine.
If you wouldn't have come...
How could I not, ma'am?
He idolizes Singham Sir, Avni.
It has always been his dream
to work alongside him as his Lakshman.
Looks like Singham Sir is here.
Satya!
Sir, we've deployed our forces
in Rameshwaram and at nearby exit points.
We've also alerted all check posts.
Our teams are already stationed
at all the hospitals in the area.
There's only one way out of here, sir.
It leads to Madurai via Sivganga.
Shakti's already on it, sir.
I've informed her.
I'm really sorry
I couldn't stop him, sir.
I hope Avni Ma'am is okay.
Avni will be fine.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
- Hello?
- Hello, Singham.
How are you?
You're searching for
Danger Lanka, right?
Danger Lanka is a name given
to me by the people.
Do you want to know
who I really am?
Remember when Omar Hafiz said
that this war is the sole purpose
of his lineage?
I'm the firestorm he referred to,
Singham.
I'm Zubair Hafiz,
Omar Hafiz's grandson.
Uncle Raza and I spent
the best years of
our lives at London University.
And now you're heading there
to study as well.
Anyways a lot is about to happen here.
If anything happens to me,
know that you have inherited
my fire for revenge.
I won't let anything happen
to you, Grandpa.
You'll witness our revenge succeed
with your own eyes.
I promise.
I am the Ravan of your story.
I know Avni is hurt,
but you should be more concerned
about her life than I am.
Because if something happens to her,
your time will start ticking down.
I've heard so much about you.
Singham this, Singham that.
Singham is a warrior.
He's the embodiment of loyalty.
He follows the principles of Lord Ram.
If you truly are Lord Ram's disciple
in this Kalyug,
bring your officers Simmba
and Sooryavanshi along with my grandfather
and come get your wife.
I swear on my mother, Zubair,
if I don't come for Avni,
then Singham is not a true Maratha!
She's out of danger now.
Zubair, she's out of danger.
I've waited two years
to see you in this state.
I'm proud of my grandson.
If he were a real man,
he would have come at me directly.
Did you really think you
and your grandson will be spared
after using an innocent
woman as a shield?
This is war, Singham.
And everything is fair in war.
You know Genghis Khan, don't you?
He once declared,
"I am the punishment of God."
Zubair is that punishment,
for you and your friends.
You don't know Bajirao Singham.
Bajirao has taken
only two vows in his life.
The first, when he put on his uniform:
To serve his country
until his last breath.
The second, when he married Avni:
To always protect her.
Today, I make a third vow.
If my wife is harmed in any way,
you won't receive
your grandson's corpse,
just like you didn't receive your sons.
He's a firestorm.
Everyone's going to die.
I should have gone with Mom.
Your mom will be fine.
He's been planning this for two years
while hiding out in Tamil Nadu,
and our team didn't even
catch a whiff of it?
We have to admit, Singham,
this is the biggest failure of
our intelligence network.
No matter which corner
of India Zubair hides in,
we won't let him go unpunished.
We will deploy our entire force
and all our resources to find Avni.
Sir, he has also demanded for
the three of us along with Omar.
He's executed
this plan very intelligently.
I'm certain he won't make
the mistake of staying in India.
I believe he's on his way
to Sri Lanka.
Sir...
Come what may,
we'll continue with the Ramleela play.
We'll all make Mom proud.
Connect.
So when are you three bringing
my grandfather?
First, tell me where I need to come
I'll let you know, Singham.
Just arrange for
my grandfather's release for now.
None of your demands will be met
until I'm sure Avni is safe.
Your wife's life could be in danger
if you don't do as I say.
If anything happens to my wife,
I'll behead your grandfather
and hang his head on the Red Fort.
Whoa! Someone's really angry!
But you have a good reason to be angry.
It's a family matter, after all.
And who would understand
that better than us, right?
First, I'll come alone to see Avni.
Singham, you know if you come here,
you won't make it out alive.
And then your government
won't let my grandfather go.
Let's do one thing.
Send your favourite
to check if Avni is alright.
Who's he talking about sir?
POLICE!
You can say no if you want.
This isn't an official mission;
it's personal.
Personal?
So am I just "impersonal"?
Do I mean nothing to you?
Does your wife mean nothing to me?
You hurt my feelings, sir.
It's not like that, Simmba.
I don't think it's fair.
I'll be putting your life at risk
to save Avni.
It's a dangerous mission.
So what?
I'm dangerous too!
You're the Super Cop;
I'm the Robo Cop.
We are the Lethal Weapon, sir.
Don't you think you're speaking
a bit too much English today?
Yes, because you are emotionally
damage me, sir.
Personal, huh?
Personal!
Alright, don't be upset.
But I have one request:
Cut down on the English.
This is the first time Simmba
has a chance to help Singham, sir.
From giving my life to taking one,
whatever the task is, consider it done.
Sorry.
Be careful.
He seems like a maniac.
We'll see, sir.
Hampi, Karnataka
where ancient temples still bear
witness to the Monkey Gods.
Do you know why?
Because the Hampi
we recognize today
was once known as Kishkindha
in the Treta Yuga, the Silver Age,
a realm ruled by the Monkey Kings Bali
and Sugriva.
Not far from there lies one
of India's five sacred lakes,
Pampa Sarovar,
where Lord Ram
and Lord Hanuman met for the first time,
marking the beginning of
a new chapter of courage and valor.
The word has spread through the jungle
that Simmba has arrived
to support the Lion.
Singham, his flight departs tomorrow.
Make sure Simmba catches it.
My men will be waiting
for him at the airport here.
Colombo.
Columbus! Columbus! Columbus!
Where's Columbus, ma'am?
Isn't it in America?
It's going to be a long flight, right?
Boss, I prefer traveling
in business class.
My legs start tingling in economy.
It's not Columbus; it's Colombo.
Colombo is in Sri Lanka.
Ah, I see - our neighboring country,
the one to the south.
Alright then,
let's head to Sri Lanka
and have some fun.
Activate all our agents in Sri Lanka.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, okay.
- Share the details please.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Dilip?
- Yes, ma'am?
- Crosscheck the coordinates.
- Sure ma'am.
Ma'am, it'll take me two
and a half hours to get to Colombo.
So, what's the plan after that?
Simmba, I suspect that as soon
as you touch down,
Zubair's men will grab you
and throw you into a car.
How can you say that, ma'am?
"Grab you and throw you"?
What am I? A checked-in bag?
Hey, it's not my plan.
But it could be Zubair's.
What do you mean "it could be"?
If Zubair wants Omar,
he'll definitely take you to Avni.
And through your location,
we will be able track her down.
Sir.
Here's the live feed
from Colombo Airport.
Our satellites will keep tabs
on you every moment from here.
Technology!
India's intel is
at a James Bond level, right?
Self-reliant India!
Mind is blowing!
Boss, I have a doubt.
If I need to make an emergency call
and the Aunty managing
the satellite says,
"Singham is busy on another call,"
then Zubair will have me
done for, right?
Don't worry, Simmba.
Singham Sir will be in Negombo
by the time you land in Colombo.
Sir, our coast guard will drop
you off on a trawler near
the Sri Lankan border
which is arranged by our team.
And you'll reach Negombo
where our R&AW agents
will be waiting for you.
So, that's the game plan.
And where's the player?
You'll find out when the time is right.
Sir, do you believe just
the three of us can pull this off?
Who said it's only the three of us?
No, Singham.
This doesn't feel right.
This is a suicide mission.
Let me consult the
Sri Lankan government first.
No, sir.
Zubair is quite shrewd.
If he discovers that
the Sri Lankan government
is involved,
he'll escape.
This is our only chance
to capture him.
And Avni? What about her safety?
Zubair callously killed
15 police officers in Madurai, sir.
Their families will only find peace
after we get our revenge.
As for Avni,
had she been here,
she too would have said,
"I may die if I have to,
but India doesn't negotiate
with terrorists."
If we're meant to die,
then so be it.
But I swear we will take Zubair down.
So, it's just going
to be the three of you?
Isn't it a bit too dramatic for
only the three of us to go?
We'll need backup
from your other forces.
I'll need to get permission
from Sir.
We've already done
it twice before.
Let us invoke the blessing
of Lord Hanuman
and carry out this operation
a third time.
Why did you do this, Mrigaya?
For money?
Why?
Avni, her name isn't Mrigaya;
it's Iqra Hafiz.
She's my aunt.
Do you really think
we're doing this for money?
No, ma'am,
we're seeking revenge
for our family.
Just so you know,
I'm Zubair Hafiz,
the grandson of Omar Hafiz.
She is the widow of my uncle Raza,
who was killed
by your husband, Singham.
Bilal's sacrifice shouldn't go to waste.
Okay, Father.
You may eliminate us today,
but tomorrow,
a hundred more like us will rise.
Riyaaz and Raza
have both become martyrs.
To be honest,
I was scared for a moment
when you were shot,
wondering what would happen
to my two years of planning.
But must say,
you are a very strong lady,
just like Sita from the Ramayan.
By the way, I find Ravan's
character in the Ramayan
to be the most interesting.
Because he had no interest in Ayodhya
and wasn't fighting for Dharma.
He only sought revenge
for his family.
And I'm doing the same.
I'm not sure if it's just a tale
or the truth,
but I read somewhere
that Ravan would return
in Kalyug, the age of darkness.
So here he is.
If Ravan has returned,
then Ram will also come
to rescue his Sita.
The only difference
this time is that Ravan
will emerge victorious.
No matter how many times
the Ramayan is rewritten,
Ram will always win.
This is Kalyug, Avni,
the age of darkness.
This time,
Ravan will triumph.
Truth always prevails,
no matter what time we live in.
We'll see.
Even if I don't return,
your mom definitely will.
Just Google the name
Bajirao Singham, Dad,
and you'll know
what my dad's capable of.
Not just Mom,
both of you have to return.
Because then Diwali won't hold
the same meaning
if Mother Sita returns without Lord Ram.
Dad...!
Jai Hind!
- Jai Hind, sir.
- Jai Hind!
We have three hours until
Simmba's plane lands.
and till then we need to secure
you in a safe location.
And the safest place
is Seetha Amman Kovil temple,
or Ashok Vatika,
as mentioned in the Ramayan.
They say Ravan held Mother Sita
captive over here for a year.
She is with us.
This is the only temple
in Sri Lanka dedicated to Mother Sita.
This is where Lord Hanuman first met
Mother Sita in Lanka.
Wherever Lord Hanuman stepped,
he left a footprint.
It is said that this is one
of those footprints.
Sir, Simmba has landed.
Sir, Simmba has landed in Colombo.
Satellite vision is perfect.
Send me Simmba's
location tracking details.
We'll follow his movements.
Right away, sir.
Why so serious?
What is name?
Like it?
Nice...
Hey! What the hell!
This is my first time in Sri Lanka!
Let me enjoy the scenery at least!
Escort party is heading
towards Galle, sir.
You've got water, snacks, anything?
Seriously, nothing?
Just letting you know.
I'll ask you to stop when we cross a foodcourt.
Oh hello!
Oh my God,
which of these cars is Simmba's?
Quickly track the cars.
Jot down these coordinates.
Which car do we follow now, sir?
Hold.
And here we have Sigiriya Fort
in Sri Lanka.
When they did carbon dating on it,
they discovered it's not just historic
but a pre-historic site.
Ten thousand years ago,
there was just one empire here
of such grandeur,
and it was ruled by The one with ten heads -
Dashanan Lankesh.
This is also where Lord Hanuman was taken
after he was captured in Ashok Vatika.
Hey, you're messing up my look!
It's my favourite jacket.
I want it back.
You'll get it all back.
Let's head inside.
Come on.
Scared you!
I scared you, didn't I?
Hey, Sister-in-law!
Simmba?!
What are you doing here?
Don't worry about me;
just tell me how you are.
I'm fine, but you...
Singham Sir sent me here
to check on you.
Thank you, Sister-in-law!
Because of you, my empty passport
finally got stamped with a visa.
Look at that!
She got hit with a 9mm bullet
and still manages a 200-watt smile!
I hope they are feeding you well.
Who's that aunty?
Is she with them?
Hello, Aunty.
Greetings, ma'am... or whatever!
Don't worry...
Singham...
- Hey!
- What?
Alright, enough with the chit-chat.
Let's go!
Yes, let's move.
I hope you've set me up
in a separate room.
I'm not sharing with anyone.
Hey, by the way,
do you know Marathi?
- No.
- Aunty, what about you?
No?
Sister-in-law, big brother
and our team are here.
Don't worry.
We're going to take them down.
Jai Maharashtra!
Singham's devoted follower,
Sangram Bhalerao, aka Simmba!
Every kid's favorite in Shivgadh.
Tell me something I don't already know!
Tell me something I don't know!
No longer just a local legend,
I've gone national.
Not just the kids in Shivgadh;
Simmba's a favorite among every child
in India now!
Wow! Gabbar Singh!
You've got a dangerous look, Danger.
You look like a hero straight
out of a South Indian movie.
You were my favorite too
when you thought duty
and responsibility were just jokes
and all you cared about was money.
Hmm.
What changed, Simmba?
Life taught me that
relationships and duty are more
important than money.
And revenge's even more important!
Here, concepts of right and wrong,
good and bad don't really matter.
What you desire is what truly matters.
By the way, when did a corrupt guy
who'd accept bribe start dressing
like a stand-up citizen?
There you go!
If I wear clothes, it's a problem;
if I don't, that's also a problem.
I don't know what to do!
Zubair, you're really --
Attitude, huh?
I've checked your history too.
Raised in London,
not religious,
no jihad connections.
So what changed?
Why did you join the family business?
When a family's destiny
is written in blood,
the heir has no choice
but to take up the sword.
Ah, so Lanka's out for revenge
for his family, huh?
But sorry for inconvenience you, bro,
this time neither you nor
your terrorist grandpa are walking away.
You have no clue what's coming.
Why? Is Singham coming to save you?
Singham isn't coming;
he's already here.
Hey, builder, open the gate
and let Singham Sir
in before it's too late.
No one's here.
What do you mean, no one's here?
Check again.
Told you, no one's here.
As if you can see that from here!
I'll go take a look.
Looks like I am about
to get whacked on my back.
He promised me he'd show up.
What did Singham Sir say?
"Who said it's only the three of us?"
Forget three;
not even one of them is here.
I told them they'd use
a satellite jammer,
but they never listen to Simmba!
Our intel officer, Devika keeps saying,
"Yes, sir. Singham Sir. Okay, sir.
Whatever you want, sir."
Wants revenge from Singham , is
Sooryavanshi's enemy,
but guess who's the one in danger?
Simmba!
Why did you say no one's here?
- Because no one's here.
- So what?
Hey! Hey he ran away...
Hey, sorry, sorry!
No, I was just... You...
Ma'am.
Oh, my God, quickly connect with sir
Sir, I spot an explosion
at Galle harbour
and I'm damn sure it's Simmba.
Continue...Continue
This is Simmba's car.
I hope he's fine.
We should do a quick scan
of this area.
You all head that way,
and I'll check over here.
The only true powerhouse here
is Bajirao Singham!
Thank you.
What is this?
Sorry, Brother. Sorry, Sister.
Sorry for destruction.
You come India,
we give you two
holiday package free.
Kashmir to Kanyakumari,
where you say there we do take care.
A guest is akin to God.
Our policy:
God... our guest our God!
Avni?
Sister-in-law's fine. Don't worry.
She was shot here,
but she's getting treated
and will be fine.
She's out of danger.
Speaking of danger,
that Danger guy is really dangerous.
He's got a massive army out there.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Sir, I promised them we'd cover
their holiday expenses.
Are you okay?
Yes sir.
Simmba, were you at Galle Port?
No, I was where the boats
and all are parked.
That is what you call a port.
Then that's where sister-in-law is.
Sir, police.
You two should go.
We will handle them.
Get the team ready
and send them the coordinates
for Galle Port.
Yes, sir.
Turn left.
Sir, um... turn right.
This is my first time here, you see.
He has a lot of men, way too many!
I suggest we wait outside
and have a cup of tea.
He's going to join us anyway, right?
We'll wait outside.
He'll arrive in a helicopter,
hanging out of it as usual.
Why do the two of us always have
to do everything, huh?
Let him come.
You've called him, right?
Damn it...
Sir, I really think we should wait.
We shouldn't go in like this.
Turn right.
Singham!
My door is stuck, sir.
You should go, sir.
I'll catch up with you.
Are you okay?
Welcome to Lanka, Singham.
Must say, what a personality!
Can I be honest?
Honest confession:
I've been wondering how I'd react
when we finally met face-to-face.
When people see
Bajirao Singham for the first time,
they either whistle,
applaud
or salute him.
But I've got a different plan in mind.
I'm going to take you out.
Now all I need to decide
whether I'm going to do it now,
or wait until Oman Hafiz gets back.
If you wait, you will get
a few more hours to live.
What has got you feeling
so proud of yourself, huh, Singham?
Your government's plan has failed.
Simmba lies down there.
You are standing here staring death
in the face.
I kidnapped your wife just like that,
and you couldn't do a thing about it.
So Avni, what exactly is he
so proud of, huh?
You made a very big mistake.
I made a mistake?
You think you can teach me right
from wrong?
Your Indian Army killed my father,
you and your friends
shot down my family,
and you have the nerve
to lecture me on morality?
There's no such thing as right
or wrong when it comes to family.
You came here for your family,
didn't you?
You came for your wife, didn't you?
The ones we killed were terrorists,
and we'll do the same thing
in the future as well.
If you so much as look at our country,
we will kill you!
If you so much as set foot
in our country,
we will kill you!
And if you try to flee and hide
in another country,
we'll track you down there
and kill you!
I told your grandfather the same thing,
but the old man just wouldn't understand!
- Hey!
- Today, I am letting you know as well.
The one standing
in front of you respects
Mahatma Gandhi,
but the one he worships
is Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj!
I told you, I'm a Maratha!
I promised I'd come for Avni.
Today, I'm making you another promise -
I swear on my mother,
I'll tear you apart before I leave.
Come on, Danger Baba!
How are you going to see your grandfather
if you go and kill them?
Cool down. Let me talk to him.
I'll talk to him, alright?
Are you out of your mind
or something?
Sister-in-law,
talk some sense into him, will you?
Cool down, man.
Cool down.
Look, tomorrow Sooryavanshi Sir
is going come here with your grandfather.
The three of us can sit down
and figure this out together.
Forget about them, okay?
You... cool down.
Hey, you want a cold drink
or an ice cream?
Hey Builder,
go get him an ice cream.
Fine, don't have the ice cream.
Don't have it.
I said don't have it.
It's got too many calories anyway,
so don't have it.
I told you I'll go check on things,
so why did you come out here?
Yes, grab me and take me
back inside.
Take us with you.
Oh no, we got caught!
We got caught!
Come on, let's go.
Sorry...
that you had to endure all
this because of me.
I am Bajirao Singham's wife.
These minor wounds mean nothing.
You are my strength.
And you are mine.
Looking at Sister-in-law,
it's clear why you act like a lion.
Yes, if you're the power,
then she's your superpower.
If you're the bun, she's the patty.
If you're the iPhone,
she's your charger.
Sorry, continue.
How is Shaurya?
He's fine.
Honestly,
I was worried about how to explain
what happened to his mother,
but he handled it bravely.
He's really grown up,
and we've aged.
Oh, don't say that, sir.
These days, it's the older
generation that's in form
and causing a ruckus.
Shut up, Simmba.
Hello, Mr. Bajirao Singham,
we're not that old.
Actually, you've shown so much
courage during these hard times.
"We need to gradually increase
the love!"
"We have to go above and beyond."
You're so dramatic!
You should've been in the movies.
How did you end up becoming
a policeman?
Sister-in-law,
I've been dramatic since childhood.
I used to sell tickets
for inflated prices outside the theater.
Once, I went to watch a movie,
but the real action unfolded
outside the theater.
And guess who's the hero creating chaos?
One and only Singham!
But, Sister-in-law,
I have a sincere request.
I'll inform Mrs. Sooryavanshi as well.
You all need to stay cautious.
Otherwise, then you might get kidnapped,
and then everyone has to come together.
Coordinating everyone's dates
becomes a challenge.
Yes, ordinary people reunite
at weddings and birthdays.
Our reunions happen
when someone has a crisis.
Eh, eh, what you doing, eh?
Oh!
- Singham, we're releasing Omar.
- But, sir...
It's an order, Singham.
However, you must promise us that:
You'll return Omar
to India along with Avni.
I admire your enthusiasm, sir.
But I also want Sooryavanshi.
Yes, yes, I'll send him too.
- Avni, are you okay?
- Yes, sir.
- I'm here as well!
- Yes, Simmba.
I've seen your picture.
You look like you're in a mood to party.
And Avni, just so you know,
your Ramleela is going wonderfully.
Singham, the war begins tomorrow.
Great warriors will be there,
not just Lord Ram and Lord Hanuman,
but Lakshman will also come,
Sugreev will be there too,
and Garuda will join as well.
Poor Ravan!
On one hand there is sin,
evil and demons to defeat,
On the other,
there is a man with a promise to keep.
Yet the brave don't walk this path alone,
They find their warriors at every turn.
The army is ready,
everything is about to be set ablaze,
Virtue and vice are face-to-face,
Once again, an epic battle
is going to take place.
Omar Hafiz's plane has already departed
from India.
I thought India does not negotiate
with terrorists.
So what happened?
Did India finally yield?
Over the last 9,000 years,
many have tried to alter
our country's history.
Today, no one even remembers
their names.
Those who aspired
to shape India's future ended
up becoming history.
I must say, Singham,
even though your life is at risk,
your spirit of patriotism
remains unwavering.
Look at these two one last time,
because you will return
only with their remains.
Do you know why Lord Ram refused
to forgive Ravan?
Because he wasn't worthy of a lesson;
he was deserving of punishment.
Singham...
please give him one chance
before taking his life.
He's just a child.
- Oh my God, insult!
- Let's go.
In the silver age (Treta)
or the dark age (Kalyug),
the warriors of our land,
Chant the same mantra,
and take a stand.
They bow to women,
showing respect so true,
But when a woman's insulted,
they'll sever a head for her too.
Everyone knows who all are coming.
Don't you know?
When the Naagpaash unleashed
its fierce wrath,
Despair resounded on every path!
Lord Hanuman, in plight,
Called out to Lord Vishnu to guide.
Whenever victory makes
the unrighteous swell with pride,
A mighty,
fierce warrior arrives.
All things will perish,
nothing will stay,
When Garuda Dev parts the clouds
on and makes his way!
Show off.
Good morning, Sister-in-law.
Control to Oscar one
Rescue mission successful,
return to base.
Sir we can't find him here.
- Go check the other side.
- Ok sir.
I'm out of ammo.
So am I.
He's got to be around
here somewhere.
Found him?
No.
- Go check over there.
- Okay.
- Hand me the gun.
- Give me the gun.
Katappa!
It's not Katappa, sir. It's Simmba!
I know.
I said that because you betrayed me.
No, that's not it.
I'm a lefty, so my arm just extended
when he asked...
Yes, I'm coming!
No one called him,
yet he's saying he's coming!
Sir!
Can I say something, sir?
Sooryavanshi Sir is very
"manicure" about you.
Insecure.
Yes, right, he is very "pedicure".
You should have seen
the look on his face
when I handed you my gun.
He was giving me a death stare.
He was jealous, plain and simple.
I told him, "Alright,
you must be the great Sooryavanshi Sir,"
"but Singham is like my big brother,
damn it."
Don't be scared, keep going.
Who's scared? Not me, sir.
I'm not scared at all.
I might act scared,
but I'm not afraid of him.
He could never get my name right.
He'd call me everything
from Samba, Bamba,
Lamba to Ramba, except for Simmba.
When he goes to a restaurant and wants
'Badam ka Halwa' (Almond Pudding)
he'll end up ordering 'Sadam ka Jalwa'
(Sadam's grandeur) instead!
What he did the other day
was just too much.
I heard he dropped his kid
at the headquarters
and went to school instead.
The other day,
he tried to quote a movie line to me.
And he messed that up too!
"He who gets defeated
and then thrashed is called a sorcerer."
What else did he say?
There's nothing more to add.
He's always hanging out
of a helicopter.
I say, why not just buy a ticket,
sit back, and enjoy
the ride respectfully?
But no, he insists on hanging!
I feel like putting a bullet
in your head,
and hang you, right here, right now!
No, I have something important
to take care of.
I'll go deal with it.
- I'm coming!
- Who's there?
Sir.
What is it?
What happened
to you was really wrong, sir.
It's making me tear up, sir.
Sorry sir
You rascal,
you haven't shed a single tear
and you say you're crying.
You're enjoying my misery.
No, sir, not me,
they enjoy your misery.
You keep forgetting names,
don't you, sir?
It's not so, Tatya.
It's not Tatya, it's Satya, sir!
What just happened?
Or a place like this where
because of low gravitational force
for some time satellites loose their signal.
I'm talking about the Unawatuna region
of Sri Lanka.
Legend has it that when Lord Hanuman
was carrying the Dronagiri Mountain,
a portion of the mountain fell here,
in Unawatuna.
It's rumored that because of this,
the area has a lower gravitational force.
As a result, satellites passing
through here may encounter
glitches during tracking.
Where's your attitude now, huh?
This is what you are worth, you scoundrel.
How dare you lay your hand on my wife!
I feel like burying you right here,
but I won't.
I'll take you back to India
and keep you alive
so the whole world can see
the state you are in,
and no one else dares to be like you.
I'd rather die than live the life
you're offering me, Singham.
Don't confuse your mistake with pride.
You won't achieve from it.
This war was never
about achieving something.
My goal was to avenge my people.
You've never lost a dear one, Singham.
That's why...
The innocent Indians your family killed
were all dear to me.
The whole of India is my family,
and I am the Zubair Hafiz of India.
If my patience runs out,
I'll cut your head off
and take it back to my country with me.
Take him away!
Bajirao!
Arrogance.
Thank you.
I can't hear you.
Thank you for saving my life.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
Well, he's the ones who saved me.
Are you deaf?
Can't you hear her?
Now you know what it feels like when,
after risking your life,
your wife thanks someone else, right?
By the way, what's her name?
Avni!
My sister-in-law, Avni!
You know, you and I are exactly the same.
- Really?
- Both are orphans.
A person isn't an orphan
because of a lack of relations,
but because of a lack of loved ones.
You have a big brother,
a sister-in-law,
and friends around you.
Tell me, why did you come to save me?
Because we're family, okay?
And a crazy one.
Got it?
Yes.
And look...
our family is growing.
- May I take her, sir?
- Yes.
It's not that all the evil
in the world will be vanquished.
The enemies of our country
will rise time and again.
There will be moments
when it seems like evil is
on the verge of victory,
but whenever the night of evil descends,
the morning sun will reveal
those rebels willing
to risk their lives
to ensure that good triumphs.
This victory of good over evil
is a part of India's history
and its future.
Singham!
Aren't you going to welcome me?
The fun is about to begin!