[wind rustling softly]
[flies buzzing]
[shovel banging]
[metallic thudding]
[car beeping]
[engine rumbling]
[tense music]
- You okay?
[high-pitched whining]
[tense music]
[fast-paced heavy breathing]
[screaming]
[luggage rustling]
- Hold on, hold on.
No.
We gotta put the big
black one in first.
No, Meg, hold on.
Just wait, okay?
Okay?
All right, I got it.
[luggage thudding]
[muffled radio chattering]
I grabbed your journal.
It was under the couch.
- You hungry?
- Not really.
[turning signal clicking]
I'm not hungry.
- Okay, but I gotta get gas.
- Fine.
Sorry.
[car doors thudding softly]
[gas pump beeps]
- [Newscaster] City Hall
today, a protest
led by public safety
advocates aims to put pressure
on the Boston police department.
- [Protester] How many
other women and girls
has the Boston police
stopped looking for?
[muffled protesters shouting]
[chip bag crackling]
- [Newscaster] The
department came
under pressure this spring-
- Excuse me.
- After the shocking return
of Megan Rhoads.
The 32-year-old Beacon
Hill resident
[tense music]
[low rumbling]
had been assumed dead
by the police
after she disappeared
from nearby parking garage
nearly six months earlier.
[tense music]
- My great-grandfather
bought this place
in the 20s, I think?
We used to own everything
to the end of that road.
[Meg chuckles softly]
[kisses softly]
[luggage thudding]
[Scott sighs]
[sheets rustling]
[crow cawing]
[Meg gasps]
- Sorry.
- I'll grab the rest
of the bags.
- Okay.
[water whooshing]
Where were your parents?
- The adults all stayed
at the big house, mostly.
Let me get this.
- I got it.
Where's that?
- Well, the big house used
to be down by the beach,
but they tore it down
when I was a kid.
- Why?
- 'Cause no one could
afford the property taxes.
It was massive.
- [Meg] So you were here alone?
- Well, with the rest
of the cousins.
This was like the cousins house.
My grandmother hated
kids, I think,
so she put us all in this house
so she didn't have
to deal with us.
- She sounds sweet.
- No, she wasn't sweet.
We wouldn't see her all summer
and then one day she
would summon us down
and individually interview
us about our interests
and tell us us stand
up straight.
Can I finish this?
- Oh.
[glass clatters loudly]
Shit, sorry.
- I'm sorry.
Meg, you don't have shoes on.
Just back away, it's okay.
[broken glass rustling]
[wine sloshing]
[broken glass clattering]
- Is anyone else coming down?
- Doubt it.
It's pretty empty in the winter.
You sure you didn't...
You alright?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Thank you.
[Scott chuckles softly]
- My reward.
[Meg chuckles softly]
[tense music]
[Scott sighs]
Good?
You sure?
Come here.
[Scott snores loudly]
[Scott groans softly]
[Meg sighs]
[plastic rustling]
[tense music]
[plate rustles]
[dog barks]
[plate clatters sharply]
[tense music]
- Scott?
[Meg breathes shakily]
Scott.
Scott!
[Scott grunts]
Meg.
It's okay.
You're okay.
You're safe.
- You were sleepwalking.
- Hm?
- Last night.
Is there a dog here?
- A dog?
- I heard a dog bark and then
I dropped that weird plate.
- What plate?
[tense music]
- You remember you dropped
a glass last night?
- No, it was right here.
[Scott sighs]
- You remember what
Dr. Potter said?
Sometimes nightmares can
feel really real.
[glass clatters sharply]
You okay?
[Meg exhales shakily]
- Yeah.
[Scott kisses]
- Okay.
[clock ticking]
[Scott rustling beard]
[pages rustling]
[birds chirping]
[door clicks softly]
[tense music]
[sheet rustling]
[eerie vocalizing]
[motorcycle creaking]
[metallic clicking]
[Meg sighs]
[bird chirping]
- I've been thinking
about Christmas.
- Mm-hmm.
- It might be nice to
spend it at home.
- I thought you wanted
to come out here.
- I did, but...
[dog barking]
- [Woman] Yoo-hoo!
- Madelin?
[tense music]
[dog barking]
- Hey, Minnow.
Minnow!
[Minnow barking]
Down!
Down, Minnow!
- Minnow, off.
Talkie. [laughs]
- Madelin.
What are you doing here?
I was just out for a
walk and I saw your car.
I'm staying at my mother's
little shack.
- [Scott] How's your mom doing?
- [Madelin] Not well,
I'm afraid.
- I'm so sorry, that's tough.
- Yeah.
And Meg, I'm so glad
to see you again!
- I'm sorry?
- Meg, this is my
cousin Madelin.
You met her at the wedding.
- Oh.
- We've got a big family.
I won't hold it against
you. [chuckles]
So, how long are you here for?
Not sure.
- Through the New Year.
- I can't believe Talkie
didn't tell me
you two were coming. [laughs]
I didn't know anybody
was gonna be here.
- Talkie?
- Oh, well, Scott was
so quiet as a kid.
I don't think he said
a word until you
were what, two years old?
- Okay, I don't think we
need to talk about this.
- So we started calling
him, you know,
I think it was grandmother
who first...
In any case, we started calling
him walkie-talkie as a joke,
and then just walkie Scotty,
and then just talkie.
- Poor Scott.
- Sorry?
He just told me how tough
your grandmother could be.
- Oh, I was just telling
her about
the famous sit-down interviews.
- Right.
You know, I had a friend
in college named Meg.
It was short for Megumi.
- Oh.
- Is your name short
for anything?
- Megan.
- So you need some
cream and sugar?
- Did you forget how
I take my tea?
- Do you wanna do it yourself-
- Has it been that long?
- -you can just take care of it.
- [Madelin] Has it been
that long? [laughs]
[tense music]
[thudding]
[woman whimpering]
[doors rustling]
[Meg gasps]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[tennis ball thumping]
[Meg exhales shakily]
- Let me see how you're
holding it.
You gotta hold it
like that that.
All right, right here, ready?
- Okay.
[tennis ball thumping]
[Scott grunts]
- Yes!
Nice shot, Madelin.
[Madelin laughing]
- I've got it.
[Meg grunts loudly]
- [Scott] I'll get it.
- It's okay.
- Oh, it is really
back here, Meg.
- Sorry.
- It's lodged deep.
[tense music]
You know, it helps
if you square your hips
and start low.
Keep your eye on the ball.
Swing through all the way over.
- Yeah?
- [Scott] Got it.
- Why don't we just rally?
Give Meg a chance to
get her bearings.
[paper rustling]
[Meg breathes heavily]
[clothes rustling]
[door creaks]
[tense music]
[footsteps thudding]
[Meg whimpering]
- Meg, Meg, Meg, Meg,
Meg, Meg, Meg, Meg.
[Meg crying loudly]
[high-pitched whining]
It's not, it's not.
[calm vocalizing]
- I used to count the footsteps.
[clock ticking]
The house was old.
The sound carried.
I started counting
how long it would
take them to get
to different places
in the house.
It helped a little
to always know how long it
would take them to get to me.
[Scott sighs]
[Meg sighs]
- Dr. Potter said it
could be really helpful
to write in your journal
when you're having
moments like this.
Can I go get it for you?
[glass clinking]
So this is an Argentinian wine.
It's supposed to be really
good, sort of peppery.
Good?
- Good.
I dunno.
- No, [laughs] wait,
what are you doing?
- You hate it.
- No, I love it.
- And you're sure?
- Yes.
- And you wanna drink it?
- Mm-hmm, I wanna drink it.
- We have others.
- No, I want this one.
[Meg laughs softly]
Put the wine down, psycho.
[Minnow barking]
- Yoo-hoo!
Minnow, down.
Off.
[Minnow panting]
Oh.
Hello.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[Madelin kisses animatedly]
I brought chicken
and an eggplant.
- Oh, you didn't have to.
- Oh, my mother barely
eats anyway
and I don't want all
this to go to waste.
Here, would you get
to work on this?
- Oh, actually, I'm sorry,
we weren't expecting you.
- Oh, god, so American.
What is it, five o'clock?
[laughs]
- [Scott] 6:30.
- If you got to a restaurant
in Paris at eight o'clock,
you'd be the first ones there.
- You know what?
We can have it tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
[Scott sighs]
- Well, I better be off.
- Would you like to
stay for dinner?
- That's a good idea.
- No, I couldn't impose.
- No, it's not an imposition.
I can just set out an extra...
- Alright, well, wonderful.
Talkie, get out the
good glasses.
I have a surprise for you.
- Is that the family rye?
- The last batch. [laughs]
- You make your own whiskey?
- Yeah, well, our
great-grandfather-
- Great-great-grandfather.
- Our great-great-grandfather
was a banker
and a man owed him money, and
after the markets crashed,
he couldn't pay in cash so-
- So Pop let him pay
us in whiskey.
- We've had a basement full
of stuff for almost a century,
but we're almost out now.
- To the fall of
our great house.
[glasses clinking]
[Meg coughs]
- Let me just grab the wine
and then we will be ready.
[Madelin chuckles]
- Looks delicious, Talkie.
- Yeah.
[silverware scraping]
- How are things at the firm?
- Oh, yeah, I'm still on
leave through the holidays,
but yeah, I spoke to the
partners and they
were suggesting
a January 10th return.
- [Madelin] Oh, that's
wonderful.
- What?
- I told you that.
- And Meg, Scotty tells
me you were an engineer.
- Am.
- Hm?
- I am an engineer.
I'm also returning to
work in the new year.
- Oh, that's fantastic news.
Scotty didn't mention it.
- Yeah, thank you.
- When?
When are you going back?
- I'm not exactly sure yet.
They're still reconfiguring
my position.
- Of course.
I'm sure they had to
shuffle things around a bit
when you got back.
- What do you do?
- Oh, a little of this,
a little of that.
I take care of my mother,
and then there's the land.
That just never stops.
- Madelin actually taught
in Korea after college.
Meg was born in Seoul.
- Oh!
[speaking Korean]
- Sorry, I don't speak Korean.
- Oh, [laughs] don't
worry about it.
I just asked when you left.
- Oh, I was adopted
when I was three.
- Oh.
- Can you pass the salt?
- Yeah.
- So I ran into the
Harrisons at the market.
- I heard they were selling.
- [Scott] Indeed, they are.
[Madelin gasps]
Their neighbors
[Minnow whimpering]
bought the property.
- Uh-huh.
- They're putting in a
pool over the entire lot.
- [Madelin] Oh.
- [Scott] Tearing down
the old house.
- Stop it.
You teach a dog to beg,
it'll never stop.
- Pass the salad.
[water whooshing]
[plates clinking]
- How are you guys
related again?
- [Scott] We're cousins.
- Like first cousins?
- Our dads are brothers, why?
- Nothing.
It's just
what was with Madelin
speaking in Korean to me?
- I think she was just
trying to connect.
- Okay, but I also have
family in Sweden.
I bet she wouldn't have tried
to speak in Swedish to me.
- Well, I don't think she
speaks Swedish, but okay.
[Meg sighs]
[Scott sighs]
Do you want me to talk
to her about it?
- No, thank you.
[Meg sighs]
- I know.
It's always made me kind
of uncomfortable,
but I [laughs] can't control
what they put on their walls.
- [Meg] Yeah.
- [Scott] And it was
a long time ago.
- But...
[Scott sighs]
- What?
- Well, what did your
grandparents do
when they were over there?
- My great grandparents
were missionaries.
- So they built churches and
taught people English, right?
- Right.
- Okay, and what did Madelin
do when she was over there?
- Okay, she taught
at a university.
- She taught English! [laughs]
- It's not the same thing.
- Really?
'Cause it feels like a
different iteration
of the same thing to me.
[Scott sighs]
- Well, I guess we
just disagree.
We can disagree, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[Meg gasps]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[tense music]
- Scott?
[high-pitched whining]
[slow thudding]
[Man whistles]
[muffled shouting]
- Hi.
- You gotta stay below
the water line
if you're gonna walk
around here.
- Why?
- It's private property.
- Are you a Whitman?
[Man laughs]
- No, I just do some
repairs for them
in exchange for fishing rights.
They're really uptight
about trespassing.
- I'm actually here with
my husband, Scott Whitman.
- Shit, sorry, I'm an idiot.
- [Meg] [laughs] No, it's fine.
- I didn't realize he was back.
Yeah, the summer crowd
doesn't usually come so often
during the off season.
- What do you mean so often?
- Nothing, just he was here
last winter for a while.
Hey, I'm really sorry
about what happened to you.
- Thank you.
[tense music]
[door thuds softly]
Why have we never come out here?
- There's just so much baggage,
so much family stuff out here.
I guess I'm realizing that
it's been so long since
I've been out here.
I'm glad we're here now.
[coat rustling]
[garage door rumbling]
[wrench clicking]
[screwdriver clicking]
[parts rustling]
[pencil scratching]
[tense music]
[both breathing heavily]
[door thuds]
- Stay with me.
[door thuds loudly]
[tense music]
[door banging loudly]
[high-pitched whining]
See?
Everything's fine.
[glass clattering sharply]
[tense music]
[Madelin singing eerily]
- Shit.
- Meg!
[Madelin laughing]
Go in, go in, I'll
be right there!
[footsteps thumping]
It's incredible for
the immune system,
the cold air and hot
water together.
I haven't been sick in years.
- Oh, thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
My mother became obsessed
with oil painting
when she got sick.
Can't tell you how many
hours we sat like that,
posing for her.
- You used to be blonde?
- Briefly.
- It doesn't look like you.
- She wasn't a great painter.
[Meg laughs softly]
- Who's the little boy?
- My brother.
- Your brother?
- He died when he was
five and I was eight.
We were swimming right
off our beach.
- I'm sorry.
- For most of my childhood,
I thought I dreamt
the whole thing.
My parents never talked
about him.
I don't know what possessed
my mother to paint him
into that portrait.
I'm not even sure it's
a good likeness.
- I think I saw her earlier.
- Who?
- Your mother, walking
in the woods.
- My mother is bedridden.
She hasn't left that
room in months.
- Oh.
How is she?
- She's dying.
- I'm sorry.
- She hasn't enjoyed
life for many years.
Death will be a mercy.
[tense music]
Coyotes.
They can be a real menace.
Mm, what's that?
- Oh, it's nothing.
Just a nervous habit.
- What are you nervous about?
- Nothing.
- Is it all the talk of death?
[Madelin chuckles]
Are you afraid of dying?
- Everyone is.
- Not everyone.
Some people believe we
go somewhere better.
Other people think anywhere
is better than here.
- May I use your bathroom?
- Right at the top
of the stairs.
[low rumbling]
- Wrong way.
[Meg chuckles awkwardly]
Upstairs.
[footsteps thumping]
[low rumbling]
[door clicks]
[footsteps clicking]
[door thuds]
[garbage clattering]
- Fuck!
[Meg grunts]
[tense music]
- Yoo-hoo!
[Minnow barking]
So I steal the keys.
- Naturally, I stole
the booze. [laughs]
- And we get out on the
water and it's pitch black
on the water, and I
look at Madelin,
I hand her the keys, and that's
when we realized [laughs]
neither of us knows how
to drive a boat.
So we just floated for a
little while and about an hour
into it, we realize we have
drifted well off our mooring,
like out into the bay,
and suddenly Madelin
gets a look of confidence.
- I mean, gin can do
that to a girl, you know?
- And she declares, "I'm
gonna drive us back."
- [Madelin] Yeah, and I did!
- Well, you did,
but you drove us
right into the neighbor's dock,
to be fair. [Madelin laughs]
So if the boat is totaled.
Their dock is like splinters.
She looks at me.
You remember what you said?
I'll never forget.
[Madelin clears throat]
- "Do you think mother will
notice the gin is gone?"
[both laughing]
- I love that story.
Oh, man.
- So what did you do?
- About what?
- The boat.
The dock.
- [Madelin] Oh, we had it
repaired, I mean. [laughs]
- Must have been expensive.
- Mm-mm.
We don't talk about money
at the dinner table.
- But we're already talking
about money.
- Meg, it's just a story.
- What do you mean?
- Well, that's what this
whole story is about.
[Scott sighs]
It's fine.
I'm not saying it's bad.
I just think it's funny.
Only rich people think it's
rude to talk about money.
- It's interesting you don't
consider yourself rich.
- Well, it's different.
I didn't grow up with money.
- But you have money now.
- My parents' life
insurance, not a trust fund.
- Because as I understand
it, you actually have
a good deal more money
than either Scott or me.
I'm not saying it's bad.
[wine sloshing]
Just funny.
[Meg chuckles quietly]
This has been lovely.
I should really go check
on my mother.
- Oh.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Yeah, I'll just...
If you're not done, we can...
[Meg laughs quietly]
- I'm done.
It's fine.
- She'll eat it later.
- It's fine.
- She doesn't like to eat
in front of people anymore.
- [Madelin] You poor thing.
[chair bangs]
[Meg chewing loudly]
[fork clangs]
- All done.
[door bangs]
[door creaking]
[drawer rustling]
[sheets rustling]
So we're just not gonna
talk about it.
[Scott sighs]
- They poisoned your food.
Not every time, but
enough to keep you scared.
And I'm sorry, I don't...
I'm sorry they did that to you.
[Scott breathes shakily]
- They made me make videos.
[tense music]
They made me beg you for help.
- Not tonight.
- Are you serious?
- [Scott] I'm tired,
I'm not doing this.
- We're having a conversation.
- No, we're not!
- You can't just decide that!
[door slams]
[high-pitched whining]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[garage door creaking]
[parts rustling]
[screwdriver scraping]
[wrench clicking]
[metallic clacking]
[motorcycle creaking]
[metallic clicking]
[high-pitched whining]
[slow music]
[engine rumbling]
[door creaking]
[slow jazzy music]
[muffled singing]
[patrons chattering]
[Meg clears throat]
[Man sighs]
- Look who it is.
- Oh, hey.
- Never thought I'd run
into a Whitman woman here.
- Thanks.
- I'm not a Whitman.
- You what?
- I kept my last name.
It's Rhoads.
- I'm Joe.
- Meg.
- Not Whitman.
[Meg laughs]
- So how long are
you in town for?
- Too long.
- [Joe] You don't like it here?
- It's a little...
- Lonely.
- [Meg] I was gonna
say claustrophobic.
[Joe laughs]
- [Joe] Thanks.
- Hey, do you know Madelin?
- [Joe] Madelin?
- My husband's cousin?
- Mm.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, I don't know her,
but I see her around.
- And my husband Scott.
You saw him around
too, last winter?
- Yeah, a couple times.
- Were they here at
the same time?
[Joe sighs uncomfortably]
- Can't you ask your
husband that?
- I'm asking you.
[Joe laughs]
- Look, I'm not keeping
a calendar
of every time I see a Whitman.
[Meg sighs]
- Right, sorry. [laughs]
- [Joe] All good.
- There's just something
off about her.
- Madelin?
- She's intense.
- I can believe that.
- [Meg] The way she smiles.
- Mm.
- She does it a lot.
- What a bitch.
[Meg laughs]
- [Meg] You think I'm crazy.
- Mm-mm.
No, no, no, no.
- Maybe I am crazy.
I feel fucking crazy.
- No, really, I get it.
In-laws are tough.
And the Whitmans...
[jaunty song begins]
Okay, stand up.
- No.
Wait, what were you saying?
- [Joe] Come on.
- What were you gonna say?
- Now, this is an old
Cape Cod-ian song.
[Meg laughs]
Come on, do another one.
[both laughing]
Do you know how to slow dance?
- I...
- Or waltz?
- Maybe, yeah. [laughs]
- Okay.
Seems like-
- Yeah. [laughs]
I've done it once
or twice before.
- Okay.
♪ Bonjour Tristesse,
Hello Sadness ♪
♪ It'’s all over now
pour toujours♪
[tense music]
- I'll be fine.
- No fuckin' way.
[Meg laughs]
- I swear, I'm fine.
- [Joe] I can't let
you drive home.
- [Meg] I gotta get
it back! [laughs]
- [Joe] Well, you can come
back for it in the morning.
- I can't leave it!
It's not mine.
- I'm right up there.
- No, no, no.
I wanna drive myself.
- You can't drive,
you're wasted.
- I wanna go home.
- I'm taking you home.
Careful, careful.
- Give me my keys.
- No way. [laughs]
- Get off me!
[Meg shouts]
[Joe grunts]
[tense music]
[Meg breathes heavily]
[engine rumbling]
- What the fuck?
[Joe groans]
[tense music]
[Joe spits]
[door creaks]
[footsteps thudding softly]
[Meg sighs]
[door clicks]
[coin rattling]
- [Scott] Where were you?
- Out.
[Scott sighs]
[footsteps thudding quietly]
Where were you?
Where were you when I was gone?
- Are you drunk?
- [Meg] Answer the question.
- You need to go to bed.
[clothes rustling]
- I wanna talk about the videos.
[Scott sighs]
- Oh my god.
I didn't get any fucking
videos, okay.
- Then why weren't you parked
in the driveway that night?
[Scott sighs]
- You sure you wanna do this?
You sure you wanna do
this again tonight?
- You asked me to get
your phone from the car,
but you weren't parked
in the driveway.
You were parked in the garage.
We never park there.
Why weren't you parked
in the driveway?
[Scott sighs]
Answer the fucking question.
- Am I under investigation here?
Am I?
Because you know, the
police, they asked me
all these questions already.
You remember?
And they were satisfied
with the answers I gave 'em,
so why aren't you satisfied?
Huh?
[Meg cries quietly]
Why aren't you satisfied?
[high-pitched whining]
Answer me.
Answer the fuckin'
question, please.
[Scott breathes shakily]
[tense music]
Meg.
[footsteps thudding]
[door bangs]
Meg!
Meg.
Open the door.
[door thuds]
Meg, open the fucking door.
[loud thudding]
[Meg gasps]
[door banging]
- Scott?
[water sloshing]
[Meg breathing heavily]
[calm vocalizing]
[Meg sighs]
- Meg.
[Meg gasps]
I'm so sorry, Meg.
[footsteps scraping]
[footsteps thudding]
[birds chirping]
[footsteps thudding softly]
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
Meggie.
Meg, please.
Meg.
Please, Meg.
I'm so sorry.
Meg, I'm so sorry.
Look at me.
Meg, Meg.
Meg, look at me.
[Scott cries]
I'm such a piece of shit.
I'm such a fucking asshole.
I can't lose you again.
I'll do anything.
[Meg breathes shakily]
[crow cawing]
- I wanna go home.
- Okay.
Okay.
Okay, we'll go home.
We'll go home tomorrow.
- Today.
- All right, we'll home today.
Thank you, thank you.
[Meg cries quietly]
Thank you.
[tense music]
[drawer rustling]
[clothes rustling]
Meg!
Meg.
So they can send someone
tomorrow.
It's okay.
We'll be back home tomorrow,
all right?
Just one more day.
You okay?
[Scott kisses]
[grass rustling]
- Why are we here?
- Just one drink, I promise.
We have to say goodbye.
- Why here, though?
- We used to throw parties
here when we were teenagers.
[Madelin laughs]
- Hello.
[tense music]
- Let's see if we still got it.
[ping pong ball clattering]
- [Scott] We threw this
big party here
at the end of the summer.
[Madelin laughs]
Do you remember the punch?
- [Madelin] Yeah, we
mixed it in a garbage can!
- Whoa, let me show you that.
[loud whistling]
- Come on, serve!
[knocking]
- I'm comin', I'm comin'.
Try it.
I think I fell off my
bike every 10 yards
on the way home.
- I wish I'd brought my bike.
Maybe then I would've
made it home
instead of passed
out on the beach.
- [Scott] [chuckles]
I forgot about that.
- I swear, my mother never did.
- How is your mother?
- She's hanging in there.
- We should stop by
before we leave.
I'd love to meet her.
- My mother is very frail.
- Don't you think she'd
enjoy some company?
- No, I don't.
Do you like it?
It's an heirloom from our
great-great-great-
great-grandfather.
Woo!
- Oh, come on.
[Madelin laughs loudly]
- John Jacob Whitman.
- Oh, wow.
There's a huge spider down here.
- [Meg] The banker?
- His great-grandfather.
- No, I'm good.
[alcohol sloshing]
- John Jacob Whitman was
a merchant and a diplomat.
He's credited with
opening the port of Canton
to Western trade.
[loud whistling]
[tense music]
You try.
- Uh-oh.
Look what we got here!
[Madelin gasps]
- Oh my god, let's play!
- Play what?
[tense music]
- Charades.
- Old rules apply.
[jar rattling]
- What do I have here?
Okay.
- One word.
Three syllables.
First syllable.
Drawing, writing, sketching,
painting.
Painting!
Art, art.
Art, art, art!
Art.
Third syllable.
Squeeze.
Angry grabbing.
Strangling, strangle.
Strangle, strangle.
Scott, I don't... Do something
else, do something else.
Try something different.
Try something different!
[Scot spits]
[Scott choking]
- Scott?
- Oh, choke! [claps]
Artichoke!
[Madelin laughs]
- [Scott] I scare you?
- My turn. [laughs]
[jar rattling]
Ah-ha.
- Here we go.
[Madelin clears throat]
Motorcycle.
Motorcycle diaries.
Drinking.
How many words?
Is it a book?
♪ Hello Sadness
♪ It'’s all over now... ♪
[Madelin breathing heavily]
[loud grunting]
I'm stumped.
Meg, you got any guesses?
Atta girl.
- So what was it?
The clue.
"Easy Rider."
All right, you're up,
you're up, you're up.
- That was really
bad "Easy Rider."
- [Madelin] What did you say?
- That was not good.
- [Madelin] Maybe you're
just a really bad guesser.
- Obviously I would've
been on the right track
if anybody was giving me
anything to work with.
[both laughing softly]
[low rumbling]
[tense music]
Meg, are you alright?
Aw, did you get a paper cut?
- No, I...
All better.
How are we looking?
Here you go.
I wanna go home.
Come on, it's just a paper cut.
[piano tinkling]
- Scott!
[bright piano music]
[tense music]
[glass clattering loudly]
[piano banging]
- [Madelin] You alright?
Meg, you need some water?
- I wanna go home.
- Let's go for a swim!
- What?
- The ocean is right there!
- It's freezing!
- Cold water is good for you!
- No!
- Suit yourself.
- Talkie?
- Megan, come on, come on.
- Scott!
[door bangs]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[water whooshing]
- No, no! [laughs]
No, it's too cold,
it's too cold,
it's too cold, it's
too cold! [tense music]
- [Scott] All right,
you gonna do it?
- Yeah, yeah!
One, two, three!
[Madelin laughing]
- What is wrong with you?
- No! [laughs]
- You wanna play dirty?
All right.
[Madelin laughing loudly]
Get in the water!
[tense music]
Meg!
Come on down!
- Join us!
[Meg breathing heavily]
[metallic rattling]
[engine rumbling]
[dog barking]
[loud crashing]
[Meg breathing shakily]
[Meg grunts]
[birds chirping]
[grass rustling]
- [Scott] She doesn't seem
to be getting any beter.
[muffled chattering]
- [Madelin] But you're
doing the best you can.
There's nothing more you
can do in this situation.
[birds chirping]
She needs real help.
[door scraping]
- Meg, Jesus Christ.
Where have you been?
Are you hurt?
Where's your coat?
- I'll make you some tea.
- [Meg] Get out.
- Meg.
- Excuse me?
- Get out.
- Hey, calm down.
- Oh my god, get the fuck out!
- Meg!
- Get out, Madelin! Go!
[footsteps thudding]
Goodbye!
[Madelin sighs]
- What the fuck is
wrong with you?
- [Meg] Where are the keys?
- [Scott] Meg.
- Where are the keys?
- [Scott] Meg, what happened?
- I'm going home.
- Meg, talk to me,
what happened?
- I don't know, Scott.
What could've happened?
What could've happened
in the last 24 hours
that would make me
wanna leave you?
Do you have any fucking guesses?
- Meggie.
- Just tell me where
the keys are!
- Can we just talk about this?
- I don't wanna talk
about it! I wanna go home!
- We'll go home, okay?
We'll go home.
- You knew she would
be here with us.
[Meg sighs]
Is Madelin even your cousin?
[chair thudding]
- Madelin is my cousin.
[Meg breathing shakily]
- Why did you bring me here?
Scott?
- I'm trying to be who
you need me to be,
but I'm out of my depth, Meg.
You've been having
such a hard time.
You won't talk to the
doctor, won't talk to me.
Sometimes it feels like
you're not even really there,
like you're seeing
something that I don't see.
[tense music]
Madelin, She was just
trying to help.
I needed help.
You need help.
You're barely eating,
you're barely sleeping.
Now with your sleepwalking-
- Wait, what?
- It's like living with a ghost.
[clinking]
- Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Babe, what's happening?
Tell me.
- I'm scared.
[Meg crying]
- Just calm down.
It's okay.
[water trickling]
I want you to write
this down, okay?
[Meg breathes shakily]
That's it.
That's a good girl.
[water sloshing]
[paper rustling]
[clock ticking]
[sheets rustling]
[Meg sighs softly]
- Scott?
[footsteps thudding quickly]
[sheets rustling]
[doors rattling]
[fabric rustling]
Where are the keys?
[drawer rattling]
[rustling]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[fabric rustling]
[Meg breathes heavily]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[computer clicks]
[Meg whimpering]
Someone please help me.
[Meg breathes shakily]
- [Kidnapper] Talk to him.
- Scott, please.
They're gonna kill me!
[Meg screaming]
[Meg crying]
[Meg screams]
[tense music]
[Meg breathes heavily]
- Minnow!
Minnow?
Minnow!
[Meg breathes shakily]
[tense music]
My mother is bedridden.
[gun clicking]
Hi, Meg.
I've been looking for
Minnow all night.
You'll help me look.
- Minnow?
Maybe we should go back.
- He could be hurt.
- What are you doing?
Keep going.
- It was an accident.
It was an accident.
Please.
[Meg breathes shakily]
[Madelin breathes shakily]
[loud thudding]
[Madelin grunts]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[Meg grunts]
[grass rustling]
[low rumbling]
I've been thinking about
your brother.
It must've been awful.
And afterwards, your parents
wouldn't talk about it.
You must've been so lonely.
And Scott, he was
like a brother.
And I can understand.
I'm not your enemy.
I just need to know
what happened.
Who hired them?
Was it you or was it Scott?
- Fuck you.
[tense music]
- What's the plan now?
Just kill me yourself?
- Why would I kill you?
You'll do it yourself.
You'll never feel normal again.
How could you, after
what you went through?
A person doesn't just recover
from something like that.
It rewires your brain.
It lives in your body
now, and you'll always,
always feel this way,
this emptiness,
like you're watching your life
pass by from behind glass.
You'll go through the
motions and you'll know
when you should be happy, but
you'll never really feel it.
And after a while,
that'll make you bitter.
You'll resent others for
moving on from something
that you can never leave behind.
- [Meg] Shut up.
- [Madelin] Eventually
you'll just be a burden.
- Shut up.
- You can make it all go away.
It will be a mercy.
- Shut up.
Shut up!
- [Madelin] You're broken!
- Shut up!
- You can't tell what's real-
- And what's just
a symptom of your
diseased brain.
- Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up, shut up!
- Madelin?
Madelin?
Oh, god, Madelin!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Madelin, Maddie, Maddie,
Maddie, Maddie.
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
Are you alright?
- What did you do?
- You wanted me dead.
- What the fuck?
- You made me go
into that garage
so you could take my money.
- We have to get her
to the hospital.
- Because you wanted
me to be with her.
Meg, you have to help me, okay?
Help me carry her.
- I saw the videos!
- I didn't do anything!
I don't know who took you!
- How am I supposed
to believe you?
[Scott sighs]
- You never will.
The first video was
delivered to our apartment
with a note while I
was still out here.
I didn't see it for
almost a month.
I thought you were dead.
I felt like I had killed you.
It was another month
before another video came,
and by that point, I
didn't know what to do.
I couldn't show the police.
They were already
investigating me.
[Scott cries softly]
I had already lost you, Meg.
I grieved for you.
- You grieved for me?
- I should've told you, I
should've told you, Meg.
I should've told you.
I'm so sorry.
- You grieved for me
for a month.
[tense music]
You grieved for me because
you missed the ransom note,
because you were here with her.
- You were already dead.
- I bet you liked the
attention, didn't you?
You liked being the handsome
widow on TV.
- No!
- Poor Scott Whitman, his
little Asian wife is dead.
I bet Madelin played
right along.
She made you feel special,
didn't she?
- You were already fucking dead.
- You're a coward.
[high-pitched whining]
Scott.
- I can't live like this.
It's too much.
[Meg cries quietly]
- Please.
- I'm sorry.
[gun clicks]
[loud thud]
[Scott grunts]
[Meg shouts]
[loud thud]
[Meg choking]
I'm sorry.
[Scott shouts]
[Meg gasping]
[footsteps thudding quickly]
[Meg breathing heavily]
Meg!
Get back here, Meg!
[gun rattling]
Meg, please.
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
I'm such a piece of shit.
I'm such a fucking asshole.
[tense music]
[gun clicks]
- Meg
- Let me go.
- Put the gun down.
- [Meg] Let me go.
- What?
I just wanna leave.
- You're the one with the gun!
[Scott laughs incredulously]
[high-pitched whining]
If you wanna go, go!
Yeah?
[water sloshing]
[Meg gasping]
[tense music]
[low rumbling]
[Meg choking]
[water sloshing]
[Meg gasping]
[Meg grunts]
[engine rumbling quietly]
- Hello?
[Meg breathes heavily]
[Meg cries quietly]
Are you okay?
[gun clicks]
[Meg breathes shakily]
[door thuds]
[engine rumbling]
[Meg screams]
[Meg laughs]
[keys jingle]
[door thuds]
[siren wailing]
[tense music]
[rhythmic vocalizing]
[eerie vocalizing]
[slow music]
[calm vocalizing]
[chill electronic music]