(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
(people chattering)
- It's bullshit.
Straight up government crap.
- I'm just happy to have a job.
- This place is a piece of shit anyway.
I'm glad it's getting shut down.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Andy.
- I'm on my last round today.
- Oh.
- Gosh, I'm gonna
miss this place.
- How you doing, Andy?
- I'm okay.
- Good.
- I've been here
30 years now.
Made a lot of memories.
- Yeah.
- See you guys.
- See you, bud.
- 30 years. Fuck.
- Nothing to miss about this place.
- Well, I'm looking forward
to a new work group.
- Wish I could say the same.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying I didn't get a new position.
New technology. Pay cuts.
I'm done.
Retirement won't be so bad.
Drinking, fishing,
banging Mrs. Jeeves.
- Ugh.
- Nice.
- You ready for our last shift?
- Yeah, there's just a lot of paperwork.
It's okay.
- It's our last shift, so.
- I know, I know. You're right.
Last shift.
- [Mason] So it is.
- Can I ask you a question?
(cup tapping)
Is it time we told everyone about us?
- Mm, go for it.
- Really?
- Everyone knows anyway.
- Who knows?
- You're not gonna believe it.
Hang on.
Mason, do you copy?
Mason, you there?
- Answer it. We'll chat later.
- Go ahead, Maise. What's up?
- [Maise] We need you in the office.
And bring Ashley with you.
- Why don't you call her?
- Mason, it's the worst kept secret
since Jeeves tried to sneak a joint
into the building in 1969.
- It was actually the '70s.
(Noob laughing)
- We're getting a new prisoner
for Ashley to evaluate.
Something about a trial.
They need to know how to
treat his insanity plea.
This demand's coming
straight from the state.
- Your kidding me?
- We don't make the rules,
we just follow them.
- What's the ETA?
- [Maise] The email just
came into the office,
but I think the bus is
already out the front.
- Fuck's sake.
Righto.
- I don't understand.
We're shutting down tomorrow.
I mean, I don't even
have all the resources
to do an accurate evaluation.
- All right, I better go meet them.
(Ashley sighing)
- Love you.
- [Mason] Love you too.
- Who is this guy anyway?
Some kind of perv?
- I don't know, eh.
- Probably some psycho
with nothing on his mind
but murder, mayhem.
- Let's keep it professional, shall we?
(bell ringing)
- Well, here he is.
- All right, everyone get ready.
(bell dings)
(suspenseful music)
- [Mel] Looks like something
out of a fucking horror movie.
- Time to move, big fella.
(suspenseful music)
(bell ringing)
- [Elevator] Doors closing.
(suspenseful music)
- You mob take him to accommodation.
I'll sign the paperwork.
- This way, mate.
You gonna play ball
or do you wanna get dragged?
(suspenseful music)
Play ball.
Good choice.
- Hickey, come back.
- And before you ask,
that thing oh his head doesn't come off.
Ever.
- [Mason] Why is that?
- Well, don't ask me, mate.
- Run this up to Ashley.
(keys tapping)
(Hickey knocking)
- Come in.
- Anyone home?
- Hey.
- Ash, what's going on?
- Nothing.
- Mason got this from the driver.
He asked me to bring it to you.
- Yeah.
Thanks, Hickey.
Okay.
What are you doing here then?
(light music)
And the trigger was?
(door shutting)
- What's wrong with you?
- Um, this patient that's just come in,
he, um,
he killed five women.
- [Maise] Mm. Yeah.
(light music)
- It just shocked me.
It's fine.
(dramatic music)
- Who's that?
Why has he got that
fucking thing on his head?
Hi, I know something.
I'm not fit.
(Klara laughing)
Come play with me.
You gotta go in.
Won't make no difference.
- This will be your new
hotel for the next 10 hours.
Enjoy.
I'm heading back to the camera room.
(door shutting)
- [Elevator] Doors closing.
- [Ashley] Ashley to Mason. Do you copy?
- Yeah, Ashley, go ahead.
- [Ashley] I can't review this guy.
- All right, I'll come up and chat.
(suspenseful music)
Why not?
- I just can't. I can't explain it.
- Can't explain what?
You can't say no. It's your job.
- [Mel] The new guy's losing his shit.
- Can someone check on
the new guy, please?
I can't do this right now.
But you should know by now,
you can trust me with anything.
- I do.
- So then do what you're good at
and get it over and done with, okay?
(keypad beeping)
- Hey, you dog.
You all right?
(intercom beeping)
- Oh.
(Klara knocking)
(intercom beeping)
- Gotta take a shit. Fuck.
(keys jingling)
(water splashing)
- [Phone] Fuck single moms in your area.
No signups, no worries.
Just text and ask to fuck.
View pictures of horny moms now.
(lighter clicking)
(door creaking)
(water running)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
(fists thudding)
(dramatic music)
(water running)
(suspenseful music)
- Shit.
Attention. Attention.
This is not a drill.
We have a code Black.
The patient is out confinement.
This is not a drill.
We have a code Black.
The patient is out of confinement.
(suspenseful music)
(radio thudding)
- [Mason] Team, let's
limit the chat on comms
and prepare for full lockdown.
(suspenseful music)
Mel, green light to
initiate full lockdown.
(alarm beeping)
- It's okay. It's okay.
We'll be okay.
(suspenseful music)
(door shutting)
He can't get in.
Look, Andy's locked the door.
We're completely safe.
(suspenseful music)
- Mel, can you see where he is?
- Nothing as yet.
Come on, where are you, you ugly bastard?
Should I call the cops?
- Yeah.
Then lock yourself in there.
- [Voice On Radio] No orders to him.
No other warnings. No offenses.
Have a look at some emails that were sent
for the other member.
- [Dispatcher] Delta 11?
- Delta 11. Go ahead.
- [Dispatcher] Delta 11, we
have a 101 and a possible 104
at the hospital on Blake's Road.
Can you attend?
- Delta 11. Roger that.
- Ashley, Maise, where are you?
- [Maise] We're in the
office. Andy's here too.
- I need you here.
Where's Noob?
Noob, come in.
You there? Noob?
- Mason, we're gonna stay here.
Everything's locked up. We're safe.
(suspenseful music)
(Ashley screaming)
What now.
Oh, it's alright.
Back up generator should come on.
(alarm beeping)
- Bet you didn't think this
would happen on your last night.
- It's happening.
We need to come up with a plan.
- Or kill him.
- Oh, shut up.
Mase, Klara's still up there.
How do we secure the patient?
- What about the police?
Can we call them?
- [Mason] Mel's onto it.
- Yeah, why can't we just wait for them?
- What do we need the cops for?
- [Mason] Mel, do you have eyes on him?
- Not as yet.
Wait, something's happening.
Mason?
- Yeah.
- We got a problem.
- [Mason] What now?
- The screens turned black.
I think he's covered the cameras.
- [Mason] What do you mean
he's covered the cameras?
- [Mel] He's covered the fucking cameras.
I can't see shit.
- How the hell does he
know how to do that?
- Well, they always do it in the movies.
- Well, just be glad this isn't
Silence of the Fucking Lambs.
- [Mason] Make your way
down to the team room.
Be careful.
- Okay, I'm coming.
Fuck this shit.
- What the fuck is going on?
(everyone chattering)
- All right, Calm down.
When Mel gets here,
we'll discuss how we're gonna handle him.
(light music)
(door creaking)
(door shutting)
(suspenseful music)
(door creaking)
(Mel yelling)
Get down. Get down now.
- Mel.
(dramatic music)
(Mel gasping)
(static)
(dramatic music)
Mel, answer me.
(light music)
- I say we make a run for the exits
and let the cops handle it.
What? I'm retiring tomorrow.
- We've got the manpower.
We can put this guy back in his place.
- All right, cowboy.
What is it that you
think you have to prove?
- Let's find a private little
room and I'll show you.
- Oh, you are so not my type.
- Shut up!
(suspenseful music)
Ashley, you still got
the file there, right?
What does it say? What do we need to know?
- [Ashley] I'll read what it says.
Paul Atkins, convicted for
the murder of five women
pending a mandatory
mental health assessment
by order of the presiding judge.
And it also says here,
he lost his family in a hit and run.
(suspenseful music)
- We need to find this guy.
Jeeves, you and Hickey team up.
Fiona, you and Stephanie.
- Really?
- I'll go get Andy.
All right.
Let's get it done.
(suspenseful music)
- You got really worked up before.
- I know I'm not supposed to.
I just,
I just took it really personally.
- Do you wanna talk about it?
- No.
I mean, maybe one day,
but not here like this.
- Listen, I know that Paul fella's
done some monstrous things,
but I read in his file that
he lost his whole family
to a hit-and-run accident.
- Yeah, I, um, I read that too.
- You know, that's how I lost my Howard
and my little girl, Sally.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
- Sally didn't die on the road that night.
But that's why I spent
so many years of my life working here.
- I don't understand.
- Well, she had a room here
in this facility for 10 years
before she passed away.
(somber music)
Anyway,
with Andy on the job,
no one's getting through the door.
(Maise and Ashley laughing)
- This is fucking bullshit.
Last night on the job, I'm
chasing a fucking fugitive.
- Shh.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And seriously, I've
worked here all of my life
and I can tell you now,
nothing like this has
ever happened before.
- Did you see that?
- I didn't see anything.
- I saw something. I'm sure of it.
Do we radio Mason?
- No. Make too much noise.
And that spithood wanker would hear us.
Come on.
What do you reckon?
Up or down?
- Down, I think.
- All right, son.
Lead the way.
- Me?
You're the security guy.
- You'll be all right.
(suspenseful music)
(keypad beeping)
- It's empty.
(suspenseful music)
- Hickey! Hickey!
Hickey. Hickey, hang in there, mate.
Don't hurt him, you fucking asshole.
- [Hickey] No.
(fist thudding)
(dramatic music)
(keypad beeping)
(suspenseful music)
- Fuck! Fuck me!
God.
Jesus. God.
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus, come into my life.
Forgive me my sins
and grant me the gift
of eternal salvation.
Amen.
(suspenseful music)
Jesus fucking Christ, I need a joint.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Oh.
Fuck me.
- He's gonna get in here.
- No, that's not gonna happen.
- Maise?
- Mm?
- What would you do
if you found the person
who killed your family?
(light music)
- I hate this place.
It gives me the creeps.
- I'm gonna get a glass of water.
- All this craziness going on
and you wanna get a glass of water?
(water pouring)
(suspenseful music)
(wall banging)
(pan crashing)
Fiona?
(suspenseful music)
(Fiona screaming)
Oh my God.
Seriously?
- Got you good, didn't I?
- That's not funny.
- It's a little bit funny.
(suspenseful music)
(Fiona screaming)
(Stephanie thudding)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Fiona screaming)
- Help me!
(suspenseful music)
(door banging)
(lid banging)
(garbage banging)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Fiona screaming)
(dramatic music)
(phone buzzing)
- Is that little Johnny, is it?
- It's John. You know he hates that.
- Oh, I know he hates it.
That's what I call him it.
He's a bit of a dickhead.
- You're a bit of a dickhead.
- He's a fucking dickhead.
- [Radio] Address on Old County Road.
- I just don't think he treats you well.
- He's not so bad.
(person on radio speaking indistinctly)
- Let's go check this out, eh?
- [Radio] Zero, three, six,
four, seven, one, four, four, four.
(car doors shutting)
(person on radio speaking indistinctly)
(dog barking)
- [Radio] Yeah, roger that.
(person on radio speaking indistinctly)
- Thought this place was a hospital.
(dog barking)
- Can't see any lights on.
- There's nothing here.
- [Officer] It's all boarded up.
- Wanna call it in?
- Yep.
Delta 11.
- [Dispatcher] Delta 11. Go ahead.
- Delta 11. We don't see anything here.
So we're gonna resume patrols.
- [Dispatcher] Roger that, Delta 11.
(car doors shutting)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
- Ashley.
(door slamming)
Ashley.
Ashley, wake up.
- I just had a bad dream.
I couldn't move.
It was him.
- You were screaming and sweating.
I had to wake you up.
- [Ashley] Maise.
- Yeah?
- [Ashley] You didn't answer me before.
- [Maise] When was that, love?
- I asked you what you would do
if you found the person
who killed your family.
- Well, I'd want justice.
(suspenseful music)
I'd fucking kill him.
(phone ringing)
(suspenseful music)
(door shutting)
- Why haven't the cops shown up yet?
- I don't know.
But we need to get back upstairs.
- What about Stephanie?
She was with Fiona.
- Stephanie, come in.
Stephanie, you there?
- It's not like her not
to respond straight away.
- Radio silence.
Look, we should check on Klara.
We've still got a duty to care to her.
- You guys check on Klara.
Meet me back at the office.
- I don't reckon we should split up, Mase.
Mase.
(door shutting)
What are you doing?
- Just some rubbish, that's all.
(keypad beeping)
- Klara, you all right, love?
- It's gray's birthday.
- Let's get her back to the office.
- Yeah.
Just get your, your shoes on.
Why don't you get them on?
(suspenseful music)
(door slamming)
Andy, what are you doing, mate?
(suspenseful music)
Andy, get back in here now.
Andy. Andy.
Andy, get back in here.
Andy.
(door banging)
Leave him alone, you fucking bastard.
Fucking hell.
You bastard.
Shit.
(Andy thudding)
You fucking bastard.
(door banging)
- [Mason] Ash. Ashley.
- Mason?
- Help me, Ash.
- We haven't caught him yet.
- Are you saying he's still out there?
- [Mason] Yeah.
- What about the cops?
- Mel rang them, but they didn't rock up.
- Well, fucking ring them again.
- Doesn't matter anyway.
This place is built to ensure
that if a lockdown comes into effect,
no one can get out, meaning
- No one can get in. Fuck.
- They probably came and left,
thought the place was closed.
- My daughter died in this place.
I never thought I'd die here too.
- Andy, Jeeves.
Jeeves, you there?
- Okay, man. Yeah, yeah.
I'm here, Mason.
- Can you and Andy come
down to the office?
- Sorry, mate.
I can't do that right now.
- Are you okay? What's happened?
- No, mate.
Andy's dead.
Look, I'm,
I'm stuck in confinement.
Can you get Ashley to
release cell door two?
- [Mason] Yeah, copy that.
Where's Klara?
- I'm here.
- No.
She's here, mate. She's here.
I'll tell you what.
If she wasn't crazy
before, she fucking is now.
(Klara laughing)
(keypad beeping)
- Maybe we just wait him out.
- It's not that simple.
- What the hell does that mean?
- In his file, you said
his family was killed.
- Yeah, hit-and-run. Left them for dead.
- What if the driver didn't?
- Didn't what?
- Drive off.
- What?
- What if the driver stopped
first and then drove off?
Something or someone in
here has triggered him.
(light music)
- Okay, so what now?
- I have an idea.
Paul.
Paul Atkins.
I know you can't respond,
but I also know you can hear me.
I'm sorry for what
happened to your family.
I really am.
But all I wanna do is talk.
I'm not going to hurt you.
You have my word.
You can trust me.
(light music)
(somber music)
(suspenseful music)
- [Maise] Mason, you got him trapped yet?
- Maise, Ashley, are you there?
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
- I was the one who killed his family.
- I, I don't understand.
- I was driving the car that day.
(somber music)
- Are you telling me all
of this is because of you?
- [Ashley] I'm so sorry.
- Is, is that
what you're telling me?
- I'm so sorry.
- Oh, Jesus Christ, Ashley.
- [Maise] None of them had to die, Ashley.
- Maise, I'm so sorry. None of
this was supposed to happen.
(somber music)
I'm sorry, Maise.
- Just stop.
Stop talking.
Oh.
(somber music)
Well, I don't know how
you're gonna sleep at night.
- Oh, Maise.
- Don't, don't, don't.
Just
- It wasn't supposed to happen.
- Jesus, I never would've,
I know I, just don't.
- It didn't
- Op.
(somber music)
How pathetic.
- [Ashley] Please don't tell.
- Pathetic.
- [Ashley] Please, just don't tell anyone.
- You're asking me to keep
your filthy little secret?
I don't think so.
You're gonna pay for this.
For every single one of them.
Do you hear me?
Every single one of them.
(somber music)
- I'm sorry.
- It's not me you have to apologize to.
It's all their families.
You've gotta go and tell them.
You're a coward, Ashley.
- I'm sorry.
(bell ringing)
(bell dings)
(suspenseful music)
(Jeeves groaning)
(bottle thudding)
(suspenseful music)
(light music)
(light music continues)
- [Mason] Maise, do you copy?
- We're here, Mason. I
need to tell you something.
- What? You can't tell him.
- [Mason] I need you to
take us outta lockdown.
And when I say, lock it back down again.
- It's my job.
- You tell him or I will.
I'll be right back.
- Maise.
I have a really bad feeling about this.
- I'm going.
(suspenseful music)
- Maise, lock it down now.
(alarm beeping)
(door shutting)
- Ashley?
Ashley?
(light music)
- Ashley, what are you doing?
- His wife's name was Sarah.
(somber music)
It was me.
I'm the driver.
I love you, Mason.
Stop. Stop.
Stop, Mason, stop.
Mason, no, no, no.
Mason! Mason!
Mason, no.
Mason, Mason, Mason.
Please.
(soft music)
No, no, no, not Mason.
Mason, stop. Wake up!
Please. (cries)
(soft music)
(door clanging)
- See?
I told you I'd get it done.
(dramatic music)
Hey.
I'll take care of those.
(dramatic music)
(sirens blaring)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)