Gayatri, open the door!
Open it!
Gayatri!
Come here, Gayatri.
Ms. Gayatri put a lot of faith
in this search.
We don't have much time.
Not yet.
We're still at a dead end.
Ask her to be patient.
For how long?
We've been patient for 20 years now.
And all this must be
passed on immediately.
Dewi?
Mom.
Wi, here.
Here. You have to wear this all the time.
This is just some leaves, Mom.
- Look at me. I'm okay.
- No. It's dangerous.
Where's Sena?
Is he still not home? It's already late.
VOTE DARMAJI FOR SUB-DISTRICT HEAD
PROGRESS FOR KISAREJO
WE CAN DO IT WITH DARMAJI
What do you want? I'm with my boss.
Where are you taking him now?
Do you know what time it is?
Do I need to explain it to you again?
If you're not home by this hour,
Mom never shuts up about it.
I'm just tired.
I served people here and there for money.
And now I have to
face someone stubborn like you?
Can you just shut up?
I'm tired too!
I'm also working
an extra job for you and Mom.
Can't you even be grateful?
What extra job?
Your boss is a stingy man.
What's wrong, Mom?
- This is dangerous.
- What is it?
They're trying to separate us.
We have to find a way.
Nobody can separate us, Mom.
This is dangerous, Dewi.
We're safe, Mom. I'm here.
Because you can't see
whoever's coming. You can't see it!
You say it all the time,
but nothing has happened, right?
- But…
- We are safe. I got you. Come here, Mom.
Just breathe. I'm here.
Let's go to your room
and take your medicine, okay?
Sorry, ma'am, but did you record that?
No.
This is just another video.
Sena.
Here, for earlier.
Don't forget to wash the car
after what we did earlier.
Remember how last time
Mr. Darmaji almost found out about us?
Sorry, ma'am.
Mom?
Mom.
Come on.
What are you doing, Mom?
Mom?
Mom.
- Dewi…
- Mom.
Mom…
What are you doing, Mom?
What is that in your mouth?
Mom, that's just jujube leaves, not food.
- This is the only way.
- There is no one here.
No one is coming, Mom.
Nobody's there. I was just inside.
Go back to your room, okay?
Come on.
It's just me.
Okay?
Come on.
Sit down.
Oh, you're back already?
I had to do overtime.
You should have let me know.
I bought you a phone
so I could call you when I'm with Mom.
She's having another episode.
And I had to calm her by myself.
Where is she now?
She's asleep.
Really?
Should I wake her up?
So what should I do?
Give me the bike key.
I need to use it.
What now?
It's out of gas.
You asshole.
Oh, and I haven't paid
this month's installment.
Can you pay it?
Are we installing it right away?
Go and check inside, let me prepare it.
Ouch.
SUB-DISTRICT OFFICE
- Morning, miss.
- Morning, Ms. Dewi.
I'm from Best Net, can we set up now?
I'm really sorry, Ms. Dewi,
but the boss changed his mind.
What happened?
He asked for another provider.
But this is too sudden.
I don't know about that.
Bara.
Make sure that my work is not interrupted
because of bad internet service.
Yes, sir.
Tari, have you let them know
that we're switching providers?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, miss.
DARMAJI'S TEN WORK PROGRAM
You're Sena's friend, aren't you?
Used to be.
Some asshole your boss is.
- Canceling at the last minute like this.
- "Asshole"?
Like your brother, then?
Hello.
Okay, got it.
Where's your brother?
Where is he?
Listen.
I have been waiting for this.
Because he needs to pay for his sins.
I don't know…
- Where is he?
- I don't know!
- You son of a bitch!
- Quiet!
Shut up.
Shut up!
Mom!
What do you want?
Bastard!
Mom!
Yes, boss?
We only found his sister and mother.
- Get rid of them.
- Yes, boss.
Where is Sena?
Mom!
Your son is an idiot, you know that?
He slept with another man's wife!
Mom!
Let's get out of here!
You son of a bitch!
We finally found Ms. Diah.
DEAD BODY OF A MURDER VICTIM
FOUND IN HER HOME AT KEBUN KARANG
Does Ms. Gayatri know about this?
She does.
And I've texted you the address.
Alright.
Everyone, stay out!
We're leaving.
What did you do this time?
Answer me.
They came here…
neither for me…
nor Mom.
But you.
They were looking for you.
They said it was because of your sins.
And Mom had to die for that.
You did this to her.
Dewi…
You're tired. You're talking gibberish.
Dewi!
I know about your friend
from the sub-district office.
I'm begging you,
please explain to me what's going on
before I hear from someone else
about what you did.
I don't know.
Answer me.
I know you know it.
- Tell me!
- Dewi, please.
- Just answer me!
- I said, I don't know!
Are you done?
Are you happy now?
- Hey!
- This idiot can't even pay for his bike.
You asshole!
Next time, pay your installment!
Dewi.
- Dana…
- Sena.
What are you doing here?
I want to apologize.
For what?
I want to apologize
for leaving you and your mother.
I want
you to come with me.
You waited until Mom was dead.
- Then you finally come for us… What?
- Dewi.
- Are you defending him?
- I'm not defending him.
Then go with him.
You don't have to ask me.
Can you live alone?
All this time,
I've been taking care of Mom alone.
You weren't there.
Never mind this man.
It was just me.
I never intended to
leave you and your mother.
Dewi.
Why now?
If you two come with me,
there's one big thing
that we can fix together.
Who killed her?
Sen?
What are you doing?
Sena?
Sen?
Dewi, help me.
Dewi?
Help me!
Mom?
Dewi, it's me.
What's wrong?
I saw Mom.
No, Mom is not here.
She's not here. It's just me.
It's just me.
Take a deep breath.
Dewi.
I understand
that you're disappointed in Dad.
But you have to leave this place.
Look at this.
There's only trauma, and sadness.
Can you guarantee anything?
Whatever it is,
it's better than being here.
Esti. This is Dewi.
And this is Sena,
you've met before, right?
Welcome back, Sena.
Dewi.
She'll take care of your needs here.
Just bring your stuff.
She will show you the room.
Right. Come on.
Dewi, Sena.
Come with me, please.
Dewi. This is Ms. Gayatri.
Grandma.
You've grown up, Sena.
Yes, Grandma.
Esti, take them to their rooms.
Yes, ma'am.
Please.
Those are pictures of
the heads of the family.
They are your ancestors.
It has become a tradition in our family
that the company leadership
is carried out and passed down
from woman to woman.
And finally,
the family line is also led by
us, the women.
And I really hope
that you can replace me
as the company leader
and carry on the family line
that has been built by your ancestors.
Can I eat this right away?
Yes, you can, Sena.
Go ahead.
What have you been up to all this time?
Just working odd jobs, Grandma.
As long as I make money.
What do you mean by odd jobs?
Breeding chickens,
and selling them to the market.
Selling bootleg DVDs.
Swallow it first.
Swallow your food first.
Sorry.
Sena used to be a private driver.
And Dewi
is an internet technician.
That's great.
You're not eating?
No, honey.
You can eat as much as you want.
Tomorrow you're going to learn
everything about our family business.
What are you doing here?
Sorry,
I thought it was the bathroom.
Not anymore.
No one is allowed to enter this room.
The bathroom is over there.
Dewi.
Dewi…
You're here already.
Yes, Mother.
Three generations of
our family have made a living
from meat processing.
I brought you here with one purpose
so that you can learn.
Because all of this
will be yours to manage in the future.
- Dewi?
- Let me go after her.
It's alright.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
- I will take care of it.
- That's okay.
I've heard what happened to your mother.
I understand how you feel.
Remember.
No matter how bad your experience is
you must realize that it has passed.
And now it's time for you
to live your future.
And your future is here.
And I'm here too.
I will make sure that whatever you want,
I will make happen.
Like this?
- That's good.
- Right?
By the way, Dad.
I accidentally found a room
filled with old kinds of stuff yesterday.
What was that?
You went into your Grandma's private room?
Well, it wasn't on purpose.
I thought it was the bathroom.
Because I remember it was
the bathroom when I was little.
And inside, there were photos,
but the males are all crossed out.
What's with that?
Good afternoon, Mr. Agung.
- Where were you, Jaka?
- I'm from the office.
Let me introduce you. This is Sena.
This is Jaka.
- Hello, sir. Jaka.
- Hi.
He's a friend of mine.
I consider him like a son.
You don't have to say that.
I have to go now.
I have to meet Mr. Darsono.
- Okay.
- See you later.
Excuse me, Sena.
- Good morning, everyone.
- Thank you, sir.
Good morning, ma'am.
Dewi.
This is Jaka, our head of administration.
Jaka. My granddaughter, Dewi.
Teach her everything.
Yes, ma'am.
Please, sit down.
Thank you, Mr. Jaka.
Just call me Jaka.
This is the company profile.
And here's the financial report
and the administration's SOP.
Let me explain our financial report first.
Here you can see
that from 2000, the numbers are good.
Up to 2003, 2008, and even 2013.
But in 2017
our income dropped drastically again.
Until now.
What was the reason?
That year, many of our cows
started to get sick.
I don't know why.
Next, you can see our company profile.
Please read it.
Are you sure this isn't a misprint?
"Ms. Gayatri Desari
has run the business since 1935."
No. It's really like that.
Ms. Esti, we heard some strange news.
Suddenly, the adult cows
have been recovering.
Their vitality is stabilizing
and their blood pressure is
starting to drop.
- Okay.
- Yes, ma'am.
So what should I do now, Esti?
Even though they're both back
and the slaughterhouse
is in a better state,
their arrival is making you sick.
I understand that they just arrived.
But we have to speed up the inheritance.
No.
We have to give them time.
Who's that?
SEARCH
RATU SUBUR ABADI SLAUGHTERHOUSE
NO SEARCH RESULTS FOUND
END OF SEARCH
You idiot.
- Knock first.
- Sorry.
Do you know that Grandma is sick?
Sick of what?
I don't know, but
I heard she and Esti talking
about her being sick and in pain.
What's wrong with her?
Well, she's an old lady.
But she sounded very angry.
She was angry at something?
Who else talks like that?
Of course it was her.
And then?
Then I heard them talking about
an inheritance
that needs to be passed down soon.
It's normal for old people
to talk about inheritance.
You're right.
You don't make any sense.
Now get out.
- These are the leaves you're looking for.
- Thank you.
- The room key…
- I'll let you know, okay?
What are you doing?
I'm making myself a cup of tea, Esti.
I've told you if you need anything,
you can call me.
Thank you.
I need to ask you something.
I read about the company's history.
It says that Grandma
has run the company since 1935.
Are you sure they didn't make a mistake?
That means
she's about 100 years old.
Who told you that, Ms. Dewi?
Jaka.
I was put in charge of
the administration with Jaka.
Grandma ordered him to do it.
All you need to know is that
a lot of people in the company are jealous
of Ms. Gayatri and Mr. Agung's success.
That's why I told you,
if you have a question or anything
just ask Ms. Gayatri.
Not anyone else.
I need to talk about Ms. Dewi.
I told you last night
to give her some time.
We don't have time anymore, ma'am.
We've been waiting for
20 years, and we can't fail.
And it looks like Mr. Agung
and Jaka are working on their plans.
Give me two days.
Yes, ma'am.
How long have you been here?
About five years, sir.
Five years.
That's quite a long time.
So you know a lot about this business.
And you're pretty close to my family.
You even came to
our home during the night.
Yeah, pretty much, sir.
As Mr. Agung said,
I'm pretty close with him.
That's why I also know
that you just met Mr. Agung
after he left you
at the age of seven, right?
What do you mean by that?
Nothing, sir.
I just think that I owe Mr. Agung.
My father used to work here
then he got into an accident and died.
Since then, I have been…
A day off, finally.
A day off?
What are you talking about?
They told us to have a day off. They said,
Ms. Gayatri had an event with her family.
Maybe to celebrate
her grandchildren's visit.
Hello, sir.
They're moving ahead, sir.
Yes, I'm sure.
I just got the news
that we're going to have a day off.
Yes, sir.
Sena.
Hey.
You drive. Okay?
Can you do it?
I'm a driver, Dad.
Right.
Don't forget to pick up your stuff
in the trunk tomorrow.
Why not now?
Just do it tomorrow. Okay?
I want you to promise me one thing.
And I want you to keep that promise.
What is it?
You said she was in pain.
How should I know?
That's what I heard.
Are you two talking about me?
- No?
- Yes, he said…
So is it yes or no?
Esti.
Sorry if I keep surprising you, Ms. Dewi.
If you're done,
please go straight to madam's room.
She needs to tell you something.
Come in, dear.
Come in.
I hear from Esti
that you like to listen to music.
Correct?
These are yours?
Yes.
I've been collecting them
for almost 30 years.
Vinyl. Cassette tapes.
Your father also loves them.
But lately, he's not into it anymore.
Because he said I have too many records.
He gets overwhelmed when he sees them.
"If you don't want to listen to them,
just put all the records in the closet."
That's what he said.
Esti.
Beat me this time.
Are you listening to Iga Susanti too?
"Morning and Night Together."
This is one of my favorite albums.
Really?
I also like this album.
I have the tape version, it was Mom's.
I know.
That's the tape player
that you like to use before bed, right?
How do you know?
I bought the tape player for your mother.
Your mother liked to
spend her time with me.
Because I used to be sad and lonely
when I didn't have anyone to accompany me.
I miss my mother.
For some people
death is a mere passing.
Not a separation.
But if we want to meet with those
who are no longer with us,
I think you need a struggle to get there.
Don't you think so?
What do you mean?
No.
I just think too much sometimes.
In short,
your mother and I had a lot in common.
Especially in our taste of music.
Let's dance.
- I can't dance.
- It's easy.
I will teach you. It's easy.
Like this. Move this foot forward.
- Forward.
To the side.
Back.
Forward.
Do you get that?
You're good at it now!
It's easy, right? I know you could do it.
What's your big plan?
I'm just taking care of my master.
And if your plan fails?
Hey!
Stop!
I let you win all this time.
But not now.
This time,
you're the one who failed.
Forward. Step.
Back. Step.
You can do it, right?
Of course you can.
Grandma?
Esti!
We got a burglar, Dad.
- A burglar?
- He's out in front. Let's go.
I heard a voice in that room.
And then the burglar
ran towards the front gate.
But now he's gone.
Come on!
Just go back and rest.
What about the burglar?
We're not going to do anything about it?
I think you better rest for now.
Okay?
What's wrong with her?
I don't know.
She was teaching me.
She was teaching me
how to dance and then she fell.
She has chronic anemia.
She mustn't do heavy activities.
Including dancing.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Now you know.
And there are still many things you need
to know about Ms. Gayatri and the company.
If something happens to her,
you will inherit everything.
And whether you want it or not,
you have to be ready.
Please.
Here it is, sir.
I'm still confused, sir.
Why now?
Do you know what the condition
of our slaughterhouse was like
before Sena and Dewi came?
Yes, I know.
It was miserable.
Many livestock were dead.
And after they came
the livestock became healthy again.
The demon in my mother's body has risen.
And it's eating her from the inside.
Trying to find a new host.
And do you know who the new host is?
Oh, of course.
This is the only thing that can
stop the demon from poisoning my family.
My life will be better tomorrow, Jaka.
Tomorrow,
meet me and Dana in the slaughterhouse.
- Who is Dana?
- I mean Sena.
Yes, sir.
Forgive me, Mother.
I have to do this for my children.
- Mr. Agung!
- Who did that?
Oh my god!
Who did this?
Let's ask Jaka.
He was here the whole time.
- No… That was…
- Jaka.
- No, I just got here.
- What did you do?
Jaka.
- I didn't do it!
- Help him down.
- Get back here!
Stop, Jaka!
- Stop, Jaka!
Dad!
Get me a ladder!
Dad…
Agung
was never a perfect child.
He wasn't a respected father either.
But his intentions were always good.
He always tried
as much as possible
to carry everyone's burden.
Let's sit inside.
But in the end
the burden was too heavy
for him to carry alone.
Even so,
you will always be remembered, my son.
We have to get out of here.
You're the one who wanted to come here.
Why do you want to leave now?
I can't explain it right now.
But the point is,
we have to leave.
Sena.
Sena!
- Wait!
- What do you want?
Sit down.
Talk slowly.
I know you're upset now.
I know we just lost our father.
I felt so miserable too
when we lost our mother
that I went crazy.
Don't you dare compare her to Dad, okay?
Dad is a sane person.
Do you know what he said?
"We have to take care of Dewi."
So it's impossible that he killed himself.
He wasn't crazy like Mom.
Watch your mouth!
You asshole.
If he were a sane person,
he would be here to take care of us.
Where was he?
Mom went insane because of Dad.
- Dad was never there.
- It's all because of you!
Mom lost her mind because of you!
They were separated because of you!
My life was happy for seven years.
And then you came and changed everything!
So that's your excuse?
You were never there for us.
I had to be responsible for everything!
I almost went crazy because of Mom!
Because you were
never there, just like Dad!
You always ran away from us!
Don't forget that Mom died because of you!
And Dad must've died because of you too.
It's all because of you! Don't you--
Go to hell!
Sena.
I know you're both uncomfortable.
But Mr. Agung
helped me a lot.
I owe him a lot
because Mr. Agung helped me to work here.
Now I can't repay his kindness.
Jaka did this, sir.
I hope this helps you to get closure.
Excuse me.
SENA, MEET ME AT THE COWSHED TONIGHT
PLEASE COME ALONE… THANK YOU
Dewi.
Mom.
I miss you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
I couldn't do anything.
Calm down, Dewi.
I'm always here for you.
I need you here, Mom.
You have to listen to me, okay?
Yes, Mom. Anything.
I will do anything for you.
But please stay with me.
Don't leave me again.
I'm so lonely without you.
You're here alone, right?
Sena.
I know what happened to my father.
It's hard for me to accept.
But I can explain everything
that happened to your father.
Sena.
Calm down.
Why did you kill my father?
Kill him?
- I can explain everything.
- Was it money?
Sena…
Or power?
No, I can explain everything.
He was kind to you.
They did all this because of Dewi.
Dewi?
You're still awake?
Sena, no!
You're trying to get rid of me.
Dad is dead because of you!
Dewi changed because of you!
It's all because of you!
Dana!
Open the trunk.
The trunk…
I think I'm going crazy.
I miss my mom.
She comes here a lot.
But then…
she suddenly disappears.
Sometimes she looks scary.
But…
Mom came earlier.
And she was kind.
But…
I'm here for you.
Lady Heras?
THE PROPHET
Esti?
INHERITANCE RITUAL
I'll do anything for you.
Do you want to meet your mom?
I do. I want to see my mom again.
There's a way.
But it's full of sacrifices.
Whatever it is. No matter what.
I will do it.
Of course.
Like this.
Are you kidding?
Now you do it.
Good.
Incision in hand?
A pact?
Jujube leaves for my wife and Dewi.
Don't forget to always remind them to
take care of the bonsai that I gave you.
The inheritance ceremony will be held
when the female
offspring enters adolescence.
The male child will be sacrificed.
So I have to stop it by killing my mother.
Slowly.
Good.
Let me take that.
Okay, now we do this.
We unite our hands.
And you'll meet your mother right away.
She'll be here soon.
Dewi.
- Sena.
- Dewi?
Dewi?
Sena?
Dewi! What happened?
Come on. We have to get out of here.
Why did Mom have to die?
- Why did Dad have to die?
- Dewi, you're talking nonsense.
- Why…
- Come on!
- Why did it have to be them?
- Dewi, please, stop it!
- Why Mom?
- Please, Dewi. Please.
Why didn't you die?
You gave me your promise, Dewi.
Now it's time to go home.
Soon you will meet her.
Mom?
We are not worthy
of being protected forever.
We are nothing but a mere burden.
We are just a vessel
for the sacrifice.
For the glory.
That is worthy of all souls.
I am just a burden.
In time becomes eternal.
Heras is the immortal.
Universe bliss.
Everlasting.
Mom.
Mom!
DARKNESS ALWAYS SEEKS YOUR SADNESS,
YOUR ANGER, AND YOUR HAPPINESS
AND ONLY GOD IS THE BEST SALVATION