Senior Yus.
Do you know Malay martial arts?
Yes, I do. Why?
Well, I was actually
thinking about learning...
the art of self-defense.
Jusoh to control center.
The cops are here for routine check.
We're scanning their IDs.
The art of self-defense?
You've come to the right person.
- Really?
- Yes.
Back when I was 12,
I was a champion in Malay Silat.
District level.
After that, I learned Taekwondo...
Control Unit,
I'm taking them to the CCTV room.
Karate.
Wushu. Aikido.
Muay Thai.
Wing Chun.
Even Jeet Kune Do.
Oh wow. Jeet Kune Do!
Jeet Kune Do.
You know... Bruce?
Bruce Lee? Yes, yes.
I am developing my own...
"art of martial."
Art... martial.
Come. Let me show you.
Senior Yus. It's okay.
Danger is always lurking.
We have to always be ready...
- as secutoret guards.
- Se... security.
Danger comes unannounced.
Look at that! The strong room.
Millions stored in it.
- But it's okay. I'm here.
- Senior Yus...
- Back in the day, I alone could take on...
- But...
Senior Jusoh...
disappeared.
Where is Jusoh?
Senior Jusoh, come in. Senior Ju...
Peace be upon you. Police!
Police?
Just police protocol.
Let me handle it.
Yes, sir?
It's here.
Senior Yus!
What took you guys so long?
POLICE
Angah, hurry up.
Hang on!
Senior Yus!
Okay. Done.
Quiet!
He is not breathing, Long.
How's that possible with just a punch?
Emma, someone is coming.
Mr. Jusoh.
How about you...
put down that walkie-talkie
and we have a chat?
Control. Control Room, come in!
Keep it up!
Louder!
Now the shine...
One of a kind, Long.
What are we waiting for?
Wrap them all up.
Latest news. A daring heist
of 40 million ringgit...
The biggest heist
in the history of Malaysia...
...and their whereabouts remain unknown.
TEN YEARS LATER
Along.
Sure you don't want to come?
It's okay. Just go.
Okay.
Where's Arif and Sofia?
Along!
Arif and Sofia!
Kiss! Where are you going?
Emma!
That's a lot of stuff.
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
Never seen a hot babe behind the wheel?
It's not that I've never seen one.
It's just been a long time.
No wonder.
You look deprived.
Come here.
‎Long time...
Not my hair!
That's...
That's more like it.
You know...
I've waited ten years for this.
Hey!
Ten years and you haven't quit?
No need to smoke here.
Okay.
I can wait.
Let's go.
Or do you still want to sleep here?
‎What are you guys doing?
‎Please hand me the butter.
What is this nonsense?
Don't you get it?
Hello, there's 10,000 views here.
Broke my back.
Hang on, babe.
You've got to be tough to go viral.
I don't get this thing.
Keyrol.
Kids nowadays...
love to dance in front of their phone.
Give me a break.
What's important...
is people can see my art.
How can I compare to you...?
Huh? IT? Hang on.
Six, seven.
Is this not maintenance?
- IT who?
- IT Mana--
Wrong extension.
- Yes!
- You're very good, Angah.
Not like Emma. She only knows
how to part out cars.
Hey you.
Parting out a car is just her side hustle.
Now she has become
a film star!
I won't let you get hurt.
Even from a mosquito bite.
I got goosebumps.
Okay.
When...
Once he's done with his dialogue,
you stop the car...
with style.
Okay.
Slate 1014. Take 1.
I won't let you get hurt.
Even from a mosquito bite.
You just...
You?
Ten years in jail.
Surely you have good stories.
Tell us.
- Tell us.
Nothing.
Nothing? Just tell us.
It won't do any good anyway.
You!
Just tell us the story.
‎Tell us.
Okay.
There's a contact on the inside.
He says there are some
fresh goods worth RM 300,000.
RM 300,000 was it?
Wow!
Why?
Retired?
Listening to Along?
What about me?
Nothing, Long.
Keyrol.
Keyrol has...
Just say it.
He said he has an inside contact.
Ouch!
Let the story from inside stay there.
You're out now, right?
I'm just telling a story.
It's nothing more.
In the end you'll be the one
making the final decision, right?
You know, right?
The reason I made that call?
What was the reason?
Because of me?
- Or was it Dad?
- Keyrol.
There's no point talking.
Hey, Rol!
Rol!
Where are you going?
Don't bother.
Relax, will you?
Along is just concerned about us.
What kind of concern is that?
All you guys do is listen to him.
You guys will just do
whatever he says, right?
Enough, Keyrol. What's past is past.
Let it go.
You're all as hard-headed
as your eldest brother.
You want me to die?
Face all of this alone?
Isn't there another way, Dad?
There is.
But I have to help the creditor.
Help?
What kind of help?
Dad!
So cool.
Cool, right?
Take it.
Peace be upon you.
Look familiar?
Let's meet.
Why won't it hit?
You avoided it, didn't you?
Ball.
You think I don't know how to swing?
Let's fly.
The big brother!
Give me a moment.
Hey!
- We...
- What are you doing?
- I'm here, aren't I?
Let my brother go.
I don't want to.
Let him be. It's okay.
We'll take Lan's kids after this.
Then...
His sister, Emma.
Hey.
What is it that you actually want?
Where's the thing I asked for?
In the car.
Now that you've got what you wanted,
you stay away from my family.
You get it?
Wait a minute. This...
I think you've got it wrong.
That's just a deposit.
That's not the thing I actually wanted.
Come.
I'm sure you've heard of them before.
The family of Five Ivory.
In three days, there will be a party.
It's weird, still feels weird
They will appoint their new leader.
The ring will be there.
We don't do that kind of work anymore.
You can take it back.
What a snob.
You won't do it anymore.
Farid, you may be able
to hide from the law.
But there's no way you can hide from us.
Move.
How the hell was there
a bomb in your car? Damn!
Three days.
Don't get busted.
Peace be upon you.
Sorry guys, I am...
late.
Was it settled?
Yeah. I've sent them to my in-law's.
Truthfully, I don't
know how to tell you guys.
But we have a problem...
related to...
The Five Ivory gang.
Five Ivory?
This is a suicide mission.
You. The minute you get out,
you create trouble.
Along, don't we have other choices?
How did we get involved
with the Five Ivory Gang?
That's not important.
The point is we're now involved.
Like it or not, we have to do it
if we want to stay alive.
No.
I don't need to get involved.
If you're trying to run,
take us with you.
Right?
You!
‎Hey!
Proceed.
Okay. This is the information I have.
Rahman Mustapha.
Head of the Five Ivory gang.
On the surface, he runs
a legit business as a coverup.
A hotel business.
Two weeks ago, he passed away.
His son, Bashir will take over.
Except it is not official yet.
In three days' time, at the Palace Hotel,
they will have a proper coronation
to appoint their new leader.
There, he will inherit the leader's ring.
Our job,
is to steal the ring
before it gets to Bashir.
All this trouble to get us,
just to steal a ring?
Is not about how much the ring is worth.
Imagine a king ascending
the throne without a crown.
Would he still be the king?
Between Bashir and the ring,
there are two important people
we need to know.
Firstly, the person
who is responsible for making sure
all his dirty businesses look legitimate.
Miranda Rahman.
How she keeps
the ledger clean is beyond me.
Secondly, Jaafar Mustapha.
Uncle to Bashir.
This old fox controls all
of Five Ivory's underground trading.
The ring will be there an hour
before the ceremony starts.
Then, go straight to
the vault hidden under Palace Hotel.
The security of the vault
is among the most complex.
In this hotel, there is only one corridor
that leads to the vault's lift.
This is our only way to the ring.
But the elevator's floor
is pressure sensitive.
The moment someone enters
it activates a five-second countdown.
Without the encrypted key,
the alarm will go off.
Only the head of security, Mizal, has it.
Down there, you'll be greeted
by a guard with a shotgun.
Disarm him and we'll
get access to their vault.
The entry only uses Miranda's thumbprint,
no one else's.
The safe is in the vault.
Fingerprint, access card,
pressure sensitive floor,
security guards, safe. Wow!
Anything else you would like to add?
There are still the CCTVs.
Along, are you sure about this?
It's been a long time since we...
Yet, we have never failed
when we've worked together.
I'll make sure it's
no different this time.
Shall we?
Work.
The office hasn't been used for ten years.
Some housekeeping is due, no doubt.
We've only got three days.
Don't slack off.
Hey, take this.
Work, you idiot!
We've only got three days, moron!
Amer!
One...
Sign here, please.
Mr. Bashir.
Step two, reconnaissance.
Rol, we need to know their movements.
How does it fit? Good?
It fits perfectly.
Where else would the apple fall?
The ring needs to be
resized for the new leader.
This morning, Bashir will be fitting it
at Amee Philips, Bangsar.
We need to know
their protocols in handling this ring,
security details
and where they keep the ring.
No. No.
No problem.
Okay, lazy bum.
Get Miranda's
schedule for these three days
leading up to the coronation.
From there, we will devise
a plan to steal her fingerprint.
Step three. Rol, you
and I will infiltrate their base.
Our target, Mizal.
There must be a time
when the key isn't with him.
I will create a distraction,
you'll clone the key.
And Lan, make a copy.
What's happening?
Epy, what happened?
I don't know. The alarm went off suddenly.
Huh?
Suddenly, the alarm went off.
Hey!
Can't you just switch it off?
Have you checked the exits?
- What?
- The exits!
Have you check them?
Not yet.
Turn this off.
Then go check Exit 12 to 16.
Huh?
Check Exit 12 to 16.
Okay. Regarding Miranda.
Hold it there. Let me explain this.
After I get her schedule,
which I would undoubtedly acquire
I will continue to follow her
to get more information.
Follow her?
Follow her.
- Stalking?
- Correct!
Stalking.
Even last time, I was a specialist.
In stalking.
Stalk all you want.
Okay. Regarding stalking.
There are more than
500 CCTVs at the Palace Hotel.
Lan, hack into their server
and give us full control.
Okay. Pictures up.
Step five, transport.
In, out, one car.
Make sure the car can
handle our combined weight.
Remember, this is a mafia event.
Not your usual hoodlums.
So, get a car that blends in.
Definitely need a turbo
and some custom suspensions.
I did good, right?
The exterior is cool, isn't it?
Under the hood, there's a monster.
Diesel engine?
Yup.
Come on. Diesel sounds terrible.
Might as well drive a garbage truck.
Nice, right?
You're all talk.
Where is the key?
Why do you need it?
I want to test drive the car.
No way. You'll crash the car
before anything happens.
Stingy.
When it's about me,
nothing is right. Everything is wrong.
It's just a car.
This is the most important
and the most challenging.
The time limit we have to crack this safe,
five minutes.
This is not our usual safe
with a single dial.
This has three.
Three?
A single dial is close
to a million combination.
Three dials would mean 30...
It's impossible to crack in five minutes.
There's only one solution.
How is he doing?
Stubborn.
Can't get anything.
Damn it.
You're turning it too fast, Keyrol.
Do it slowly.
I think it's 70.
There's no 70.
Third wheel is six.
Okay. Good!
Forty-five.
Seventy.
Six.
Damn it!
You're not consistent.
That's why I told you to turn it slowly.
Keyrol, in that vault
there are nine plates in a row.
The further the plates,
the harder they are for you to feel.
That's why we're using the soundwaves.
Angah. Reset it. Let's do it over.
Wait.
When we get to the vault on that night,
I am your eyes.
And I am your ears.
If you want my help,
you need to let me help you.
You know the difference
between counterfeit and original?
If we buy original stuff,
only the rich become richer.
If you buy counterfeits,
the laborers
the factory workers and even the sellers,
everyone gets the benefit.
So cool.
Cool, right?
Keep it.
It's yours.
Are you for real, Dad?
Of course.
I have another three at home.
This one is for you.
The other three are for my girlfriends.
You told me it was two the other day.
Now it's three. Show off.
While I'm still able,
my knees aren't shaking,
we can marry four wives
- but have a lot of girlfriends.
- But have a lot of girlfriends.
It's okay. Go.
Go.
Along.
What are you looking for?
Looking for this?
When did you lift it?
Here, take it.
Dad.
No, I'm good.
Why did you come here?
- I...
- I'm asking why are you here?
I don't know who else to go to.
I need your he...
I told you before, right?
Right?
I'm in danger. They're looking for me.
Of course they are!
Every day there's someone here
looking for you.
Who haven't you pissed off out there?
I just want to borrow one gold bar.
Can you just think for a moment?
People are sniffing it out.
They're looking for it.
If anything happens,
who will take care of my siblings?
Who?
You?
How could you do this to me?
I brought you into this world.
I taught you all your skills.
All of you.
I raised you all. This is how you repay...
What exactly have you taught us?
What kind of things did you teach us all?
Every time you screw up,
I have to deal with it.
Don't you dare ask for anything
from us anymore, understand?
So much for raising us.
I thought hiring a Master's degree holder...
I don't even have a Michelin Star yet.
I used Wagyu Oxtail.
Very delicious!
Presenting Wagyu Oxtail Beef Bourguignon!
I'll change it, I'll change it.
I cooked that for 12 hours!
Before I destroy your future.
You get it? Jezz!
- Marco!
- Yes, Chef.
- Yes?
- Marco! My eyes are wide open,
but I can't see anything.
Chef, you're having a panic attack.
Marco!
I cooked for 12 hours!
Did you see that?
Don't you see?
My dish.
‎Whatever...
Where did the cup go?
There you are.
The 12-hour artwork
is actually quite delicious.
Let me try.
Oh, it's so good.
His art is very deep, right?
Okay. Look for 53.
Fifty-three is confirmed.
- Eighty-seven?
- Nope.
No?
Nope. Not 87.
Ninety-eight!
14, 53, 98. Try it!
Four minutes and 58 seconds.
Good job, Keyrol!
I told you he could open it.
Peekaboo!
I'm such a genius
at finding people, ain't it?
Who is that, Along?
Didn't I tell you,
they're the best of the best.
What do you want now?
Relax, big brother.
Can't I just come to cheerlead?
Keyrol!
Do you know you're a rare gem?
There's a bright future ahead of you.
Luckily, my swing
the other day didn't hit your hand.
Or else you'd be whining,
"My pretty hand is ruined!"
"My pretty hand is ruined."
"I can't rotate the dial."
Are you done?
If you're done,
we have a lot of other things to do.
This is the problem.
Hanging out with the youngsters,
but there's this old man here
flexing his muscles.
But it's actually good.
So you can shape your little brother,
who's always fighting back. Good!
Okay. I've seen
your progress and I'm satisfied.
I will take my leave.
Because I want to give an update
to my client that you're all impressive,
the best and most convincing.
Your mom asked?
Then, what did you say, baby?
Look.
You reply to her like this.
Tell her that I'm busy.
I'm very important in the office.
If I'm not there,
my boss can't do his job.
No.
Am I worried?
Of course I'm worried.
Okay. Listen to me, baby.
There isn't that much work left.
Once I'm done, I'll pick you up, okay?
Five.
Hey, catch!
What's wrong with you, Rol?
Sulking alone.
I got you all into this, right?
I should know my place.
Who said that?
It was you...
You like to think of nonsense.
What else should I think of?
Swear to God. No one has said anything.
From what I see
we're more alive now.
Keyrol. You've never changed one bit.
Always need me
to cheer you up. Such a baby!
Don't start your big sister act.
You could have been the youngest.
Goes to prove how much I love you.
How so?
Because I came out
to face the world first.
I prepared the canal for you.
Wow! Load of rubbish.
That hurts, you idiot!
Load...
Emma...
Amer needs your help.
Men.
Annoying.
So, how is it?
Are you ready for tomorrow?
Yes.
All the tools are packed.
I've double-checked.
I think it's okay.
That's not what I meant.
Keyrol.
I know it's been ten years...
Along...
Ten years...
of anger.
Along, I'm not angry.
I'm not angry.
The angry phase is long gone.
But the bitterness
is still there. Isn't it?
If only half of what we do now
combined with your brain,
went to help Dad back then.
Guess we wouldn't have ended up like this.
Help? Help him with what?
He asked me to steal something.
Okay. Confirm. That's the lorry.
What is this, Dad?
There are no bullets.
It's just to scare them.
Where did you get this?
As usual, I stole it.
Okay. Now.
Don't move.
You got a death wish?
Hand. Your hands.
You're messing with
the wrong people, old man!
Hey! You think I'm playing?
I will shoot your brains out.
Dad, let him go.
- It's not the stuff we're looking for.
- Then what is it?
Those are not computer parts.
Dad!
Keyrol.
Dad, come here!
You know, right? You know why I didn't...
Never mind.
And this is what you want now?
You want us to be like
the old days. Working together.
Even if is just for one day.
A day like we once were.
And we'll part ways after this.
I'm going to bed.
Wow! Your suit's tight like your face.
Chill, dude.
This isn't your first time.
Just been a long time.
So, how is your favorite brother?
Okay, you don't have to tell me.
I can tell from your face.
Hey, you...
If you want someone gone,
I can help.
I can look for anything you want.
But the issue with your brother,
even I can't help.
Puts Hong Kong drama to shame.
Looks alright.
Let's go eat pig.
You're the pig.
I meant barbecue.
The Crown Prince is moving.
The crown has arrived.
Alright, guys. Get into position.
The party is on.
We got eyes.
My lonely night
Only you
In my heart
Don't look at me, dear
I'll fall to your arms
If you like it
Don't just move it
Three syllables only.
Sa-ri-ban!
Sariban?
Is this your real name?
Or are you just lying to us?
How can I ever lie
to cute girls like you both.
Angah, two o'clock.
Okay, Keyrol and Emma.
Anytime when you're ready.
Emma, I'm in position.
You're a piece of trash.
How long do you want me to wait?
Six months is not enough?
Looping footage.
Six month and you say that's not long?
The sentence, "I'm divorcing you"
wouldn't even take six seconds to say.
You want to talk about this handbag?
You think I care about it?
I dare you, say it one more time.
Say it again!
Now. Go.
Hey, what do you think I am?
Your part-time job? Your weekend conquest?
No, you don't get to waste my time.
The thing is
since you love
your old hag of a wife so much,
both of you can go to hell!
This is a restricted area.
What's your problem? Can't you see?
I'm having a meltdown here.
Ma'am, take this.
My man is leaving me.
And now you want to kick me out?
Now. That's enough!
You are quite rough.
But it's alright.
I like...
a man who gets rough with me.
I need to report this.
‎Hey!
Wouldn't you want to
get rough with me as well?
Two rough men.
it will be wild tonight.
You said something
about restricted area, right?
Evil.
What's wrong with this thing?
What's wrong?
I think the cable is knotted.
Is just a bit. Wait, let me try.
Settled.
Be careful, Keyrol.
Damn it.
What's happening?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Oh God!
Vault Unit, come in.
What's going on down there?
Hang on. I'm checking.
Give me a minute. Once the alarm
is triggered, all cameras are on reset.
It's weird.
There's nothing here.
Might be a glitch in the system.
Okay. It's done.
Keyrol.
Keyrol?
I'm okay.
Don't keep us hanging like that.
Hey, one at a time, alright.
I need to handle
the elevator and the guard.
Give me a break.
Angah, the fingerprint won't go through.
Oh, my.
Try uploading it again.
Guys, it won't budge.
How can this happen?
You. Angah. Did you check
the thumb print properly?
I did. I scanned the cup
that Amer gave me five times.
That's true.
That's the cup I took from Miranda's hand.
Are you sure there were no other cups?
What other cups could there be, Along?
Amer.
I think we may have taken...
her assistant's cup.
Oh no!
Damn it!
You guys are idiots.
I'm already down here, damn it.
When you were young,
you refused to get educated.
Now, you're dumb and a burden to us all.
Lan.
Show me all cameras at that party.
What for?
Just do it.
Sorry, Along.
I know I messed up but I...
- Yeah, you messed it up!
It's a simple thing.
Camera 32. Enlarge that.
It's just a fingerprint.
How's that even difficult?
Along, we can't rely on Amer.
Why don't you try and get her fingerprint?
You're at the wrong
and you won't even admit to it.
You! Why did you go
and push the assistant's cup?
Found you.
How is it my fault now? You're such a...
Amer, Emma.
Listen carefully.
I've never watched a heist film
where getting the fingerprint failed.
It should be the easiest thing.
You must think that we're
a group of stupid robbers, right?
Now, I present to you the iron lady,
also the heart of this party tonight.
She will perform a special dance
dedicated to her brother.
The stage is yours.
I am a much truer man.
Korti.
Sariban Korti.
Hey.
Where is it?
Yes. Take this.
How is it?
- What?
- How many stars do I get?
Oh my. Okay. I'll give you five stars.
That's just because you were dancing.
Piss off.
- Here.
- Okay? You got it?
Okay. Nice.
Finally, it went through.
Along, the speech has started.
Okay. After the speech
they are going to fetch the ring.
I can't believe in this life
of mine, I still get the chance
at an event like this to give a speech
for the appointment of our new leader.
Keyrol, five minutes...
starts now.
Twenty-one?
Twenty-one, confirmed.
Keyrol, the first dial is 21, 76, 3.
This time around,
I'm going to keep this short.
I just want to remind everyone
of a thing that I once said.
A quarter of the speech is done.
The second dial, 31, 15, 91.
Nice.
Along.
How are we doing for time?
Don't worry, Keyrol.
Stay focused and maintain your pace.
This is the most difficult dial.
The responsibility of a leader...
Guys, it's half the speech.
It'd be great if we had more time.
Rol. That's too fast.
You need to do it slowly.
In any decision,
there will be people who celebrate it.
And there will always be haters.
I think it's 25.
There's no 25.
Negative.
And when the decision is made
that causes hatred,
even though...
Along, the woman is gone.
She's gone?
I swear.
My eyes were on her.
I turned away for a moment and she's gone.
And you claim to be
a specialist in stalking.
The one person you're stalking is gone!
Shut up!
Along. What do we do now?
One.
Two.
Three.
We won't even have three minutes.
It's impossible, Along.
Are we going to abort?
Keyrol.
If we leave here empty-handed,
the repercussions are much more severe.
Are you for real?
I believe you, Keyrol.
Forget about the stethoscope.
Whatever happens, I'll be by your side
until the end.
Okay. We're not done yet.
We need to move now.
Meet at the loading bay.
I would like to
express my sincere appreciation
to every family member of Five Ivory
who attended this event tonight.
Your presence is an honor for me.
Thank you.
Without further ado,
we're officiating the appointment
of the newly crowned owner of Five Ivory.
Ladies and gentlemen, let's take a break.
In the meantime, let's enjoy the night
with some songs. Music please.
We have a situation.
Seal the building now.
Guys, we must hurry. They're coming fast.
Hey, Amer.
Along, the plan is a no-go.
They're closing the back door.
We'll meet in the basement.
For real? We're already outside.
What is your problem?
Why is it so difficult
to give me what's rightfully mine?
Bashir, calm down.
We'll find it.
I will find it.
Get the lift.
Sir! Excuse me, sir.
You go down first.
- What about you?
- Just go.
Along.
Sir?
Yes, sir. Is there a problem?
There's no problem but there's been a...
Camera eight.
No one gets in and out
of the hotel until he's found.
That's him!
‎Hey!
Ma'am, we found
the suspect at Restaurant Celestial.
I repeat, we've found the suspect.
Emma.
If I knew this would happen...
You made this happened too.
Sir.
Please cooperate.
Angah.
Why is he waving at us?
And why are you waving back at him?
We'll take him now.
He can actually run.
Go!
‎Hurry!
Angah, jump!
Jump?
- To the front!
- Front?
Now!
What kind of stupid plan is this,
damn it?!
How is it our fault when you can't fit?
Long!
Pull me in.
This is one hell of a pull.
Not yet.
We need to find a way out.
Keys.
Along. We've got Angah.
You go ahead.
What about you guys? We can't just leave...
Emma, go now.
Damn it!
Along.
Hey!
‎Oh, my God!
Hey, you're crazy, Emma!
We left Along and Keyrol behind.
That's crazier.
The key, Keyrol. Key!
Let me do it.
Hurry up, Keyrol.
Hurry up.
Okay.
What is this, Keyrol?
What are you doing, Keyrol?
I think you have your way.
I have my own way.
No. Don't do this. Don't do this.
Do you know what will happen
if you work alone?
Have you forgotten about it?
You want to repeat your mistake
from back then?
Even in this situation
you still don't get it?
You think the ten years I was in there,
it was my mistake?
Here, Dad! Here!
Come here!
Look!
Dad!
Here, Dad!
Police!
Dad!
Let's go.
Let's go, Dad!
- Here.
- I can't, Keyrol.
I can't.
- Dad, we need to get up.
- Where are they? Move!
We need to run. Come on.
- Come on.
- Check over there.
Up the hill, let's go.
Listen to me, Keyrol.
Listen.
I hope
this is enough as an atonement
for all my mistakes.
Hey!
You're looking for me,
right? I'm right here!
Over there!
Put your gun away! I said put it away!
I've been thinking for ten years.
The conclusion is clear.
Dad is dead
because you chose not to help him.
- Calm down.
- Gun!
That night, he didn't
choose to save himself.
He chose to save me.
What did you say, Along?
Don't repeat my past mistake?
That is exactly what I'm doing right now.
I don't want to live
with you making the call
where you get to
choose who lives and dies.
There are things that you think you know
but you actually don't understand.
You don't understand.
The moment you give them
the ring, you will die!
At least, this is my decision.
You take care of yourself, Along.
Keyrol. Rol!
Keyrol!
I thought you were
only good at cracking safes.
You're also good at
betraying your brother.
What's wrong?
Afraid of the dark?
Why didn't he pick up the phone?
Guys. I don't think
we should stay here anymore.
We need to split up and run.
And?
Disappear one after another?
Are you crazy?
Don't try to be a smarty-pants.
You dare to be responsible of our lives?
You are such a jerk. When you messed up,
did anyone hold you accountable
for our lives?
What has this got to do with me?
Can you guys please...
- Along.
Along.
Where's Keyrol?
Where's Keyrol, Along?
Keyrol is gone.
Keyrol is with them.
So, does that mean we're good?
No.
We should've done this job quietly.
Now, all of Five Ivory knows it's us.
Birds that are caged too long
will become spoiled.
You?
It needs to be fed.
I never imagined this.
Imagined what?
That I like birds?
Or, you feel like you're the bird?
Where are my gold bars?
Patience, kid.
I'm actually rather confused.
You're bored being
under your brother's wing. I get that.
Just like me.
I did all this
because I want to save my family,
Five Ivory.
But you...
What is it about?
You double-crossed your own brother.
Don't tell me you're just being...
rebellious?
I knew it.
You're just like these birds.
When kept in a cage
they desperately want to be free.
But once they're free,
they live like they are in the cage.
Hey, Grandpa!
Only I know where the ring is.
Are you sure
you want to play it like this?
What now?
You want to threaten me?
Or kill me?
Kill you?
Keyrol...
The ring is of no importance now.
Your face right now
looks just like your dad's,
Johar.
Give me some more time.
I'll get you the gold bars.
Just a little more time.
Or you can run an errand for me.
Steal something.
To ease your job.
Get lost.
Never mind then.
Thanks, bro.
Dad, we need to go.
It's not the stuff we're looking for.
Then what is it?
Those are not computer parts.
Dad! Here, Dad!
How dare you steal my stuff?!
Emergency call 999.
Police! Freeze!
That should have been the end for Bashir.
But my brother
was willing to go through hell as long as
that devil of his was saved.
Your father was a waste of bait.
Shut up!
You son of a gun!
Life is funny, isn't it?
Ten years ago,
your father came easily to me.
Now, it's you.
A rather sad coincidence.
But maybe that's how life goes, right?
No matter how hard we fight
not everything is in our hands.
Damn you!
It breaks my heart...
to kill talented people.
Let's go.
Patience.
Your pain is only worldly.
It will soon be gone.
Along, what are we going to do now?
We can't just be waiting here like this.
They will kill Keyrol, Along.
Wait!
That's enough of a fight.
Bashir.
Take me away!
Hey, old man! Where are you running to?
Bastard!
Boss! Hurry up, boss!
First a traitor,
now you want to be a murderer?
Keyrol.
What if we agree to a truce?
A truce?
Just say it.
What's your price? I'm willing to pay it.
I'll pay.
Even if it's more than your gold bars.
No! You son of a gun!
If you kill me,
my vengeance will
follow you to hell, bastard!
This...
is for my father.
I'm not a murderer.
Not like you.
It's all settled.
How?
You think you're
the only one puppeteering?
My family is in danger.
Sorry for the trouble.
It's no trouble for an old friend.
Let's work.
At 9:30 p.m. Day
after tomorrow at the Palace Hotel.
All the details are in there.
Be careful.
Bashir, I know you're angry right now.
- Talk!
- Just think for a minute, Bashir.
What would I do with the ring? Damn it!
Are you playing riddles with me?
Someone forced me to do it!
Someone set all this up.
There's a traitor in your family, Bashir.
He told me about tonight.
You've heard of it before, right?
The Five Ivory family.
In three days' time,
they will appoint their new leader.
In order to bait a traitor out,
my coronation was sacrificed?
You bastard!
Who do you think you are to decide for me?
All of Five Ivory
will worship you, Bashir.
If you find the traitor.
The traitor who betrayed you tonight
is the same person
who betrayed you ten years ago.
I would've never imagined.
What would you have never imagined, Uncle?
My family and I...
We're good, right?
Let's go.
Bashir.
We've arrived?
Yes. Get out.
What are we doing here?
Shouldn't we go celebrate or something?
Didn't we say we were meeting Ah Teck?
We could just meet him at karaoke.
What is your problem?
I've been holding my pee in since forever.
If we meet at the karaoke,
I could use their loo.
You could have peed much earlier.
Take care of yourself, Along.
Keyrol!
I know who set Dad up.
The one who forced us
into stealing this ring.
He's the same person
who set you and Dad up ten years ago.
Give me a chance to repay
my debt to Dad!
You were there, weren't you?
That night.
Keyrol! Dad!
Forgive me, Dad.
Keyrol.
Sir! There's another one, Sir!
Hey...
Stay calm.
Stand up.
Dad.
- Dad!
- Hey!
- Don't move!
- Dad!
- Spread his leg.
- My father.
- Mister.
Don't move!
Dad!
- Don't move.
- Stay calm. Hold him down.
- Dad!
- Calm down.
Dad is gone, Keyrol.
Dad!
I know I wasn't right all this time.
That's why for the ten years I was jailed,
never once did you come to see me?
It's not...
I didn't know how to face you, Keyrol.
Do you know all this while I thought...
Why didn't you tell me all these, Along?
What would it have done?
Would it have changed anything?
It's time we go our separate ways, Along.
Really?
Keyrol.
I hope, one day
there will be a space
in your heart to forgive me.
That's my only wish.
You want to dictate
even the space in my heart?
Help me to repair this.
Make it work again.
I dropped my cigarette.
Why are we meeting in such a place?
Are you copying the Hong Kong gangsters?
We should've met at the karaoke.
I told you.
Ah Teck.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
How's the four-eyed prick?
Was it easy to make him talk?
Not a problem.
He is just a toothless tiger
without his master.
By the way, I think
I found your belongings.
And I was helpful enough
to bring them along.
What's this?
Ah Teck!
When you needed help,
you said, "Help me, Ah Teck.
Help me, Ah Teck."
When it's time to pay, you say, "Woi."
What should we do, Along?
Just give it to him.
Along says just to give it to you.
- See you.
- Alright.
The smell.
Just wanted to know how it feels.
Quite nice isn't it, Emma?
‎Got you!
- Along.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong with Along?
That's hard.
That's really hard.
Angah!
- I got you again.
- Along's turn!
That hurts!
- Emma.
Don't you dare!
- Don't sit. You'll get boils!
- I dare you!
Emma.