- You do this for a better life, right?
- Yes.
If God permits, I will help you.
Thank you.
Are you sure, Ning?
We can go, just the three of us.
Myself, you, and Nirmala.
Yes, I'm sure.
Sulaiman is a good man.
I just want you and Nirmala
to have a better life.
My ATM card got blocked.
You have cash, right?
Give me some.
I'll pay you back tomorrow.
Mom, I want to go home.
We'll be home soon.
SEVERAL MONTHS LATER
The Kungkum Kedung ritual
is what's been bringing us money, Ning.
As well as the blessings.
Everyone knows you're a fraud.
Don't become stupid like them!
People like us don't have
a lot of choices, Ning.
Come on.
- No.
- Let's move!
- Move!
- No.
- Come on!
No, no!
Come on!
Okay!
Okay. Okay.
But don't hurt Nirmala
and my mother ever again.
Come on.
If I lose consciousness,
pull the rope as hard as you can.
Got it?
TWO WEEKS LATER
Later, I'm going to learn to make
origami again with Mr. Tetsuya.
What are you saying? Take it out.
You're going to get electrocuted.
Mala, don't put this in your mouth!
When you're with Granny later,
don't bother her too much.
Don't trouble her.
Don't trouble Mr. Tetsuya, too. Okay?
Mr. Tetsuya is actually very kind to me.
This is for you.
Mr. Tetsuya said that
an origami crane can...
What was it again, Granny?
They can bring fortune.
That's it.
Come on, hurry up.
I'm late for work.
Yes.
My name is Mala.
My full name is Nirmala Aisyah.
Once that's done,
I really want to learn how to swim.
Why swim?
If you want to be a policewoman
you have to be able to swim.
PROMO PRICE
RP 80,000
- Do you like it?
- Yes, I want this one.
Stop, stop!
Ning!
Where's Sulaiman?
Where did he run off to?
Ask him to pay me back!
Stop it, Dad.
- He said, "One month!"
- Dad! People are watching.
That fake soldier! What a fraud!
I get it, but let's not make a scene here.
Husband and wife, you're both the same!
Stop it! You're embarrassing me.
How many months has it been?
Get in. It's about to rain. Quick.
Be careful. One by one.
Are you okay, Ning? You look pale.
You look sad.
I'm okay.
- Let's go home now.
- Yes.
Should we pick up your daughter
on the way?
That's okay.
I'll pick her up on my motorcycle.
But it's about to rain, Ning.
Yeah.
Can I come in late tomorrow?
I have to fix my motorcycle.
No problem, Ning.
What's wrong?
Where have you been?
What took you so long?
What's with her?
We'll talk later.
Let's go home now. Let's go.
What is wrong with you?
It hurts...
But it's raining, Mom.
Shouldn't we wait until the rain stops?
Let's just go home.
- What's wrong, Mala?
- It hurts, Mom.
It's okay, we're going home.
We'll talk about it later.
That's enough, Mala. Stop crying.
Next time,
I won't let you go with Uti Yah again.
Ning, go left.
The other way is too dangerous.
It's faster this way.
Ning! Are you sure?
- Mom!
- This is dangerous!
Be careful!
Nirmala?
Mother?
Ma'am.
It's dangerous here, ma'am.
- I'm looking for my daughter.
- Find her later.
- My mother is missing, too.
- Yes.
Let's go up for now, ma'am.
It's dangerous here.
We're going up.
How did it happen?
MAJAKUNAN,
CENTRAL JAVA - RAINY SEASON 2022
- Sir.
- Yes, ma'am?
My daughter is still missing, sir.
Yes. We will take care of it.
- Arya!
- Yes, sir.
The girl is still missing.
She might have fallen into the river.
Call SAR immediately.
Hendro, come in.
There's still one victim
who has possibly fallen into the river.
Uti Yah.
This is the grandmother.
The daughter hasn't been found.
Are you sure, Ning?
THE REDEMPTION OF SIN
Jump in.
I'm scared, Miss.
Let me ask you something.
How are you going to be a swimmer
if you're too scared of
getting in the water?
Jump in.
I want to go home.
Let him go, Gus.
Miss, he is Mr. Wiro's son.
Head of the sectoral police.
He wants us to make him an athlete.
But he doesn't want to, Gus.
He already paid
for a year's worth of classes.
Okay.
Ready?
Tirta! Miss Tirta!
Life...
Water...
Life, water.
Life. Water. Life. Water. Life.
Life is like water in the river,
flowing unimpeded.
Unstoppable.
Until it reaches an estuary
and merges...
into the ocean.
Mr. Adang!
Please tell them not to move yet.
They haven't checked that side.
Mrs. Wening, it's getting dark.
Go home and rest.
There are some areas there
that haven't been searched yet.
So why are you moving here?
Sir. Please accept this.
- I can't, ma'am. No.
- I want to ask,
is it not possible for the police to help
with the case?
Here's the thing, ma'am.
This is SAR's territory.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
I know you're going through a hard time,
but I really need the money
for my husband's medical treatment.
If you want to extend the contract,
please pay the rent immediately.
Soon. I promise.
When are you going to pay?
Soon.
- Soon, please. I'll be waiting.
- Yes.
Thank you, ma'am.
Here. This one is empty.
Ning, starting from tomorrow
you don't have to come to work.
When everything is settled,
you can come back.
I'm the one taking the loss.
You're not focused, Ning.
You're not doing the job right.
You've ruined two clothes this week alone.
I wanted to help you out,
but why are you doing this?
Next, let's not forget the foundation.
It's from eLGe Tech.
This brand is really good.
Look at this series.
This one is also important.
This eyeliner pencil is for the undereye.
We found items from the river yesterday.
There are clothes and shoes.
Please have a look.
Maybe you'll recognize something.
Recognize anything?
Someone said that Nirmala can swim.
I didn't know that.
- If she really can swim--
- Then where is she?
My daughter, Nirmala,
has been missing for a week.
But I believe...
Hoping you'll find guidance from God
...that she will be found.
God's warning, go and pray,
stop the livestream
Please pray for her.
Mom!
- What is this?
- Just open it.
Happy birthday, Mom.
So when you're live-streaming,
you don't have to put the phone
on the can of crackers.
Right.
Are you sure, Ning?
"Rest in peace."
What kind of peace?
Aren't you scared of being alone at home?
How much?
Ten thousand.
Sir.
Is this the woman
who died in the bridge accident?
Uti Yah.
That was Wening, her daughter.
She rode the motorcycle that night.
Her 11-year-old daughter, Nirmala,
is still missing.
Even if they find her,
she's probably dead.
Need to copy anything, Ms. Tirta?
Ten copies of this.
Another swimmer like you?
Let's hope.
Yeah, hope they'll become good.
They're only used to swimming
in the river, like villagers.
Well, I'm from the village
and I used to swim in the river, too.
Hey, this is her.
Tirta. The kids are ready.
Listen up, everyone.
Those who haven't paid
are not allowed to join.
Dodo, Ratih. Sit down.
The rest of you, go warm up.
Go. Warm up first.
Gus.
Miss. Miss.
A new kid who wants to join the class.
Do you have your swimsuit?
- No.
- No?
So are you going to swim in that dress?
The SAR team is still searching.
Confirmed by Adang Sutanto,
as the head of SAR operations,
they admitted the search was difficult
because of the strong river current.
With the available equipment,
the search hasn't been successful.
Sir!
Sir! Where are you going?
Mr. Adang!
Sir, what is happening?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
We had to stop the search.
It's been ten days.
The chances of finding her now
are next to none.
We suspect that her body
has been carried far away.
My daughter is still alive.
She is not dead.
Who do you think you are?
God himself?
How can you determine someone's fate?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
But our decision is based on
rational and assessable facts.
Hello. Good evening.
I don't know where else to ask for help.
So I'm asking you.
My daughter is still missing.
The SAR team were looking for her.
But they stopped the search.
I'm sure...
my daughter is still alive out there.
Even if she's not...
I need to find...
her body.
There...
Good.
So, hey, you can teach me, yeah?
It's very good. Do you know the next step?
- Thank you, Mr. Tetsuya.
- Thank you. See you soon.
Bye, bye.
See you.
Andi.
Is there any space left?
Yes.
- Thank you, Mr. Tetsuya.
- Thank you. See you.
- Take care.
- Yes.
Bye, bye.
I've come to deliver your laundry.
I think my mother forgot to return it.
If I'm not mistaken,
she had to do your laundry at home
because the washing machine
here was broken.
Sorry, the fragrance
has probably gone by now.
I'm sorry I haven't thanked you sooner.
You came to the funeral
and helped with the cost.
- Daughter?
- Daughter.
I'm going, sir.
Oh, wait.
How much should I...
- pay for this?
- That's okay.
Besides, I no longer work
at the laundromat.
I'm leaving.
I'm currently unemployed, sir.
Is it possible for me to work here
to replace my mother?
- Here?
- Yes.
If you've already found
a replacement, that's fine.
No, it's fine. I get it.
Thank you, sir. Please excuse me.
Wening.
Can you start working tomorrow?
Sure.
Like my mother did, Mr. Tetsuya?
Just call me Tetsuya.
All right, Tetsuya.
Welcome to Tirta Today.
Dissolving, unraveling,
awakening, strengthening.
In the previous episode,
we talked about...
shattered dreams.
This time...
we will talk about...
a tragedy.
No one ever plans
for when a tragedy strikes.
Everything that existed before...
gone in an instant.
Anger.
Sadness.
Disappointment.
Regret.
Emptiness.
IN PEACE
Fear.
They come crashing
like a storm over Mount Semeru.
I can sense it within you.
Right now, you are within the currents
of your new and winding life.
Please accept this, a gift from
Uti Yah's 7th day of remembrance.
Thank you.
Clear water turns murky.
Flowing toward an unknown estuary.
Is your estuary a tragedy?
Is the current that drags you
the comedy of life,
enthusiastically teasing you
to laugh heartily,
forgetting all of your sorrows?
Nirmala?
Ma'am.
Be careful. It's slippery.
Wening is interesting, Gus.
Interesting enough
to be your content, right?
Gus.
I want to invite her as a guest
on my podcast.
- What do you think?
- I guarantee it's going to go viral.
Viral.
Problem is, does she want to be in it?
Excuse me.
Mrs. Wening?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Who are you?
Her name is Miyako.
Miyako?
May I?
- Hope.
- Hope?
- A thousand?
- A thousand.
A thousand cranes.
- Hopes.
- A thousand cranes of hopes.
How do I say it...
A strong bond.
A mother surely has
a strong bond with her daughter.
Sulaiman. He's a fraud.
That fake soldier.
He has tricked many people.
Fake investment schemes
and phony job offers in Taiwan.
He never paid his debt to Lastri.
And the list goes on.
Where is he now?
No idea. Probably ran away.
Nobody truly knows.
He left his debts and unresolved problems
and left Mrs. Wening
to deal with everything.
That man is useless. He's a jerk.
She has so many problems.
The more problems she has,
the more fun the podcast, right?
Mr. Tetsuya. The food is ready.
What is it?
The food is ready, Mr. Tetsuya.
Sir.
- I want those papers.
- Which paper?
That one. The one on top.
Yes.
Miss.
Hi, Mrs. Wening.
So I can talk about anything
on your podcast?
Sure.
- Am I allowed to protest?
- You can.
- When?
- Whenever you're available.
I need a thousand origami cranes.
If you can help me,
I'll do the interview.
Okay, ma'am.
Mrs. Wening.
I'm sorry, I have to go now.
I'll leave you both here.
Please excuse me, ma'am.
It's like this.
Okay? It is difficult
if you're not used to it,
but you will get the hang of it.
The origami crane is not only beautiful,
it can also be a symbol of hope,
a symbol of luck.
So, let's continue.
The next step
is to make the triangle base.
Fold it like this.
Is that your husband in that photo?
...by following the diagonal fold
we made earlier. Okay?
Next, we'll make the...
...meet at the top part.
Okay. Let's continue.
Fold the sides to the middle with...
Here.
...facing upward. There you go.
Then we fold the two sides again
so that...
Ma'am.
I admire you, ma'am.
You are strong, resilient,
facing this tragedy on your own.
You're amazing.
I don't have a choice.
Let me do it.
- You can make the cranes.
- Sure.
Are you sure, Ning?
Are you...
Ma'am?
Mrs. Wening.
Do you really believe that these cranes...
- can help you find...
- It doesn't matter
what I believe or not, Tirta.
I'm not a saint, Tirta.
I have sinned.
Nirmala gives me hope that there is
finally a decent person in my family.
Have you been recording me?
Yes, ma'am.
I don't like being recorded like that.
I'm sorry. I'll delete the recordings.
Tirta, thank you.
I'll pick you up for the interview
later this evening.
Okay.
Actually, the gap is clear.
Your intention is to help her.
That's true. But making her
a guest star is not enough.
- We need concrete proof.
- Thanks.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Yeah.
I can introduce her to Mbah Gowa.
Mbah Gowa?
Mbah Gowa is the one who helped
Mr. Wiro find the terrorist hideout.
- Is he a shaman?
- Yes.
The police hunts terrorists
with a shaman's help?
Yes.
They used the Internet, too.
Do you think she'll be
interested in black magic?
Even a God-fearing person
might resort to black magic
when she's desperate.
You just need to convince her.
- Interesting.
- Of course.
Wening.
You don't need to clean that over there.
There are a lot of ants here.
They're so annoying.
Some ant species
can actually get into the roots.
They gnaw it and kill the plant.
That makes my work in vain.
Enough.
- Wait, ma'am.
- Okay.
- Please come in.
- Thank you.
You're from Jakarta.
Why did you move to a small town?
I ran away.
I failed as an athlete after an accident.
Well, this life is enough for me now.
Some people say that.
You don't need to be afraid and hide.
And you don't need to be scared
when you've done nothing wrong.
The accident wasn't
really your fault, right?
It was my own fault.
Welcome to Tirta Today.
Dissolving. Unraveling.
Awakening. Strengthening.
In this episode,
we have an amazing guest star,
a woman who has faced
the biggest tragedy in her life.
Is it true that Nirmala is still
nowhere to be found since that night?
Yes.
Wasn't there a SAR team
who searched for Nirmala?
There was,
but they stopped the search because...
they believed Nirmala to be dead.
How are you so sure...
that Nirmala is still alive?
Ma'am, what if we ask a shaman to help us?
I thought, maybe if you believe in
the power of those origami cranes,
it wouldn't hurt to try.
Who?
Ms. Tirta. Miss.
Mrs. Wening.
Let's go.
Mbah Gowa.
- Yes?
- She's here, Mbah.
For seven days
after leaving the physical body,
the soul remains trapped
in an unfamiliar realm.
On the 8th day, stronger spirits
can break free from the unknown realm.
Slow down.
They are free to travel anywhere
until the 40th day.
Your daughter, Nirmala.
She is in a dark place now.
Do you mean she's still alive?
There's another force holding her,
preventing her
from leaving that dark place.
It's your sin from the past.
Redeem your sin,
and she might be free.
What sin?
What came to your mind
when I said, "Redeem your sin"?
Are you sure, Ning?
- Nirmala?
- Yes.
I need to go to Cirebon.
May I have my salary in advance?
- Okay, just wait a moment.
- Thank you.
He seems nice.
Yes, he's kind.
He has a daughter back in Japan.
He's divorced.
Tirta.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
You can't go alone.
I'll come with you.
How is the situation, Cak?
- Can we go to work today or tomorrow?
- How's it?
I'll fill this up first.
Get it back tomorrow.
What I did to him...
is probably my greatest sin.
Wening.
Ning, where are you going?
I thought marrying you would improve
my life and lead to a brighter future.
But now I see that I married
a middle school student
who's obsessed with racing.
Ning, I've told you a million times.
I've worked really hard for you
but it's never enough for you.
What? I had to work on my own
to fulfill my needs.
Now, I'm taking care of myself,
my daughter, and my mother.
Just take care of your racing
and your ill mother.
I have never once talked badly
about your mom.
Just stay here with me, honey.
- Sorry, Wicak. Uti Yah.
- Ning.
Ning.
He's actually a good man.
ABANDONED BY WIFE, HUSBAND BURNS HIMSELF
- Yes, this way, ma'am.
- Thank you, ma'am.
Tirta, wait here for a bit.
Two weeks ago, he tried to kill himself.
But that was not the first time.
He had made multiple attempts before.
Come in.
Wicak, I had a motorcycle accident.
Uti Yah didn't make it.
Nirmala...
is still missing in the river.
Nirmala.
But I am sure she is still alive, Wicak.
I came here to apologize.
I have made you like this.
My greatest sin seems to be...
why Nirmala is still missing.
Kill...
me.
I...
will...
forgive...
you...
if...
kill...
me.
The pillow...
I can't!
Help!
What's wrong, ma'am?
Oh, my God!
What happened, ma'am?
Mr. Marno! Help!
He bit his own tongue!
Ma'am.
Tirta.
You've helped me a lot.
Go home now.
This isn't interesting anymore.
This is tragic, Gus.
She went to see her ex-husband.
Wicak.
Her first husband.
Tell Mbah Gowa that she is serious
about seeking redemption for her sin.
Hello, my darlings.
I hope it's true what you said
about Mbah Gowa, Gus.
That he can help her find Nirmala.
I'd like to show you
how to achieve a natural look.
Striving for viral content
doesn't mean anything anymore.
I'll show you, my darlings.
Use a generous amount
and tap your face with it to moisturize.
Mr. Tetsuya. Are you home?
Mr. Tetsuya.
Mr. Tetsuya, I'm sorry
to bother you this late.
May I stay here tonight?
I can't stay at my house.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Mr. Tetsuya.
Do you believe in ghosts?
Thank you, Mr. Tetsuya.
You're welcome.
Wening.
I don't believe in ghosts.
I believe in...
the tangible realities before me.
No ghost can disturb me.
Things that disturb me are ants,
and the memories of my daughter.
Mom, I want to go home.
We'll be home soon.
- Let's go home.
- What happened, Mala?
Mom! This is Mala, Mom!
It's Mala, Mom!
Help me, Mom! Help Mala!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Miyako
Wening.
Please prepare some snacks for the kids.
I want them to join Miyako's
birthday celebration today.
All right, Mr. Tetsuya.
Mrs. Wening!
Ma'am.
What is it, Tirta?
They found a dead body.
- The legs, the body.
- It doesn't smell, sir
- It doesn't smell.
- Look.
It's swollen. The leg.
Open it.
It's not Nirmala.
What is Mbah Gowa doing here?
I don't know.
When they found a dead body,
Mbah Gowa asked me
to take him to Mrs. Wening immediately.
You redeemed the wrong sin.
You know whose body that is, don't you?
I had to let go.
Otherwise, I would have drowned, too.
It's obvious now. He's the one
who's been keeping Nirmala captive.
Then what should I do now?
Don't ask me to apologize, let alone
beg for mercy before that man's body.
It will never happen.
Mbah Gowa, he hurt me.
He hurt my mother, Uti Yah, and Nirmala.
You must perform
a river purification ceremony.
The ritual will compel Sulaiman's spirit
to release Nirmala from his grip.
Gus.
- Yes, ma'am?
- Please help Mbah Gowa.
Help him prepare
a purification ceremony by the river.
Okay. What do you need, ma'am?
- A Javanese goat.
- Yes.
A black male goat. And tumpeng rice.
Let me help you.
Gather as many people as you can.
Clear the site of the accident.
The ceremony will be held there.
Mr. Tetsuya. This is my friend, Tirta.
It's a training method, sir.
I want them to be brave enough to--
Including Nirmala.
Nirmala?
It's not like that, sir.
Nirmala actually wants to swim.
Wait, you never told me that
Nirmala took your swimming class.
Yes, she went once.
This man dropped her off.
Even if Nirmala can swim--
You also never told me that
you've met Nirmala before.
- Listen.
- What else are you hiding, Tirta?
Don't come near me ever again.
Leave.
Yes.
Mr. Tetsuya, can I ask you
for one more favor?
The connection...
Gus! Ragus!
See you.
Where's Mbah Gowa?
Sorry, Miss. You're not allowed to get in.
Why?
You're a woman.
Women are not allowed
to attend the ritual. It's only for men.
You're kidding me.
I'm dead serious.
Mbah Gowa warned us,
a woman's presence
will make this ceremony pointless.
You should go home now.
I'll update you on the results.
- It'll work this time.
- Thank you.
Nirmala must be so proud
to have a mother like you.
Maybe...
I should've learned from you...
on how to make peace with my loss.
Thank you.
Nirmala!
Hey! We found her!
She's here! Here! Here!
I'm scared, Gus.
Your sins are too heavy, Wening.
They cannot be redeemed.
They cannot be cleansed.
Nirmala's loss is
the only just punishment for you.
No one can help you find Nirmala.
Unless...
Where is Nirmala?
She's with you, right?
Where is she?
Uti Yah, please forgive me.
Wicak, please forgive me.
Nirmala, please forgive me.
No one can help you find Nirmala.
Unless...
you follow her.
He has a daughter back in Japan.
He's divorced.
FATAL ACCIDENT IN KASUMIGAURA.
MURDER-SUICIDE BY FATHER?
FATHER PLEADS NOT GUILTY.
Gus.
We should see Mrs. Wening.
Finally, Sulaiman's debt
has been paid off.
Your son, Ragus.
He is incredible.
You are the one who is incredible.
That redemption of sin idea.
Keep talking.
Keep laughing.
Turns out, you three are frauds.
Talk.
Bastards.
Get down.
Okay.
Take care, Uncle.
I can introduce Wening to Mbah Gowa.
You just need to convince her.
Please tell Mbah Gowa that she is serious
about seeking redemption for her sin.
You're insane.
Bastard!
Ma'am.
Mrs. Wening.
I know you are still mad at me.
I want to apologize.
Mr. Tetsuya.
I just realized.
Tirta said you took Nirmala
to her swimming class.
Is that true?
Thank you.
Open the door, please.
Ma'am.
Mrs. Wening.
I want to help you find Nirmala.
You haven't answered my question.
The first time Uti Yah brought
Nirmala here...
I felt very calm.
I never expected that she would look
a lot like Miyako.
Mr. Tetsuya.
The dress fits perfectly.
Thank you, Mr. Tetsuya.
My longing for my daughter
is healed instantly
every time I see Nirmala.
That Japanese man is a liar.
He's not divorced from his wife.
His wife and daughter
died in a car accident.
And he did that intentionally.
When I picked up Uti Yah
and Nirmala that night,
Nirmala seemed to be in pain.
She fell.
She was running around and fell.
She fell?
Let me help you.
It's fine.
Just drink the tea.
I translated this for you.
See for yourself, ma'am.
Why did she fall, Mr. Tetsuya?
Some Japanese prefer the infusion of--
It's more balanced in taste.
The first one was strong.
Mr. Tetsuya.
What really caused Nirmala to fall?
She was naughty.
Miyako.
Naughty.
I...
dislike...
naughty kids.
Kids...
respect...
their parents.
Especially their father.
They found this.
What actually happened?
Do you know where Nirmala is?
Miyako.
Mr. Tetsuya! I'm Nirmala!
Sir! It's me, Nirmala! I'm Nirmala, sir!
Where are you going?
Miyako!
Miyako! Are you okay?
Are you okay?
It hurts!
Where? Please tell Dad.
Please tell Dad.
Sir! Stop it, sir!
Where does it hurt?
Stop it! Are you crazy?
I can report you to the police!
I'll report you to the police!
It hurts. It hurts.
Nirmala.
Throw it away. Don't put it here.
If I stay here...
It's Mala, Mom!
Help me, Mom! This is Mala!
And the naughty kid must to be punished.
I will introduce my daughter to you soon.
She's back.
This is the wish granted by 1,000 cranes.
Bastard!
Ma'am!
Ma'am.
Nirmala...
- We have to get out of here.
- Nirmala...
- What do you mean?
- She's here.
Mala is here.
You bastard!
You're awake?
My daughter will teach you
how to make an origami crane.
Do it like how I taught you.
Nirmala?
Mom?
Wait here.
What do you want?
You should understand.
I just want my daughter back.
I appreciate that.
NAME: WENING SUQATI
PLACE, DATE OF BIRTH: INDRAMAYU 20-03-1984
HAND OVER MY DAUGHTER TO TETSUYA...
Coach.
With this letter,
she's officially my daughter.
So don't be too harsh on her.
Hey. Why don't you show us
how you make origami?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Come here.
Fold the paper in half,
then unfold it.
Fold it on the other side, then unfold.
Are you sure, Ning?
Let her go!
Come!
Mom!
Let her go. She's my daughter.
I know that!
No.
She's happier with me.
You're a killer!
Mom!
Misfortune easily befalls
those who strive hard
for a better life.
They call it the trials of life.
And death...
is a recurring experience for me.
I've died multiple times.
Wening Suqati was found guilty
by the district court judge
of negligence that resulted in the death
of her husband, Sulaiman.
She was sentenced to five months
in prison, with time served deducted.
Wening, who is also the witness
in the case of her child's abduction
by Tetsuya Mori, a Japanese national,
is currently imprisoned
in a women's correctional facility...
Go get changed.
Can you do it on your own?
FIVE MONTHS LATER
See? You can.
Again. One, two...
Again.
Now try that way.
- Again. One... Three.
- Two.
One, two...
Three!
One, two, three!
Have you thought about it?
I really...
want to support you and Nirmala.
I have, Mr. Adang.
We are fine on our own.