In the '80s, many tattooed thugs
were mysteriously murdered,
and shocked the country.
The thugs were scattered in many places,
and came from many circles,
both organized and unorganized.
The organized ones
are commonly known as "Sugali,"
which comes from the word "Gali,"
which stands for "Gabungan Anak Liar,"
or "Wild Kids Society."
It is said that some Sugalis
cannot be killed
either by bullets or sharp weapons.
CENTRAL JAVA, 1984
That's enough.
Get out.
I said get out!
Okay.
Dump them inside.
Anyone else?
I said, "Anyone else?"
Thanks.
You won't get away with this.
You think you can use me?
Then dump me like a stray dog?
Don't overvalue yourself, Djarot.
You are lower than dog shit.
You too, Prapto.
You've really become his lackey.
You think he's going to appreciate you?
You're out of your mind, Djarot.
You were told to create chaos,
but you don't have to drink their blood!
I don't know if you're a human or what.
The time will come…
when you will know…
what I really am.
What do you think you will achieve
with your incantation?
I will make sure
that it will all be in vain tonight.
As long as my blood still flows,
and my body still treads
on the land of the village…
I will keep coming back.
You will all feel my wrath,
piece by piece…
body by body.
I will take all of you…
until there's nothing left.
Then I'll come for you, old man.
I will get my revenge.
I've read your ritual book.
The yellow book…
right?
Maybe you can only be stopped
by your flesh and blood,
but I have another way.
Yanto.
As long as my blood still flows
on this earth,
you will face your doom.
This ends tonight!
MYSTERIOUS KILLINGS OF THUGS
DOZENS OF GALIS WERE EXECUTED: WHO DID IT?
DOZENS OF GALIS WERE FOUND DEAD
EDITORS WERE SENT A PACKAGE
CONTAINING HUMAN HEAD
THUGS ARE MURDERED IN SEVERAL CITIES
WITHOUT ANY REASON
THE WILD KIDS SOCIETY OR "GALI"
INVOLVED WITH BLACK MAGIC?
THUGS ARE MURDERED IN SEVERAL CITIES
WITHOUT ANY REASON
THE WILD KIDS SOCIETY OR "GALI"
INVOLVED WITH BLACK MAGIC?
"KROMOLEO" THE PALLBEARERS, WHO ARE THEY?
KROMOLEO, REAL OR MYTH?
MYSTICAL STORY OF KROMOLEO,
IS IT CONNECTED TO THE GALI?
TRACKING THE WILD GANGS,
WHERE ARE THEY?
MANY "GALI" FOUND DEAD
THUGS ARE MURDERED IN SEVERAL CITIES
WITHOUT ANY REASON
THE WILD KIDS SOCIETY OR "GALI"
INVOLVED WITH BLACK MAGIC?
"KROMOLEO" THE PALLBEARERS, WHO ARE THEY?
MYSTICAL STORY OF KROMOLEO,
IS IT CONNECTED TO THE GALI?
10 YEARS LATER
Are you sure this is a good idea, Zi?
We can still go back to Jakarta
if you change your mind.
I only have one mother, Dik…
and she died.
If they think
I won't come to her funeral…
and think of it as if nothing happened,
then they're wrong.
I still remember…
There were a time
when my mother was good to me,
but there were times
when people would see me as trash.
I'm just an illegitimate child.
Hey, you're not
an illegitimate child, Zia,
and there's no such thing as that.
I just don't understand.
There are too many secrets
about my father.
Is he really that bad of a person?
WELCOME TO MAJENANG VILLAGE
- Sir, can we pull over ahead?
- Yes.
Grandpa?
I already said you didn't need to come.
My mother died, Grandpa.
Why shouldn't I be here?
The funeral is done…
so, you can go back now.
Now you're going to hate me too?
I can't be here even for a day?
No one hates you.
It's completely the other way.
What is he doing here? Is it necessary?
Yes, it is.
Grandpa?
I thought I could help you here,
especially now that you're alone.
- I am used to being alone.
- Grandpa, I'm serious, Grandpa.
It's not safe here, Zia.
- Why isn't it safe for me here?
- You know why!
Is it still because of my dad? Grandpa…
he's been gone for ten years,
can't the people here forget about it?
Time moves differently here.
You are well aware of that.
Ladies and gentlemen…
I've gathered everyone here…
because of an incident that
should not have happened in our village.
- What incident?
Earlier…
Mrs. Ida's daughter came to the funeral.
- Oh, God.
- You all know what I mean, right?
And for you kids,
you've definitely heard of the stories.
But now, more importantly…
I'm asking you all
to not leave your houses tonight.
What if we want to pray?
If you want to pray, then pray at home.
Just pray at home!
Do you understand?
Stay away from windows,
and keep them shut.
If you have curtains, keep them closed.
If someone knocks on your door,
do not open it!
Those who have children,
don't let them out of your sight.
And for those who are unlucky enough
to meet "them" in person,
do not ever look
straight into their eyes. Understood?
What happens
if we look directly into their eyes?
He will come for you…
to take your life.
Mom's favorite dress.
Zia?
What is this thing?
Zia!
- Have you packed your things?
- Not yet.
You don't have much time.
I will take you to town.
- What's this, Grandpa?
- Forget it. That's not important.
These are my personal belongings.
Come on, hurry up!
Why is he in a hurry to kick us out?
We just got here, Zi.
He's worried about the villagers.
Worried about what?
Because they don't like my father.
Grandpa said
my father owed a lot of debts here,
… and he just disappeared.
What does it have to do
with you being here?
Because they are afraid
that my father would appear again.
I also can't meet him.
What if he comes back…
Well, you said that he left his family,
maybe your father…
I don't think he ran away, Dik.
He really loves me.
I'm actually suspicious
about his disappearance.
When I heard
my mother and grandpa's conversation
on the phone last year…
she wanted me to come home
for just one day,
because my best friend
was getting married,
but Grandpa wouldn't allow it.
He said if I came here…
it would cause fatal consequences.
I actually feel like…
my father wants to come back…
but Grandpa won't allow it.
So, what do you do now?
I'm sorry…
for dragging you into this.
This must be Yanto's doing.
Come on, pick up.
You, come with me.
- Me, sir?
- Yes.
- What about me?
- Stay here.
- If anyone comes, you hide.
- What exactly is your plan?
I'm trying to find a way to save you.
Let's go!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Grandpa!
Why can't I just stay here for a day?
- Just until the tire gets fixed, Grandpa.
- Because it's dangerous, Zia.
I know this is hard for you to understand,
but you need to trust me.
Please.
You don't need to be here. Let's go.
You, look for help over there.
- Tell them we need help.
- Is it far, sir?
If you keep asking,
we'll never get close!
- Go!
- Yes, Boss.
The road has not been repaired
by the village chief.
Do you think we should go back?
Just relax.
If there's danger, I'm not afraid.
- I lift weights every day.
- Whatever.
By the way,
no one actually left their house.
It's like a dead village.
People are stupid
for listening to the chief.
Nobody is bringing a curse here.
Meli!
- Yes, Mom?
- The phone.
- Hello.
- It's me, Zia.
- Zia?
- Sorry, Mel.
I can't come to your wedding.
- You know how my grandpa is.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry about your mother.
- Thanks, Mel.
What?
Sir? Sir? Hello? Sir?
Hey! Go back to your home!
Shit.
- I'm out of here, Bud.
- It's just a blackout, Jon.
Jon?
Damn it, he left.
Mom? What's going on?
- Mom?
- Get inside! Do not come out!
- What are you doing?
- I surrender! I surrender!
Zia?
What's taking you so long?
Where's Grandpa?
I thought…
- We have to get out of here now, Zia.
- What are you doing?
He must've brainwashed you, didn't he?
I'm serious, Zi. We have to go.
There's something wrong here.
- What is it?
- I saw a group of strange people.
- They carried a corpse, Zi.
- What corpse?
They're strange, Zi.
- Did you see a ghost?
- I'm not kidding. I'm serious.
You shouldn't have sabotaged
the truck's tire, Zi.
- I just need to know, Dik.
- No.
We have to go home. I want to go home!
- Dika!
- I want to go home!
Stop!
- Jon, where are you?
- Bud?
I thought those things
kidnapped you.
You ran away
when your friend was in trouble.
- You idiot!
- You're an idiot for not believing me.
Please help.
Please don't hurt me.
Let's tell everyone.
Jon?
- Help me, Jon!
- Bud?
- Jon.
Bud? Bud?
Bud, say God's name, Bud!
- Help me, Jon.
- Bud!
Jon!
Jon! Jon!
- Bud?
- Jon!
GUARD POST
MAJENANG VILLAGE
- I want to go home, Zia!
- Stop!
Dika! Dika! Dika!
Dika! Dika!
- Run!
- Come on, let's go, Dika!
Wait for me.
Wait a bit.
- Grandpa, what was that?
- You shouldn't be here!
- What was that? Explain it to me!
- You've seen them, right?
- Who are they?
- A group of pallbearers!
I've seen them, sir.
A group of the demon pallbearers.
"Pallbearer"?
We should go there now. There's no time.
We have to get help. Come on!
Grandpa!
Let's take a short break, Grandpa.
We can't do that, Zia!
We've walked far.
They won't follow us, Grandpa.
You're not safe
as long as you're in the village.
Grandpa! It's time you told me.
What actually happened here?
I know that you know the truth.
Tell me!
- Sir? That's them, sir.
- Hold this for me.
Come on. Run!
Dika! Grandpa! Dika!
Grandpa!
Ah!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
- Run!
- Come on!
- Wait, Grandpa!
- Run!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
- Dika!
- Come on, Zi!
- Grandpa!
- Come on, Zi! Come on!
No, Dika!
Zi? Come on, Zi.
We can't go back. Come on!
My grandpa is there, Dik.
We have to help him. Please.
How? We don't even know
what that thing was.
- We're going to die too!
- He's the only family I have, Dik. Please!
Zi!
If anyone can survive now,
it's your grandpa, Zi!
You know that.
Now, we have to look for a house
with a phone.
We ask for help, just like he planned,
and then we look for him.
Come on, Zia.
Zi, come on.
Come on.
- Meli.
- Meli?
- Meli's house.
- Who is Meli, Zi?
My childhood friend.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Mel?
Meli?
Dika! Dika! Dika!
Help!
- Meli?
- Help.
- Meli!
- Zia!
Meli!
Are you okay?
Kromoleo, Zi…
What's that, Mel?
Mother…
Say God's name, Mel.
Zi.
- We have to get out of here.
- Yeah, but how, Dika?
I don't know,
but we have to get out of here!
Car. Zia, there's a car!
Sir! Sir!
- Sir, stop, sir! Sir, over here, sir!
- Sir!
Sir, over here, sir! Please help us, sir!
Dika!
Get up.
Help me get him up. Come on, Dika!
Ah!
Just a little further, Dika.
Dika.
- You have to survive, Zi.
- No, Dika.
I've seen them too, Dik.
I saw them, Dik!
Zia? I love you, Zi.
Dika? Dika! Dika!
Dika! Dika! Dika!
Dika. Dika! Dika! Dika! Dika!
- He's gone, Zia. Leave him be.
- Dika! Dika! Dika! Dika!
Zia. That's enough, Zia. Zia.
Zia! Zia, please wake up!
Prapto.
- Honey?
- Prapto.
It's Mr. Danang. Wait here.
Coming, Mr. Danang.
Where's the amulet?
You have to come with me.
Honey?
- I can't leave my wife alone at home.
- Then give me the amulet.
I've been waiting for you for years.
Who are you?
Where am I?
Meli? Meli?
Where is Meli? Meli? Mel!
Meli! Meli!
Kromoleo.
Everyone who died tonight…
is because of Kromoleo.
Give me the amulet, Prapto.
This situation is beyond our control.
If this is not resolved,
many more victims will fall.
Why don't you just take her away
from our village, sir?
Someone slashed my tires!
It's too late to find help!
Djarot is back too.
There will be a lot of victims.
Come on, where is the amulet? Hurry up!
This…
this is what has kept you safe
all this time.
Safe from what?
The curse.
Your father's curse.
Give it to me.
So, what are your plans?
Are you going to revive him again?
Yes! I will ask Zia to kill her father.
Where are the salt bullets
that I gave you?
All right.
Just a moment, sir.
Here you go.
I will look for Zia. Hope she's safe.
- Close the door tightly.
- Okay.
Wait here.
Your father…
was beheaded by your grandfather.
But your father is one tough bastard.
He can't just die…
because he uses black magic.
Rawarontek.
As long as my flesh and blood
is still treading this land…
as long as my blood still flows
on this earth,
you will face your doom.
You will know the true meaning of fear.
And as soon as you step foot
in this village…
the Gali thugs arise from their grave…
in the form of Kromoleo.
And anyone who sees them…
will die.
Murdered…
by your father.
Why did you give him the amulet?
You know the risk,
our family will pay the price.
- So, what now?
- You know who he is, right?
You just can't say no
to people like Danang.
The curse is coming to us.
He will kill us!
So, who's scarier now?
That demon or Danang?
Enough, enough, enough!
Just calm down.
Whatever you say.
Prapto.
- Open the door.
- Honey?
So, my father is not dead yet?
Nobody could kill him…
except by his own flesh and blood.
Danang beheaded your father,
and buried his head
separately from his body.
Only he knows where Djarot's grave is.
But it's all in vain…
because the curse of Kromoleo
has been declared.
How can I stop it?
Honey?
Djarot!
You must revive your father's corpse.
Djarot! Bastard!
Join his body with his head…
and stab him with a sharp object
stained with your blood.
Then he will die.
That's your grandfather's plan…
using you to stop your own father.
It's impossible.
Grandpa is not a bad person.
You don't know who Danang really is.
You don't know your own grandfather!
What happened to your father…
is because your grandfather ordered
those Gali thugs to cause chaos.
If necessary, wreak havoc!
All this time…
you all have been safe
because of this amulet.
This amulet is made
from your father's tooth.
Danang?
He is a real bastard.
He's the scum of the earth!
He prepared this amulet for you…
Prapto, and himself…
while everyone else was left to die!
I saw it myself,
then I had to blind myself
so that I would never see Kromoleo!
Let me go, sir.
Let me go.
If you say I can stop all of this,
I will do it.
Even though my dad is a demon…
he was a good father to me.
He will listen to me, sir.
Who said that I want to stop this?
Zia…
this village is nothing
but a colony of evil human beings!
Including me.
They all went silent
when those thugs were massacred
like a bunch of animals!
It all ends here!
I'm tired of hiding.
I want this whole village to die,
to face the consequences
of their own actions!
Let the curse be fulfilled…
and there will be no need
for any more victims.
For doing that…
I apologize.
You have to die, Zia…
so that no one can stop the curse.
Grandpa!
Grandpa! That's enough!
I should've killed you
the first chance I got!
Grandpa!
Are you okay?
Grandpa?
Let's get out of here.
Take that.
Hurry.
You're still alive
because of my granddaughter.
Don't you dare try that again,
I won't hesitate!
We will all die, Danang.
We all deserve to die!
Let's go!
- Where are you taking me?
- Not far from here.
- The important thing is that you trust me!
- Trust you?
There's no reason for me
to trust you anymore!
I know everything, Grandpa.
I already know!
We're all under my father's curse…
all because of you!
You lied to me.
You told me he just left us for no reason.
It's good that you already know.
What are you doing?
We're going to revive Djarot's corpse,
and you will stab him with this knife!
You're such an evil man! A wicked man!
My father might be a demon…
but so are you!
You can say whatever you want,
I still love you.
As long as you can still live in peace,
I'm willing to be a demon for you.
My dad was a good person.
He loved me. He was kind to me, Grandpa.
He disappeared ten years ago.
Now, I have the opportunity
to meet him again, Grandpa.
And you're asking me to stab him?
Zia…
- Djarot is no longer human. He can't die!
- I believe in my father's love for me.
He loves me.
He won't hurt me.
Just try it your way.
The knife's already stained
with your blood.
If you can't do it,
then I'll be the one who stabs Djarot!
Then I will stop you!
But to get to that point,
we must revive Djarot first.
Grandpa!
Why are we going back home, Grandpa?
Your father's grave is in the backyard.
I buried him myself.
You don't feel guilty at all, do you?
How many more victims will it take
for you to feel guilty?
Answer me!
All the villagers are still alive
because of me!
I was the one who saved them all
from those Gali thugs.
You yourself are the one who ordered
those Gali thugs to create chaos!
You don't understand, Zia.
There's a reason for all of that!
A reason!
I know everything, Grandpa.
It was your life decisions that brought
the curse on all of us, not my father's.
The curse is back because of you!
Sending you to live in town
was the right decision for everyone here!
But it wasn't enough!
You insisted on coming back here!
You insisted, and you didn't listen to me!
Now, the curse is back here.
You never told me
why I couldn't come back here…
and meanwhile,
all my family was here, Grandpa.
If I had known,
I would've never come back here, Grandpa!
If it has already happened, so be it.
Maybe I was wrong.
But you also can't be naive.
Your hand is already soiled with blood
as a result of your decisions!
You're right.
Not just the villagers…
Dika also died because of me.
That's enough, Zia. Enough, Zia.
No, Grandpa.
Zia?
I've been safe all this time
because of this.
This amulet…
this part of my dad's body…
- this is what protected me, not you!
- Zia, don't be reckless.
We'll revive Djarot,
we'll end the curse tonight!
My father had the right
to be angry with you…
and the villagers here,
who know the truth, but never do anything…
and even with me, Grandpa,
who never tried to look for him.
Yanto was right, Grandpa.
Everyone here deserves to die…
- including me.
- Zia! Zia!
Zia!
Zia, run!
Father? Father! Father!
Father!
Father. It's me, Zia. Father.
It's me Zia, Father.
I won't mind.
I won't mind, Father.
You deserve to be angry.
Rise, you bastard.
Stay away from my granddaughter.
Danang, I won't let you revive Djarot!
You have the right to kill me.
Grandpa?
Forgive me, Djarot.
I assure you,
your vengeance will be fulfilled tonight.
As long as my blood still flows
on this earth…
you will face your doom.
You have robbed me of my time…
took my daughter.
Tonight…
I'll make time go really slow
for you, old man.
My daughter regretted
being married to you.
During the last seconds of her life,
she really hated you.
Liar.
Ida regretted having your child.
If she couldn't see
the goodness within you,
that means you are the worst being.
We used to be happy, old man.
I had stopped studying this damned magic.
But you forced me to continue,
to perfect this magic!
Because I know…
you murdered everyone
who you ordered to do your job.
You were trying to cover your tracks.
- It was an order. I didn't have a choice.
- I don't have a choice either, old man.
Everyone has a different way to survive.
It's the law of nature.
Grandpa!
Hurry, kill me
before she sees you like this.
Father?
Zia, he's not your father anymore.
He's a demon.
You are an adult now.
Father!
I missed you so much.
Zia…
Father?
That's enough, Dad. Please.
Forgive them.
They have suffered enough, Dad. Please.
And Grandpa,
you have right to be mad at him…
but please don't hurt him.
Zia…
You are very kind…
just like your mother.
But no amount of suffering
can satisfy me anymore.
- I want them to die, one by one.
- No, Father. Don't.
And my spell on this one,
I will drag it to hell with me.
Father, don't.
Don't.
Let me take Grandpa to the hospital first.
Dad, please.
After that, I promise…
I will come back to you,
we'll be reunited.
We'll make up for lost time, Father.
- Zia…
- Please, Father.
Father!
And you…
as I promised,
I will kill them one by one,
- and I will come to you, old man.
- Zia, that's enough.
Go! You don't need to see this. Go!
Zia!
Zia…
Father?
Father…
Grandpa?
- Grandpa…
- Zia?
I didn't wanna tell you, because…
I don't want you to carry my sin.
Promise me
you will be a strong child, okay?
No, Grandpa. Don't talk like that.
Come on, we're going to the hospital.
Come on, Grandpa.
Come on. Come on.
I heard everything.
This is all because of you.
People here are dead.
- My mother is dead.
- Zia! Zia!
It's all your fault!
You all have to die!
You're the one who's supposed to be dead.
- Zia!
- Grandpa?
Grandpa?
Grandpa!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Grandpa! Grandpa! Grandpa!
Don't die. Don't leave me.
Grandpa, get up.
If only that old man had told us
where he buried Djarot…
we wouldn't have to wait this long.
Take him away.