THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD
SEASON 3
Five, four, three…
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD
SEASON 3
RIGEN RAKELNA & INDRA JEGEL
HOST
Good evening,
and welcome to the final night
of The Most Beautiful Girl in the World!
With me, Rigen Rakelna, and my co-host…
I’m Indra Jegel, and I will guide you
during the next four months--
That's too long.
Fine, sorry. I'm sorry.
Tonight, we will determine the match
of our Star Bachelor, Brandon Prakoso.
Wow.
-That’s right.
-Yes.
So, can I keep one of the girls
that Brandon doesn't choose?
If so, I want that too.
Rigen, don't forget.
You have two sick kids at home.
Right, I forgot. I should probably go.
-Please don't. We’re still working.
-My kids are sick.
Oh, right.
-Kia.
-Yes?
Leave it.
The proposal can be finished later.
It's almost done.
You're so busy. Come here!
No big deal, Ram. Don't worry.
-To break the ice.
-Right. Okay, stop interfering.
Thank you for attending
today’s final night, sir.
That’s right. Put your hands together
for Mr. Gunadi Wiraatmadja.
That's right.
And we also have the prince of WinTV.
-None other than Reuben Wiraatmadja.
-Wiraatmadja.
The audience here and at home can’t wait.
-Yes.
-Who will be chosen by Brandon?
But before that, let’s check this out.
Let’s check this out.
Give me my roast chicken.
We have leftovers?
-…announce the winner.
-The winner will be from…
She'll be announced by…
We'll announce it.
-Fine.
-Okay, change this.
ANGGIE SUKMA
Are you okay?
Back again at the final night
of The Most Beautiful Girl in the World.
This moment is intense, huh, Rigen?
That's right.
We’ve arrived at the end of the show.
We will soon find out
the match of our Star Bachelor,
Brandon Prakoso.
I think it will feel incomplete...
-Yes.
-…if we don’t invite Mr. Gunadi
because we know
he is the embodiment of a family man.
-Yes, maintaining harmony in his family.
-Right.
And as the leader of a TV station…
-Guess they didn't do their research.
-…a kind man.
Mr. Gunadi, the stage is yours.
Next up, it wouldn't be complete
if we don’t invite Reuben Wiraatmadja
-to join us on stage.
-Me? This is ridiculous.
Before giving a speech,
Mr. Gunadi and Reuben should congratulate
the five finalists and Brandon Prakoso.
Yes.
-…give congratulations.
-Congratulations.
Congratulations.
Please, this is live.
Okay? Don’t make a scene.
What was that?
Whoa, she slapped him!
Isn't all of this an act?
Did you write this?
No, it wasn't me.
See? I told you, Mr. Reuben is a playboy.
-Watch your mouth.
-Don't tell lies!
What were you thinking, Ben?
Dad, we started dating
before she joined the show this season.
And she already knew she wouldn't win.
What does this have to do
with you dumping her tonight?
Nothing. I just wanted to break up.
And I'm not responsible for her reaction.
This can become
a public deception scandal.
All participants must be single.
No boyfriend.
None of the finalists are single.
All of them have boyfriends.
Their boyfriends allowed them
to date another guy for weeks.
That Brandon something. From the start,
this show was already a public deception.
After a long period of no high ratings,
this show has become our mainstay.
Let's bet on it, okay?
Tomorrow, that one scene will go viral.
And as you wish,
WinTV's rating will skyrocket.
You’re smart, Ben.
But you're cynical.
That's how you raised me, Dad.
My apologies, Gun, Reuben.
We have to return to the studio.
Time for closing.
I’m not needed, right?
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD
-Hey, Jimmy.
-Hey.
I've emailed the presentation material
for the meeting with Mr. Marc.
Have you seen it?
-Yeah. Real Shop, right?
-Yes.
I skimmed through it.
But it's crazy. You prepared it
faster than I could read it.
Did you prepare it
during that incident earlier?
What happened earlier?
I saw a slap, but I have no idea why.
You are so behind, Ki.
To focus on more important things.
That’s true.
But this is good.
I think you can present it.
Seriously?
I only skimmed it, but it's good.
Just needs polishing.
-Okay.
-Good job.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
-Morning, Mr. Reuben.
-Morning, Ivan.
Morning.
-Morning, sir.
-Morning.
Good morning.
Morning, sir.
-Morning, sir.
-Morning.
Is Mr. Agung here as your best friend,
or do you need spiritual advice?
Reuben, please don’t start.
It’s okay, Gun. I’ll leave now.
Ben,
you can be cynical with me,
but not with Mr. Agung.
Isn’t that the truth?
His official position here
is as your spiritual advisor.
Am I wrong?
Anyway, damage control is done.
I've also taken the time to see Anggie,
so people will believe
it was just a misunderstanding.
Luckily, I didn’t get slapped again.
It's good, for now.
Right.
I also want to tell you
to stop handling TSP Bank's variety show.
But why? Branded content is my thing.
Real Shop is fine. You can finish that.
But that’s the last one.
Until I've decided
what you’ll be handling next.
Well, that’s bullshit.
Branded content is the only show
where I don’t have to worry about ratings.
Unlike the other divisions
who worship ratings. Like you.
You need to learn responsibility.
What responsibility?
Real Shop is going well.
The revenue is excellent.
The performance is great.
-There's no problem.
-Hey. Listen!
I've never taught you to date girls
and then dump them just like that.
You were also dating other girls
while being involved with Anggie.
-You're talking nonsense.
-No, I'm not.
Your behavior
almost caused a scandal for us.
The ratings decreased because of soccer.
Reuben, please.
Your behavior towards girls
is disrespectful.
Wow.
Disrespectful?
This is coming from the creator
of The Most Beautiful Girl in the World,
where all the girls
are fighting over a guy.
Don't talk to me about respect.
Maybe it's time for you to settle down.
Okay?
Get married.
Settle down? Get married?
Why do we have to commit
to just one woman?
So they can leave, like how Mom left you?
This meeting is over.
So, that’s the overview
of the reality show
that we will propose
for launching on WinTV
to increase user experience in Real Shop.
In our opinion, sir,
inviting Korean stars isn’t effective.
The audience will remember the stars,
but there's no benefit for Real Shop,
other than repeating their names
during the program.
Yes, but the name of the main sponsor
will be top of mind of the audience.
Yes, I agree, sir.
But it’ll be better if we can highlight
Real Shop's strong points.
Namely, providing overseas goods
that can't be done by other e-commerce.
The budget to hire Korean stars
can be used to increase user experience
for people at home. Potential customers.
-First, we must--
-What if I tell you
that budget is not an issue?
We are aware that budget
is not an issue for Real Shop, but--
Truth be told, your idea is good.
A user experience
that involves the audience.
We can elaborate on that
during on-site executions.
But for this one,
I think K-pop stars will sell more.
-Hi, sir. Sorry for interrupting.
-Hey, Reuben.
-How are you? Good?
-I'm good. And you?
I’m good. Just wanted to say hi.
Well? All good?
-All good.
-Not really.
Your subordinate
was just picking my idea apart.
We got a little feedback from Kiara, sir.
Hey! No worries.
The owner doesn't have to intervene.
Besides, this is a usual annual program.
If there’s a problem,
I usually handle it right away.
Okay, please continue the meeting.
Jim, please come to my office after this.
Okay, sir.
Sir, please continue.
-Yes. Thank you, Ben.
-Yeah, good to see you.
What's up, boss?
I'm not in a good mood.
Not to mention…
Who was she? That girl next to you?
-Kiara.
-Yeah, that one.
She's an assistant producer after all.
Don't mind her.
Obsessed with being a producer.
But she's fast.
I don’t care if she works fast.
You know what she did?
She showed dislike towards me.
I was talking. When I glanced,
she was rolling her eyes like this.
Just let it go.
So what if a girl doesn't like you?
Your life is too plain.
A little complexity is good.
The complexity
between me and my dad is enough.
I don’t want any more of that.
Don't need it.
Good point.
No need. I've had coffee.
I'll have one, then.
Is her face really that bitchy?
That’s how she is. What can we do?
Her life must be hard, huh?
Are you done yet?
You're vomiting too much.
Stop it, okay? That's enough.
Oh, my.
Your stress management
has sucked ever since high school.
You throw up so easily.
A little problem or stress, and you vomit.
At least
my stress isn't harming anyone, Dit.
Isn't it harmful
when you throw up on someone?
-That's nasty.
-You're the nasty one!
You’re the one who threw up.
You mentioned vomiting on someone.
Enough already. Maybe it’s time
to find a new job. A different one.
Like what? I like the broadcasting world.
What can I do?
Maybe the broadcasting world
doesn’t like you. Then what?
Just let it be.
At least until I become a producer.
So I can fulfill my dreams.
I get it.
This is about your dream apartment, right?
Yes, my dream that you said is too high.
We're still going to live together, right?
Huh? What do you mean?
You said you wanted to live with me.
-One room for me.
-What is this? Never heard of it.
-Whatever. I’m leaving.
-Hey.
- You forgot your tumbler! Here!
- Oh, yeah.
Hey, Gun.
How long is Reuben going to be suspended
from branded content?
Reuben is tactical.
He’ll make an excellent leader.
Sometimes, his legal advice
is even more proper than mine.
The mitigation of Anggie's incident
proved that.
He’s really good.
That's true, but he dislikes ratings.
And he hates programs
that he considers have no class.
Is that wrong?
You were the same back then.
That was the past.
He’s definitely talented.
And he's got the skills.
-Unfortunately, he's still a mess.
-And you're not a mess right now?
Ten million!
-Are you serious?
-Yes!
Your cards must be good.
I’ll fold.
Okay. In that case, I’ll see your ten.
And add another ten million.
I'm in. Ten million.
Full house.
Are you serious?
Hey, hold that thought.
-Want to count my money?
-No.
Because I have a straight flush!
Wow, Bas.
Right?
How many times
did I get tricked by you, Gun?
That’s why you shouldn't rush things.
Take it slow.
Gosh, this man is crazy.
-Gun?
-What is it, Gun?
-Gun!
-What's wrong, Gun? Gun!
-Gun? What is it?
-Bas, come here!
-Gun?
I was thinking, it'll be so much fun
if you do an adventure program.
I want it so badly!
But I don't think
I can last for two weeks.
I'll miss you.
I mean, if you like traveling or…
-Sorry, just a minute.
-Sure.
-Hold on.
-Take your time.
Yes? What is it, sir?
Reuben.
Your dad
passed away.
IS THIS ANNA SAVITRI?
MOM, IT'S ME, REUBEN.
MOM, I NEED YOUR HELP.
A FEW WEEKS LATER
Good afternoon.
As Mr. Gunadi Wiraatmadja’s attorney,
I will read the contents of his will.
"To my son, Reuben Wiraatmadja,
the entirety of my wealth,
whether in the form of money or assets,
will be his if he gets married
to the most beautiful girl in the world
in the next six months.
And the one who will decide
whether his future wife
fulfills the criteria
of the most beautiful girl in the world
is a committee
that will be established by my best friend
and spiritual advisor, Agung Santoso.
Thus I conclude my will,
which I wrote consciously,
without any coercion from any parties,
so that it could be exercised properly."
I don’t understand.
Your dad
must have his reasons for this, Ben.
Here’s the thing.
I have very big dreams for WinTV.
Do you know, Mr. Agung?
I want to reform WinTV.
Now that dream could disappear
and it might be hard to achieve it
if I can’t fulfill these requirements.
This doesn’t make sense.
In this room,
the one
who understands your father the most
should be you, Reuben.
This might be an opportunity for me.
-What do you mean?
-Well…
An opportunity to create classy shows.
I’ll even make The Most Beautiful Girl
in the World classy.
You want to handle that show?
I'll be the Star Bachelor.
Huh? What?
Well, yeah. Hear me out.
I'm basically killing two birds
with one stone.
Okay? First,
I can fulfill my dad’s requirements.
Mr. Agung is involved in this, right?
He’s the gatekeeper.
And he's the decision maker.
Hold up.
Can't you just look for a real wife?
Then introduce her to Mr. Agung,
like a normal person would do.
There’s a second reason.
I can make a genuinely classy show.
At least this could be
my leverage for Mr. Agung.
That way, he'll consider me worthy
of WinTV's legacy.
We'll use the same title?
The Most Beautiful Girl in the World?
No need to change it.
That’s what my dad wanted.
And the logo?
-Same thing. He designed it.
-Look, boss.
This whole reality show,
The Most Beautiful Girl in the World,
it's all staged. You still have to find
a woman to be the winner.
You don’t understand.
I want to make a real show.
Nothing will be staged.
From registration of participants,
moving up to the next level,
all the way to the finals,
nothing will be staged. All real.
And finally, I myself
will choose the winner. It's good, right?
I don’t get it, bro.
So, you want to be the Star Bachelor
and you want to look for a wife
through that show? Is that right?
Yes, that’s right.
You can take care
of establishing a committee, or whatever.
Watch the show yourself,
then decide based on that.
And you said nothing will be staged?
Yup.
Here’s the thing.
Do you know
why that program needs staging?
Because we have to get the ratings.
And how do we get that?
From the drama.
That’s why we need to prepare all of that.
I want to make a good show.
As organic as possible.
And the ratings will follow.
All right, then.
-Then we will need a producer.
-Uh-huh.
Jimmy, how about you?
I'm already handling
a lot of live shows, sir.
So, maybe… Ki?
-Sorry, sir. This room--
-Kiara!
-Excuse me.
-Your name is Kiara?
Uh… Yes, sir.
Okay. Just a minute, sir.
Outside.
If I were a regular person,
I wouldn't participate in this show.
That's why I refuse to handle this, sir.
As a woman and a layman,
I consider that show very misogynistic.
Hmm.
This is good. She has the guts
to speak up in the office.
That’s great. It's good.
I get what you mean,
and we'll do this the opposite way.
This show will not be condescending
towards women whatsoever.
A little on-site information, sir.
I'm afraid you might not know.
Miss Galuh resigned
because of the same reason.
She was just being professional
by finishing Season 3.
Good luck to her.
There are lots of similar TV shows
out there.
But for this Season 4,
you'll increase the cringeworthy aspect
by making yourself,
the owner of the company--
-Future owner.
-Okay. As the future owner--
Owner!
Okay, whatever.
Not "whatever." It's "owner."
Sir, as the owner,
you will be the center of attention.
And the prize.
Sorry to say, that's a little tacky.
Well, your job is to make this show
neither tacky nor misogynistic.
You probably need eye drops
if there's something in your eyes.
Maybe your eyes are suffering
from a mini stroke, or whatever.
Try covering them with sunglasses.
-They're fine, sir.
-Okay.
I heard that you're very ambitious
and you're aiming to be a producer.
You want freedom.
And even Miss Galuh
never got this type of freedom.
Let me ask you this.
If an opportunity like this comes along,
do you think
it comes anytime and from anywhere?
Just think of it as a challenge.
Just create a good program.
Let me handle the rest.
Okay?
Well, damn.
Let's make a bet.
A lot of women will definitely sign up.
I mean, who doesn’t want to be
with Reuben Wiraatmadja?
-Me!
-Can you hear me out first?
Okay, fine. Sorry.
He is rich. Extremely wealthy.
Handsome? No need to question that.
Not to mention,
the winner will receive the title
of The Most Beautiful Girl in the World.
-Isn't that the definition of happiness?
-Ouch!
Your happiness
will last until the afterlife.
You're insane. The only odd one. Weirdo.
Can you imagine yourself
joining this competition?
It's stressful.
And the prize
is marrying a man like him? God forbid.
Yeah, you're right. God forbid, right?
-God forbid he's so handsome!
-Hey!
Don’t judge a book by its cover, dear.
I do judge a book by its cover, dear.
Don't forget, I’m a book graphic designer.
Right, damn it. I used the wrong idiom.
- Hey! The tissues are there!
- Okay, fine.
-Want a drink?
-Yes, please.
Just take it.
You said it yourself,
you‘ve been aiming
to be a producer for a long time.
And now the opportunity
is in front of you, you won't take it.
Well, yeah, I do want to be a producer.
But the thing is,
I still want to maintain my sanity.
Imagine this.
I manage to buy that apartment,
but I become insane.
What's the use?
I get it. Work-life balance.
Well, if you want to fulfill your dreams
of buying an apartment,
then you’ll probably have to try
online gambling or online loans.
Right? Both options will still carry
the risk of you losing your apartment.
Don't you have a better alternative?
I mean--
-You’re not supportive at all!
-Because you're so stubborn!
You're ignoring this opportunity
right in front of you. Weirdo!
Forget it! I’m going home.
Eat this martabak.
-You won't take some? Just a piece or two.
-No, I'm full.
-Hold on.
-What is it?
So hardheaded!
Go home!
-Bye!
First, let’s think about the storytelling.
I already prepared that.
Are you serious, Mr. Reuben?
You’ll be the Star Bachelor?
It's not a desperate attempt
for ratings, right?
The objective is to find a wife,
but after three seasons,
none of the winners have gotten married.
Thank you for the questions.
First of all,
yes, I am looking for a wife.
And I’m doing this
to fulfill my late father's last wish.
Unfortunately,
I haven’t had the chance to…
His acting is pretty good.
I urged him to try soap operas.
He refused.
Secondly, we'll flip the narrative.
This isn't about women competing
to win over Reuben Wiraatmadja’s heart.
-Instead…
-This is my personal effort
as Reuben Wiraatmadja to find a soulmate.
A lot of people say that shows like these
use women as commodities.
First of all,
this is not a beauty contest.
Assessment will be based
purely on intelligence,
personality, and compatibility.
And any woman can sign up.
If the things I offer are suitable
with their aspirations in life,
then that’s good.
If not, I will respect that.
He could be a politician.
To end this, I'd like to reaffirm
that I myself will choose the contestants
and eventually determine the winner.
Thank you, guys. Have a good day.
Already 3,000?
-How's it going, Ki?
-Oh, well…
I was just checking
the registration for this season.
We're already up to 3,000 people
on day one. That's a lot, sir.
Maybe because we're opening to the public?
Previously, we hired them.
I told you, if we open it to the public,
many people will sign up.
But are you
-happy with this?
-It's nothing special.
STAGE REFERENCE
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD
SPECIAL SEASON
I don’t have any qualities.
But who knows? Maybe I'll get lucky.
Don’t ask about my age.
The most important thing is my experience
that I can teach Reuben.
Is this what you meant
when you said you won't humiliate women?
We're basically inviting the audience
to laugh at the participants.
We can’t control the women who signed up.
That’s the risk of creating
an organic and unstaged TV show, right?
If that’s what you think,
then you're the one humiliating them.
-I’m humiliating them?
-Yes.
This audition isn't over yet.
Got it? That's the first point.
When I said I'm searching
for more qualified women,
-it doesn't--
-No qualified women
will want to participate
in a show like this.
So, you’re saying they're all stupid?
Or maybe…
Why don’t we use the old strategy, Ben?
We'll set it up, choose them, then pay.
Sorry. Just a thought.
We can’t control who signs up, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-Right.
But we can control
the audience's reaction.
We can choose who will be shown,
how we edit it,
so hopefully, their reaction will be--
-Different from your reaction?
-Positive, sir.
Do you always have to have the last word?
If you want to have the last word,
then go ahead, sir.
Okay.
-Okay.
You said I'll have the last word.
Oh, your last word is "okay"?
I didn’t realize. You didn't tell me.
Okay.
I APOLOGIZE FOR BEING OUT OF LINE, SIR.
SO, WHAT IS YOUR VERSION
OF THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD?
JIMMY TOLD YOU TO APOLOGIZE, DIDN'T HE?
YES, SIR.
PLEASE ANSWER THE QUESTION, SIR.
UNLESS YOU ALSO DON’T KNOW THE CRITERIA?
Well… How should I say this?
Intelligent women
tend to have more dignity.
You talking about yourself?
I think we have to align
your perception of The Most Beautiful Girl
in the World with Mr. Gunadi’s.
Have you two ever talked about this?
-We never discussed this.
-Okay.
Or maybe your mother
talked to you about this?
Anything at all?
I have a meeting.
CHECK TAPE
CLOCK BATTERY
-What are you doing?
-Preparing your breakfast, of course.
Gosh, such an ideal wife.
Why do you have to record this?
Cut it out.
Need any help?
Gun, please stop.
Reuben!
Come here.
What are you doing?
Hey! Cut it out!
Gun, keep him company for a while.
What are you recording?
You should record the view.
You're more beautiful.
Why are you still recording? Stop it.
My turn.
Hey! Don't do that.
-Stop it. Give it here.
-Smile!
Let me take the video.
HEADLINES
REUBEN WIRAATMADJA
WE ALL MOVE FORWARD WHEN WE RECOGNIZE
HOW RESILIENT AND STRIKING
THE WOMEN AROUND US ARE
Boss!
-What’s wrong?
-Nothing.
-We're still eating outside?
-Sure, let’s go!
As we predicted,
women who are capable, smart,
and especially beautiful,
I have to emphasize on this
once more, sir.
They are indeed too proud
to participate in our show.
That’s the reality
we must face for this special season.
Because we want everything
to be real and organic.
-No staging, right?
-Mm-hmm.
What we have to do now
is create a new perception
about Reuben Wiraatmadja.
What’s the old perception
of Reuben Wiraatmadja?
Well…
-It's like that.
-Like what?
Anyway, my idea is a talk show.
-Talk show?
-Yes.
Our class A talk show during prime time.
Jimmy, can we do the talk show tomorrow?
Sure! It’s all good, boss.
-Okay.
-Why do I feel like your assistant?
I'm so sorry.
I swear it's not intentional.
I didn’t mean it.
But can you check tomorrow's schedule?
-Don't worry about it.
-Okay.
Please check tomorrow's schedule.
I'm also going to check
the schedule for this.
Thank you for staying with Chat with Cath.
We still have Reuben Wiraatmadja with us.
Okay, Reuben,
I just want to confirm this again.
All these controversies
surrounding this special season
are simply misunderstandings?
Yes, of course.
It was just a misunderstanding.
I'm looking for a wife,
and hopefully we can also love,
value, and complete each other.
I think it's important to choose someone
who can stand by me in the future,
able to give me advice,
and we can also exchange ideas.
There should be
a sense of equality in that.
I'm looking for a partner who is equal,
in the sense that we can exchange ideas
at the same level of thinking.
That's what I mean by "equal."
So, you're not merely looking
for a trophy wife, right?
No, of course not.
You want to marry
because it's your dad's wish, right?
Well, I want to make my parents happy
before it's too late.
As humans, our time here is short.
And I need a large amount of money
to do all of that.
Does this mean
that you're only interested in my wealth?
First, it's not about what I seek.
It's about the reason behind it.
This is for my parents. After that,
then we can talk about what we believe in.
So what do you think I believe in?
I believe that you also consider money
as merely a tool to achieve your goals.
If that's not the case,
you would have never created this program.
TOP TEN
ANNOUNCEMENT DAY:
TOMORROW!
Finally.
Okay, settle down.
After picking the top 10,
we will enter
one week with Reuben Wiraatmadja.
So, a week with Reuben Wiraatmadja means
a camera will follow me everywhere
when I'm with them?
-Yes. When--
-Even in a café?
Yes, that's right.
It's basically like that.
But I have to remind you.
No touching.
Agreed.
We have to show
that this season is different,
and I know I chose the right producer.
We're finally entering
one of the most important nights
of The Most Beautiful Girl in the World,
Special Season!
The first finalist is
Aleya Sisca!
-Hi.
-How are you?
-Good.
What will you do
if you win this competition?
If I win, I’ll make sure
that I'm worthy of this title.
Because I'm not just physically beautiful.
I'm also beautiful on the inside.
Next, we've got Nikita Karen.
I might not be
the most beautiful girl in the world,
but I can be anything for Reuben.
I’ll make sure he doesn't need to look
at another women ever again.
And next, Agatha Jessica.
If I win this contest,
I will personally use this opportunity
to help young women
so they won't think that special privilege
is the only means to success, Reuben.
For the next woman,
please welcome Helen Kusuma.
Welcome.
This is the VIP lounge.
Actually, anyone can come in here.
But because my dad was often here,
they're a little scared to come inside.
We do have a small kitchen.
We can eat and drink. Yeah.
But have you ever eaten
at the staff's cafeteria?
The staff's cafeteria.
-Can you turn that off for a sec?
-Okay, sir.
Well…
I have, but not very often.
Want to try it now?
-Try what?
-The staff's cafeteria.
Oh, sure.
But we'll be wasting the food here.
It’s okay, I’m joking.
Where’s Kiara?
I don't know, sir.
- Can you please contact her?
- Yes, sir.
-Okay, after you.
-Shall we?
Okay.
What would you like?
I would prefer Padang food.
-It's very tasty here.
-Really?
Sir, were you looking for me?
Yeah. So,
Helen suddenly asked to eat here.
Oh.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Feel free to order, Helen. It's fine.
-I can order first?
This is not in the rundown, right?
-No, sir.
-Yes, it's not.
What do I do now?
-It's okay. Just go with the flow.
-Where have you been?
I had something to do.
This is fine. Just go with it.
What do you mean? I've never been here!
Can I have capcay…
What do you mean?
Just order some food. Act natural.
I have never eaten here before!
I’ll text you the menu
and how to order it.
Don’t go too far from me.
Me?
Yes, you! Don’t go too far. Stay close.
Wear your earphones or something.
Don't stop texting me!
It’s so hot in here, it's insane.
I'll open my blazer.
It’s boiling hot.
Yes, thank you.
-Are you recording?
-Yes.
Hey, what should I eat?
Okay, thank you.
Oh, sorry.
Yes. You should try this one.
It’s different.
-Different?
-Yeah.
Okay.
-Looks good.
-Right?
Do you want to make an order?
-Yes.
Ratih?
-It's Rani, sir.
-Rani! I'm so sorry.
I'd like to order…
-Order what, sir?
-I'd like to order some food.
MENUS YOU MIGHT NOT KNOW
I'd like to order stir-fried squid,
stir-fried tempeh,
musta… mustafo… mustofa potatoes,
and green beans.
-Please wait, sir.
-Sure, thank you.
Do you like doing impromptu visits too?
Not really, I’m not a politician.
But I’m used to eating here.
-To blend in.
-Yeah.
-Reuben.
-Yes?
-Can I ask you something?
-Sure.
Out of all the candidates,
I mean, the ten finalists…
If none of us is suitable for you,
will you cancel the show?
Or must there be a winner?
Here you go, sir. Your order.
Oh, yes. Thank you.
WHAT IF I SAID
THAT I’VE ALREADY FOUND THE WINNER?
Then, let me ask you something.
What is it?
What if I told you
that I’ve already found the winner?
Bon appétit.
Eat it!
You like it?
Yeah, I really do.
I'm allergic.
WE'LL ANNOUNCE THE WINNER TOMORROW.
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE THE ONE
FEELING NERVOUS, SIR?
ACTUALLY, IT'S THE FINALISTS.
OR YOU, BECAUSE YOUR MAINSTAY PROGRAM
IS ALMOST OVER.
IT'S YOUR PROGRAM, MR. REUBEN.
Sir?
It’s time.
Oh, sorry.
Are you talking with the late Mr. Gunadi?
We rarely talked,
even when he was still alive.
When we did,
it usually ended with a fight.
Sir…
My apologies, sir,
but we're running out of time.
Honestly, I haven’t found the answer
about my criteria
of the most beautiful girl in the world.
Now you should be able
to answer that easily, sir.
Your version
of the most beautiful girl in the world
will be inside the woman
that you will choose tonight.
Excuse me.
Okay.
All of Indonesia
and your future wife are waiting.
Let's go.
AWARDS NIGHT
REUBEN WIRAATMADJA
JESSICA - HELEN
TABITHA - NURHOLIA
ALEYA - YASINTA - NIKITA
LULU - CHIKA - VIA
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD
SPECIAL SEASON
All right, welcome back
to The Most Beautiful Girl in the World,
Special Season,
with me again, and also Reuben.
And today, we have ten
of the most beautiful girls
from all over Indonesia.
And girls,
all of you are looking gorgeous.
Reuben, you must be nervous.
How are you feeling today?
A bit nervous.
But honestly, I'm also relieved
because we've made it to the final.
The night we’ve been waiting for.
Are you certain of your final choice?
Yes, I am.
Is it from one of them? Or maybe me?
Definitely one of them.
Oh, okay.
-Fine, let's cut to the chase, Reuben.
-Yeah.
-The time is yours.
-Thank you.
Thanks, Patricia.
First, I would like to thank you all.
Please put your hands together again
for all the finalists here. Thank you.
Okay.
I’ve already decided.
And I choose…
Helen Kusuma.
Congratulations, Helen Kusuma!
All right, we invite Reuben
to give her a precious token.
Dude, please zoom in on Camera 3.
-Okay.
-Uh-huh. It's a good moment to capture.
Nice.
-Reuben, give her a hug.
-Okay.
What about a kiss?
We'll do that later. When it’s official.
Oh, yeah! All right.
Thank you to the other beautiful women.
See you. Bye.
Congratulations!
-Mr. Reuben!
-Hi, Mr. Reuben!
-Hi!
I’m so impressed with you.
You prepared this party for them.
They worked hard
during the past three months.
-Hi, Jim.
-Boss.
-Helen.
-Hi.
I want to talk to him. Walk you there?
Okay.
-Just a sec, Jim.
-Sure.
Alin!
Please help.
Careful.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome. Thank you, Alin.
What is it, boss?
Where’s Kiara?
You miss her?
I was just asking.
This is her show too.
There she is!
Sorry I'm late, sir.
I’ll leave now, boss.
Me too, sir.
-Kiara.
-Yes?
Why do you look so tired?
Uh, it’s okay, sir.
I just finished the report.
Pulled an all-nighter. Just the usual.
Jimmy probably prepared a lot of drinks.
You shouldn't drink right now.
Just eat some food, then take a rest.
Didn't get enough sleep, right?
Just sit down and relax.
-I’ll just drink water then.
-Water is good.
-Ten gallons, sir?
-Ten… gallons.
CONGRATULATIONS, REUBEN.
I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU. MOM.
You’re polluting the sea.
Haven't you eaten?
I have, sir.
Thank you.
Gosh.
-I should have recorded that.
-Please don't.
I’m seasick.
It's not because of the alcohol.
Jimmy said you have tummy problems?
Why would he tell you that?
-Because I asked him.
-What did you ask?
I asked about you.
But why would he tell you
about my stomach problems?
Because I asked in detail.
I want to know my producer's character.
But for what purpose?
I just wanted to know.
Are we going to talk about this
until morning?
Yes.
-No.
-Okay.
Kiara, your work is amazing.
I'd like to offer you a bonus.
The waves are scary. That's unusual.
-Whoa.
-Wow.
Sir, I'm officially
a full-time producer now, right?
That’s for sure. But that’s not a bonus.
It's about a bonus. What do you want?
An apartment?
Huh?
Sir! Oh, no!
Sir? Mr. Reuben!
Sir? Mr. Reub--
Are you okay, sir?
We're…
Damn it.
Shit.
Where are we?
I think we’re on one of the islands
of the Thousand Islands.
Then there must be someone
living on this kind of island, right?
Sir, Thousand Islands
is made up of 110 islands,
and only 11 of them are inhabited.
Maybe we're on one of those 11 out of 110.
If there were locals here,
someone should've found us by now.
Because we didn’t look for help.
-We should look around.
-Fine.
Let's walk along the coastline.
We can estimate the size of this island.
-I don’t know. Let’s find help first.
-Fine.
Don't just wait here. I'm not panicking.
-Let's move.
-I didn’t say you're panicking.
Hello!
-Don’t walk too fast.
-An island this big,
-there must be someone. It's impossible.
-Okay, calm down.
What should we do?
Isn't there any help here? Impossible!
Hello! Anybody here?
How come no one on the boat
realized we’re missing?
-They don't know?
-It was crowded.
Hello?
-Sir.
-Yeah?
These are our footprints.
We’re back to where we started.
-Oh, yeah.
-The whole island is only this big.
How come there’s no one here?
What should we do now?
Okay, I’m…
I'm going to enter the island
-to look for fresh water.
-Huh?
Humans can survive 30 days without food,
but only three days without water.
So, I’ll go look for fresh water.
Sounds like you often get stranded.
How do you know those things?
I was once an assistant producer
for an adventure show around Indonesia
on WinTV.
-Can you climb over?
-Of course. It’s easy.
Okay.
Ow!
Are you sure we should go inside?
We don’t know what’s in here.
If we get lost, sir,
we’ll just find a way back to shore again.
Still, it's scary to explore
without knowing what’s in there.
Don’t you just want to sit by the shore?
Let's just wait and stay there.
We can sit down. Maybe someone will come.
It'll be easier for them to find us.
If we go deeper inside,
the people who'll come to the shore
to save us will get confused.
They’ll have to search in the woods.
You remember what was happening
when we fell last night?
-There was a party.
-Mm-hmm.
It'll take them at least one or two hours
to realize we're missing.
After that, they have to search
all the islands in Thousand Islands.
At least seven to ten days
for them to find us.
Watch what you're saying.
We're talking about seven to ten days!
That's… Ow!
Ten days? That's crazy!
What are you doing?
Sitting down. Lose the attitude!
What is it?
Kiara?
Kia? Why are you drinking like that?
This is fresh water.
We don't know if it's sterile or not.
So, you don't want to drink?
Fine, it's up to you.
Well, I…
Sure, I want to drink.
But I want to see your reaction first.
-If you're fine, then I'll drink it. If--
-This is clean, sir.
It hasn't been boiled yet.
We haven't cooked it.
Do you see a kitchen here, sir? A stove?
A five-star restaurant? No, right?
Why are you suddenly being rude?
You were fine just a moment ago.
It's impossible when stranded with you!
-Oh, now you're being informal?
-Yeah. So what? Don't like it?
-I don't.
-Listen.
You're not my boss here.
I don't know
how long we're going to be here
and I will not be responsible
for your safety.
You want to drink or not, I don't care!
Kiara?
Kiara! I'm not done talking!
Find a bottle, fill it with water,
take it to the beach.
Then we'll build a shelter.
Okay.
-Can you do it?
-Yes, I can.
Want me to do it?
It's working! The fire is lit!
-Really?
-It's smoking!
Congratulations! You won the world record
for the longest time to start a fire.
Truly the best!
I was just about to give up, Ben.
You didn't give up on me, right?
You did okay today.
As someone who didn't know his way
around a food stall yesterday,
this is not bad.
Well, thanks, I guess.
We'll try fishing for food tomorrow.
We should take turns.
One person sleeps, the other keeps watch.
Who'll go first?
I'll take the first watch.
You go ahead and sleep. Ladies first.
Okay.
I actually don't know
what to watch out for.
We're the only ones on this island.
Nobody's here.
Well,
we never know what animals are out there.
-There could be snakes or something else.
-Huh? Hey!
Don't speak so carelessly.
Wait, don't go to sleep yet!
I don't know how to handle snakes.
Just talk to them, Ben.
Ask them about their life goals
and why they want to be a snake.
Make sure the fire doesn't go out,
or we'll get cold.
Maybe a ship will sail by us
and they will see the fire.
You can shout for help if that happens.
I thought I should shout,
"Hey, what are your life goals?"
"Why do you want to be a ship?" Right?
Please wake me up in three or four hours.
Does your watch work?
Sure, it's a Rolex!
Ben!
Wake up! Why didn't you wake me up?
What is it? I just went to sleep.
You're lying! I bet you fell asleep.
No, I didn't. I just went to sleep.
The firewood is already cold,
which means
the fire has been out for a few hours now.
No. I wanted to wake you up,
but didn't have the heart to do so.
You were sleeping soundly.
I just fell asleep.
Figured I'll keep watch.
Okay. Get up.
-For what?
-Fishing.
Don't you want to eat? Let's go!
How can we go fishing?
We don't have any equipment.
Ben, I got one!
What?
-Didn't you say it's hot?
-It is!
SOS
You didn't wake me up again.
The last text I got was from my mom,
and I haven't replied yet.
So…
how is your relationship with your mom?
Sorry. I'm just asking if you don't mind.
She left my father and I
when I was just a child.
For no reason at all.
Even now, I still don't know.
I mean, why did she have to leave us?
Sometimes,
I'm still looking for the answer.
Maybe she doesn't love me?
Or she doesn't love my father?
I finally realized that maybe
love could run out.
Has she ever looked for you?
Didn't even come to Dad's funeral.
About that apartment…
Why do you want it so badly?
How nice do you want it?
Well, just a regular apartment.
No need to be too nice.
But as someone who has been living in…
What's the right word?
An uncomfortable place, I guess?
I just want to live in a place
that suits my needs and preferences.
And your parents?
-They have passed away.
-Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
They died when I was still in college.
And I don't have any siblings,
so I live alone.
What is your biggest dream, Ki?
Is this a job interview?
I already told you. That apartment.
Your biggest dream is owning an apartment?
For someone like me,
having a decent home is an achievement.
Okay. All right.
What's yours?
Reforming WinTV.
I mean, I want WinTV
to become a classy TV station.
A station with high-quality programs,
not just focusing on ratings and ads.
If I get the opportunity to lead WinTV,
I might eliminate programs
like The Most Beautiful Girl in the World.
-Gone.
-Gone. Poof!
Disappear.
My father was always in denial
about the decline of TV stations.
But I actually think of it
as a huge opportunity
that can be turned into a positive impact.
You can use…
The last program I worked on
as an assistant producer.
Which one?
The one about traveling around Indonesia.
You can totally revive that.
It's a great program.
You do have other dreams
besides having an apartment.
That's different. That's not a dream.
-It's a life goal. A dream, right?
-No, it's not. That's a plan.
-What's the difference between the two?
-It's different.
Dreams that are not fulfilled
will make us sad.
For plans, if they do not happen,
it will just annoy us.
To be honest, I was expecting
a more philosophical answer than that.
I'm sorry,
I guess that wasn't very philosophical.
Let me try that again.
A plan is outlined in a proposal.
Whereas a dream is formulated and spoken
in our hearts every time we pray.
And before we fell off the ship.
-Am I right?
-Yeah.
Yes, you're right.
Is this cooked? Is it done?
Should be done now.
-Let's try it.
-Try it.
We've eaten this a few times now,
and it's also tasty without seasoning.
-Right?
-Maybe because we're hungry? Or what?
-No. It's fresh.
-That's it.
-That's right.
-It's fresh.
Once we're back in Jakarta,
I'll take you to a French restaurant.
The food is amazing.
Their fish is so good!
No way.
The best grilled fish ever
is the one in Benhil. Ever tried it?
-No.
-No?
We'll go there someday.
Not everything that is the best
has to be expensive.
What?
-What is it?
-Nothing.
Well?
-Okay.
I still can’t believe it.
That you got stranded
with Reuben Wiraatmadja?
What a nuisance.
Gosh, I'm choking.
I'd rather be stranded with dolphins.
My gosh!
So, what can't you believe?
That thing you said earlier.
About you wanting to eliminate
The Most Beautiful Girl in the World.
Oh, right.
From the beginning, I only participated
in that show to fulfill my dad’s wish.
And after it's done,
I figured that was it.
I think I've found…
what I’ve been looking for.
The most beautiful girl in the world?
Yes.
Helen Kusuma.
-The waves are huge, huh?
-Whoa.
I know, right?
Will it reach all the way here?
I don’t think so.
Ben!
Ben…
Ben, move!
It’s been five days
since Reuben Wiraatmadja went missing.
Any clarification?
For now, the rescue team
is still conducting their search.
A producer, Kiara Clarissa,
was also declared missing with Reuben.
Any explanation about this?
We haven't gotten the latest news,
but we suspect
that Kiara also fell into the sea.
Once again, I’m asking for your help
to protect our privacy as their family.
You already consider yourself
an official member of the family?
You don’t have to respond
to all the reporters.
-Sir?
-Yes?
This is Kiara’s best friend, Dita.
-Right.
-I'm Dita.
-I'm Agung.
-Helen.
She wants to help too.
Okay.
Sir, is that…
I want to join the search for my son.
Ben!
-Why didn't you wake me?
-You wouldn't budge! Get over there!
Come on. Go! Over there!
Ben!
We can still fix that!
Stop! Just look at me!
-We can fix it!
-Enough. Don't look at it.
Look at me. Just look at me.
Yes, but…
It's okay! It's all right!
Morning.
That's it.
Okay.
If it collapses, we'll build it again.
Over and over again.
And it’s easy to find the resources.
Fine, then. You should just live here.
I think it suits you.
That’s a good idea.
I'm serious! It’s okay.
I’m happy living here.
No burden at all.
All right, then.
So, if a ship comes here to rescue us,
I’ll go back to Jakarta
and you’ll stay here.
-No way. You have to stay here too.
-Huh?
Says who?
You're the one who wants to stay here.
So, there’s no need to make…
What was it? The one you wanted to create?
High-quality programs
without focusing on ratings.
That needs to be done.
You’ll be the producer.
You told me to stay here.
How can I be the producer?
If we go back to Jakarta,
we’ll make a good show together.
But if we have no choice but to stay here,
we'll live together.
Sorry, I think I'd rather go home.
You’re so beautiful when you smile.
Do it often.
-What's with you?
-It’s true.
In Jakarta, you always look so bitchy.
No, I don't!
I’m not bitchy. I just don't have a reason
to laugh at the office.
When we’re back in Jakarta…
When we work together again…
we should have
a lot of reasons to laugh
and to make you smile.
I think
you have to make up your mind first.
Do you want to stay here
or go back to Jakarta?
You seem very indecisive, sir.
Actually, it’s not about where I live.
-Then what?
-It's with whom.
That’s far more important.
Because it feels completely different
when we live with someone…
who can understand us, and vice versa.
Do we…
understand each other?
Was I talking about us?
NATIONAL SEARCH AND RESCUE AGENCY
AMBULANCE
EMERGENCY MEDICAL RESPONSE
EMR AMBULANCE
Reuben!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Reuben!
Oh, Ben!
Nurse, the girl who was with me…
Where is she?
She's right outside.
-Okay.
-I’ll take my leave, sir.
-Thank you, nurse.
-You're welcome.
Ki?
Reuben.
I’m so grateful you’re okay.
Why are you only showing up now?
I felt so guilty.
I didn’t even have the guts
to reply to your messages.
But I did reply your last text.
-Maybe you didn’t receive it.
-Yeah, I didn’t.
Reuben…
when I heard you were missing,
my guilt tortured me even more.
And finally, I decided to face it.
You didn’t have enough reason
to come to Dad’s funeral?
I understand.
You must have been blaming me
all this time.
Because, as you know,
I cheated on your father.
I made the biggest mistake of my life.
I was young,
and I had a busy husband
who rarely came home.
Then suddenly, there was another man
who gave me affection.
And I accepted it.
But then, I lost everything after that.
I lost your father…
and you.
Then what?
You’ll leave again?
If you want, I'll leave again--
"If you want, I'll leave again"?
You left based on your own decision,
not because I told you to.
So, don’t turn this on me, Mom.
Why am I the one…
If you want to leave, then go ahead.
-It's your call.
-Reuben.
Please forgive me.
Forgiveness won't bring Dad back.
Thank you, all of you.
Thank you, sir.
Reuben.
-My God, I was so worried about you.
-Hey.
-I'm fine.
-You okay?
-Yeah. Nope.
-Are you hurt?
What happened?
Hey.
Where were you yesterday?
Is there something urgent, sir?
The show is over, right?
I’m worried about you.
Can we continue this in my office?
-We can do it here, sir.
-Please?
What’s wrong with you?
Are you okay?
All good, sir.
About what happened earlier with Helen, I…
I didn’t know
she was going to show up like that.
And I was just trying to comfort her.
I don't think
you have to explain anything, sir.
To tell you the truth.
There’s nothing between us anyway, right?
Kiara, please.
Everything that happened on the island…
That was real.
This is not a TV show, sir.
As I told you,
we have nothing to talk about.
Which one is real, which one is staged.
The reality which I realize now
is that we're in Jakarta,
not on the island.
You… are my boss.
And you're about to get married.
If there’s nothing more to discuss,
I'll excuse myself.
Is that all? You're done?
Women can only run away
when there's a problem.
Well, that’s fine.
But don’t blame me if I feel like…
why bother with a commitment?
In the end, we’ll get abandoned anyway.
What's the point?
Okay, then.
Just maintain a casual relationship.
No need to be so serious.
We'll eventually…
Go ahead, slap me.
If I slap you…
you won't feel guilty anymore?
Don’t confuse this
with your disappointment
against your mother.
Didn't you think this through?
You already have a future wife.
You chose her in front of
millions of Indonesian viewers.
What exactly is your plan? Cancel it?
And if you cancel it, then what?
You're treating Helen the same way
you treated all your previous women.
Now, forget all of that.
Just forget it, and ask yourself.
What do you want?
You don’t know, do you…
Mr. Reuben?
Kiara, please.
So, what now?
Well, nothing, Dit.
He will definitely choose… Helen.
She’s beautiful, smart, and perfect.
He still has to save
his inheritance, right?
I wasn't asking about him.
I was asking about you.
How about you?
You know I'm terrified of having a dream.
The best thing I could dream of
is that apartment.
Turns out, I'm actually right.
Because,
the only time I allow myself to dream big…
it all comes crashing down not long after.
It hurts to fall, Dit.
Everyone has the right
to fall in love, Kiara.
But sometimes it hurts.
That's why it's called "falling" in love.
You’ll be fine.
I’ll be here. All right?
It's unusual for you to stay long.
Well, I just miss Dad.
Me too.
You're finally able to miss him?
Even though the two of you
were always fighting.
I always felt
that he could never understand me.
But at the same time,
I also never learned
to understand him better.
But he still tried.
He tried, Ben.
And he actually wanted
to get along with you.
I don't remember how he was with me.
I mean, how he treated me
when I was still a child.
Well, except from some old videos.
Your dad was a great guy, Ben.
He loved you. He loved your mom.
Maybe he had a unique way
of showing his love, huh?
Well, he's… How should I say it?
It's hard for him to express his feelings.
Why did he want me to…
marry the most beautiful girl
in the world?
Do you know the real reason?
I don’t know about that.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
Ben, there’s someone who knows more
and can help you find the answer to that.
Agung told me everything.
About the inheritance and…
the most beautiful girl in the world.
Ben,
you once asked for my help, right?
I hope this will help you
to understand your dad better.
This is the only video of your dad
that I kept.
Thank you, Mom.
-Dad?
-Yes?
I want to marry
the most beautiful girl in the world.
Do you even know what that means?
-No, I don't.
-Well…
If you marry
the most beautiful woman in the world,
a younger one will then come along,
and she'll be even more beautiful.
Then what?
I must get a new wife?
Whose smart boy is this?
Bet you learned this from your mom.
That's messed up.
You want to get a new wife?
Replace her with a younger one, huh?
Did Dad teach you that?
You're really the best for us.
The most beautiful girl in the world.
When did I become
the most beautiful girl in the world?
Lots of women are more beautiful than me.
That’s right.
But they don’t love me,
and I don’t love them.
Good afternoon, everyone.
As the producer, today I will present
the results of our reality show,
The Most Beautiful Girl in the World.
You can see that we achieved
an average rating of 3.6% and 20% shares.
Therefore, we managed
to make a significant contribution
to WinTV's overall ratings and shares.
Regarding revenues,
we obtained 15 billion from advertisements
and 10 billion from sponsorships.
Which means,
we contributed enough profit for WinTV.
Next up, here you can see
our social media reach.
We got positive responses
throughout the season,
with 20 million impressions
from all of WinTV's social media
on platforms such as Facebook,
Instagram, X, YouTube, and TikTok.
THE WINNER OF THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL
IN THE WORLD, HELEN KUSUMA
Next up
is the presentation about the winner,
which will be delivered by Mr. Reuben.
-Go ahead, sir.
-Thank you.
Helen is an amazing woman.
And I think that statement
doesn't need to be elaborated.
We now live in an era where everything
is measured and assessed by numbers.
When something can't be measured,
it will be considered invalid.
But in my opinion,
not everything can be measured
or assessed by numbers.
I've actually been thinking.
Why did my father want me to marry
the most beautiful girl in the world?
What does that mean?
He even established a special committee
to validate that title.
I may not have been close with my father,
but then I found out that for him,
beauty is not always about appearances,
and not something that can be measured.
Beauty can’t be measured
with numbers or graphics.
Especially when we're talking about love.
So, if something can still be measured
and assessed by numbers,
then that’s not love.
Love can help us face
even the most difficult times.
It’s working! The fire is lit!
Whoa!
Love can also warm our hearts
in the midst of a cold situation.
Love enables us to rebuild a home
that may have been destroyed by a storm.
Love makes us feel calm,
even when we feel empty.
For the past six months,
I have learned so much…
about the true meaning
of the most beautiful girl in the world.
I’ve learned a lot about love.
The most beautiful girl in the world
is someone who loves you
and is loved by you.
You can understand each other,
appreciate each other.
And you can only feel those things.
And I think finding a love like that
is everyone's dream.
A dream that is always spoken
in our prayers.
Maybe now is the right time
for me to make my dream come true.
Kiara, will you marry me?
I’m sorry, sir.
I can’t be a part of your TV show.
Kiara.
Kiara, wait.
Kiara, just hear me out. Wait!
Can’t I talk to you?
Hey!
-Hold on.
-What is it?
I want to talk.
You asked me what I want,
and now I have the answer.
I want you. I want to be with you.
Please.
I love you.
Ben, you don't know me well enough
to talk about love.
And you asked me to marry you?
It's not that simple.
Tell me right now.
Tell me that you don’t want to be with me.
Tell me that you don’t have
any feelings for me, at all.
Ben, marriage is a big deal.
You can’t just know someone for two weeks,
then say "I love you"
and ask them to marry you.
You think this is your reality show?
This is real life!
You want to marry me
because you have to get married, right?
I don’t want to lose you.
You don’t want to lose me…
or you don’t want to lose
your inheritance?
I'm sorry, but…
I'm not your way out.
SIX MONTHS LATER
So, with the two million
in series A's fundraising,
we will give 20% of our shares.
So, that’s it.
Interesting.
Your start-up company is very interesting.
An optimistic media
about positivity in Indonesia.
Ben, I love your spirit.
Thank you, sir.
Give me a week,
and I’ll give you an answer.
Okay, I will gladly wait.
Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-By the way,
your former employee who joined us
is a real asset.
Who is it?
I humbly apologize once again,
especially to Helen Kusuma,
for the mistake I have made
due to lack of consideration.
Also, this has no connection to WinTV.
This is purely my fault.
I believe Helen deserves to find happiness
with the right person.
I apologize once again.
I'm sorry.
Hello, Miss Producer.
Hi!
Oh, hey! My gosh! How are you?
-I’m good.
-Gosh.
I'm sorry I missed your pitch earlier.
No worries.
Oh, you look great!
Beautiful.
Thank you, and you also look…
not bad.
-Not bad?
-Not bad.
-Not too bad.
By the way,
I heard the recent news about you.
You didn’t claim your inheritance,
and built your own company instead.
It’s been a while.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
I'm just catching up now.
But I’m sure Mr. Gunadi must be proud.
And I respect you
for apologizing to Helen in public.
In the history of Indonesian television,
I think no one has ever apologized
in public. Almost no one, right?
-Maybe.
-Maybe, but it’s rare.
Yes, but it has happened before.
Dinner, tonight?
-Tonight?
-Yup.
I can't do it today.
Okay.
-Tomorrow?
-Tomorrow, yes.
Okay. At 7:00 p.m.?
-Seven is okay.
-Yup.
Good to see you.
Good to see you too.
I’m happy to see you, Miss Producer.
See you.
SEAFOOD IDOLA 88
Excuse me, sir.
- Thank you.
- Alright, sir.
We’re already hungry.
-Perfect timing.
-Yup.
Sir?
Ta-da!
So…
what’s your plan now?
If we're talking about plans,
I definitely want to try
to build my company properly.
I don’t know
what the future holds, but we'll see.
But here’s the thing.
Okay, that’s a plan.
But I want to talk about dreams.
Okay.
Have you fulfilled your dream
of buying an apartment?
Sorry.
-I have.
-Oh! That's good!
With a mortgage.
That’s fine. It’s a start.
With a very long mortgage period.
It’s okay.
I’m proud. I’m happy.
-Yeah?
-Yeah, really. I'm happy to hear that.
Thank you.
You worked hard for that.
Incredible.
Do you often visit WinTV?
Not really. Once in a while. Sometimes.
But I’m spending
more time with my mom now.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We often hang out together and talk.
I feel really happy, and so is she.
Happy to hear that.
Thank you.
So, have you tried this fish?
-Okay, let me try it.
-Okay.
Try the fish.
Well?
-How is it?
-Delicious.
Yeah, right? I told you so.
Compared to the grilled fish
from your favorite French restaurant,
which one is better?
This is better.
Maybe because I'm eating it with you.
Wow, that's so cheesy!
Did you know,
I almost got lost when I parked?
-Bullshit! Seriously?
-I did!
I've never eaten here.
Didn't know where to park.
-There's plenty of parking space.
-I got confused.
-Kiara.
-Yes?
Do you know that I love
hearing you laugh and seeing your smile?
And…
I want to be the reason
you smile every day.
That's all for now.
-That's all for now?
-Uh-huh. That's all for now.
So, if I want to hold your hand right now,
is that not allowed?
That's okay.
It's okay if I hold your hand.
You always have to have the last word
and take the initiative, huh?
Hey! If I hadn't taken the initiative,
we would have died on that island.
Yeah, you're right.
Subtitle translation by