Storm Yulee continues
its way across the UK,
prompting a rare
red weather warning
from the Met Office
for the strength of winds
battering the coast
of eastern Scotland.
Hiya.
Hi.
They want me.
Tomorrow at Clipper Quay.
That's great.
Gives you a month without me
getting in the way
- of all this stuff.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Yeah.
I'll probably have
the whole place framed up
by the time you're back.
Good. I want video updates.
I want reports.
I want to hear all about it.
Yeah. You'll get them.
Daily.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
I know.
Just remember, it's, uh...
it's like going into space
but it's underwater.
What's hilarious is you think
I find that comforting.
Humans shouldn't be
at the bottom of the North Sea.
I know. I know.
But it is pretty cool.
It's a good thing you're cute.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Cute?
Your cute, cool diver boyfriend?
Husband? Fiancé?
Uh, Chris Lemons,
one of the divers.
- Chris Lemons?
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- You all right, guys?
- You all right, mate?
How's it going?
- Oh, morning, Craig.
- Chris.
I'm just gonna find out
about the job.
- I'll tell you later.
- All right.
Duncan.
Hello, handsome.
What you got for me?
Well, I hear we got
a new captain.
Oh, yeah? Let's hope this one
doesn't cancel Christmas, eh?
Yeah, right?
- Nice to see you.
- How's the house coming?
- You finish my room?
- Yeah, it's going good.
I think we're gonna
paint it pink.
Is that okay?
Or green or purple or...
Pink is actually...
that's a beautiful color.
You know, a lot of people
think it's feminine.
Where you going?
Just taking two bottles
of hot sauce.
Okay.
Hey, Stu.
Seen how much helium
they're loading on board?
Hmm. It's gonna be a deep one.
Deeper the better, I suppose.
That's 200 feet.
- Hey.
- Huh?
- Morning, Chris.
- Made the cut.
Yep! Easy there.
You all right, lads?
- How's it going?
- Hi, Chris. Good to see you.
So you heard who's on board?
Who's that?
The Vulcan, diver one himself.
Oh, yeah?
I was starting to think
he was just a myth.
Well, should be a fun sat
if you're on his team.
Excited to get in there.
Yeah, I bet.
Okay.
You lot are gonna be living
in our glamorous tin cans
for the next 28 days,
where you'll be pressurized
down to 300 feet.
You're gonna be my hands
on the seabed
replacing a section of pipeline.
Can't have the gas flow
interrupted,
or people's homes will go cold
this winter.
Once the job's done, you'll
have four days decompression
when your hands can do
whatever they want.
Okay.
Team C: Nick, Alex and Paul.
Team B is Stu, Kirk and Brad.
Team A is Duncan, with Chris
and that bundle of joy there.
Right, I'm starting blowdown
before departure.
Doors close in ten minutes,
so get cracking.
David, it's Chris.
Nice to meet you.
Just Dave.
Dave. Sorry.
Uh, looking forward
to doing sat with you.
Yep. See you in there.
Yeah, see you in there.
- See you in there, Duncs.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I see you made Chris
feel nice and welcome.
How is the kid, anyway?
Solid.
He, uh, worked as a deckhand
for three years
before he got the nod,
but then he did
his first five dives with me,
and as we both know, I am
the finest sat daddy around.
Good.
"Sat daddy"? Really?
That sounds strange
coming out of your mouth.
As an old man,
I find I'm a bottom-bunk guy,
you know, just in case
Mother Nature calls.
Your, uh... your wife?
Uh, no. Fiancée.
Word of advice:
Once that door closes,
everything outside
is just a distraction.
Keep your focus
where it needs to be, yeah?
Hey. Don't worry about him.
He's a grizzly when he's here,
but, you know,
once he gets home,
he's a real softie.
He's just daddy
to his two little girls.
Christ, you got
enough chocolate there?
Just enough for one a day.
Divers, are we good
to lock the doors?
Team A standing by.
Team B standing by.
Team C standing by.
Doors closing now.
Doors closed. Stairs away.
96.4% helium. 3.6% oxygen.
Gas ratios confirmed.
I'm turning on the taps, boys.
Let's go for a ride.
I'll never get used to this.
What?
Here we find ourselves
at the bottom of the world.
You are now able to operate
at 300 feet below sea level,
where it will be pitch black
and bloody cold.
And remember, should you step
outside the chamber
prior to decompression,
the gas now saturating
every cell in your body
will expand so rapidly
your vital organs
will quite literally explode.
He says that every time.
How you feeling, Duncan?
Aces, amigo.
Aces.
Chris, Dave, you okay?
All right,
I'm gonna get some rest.
I'll see you
when we come on station.
Grub's up.
For God's sake,
show some modesty.
Cover yourself.
Back in the day, though,
you know,
when I was starting out,
you only needed two things:
little common sense
and a good bottle of Scotch.
Here we go.
It really was the Wild West.
Thank God it's not
like that anymore.
Yeah.
I guess I'm the last of my kind.
Kind of a relic.
Which explains why they're
putting me out to pasture.
What are you talking about?
Well, the company,
in its infinite wisdom,
has decided 20 years
is enough for me
and, uh, you know,
this will be my last rotation.
Really? Wh-Why didn't you
say something?
Because I don't want everybody
making a fuss, you know,
before going in.
You okay?
Is everything all right?
Yeah. You kidding?
It'll be great
to have some free time.
You know, I'll take up golf.
But I did think that I had
maybe ten more years left.
Or more.
If it's any consolation,
there's a high possibility
that all of our jobs
will have been automated
in ten years, so...
Oh, yeah, that does
console me, Dave. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Well, I tried.
All right. I'm going to bed.
-Night.
-Nighty night.
So this is our last sat
together, then.
Yeah.
I can't believe it, either.
Why don't you pull a Craig,
get in the hot seat,
call the shots?
What?
No.
I-I am not management material.
And I don't think I could handle
watching you guys
have all the fun.
Yeah, fair enough.
Hey. Look.
You are a great diver.
You don't need me around
anymore.
Right,
so the church holds 80 people
and the village hall
next door 150.
So, as long as we un-invite
half my cousins,
we should be fine.
What else?
Well, I'm looking
really cute today.
Do you miss me?
Nah.
You're having more fun
helping Duncan
with his crosswords.
Bye.
Marine Control, this is
dive support vesselTharos...
- Cap.
- ...arriving 127 miles
east of Aberdeen
at Huntington Oil Field.
Thank you very much, Tharos.
We're gonna be
right in the middle
of this storm system all night.
What do you think?
Well, it's borderline, Cap,
but this is the North Sea.
Dynamic positioning status?
Coming over dive site,
turning into swell.
Directional thrusters
holding our position
next to the manifold.
Locked on.
Dynamic
positioning system online.
Computers have it from here.
Prepare for diving operations.
All right.
Team A up first.
Rise and shine, boys.
This is your one hour's notice.
- Dave?
-Hmm?
You want to pop down here
for a five-minute cuddle?
I'm, uh...
I'm good, Duncan. Thank you.
All right. Thanks for pondering.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
All right,
Team A entering wet pot
for final pressing in.
What about your tools?
Got your knife, compass,
- your flares?
-Yeah.
What about you, Dave?
Need a hand?
Didn't think so. All right.
See you guys up top.
Right. Thanks.
Dive Control,
first one in the bell.
You good?
- Yeah.
- Hey.
We're on the job now, okay?
Once we're down there,
it's just the two of us.
- Follow my lead.
- Mm-hmm.
Up you come, Dave.
Second man in the bell.
Dive Control,
that's three in the bell.
All right, copy that.
Positioning bell.
Lifting off sat chamber now.
And... bell over moon pool.
ROV.
Eyes on.
Starting descent.
Steady on two.
Bell left surface at 2117.
Bell passing through 100 feet.
That's 200 feet.
And... at depth.
300 feet.
Bell, go for your door.
Copy that, Dive Control.
Wow. That is some swell.
That-that's got to be
20-foot seas up there.
Bell, it pains me, but that's
what I've got up here, too.
What can I say, boys?
Still got it.
Every bloody time.
Okay, come on. Let's go.
Turning on hot water feed.
Coming to temperature now.
It's like a bath.
You want me falling asleep
on the job?
It's two degrees
above freezing down there.
But I forgot
how you like to suffer.
Yeah, that's good.
Going in.
The hat.
Mains gas supply on.
And connected.
Lowering hat.
Hand on the hat.
Grip the hat lower.
Okay. It's all yours.
-Good?
-Hat's on.
Comms check. Comms check.
Comms clear.
Bellman to Dive Control.
How's your feed?
Yes, coming through.
Uh, Duncan,
this is gonna be a long shift.
I just want to confirm
your adult diaper is on.
That's good material.
You know, you and I
are the same age.
And by the way,
I'm a professional.
I haven't had an irregular
bowel movement since '95.
Okay. Let's do it.
Bailouts coming down.
-All right.
-Yep.
Okay.
Diver good?
Good.
That's diver one
in the water at 300 feet.
Bell, turn on lights
for diver one.
Working.
In you go.
Diver one dropping off bell.
Okay. Gas flow's good.
Umbilical's connected.
You're locked in.
Comms check. Comms check.
Loud and clear.
Are you good to go?
I'll see you in six hours.
Okay. Stay safe, brother.
Diver two in the water
at 305 feet.
Slow your breathing
down a little for me, okay?
Copy.
Diver two dropping off bell.
Touchdown, diver two.
Bell, bearing to the job?
Diver two
is zero nine zero degrees.
It's this way.
Cap, both divers are on-site.
Lower the power cable.
Copy that.
Approaching seabed.
Duncan, notify the divers,
would you?
Copy.
Divers, power cable
approaching seabed.
Copy that, bell.
I have the connector.
Moving toward manifold now.
Bell, manifold has power.
Diver one,
prep pipes for installation.
-Copy that.
-Diver two,
head for well three
to begin equalization.
Copy that.
Entering the manifold.
Bell, all looking good
from up here.
How's it looking, diver two?
There's, uh,
rust on the stanchions.
There's growth everywhere.
Visibility's not great.
Oh, I need to cut down
on my desserts.
We just lost our hydroacoustics.
Are we still in position?
Troubleshooting now.
Bell, I've got a reading of, uh,
over a thousand psi
on wellhead three.
That's way too high.
All right.
Let me try and work my magic.
Warning. Warning.
Warning.
Cap, the thrusters
have gone offline.
- How many?
- All of them.
I'm getting the same here, Cap.
Chris? The ship's moving.
Get out of there now.
What? Dave, can you repeat?
The ship is moving.
Get out of the manifold
right now.
Copy that.
Warning. Warning.
Dynamic positioning system...
I'm losing everything here.
- Where's our power?
-Dead in the water.
Cap, we're drifting
out of control.
Abort. Abort.
We have a runoff.
Get the divers as much
umbilical as possible, Duncan.
Chris, our umbilicals
are over the manifold.
We've got to use them
to climb to the top.
Chris,
you've got to really move.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Divers, where are you?
Diver one
on top of the manifold.
Bell, I-I don't have
eyes on you.
Diver two also on top.
My umbilical's snagged.
The wind's spinning us around.
Power cable's about to give!
Dive Control, there's
no umbilical left in the bell.
That's everything I've got.
The ship's not drifting.
That's why.
Look, it's being pulled tight.
Chris has become our anchor.
That's never gonna hold.
It'll snap.
Bell, I need slack
on diver one.
There is no more slack.
I can't get to you.
My gas supply.
I can't breathe.
Chris, switch to your bailout.
Hey, Chris. On me.
Switch to your bailout.
Good.
Now take slow, deep breaths.
Otherwise, you'll burn
through your backup gas.
Understand?
Dive Control?
Diver two is on bailouts.
How much gas does he have left?
Ten minutes.
What happens now?
Your umbilical, it's gonna snap.
You'll get pulled off
the structure.
Now, I will come back for you,
but you have to do
something for me, okay?
You have to get yourself back
to the top of the manifold.
I can't rescue you
if I can't find you.
Understand?
J-Just make sure I'm...
Chris, are you there?
Do you copy?
Chris?
Chris, are you there?
Bell? Bell, do you copy?
Coming back to you now.
No eyes or ears
on divers or bell.
Condition unknown.
ROV feed is back online.
Uh, can you get closer?
Dave has made it back
to the bell.
Duncan, if you can hear me,
I'm back on the stage.
What happened?
His umbilical snapped.
He's gone.
There's no news on Chris.
But we're keeping the bell down
for when we get back
control of the ship.
We'll update you as and when.
Cap?
Why don't we drop anchor,
stop us drifting any further?
We don't have control
of the ship.
There are acres of oil pipeline
down there.
The anchor could snag
any one of them and rupture it.
There's far more seabed
than there is pipeline.
If we don't drop it now,
there's no telling
how far we'll end up from Chris.
I can't risk
an environmental disaster.
We'll have to find another way.
Duncan!
Dave?
Duncan, I can't see you.
Duncan, I don't know where I am.
Mani... man-manifold. Manifold.
Okay.
Okay, 90 degrees.
90 degrees.
Okay. Okay.
Shit.
Find the manifold.
Manifold.
Bridge?
We've run the diagnostics.
There's no fault
with the thrusters.
Are you sure?
One hundred percent.
We've run them twice.
If the thrusters
are still working,
we can take
the computers offline
and control her manually.
Cap, this system is designed
to be used only in port,
never in conditions
anything like this.
I understand.
If we make a mistake,
we put the entire ship at risk.
Okay, but if we keep drifting,
there's no way of telling
how far we'll get
from diver number two.
From Chris.
And I can't do this without you.
Listen up.
Until the dynamic positioning
is back online,
the first officer
and myself will...
take control
of the ship manually
and stop us from drifting
any further.
DPO, put her in manual.
Thrusters in manual.
Port, one four zero degrees
at 30%.
Stern 40.
-Stern 40.
-Now.
Moving off drift line.
Distance to dive site
is 630 feet and increasing.
Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it?!
Oh, yes. Yes!
You beauty.
Okay.
Okay. Got to climb.
I've got to climb.
Chris.
I've gone down
that rabbit hole again.
Got myself into a right state.
I know you say
that you're always safe
in your tin can...
...but once you step outside...
...it's like you're stealing
every second.
And I know it's extraordinary...
...but what we have
is extraordinary, too.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what I'm saying.
It's just, um...
Come home.
Please come home.
It's a body recovery now.
No, it's not.
Stern 40%.
Distance to dive site:
570 feet.
ROV, you in range?
On the outer limit now.
They why aren't you
finding my diver?
Copy that.
Come on, come on, come on.
Incoming swell.
Just keep her steady.
Where are we at
with dynamic positioning?
The only thing left
is a hard reset.
It's only ever done
when we're in for maintenance.
Every part is started up
in sequence.
It takes hours.
Well, you'd better find a
work-around, then, hadn't you?
Starboard, zero nine zero
degrees at 30%.
Thirty percent.
Closing.
Can anyone see anything?
Where the hell is he?
What about up top?
Oh, my God.
He's still alive.
His eyes are closed.
All four limbs appear intact.
No sign of breathing.
Involuntary spasms are from...
oxygen starvation to the brain.
Come on, where is it?
Got you.
Bridge?
I think I've found
that work-around.
Tell me.
Every part of the
dynamic positioning
is routed through
a start-up CPU,
which is why it takes
so long to boot up,
so I'm just gonna
physically rewire it
and bypass the whole damn thing.
Are you sure you can
patch it back correctly?
You'll have to get
the sequencing exactly right.
I can do it.
DPO, go ahead. Do it.
Why don't you use
the ROV to pick up Chris
and fly him back to the bell?
It's rated to pick up humans.
You can grab
the D ring on his harness
with the pincers from the ROV.
Uh, the ROVs are only ever used
for body recoveries.
Okay? The pincers
are far too dangerous
to be used on anything alive.
I can't see any other options.
Can you?
Look, Chris is alive right now,
okay, and...
and I don't want
anything I do to change that.
But these lads
are my responsibility.
I'm going to take the controls.
Shit.
Okay, okay.
Ease up on the front propellers
and let the rears do
all the work, okay?
Copy.
Got him.
Okay, good.
Raising level now.
Come on.
He-he must be caught
on something.
Hey, check the bottom camera.
Why the hell is that carabiner
clipped on?
So he won't get washed away
by the tide
when he's unconscious.
Smart lad.
Setting her down facing Chris.
Chris and I first met
on a rescue dive op.
A lobster boat went down
off the Scottish coast.
Took us a day to find the wreck.
And taking turns,
we were down there for hours.
Hours.
We couldn't find the last body.
Guess the current
must have carried it away.
Eventually, it was decided that
it wasn't worth the money
to continue looking
for just a body.
So they gave his wife
a shoebox...
...full of stuff they'd
cleaned out from his locker.
Imagine...
a box of useless shit,
souvenirs.
I'm not giving Morag a shoebox.
You won't.
We're not gonna give up on him.
Good.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One eleven, two eleven,
three eleven, four eleven,
five eleven.
Oh, no, no.
Yes!
The DPS is back online.
Well done.
Take us back to the manifold.
Yes, Cap.
Locked on and engaged.
Let's go get Chris.
Auto selected.
Oh.
Oh, finally.
Bell, you copy?
Yeah, yeah.
We copy, Dive Control.
How you guys doing?
We're fine. What about Chris?
We found him.
He's on top of the manifold.
He's unresponsive, but we are
heading back as fast as we can.
Okay, speed up.
160 feet to manifold.
- Gas is good.
-Hey.
I'm not losing two divers today.
Copy that.
You're good to go.
That's diver one in
the water, ready and waiting.
Coming over dive site.
Got eyes on Chris.
Get me closer.
Cap, we got to push
our minimums.
We need to get Dave lower.
Do it.
Reducing to 20 feet.
Settling. Settling.
Locked on, Cap.
Diver one is clear to go.
I got him.
Bell, I'm climbing back
to you now.
He's heavy.
Shit, we lost minimums.
Bell, brace for impact.
Duncan?
I'm okay.
Wh-What about Dave and Chris?
Duncan, are you there?
I'm with you, buddy.
I'm with you.
Dave, you're pushing too hard.
Go with the swell.
Climb when the bell's
coming down
and hold tight
when it's going up.
Copy.
Duncan, this isn't working.
You can do this, buddy.
One last push.
Here he comes.
Coming now.
Wait for it.
Now! Now!
Now!
Duncan, I'm on the stage.
Ready for the winch.
Chris.
You're all right.
You're safe.
You're in the bell.
Okay, you're okay, buddy.
You're okay.
Oh, come on.
Come on!
Okay, buddy.
You're all right.
You're good. You're safe.
You're in the bell.
Can you hear me, Chris?
It's Duncan.
Is he breathing?
Yeah. He is.
Come on, let's get you
out of there.
Bell, this connection's spotty.
What's Chris's status?
Chris is breathing.
But unresponsive.
Oh, no.
Half an hour
with no oxygen to the brain.
It's Duncan. Can you hear me?
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
You're back in the bell.
You're okay.
Come on, buddy.
Can you hear me?
Chris.
It's Dave.
We got you.
If you can hear me,
move your eyes.
Squeeze my hand.
Give me something.
We're too late.
No matter what,
you got him back.
We did.
Dave.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, we're fine, Chris.
- How are you?
-Yeah, we're okay.
Duncan, what's going on
down there?
Bridge, Chris is responsive
and he's talking.
Yes!
What's happened?
Well...
we made out, but I'll tell you
about that later.
Great job, Cap'n.
You, too. You, too.
Let's get 'em home.
Aye, Cap.
Gave us a wee fright there,
Duncs.
I think I might have
actually shit myself.
Right, soon as the hatch
is closed, let me know.
I'm bringing you up.
Sorry to wake you.
Oh, it's all right.
I wasn't asleep.
Feeling all right?
All things considered.
Right, just breathe normally.
I screwed up, huh?
Just bad luck, really.
Did your job, though.
You got to the top
of the manifold.
Just following orders.
How long was I lost for?
About 40 minutes.
I should be dead.
Yeah.
Pulse is strong.
You know, it's...
it's okay, though, really.
Yeah, I know you're okay.
No, I mean, um...
just, uh...
I felt sad for Morag.
Felt like I'd let her down.
I promised her
it would be okay, and then...
...then that happens.
And I just went numb.
It was...
peaceful.
Just like drifting off to sleep.
It's really not that bad.
Um, I'll let you rest.
Thank you.
Morag Martin speaking.
That was your best
headmistress voice.
Well, that wasn't a voice
I was expecting to hear
- for a few weeks, so...
- Yeah.
Our rotation has been
cut short, so, um...
What happened?
There was a problem
with the ship, so...
I'll be back in Aberdeen
the day after tomorrow.
I'll come and pick you up, then.
No, no.
No, you don't have to do that.
I'll make my own way back.
I love you.
So, even after all this,
you're still gonna miss it?
Every damn day.
Why don't you speak
to management about it?
Get you back on rotation.
Figure it out.
Good idea. Um...
forgot my pillow.
- All right. Duncan.
- Hey.
- Love you, brother.
- Love you, too, Duncs.
Yeah.
Hey, do you need a hand
down the gangway?
No, I'm all right.
Take care, Duncan.
You, too.
How you feeling, Duncs?
I'm just not ready
for the scrap heap yet.
You're a good man, Duncan.
Hiya.
Hi.
You okay?
Yeah, there was an accident.
Um...
What happened?
A, uh... a diver got stranded
on the seabed
and had to be rescued.
Oh, God.
Are they okay?
It was touch and go there
for a bit, but...
...but they're okay now.
It was you, wasn't it?
Oh, Chris.
Hey. Hey, come here.
I was always gonna
come back to you.
I love you, Chris.
I love you, too.
♪ All I've ever known
is here now ♪
♪ So pick a stone
and throw it in ♪
Come here.
♪ Let it drift
with all our memories ♪
♪ The times we've laughed ♪
♪ And go again ♪
♪ Well, God knows
I always need you ♪
♪ And you'll come back
just like the tide ♪
♪ Starlings float
upon the air we breathe ♪
♪ It's okay ♪
♪ To leave my side ♪
♪ You can go ♪
♪ Go be free ♪
♪ 'Cause the river always
finds the sea ♪
♪ I know you'll find your way ♪
♪ Back to me ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah
♪ Mm ♪
♪ Back to me ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Ooh, ooh...
There's one person in the
room in here
who's definitely going
to hate this
probably one of only two men
in this room
who've given me a decent kiss
on the lips.
That's Diver 2
in the water at 91 metres
and Chris
don't fuck it up this time.
Roger that.
♪ Ooh, ooh.
♪ One of these days,
I'll trade in my boots ♪
♪ For a plot and a pine box ♪
♪ A place in the roots ♪
♪ No use pretending ♪
♪ I'm good on my own ♪
♪ When you take that last walk ♪
♪ You take it alone ♪
♪ No disagreements ♪
♪ No dead-end dreams ♪
♪ Everything after
and all in between ♪
♪ No midnight movies,
no moon in July ♪
♪ The reasons for living
you take when you die ♪
♪ High is the river
and low when it's dry ♪
♪ When I'm finally out to sea ♪
♪ Keep talking to me
♪ The water is silver
♪ The moon is so gold ♪
♪ You're lucky to see ♪
♪ Your family get old ♪
♪ My family saw me
where I saw myself ♪
♪ For the fun we had living ♪
♪ We traded our health ♪
♪ Someday our bodies
slow to one lane ♪
♪ Tell me our blood goes on
way past the faint ♪
♪ Tell me the Earth
is too pretty to paint ♪
♪ Cold like an iceberg
and dark neath the grave ♪
♪ Tell me my soul
ain't too sorry to save ♪
♪ When I'm finally out to sea ♪
♪ Keep talking to me
♪ Keep talking to me.